<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:02:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes bug behind incorrect Windows Firewall errors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-bug-behind-incorrect-windows-firewall-errors/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: A known issue in Windows 11 24H2 systems with the June 2025 preview update installed triggers invalid Windows Firewall errors after rebooting. The bug has been fixed in the KB5062660preview cumulative update for Windows 11 24H2, released on Tuesday, and will be generally available to all users who install the August Patch Tuesday updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-bug-behind-incorrect-windows-firewall-errors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Hazel Burton</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/humans-of-talos-meet-hazel-burton/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability or cybersecurity-relevant content. It appears to be an employee spotlight or "Humans of Talos" series featuring Hazel Burton, a team member at Talos. The conversation touches on her career journey and what drew her to join the organization, as well as her advice for someone looking to join Talos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687e75c82e0cc100010c33bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Launches OSS Rebuild to Expose Malicious Code in Widely Used Open-Source Packages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-launches-oss-rebuild-to-expose.html</link>
      <description>Google's OSS Rebuild initiative aims to bolster the security of open-source package ecosystems by providing build provenance for packages across various registries. It leverages automation, heuristics, and network monitoring capabilities to produce trustworthy security metadata, enabling users to verify a package's origin and detect supply chain compromises.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-launches-oss-rebuild-to-expose.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyote Malware Targets WILS, Abusing Microsoft UI Automation to Exfiltrate Logins</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coyote-malware-targets-wils/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft UI Automation (UIA) framework; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel variant of the Coyote banking trojan exploits Microsoft's UI Automation (UIA) framework to manipulate user interface elements and steal login credentials. The malware uses UIA's Component Object Model (COM) interfaces to evade traditional endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools, allowing it to extract sensitive data without direct process injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150817</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Groups Weaponize RMM Tools to Infiltrate Networks and Exfiltrate Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-groups-weaponize-rmm-tools/</link>
      <description>Ransomware gangs have co-opted Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) tools to orchestrate sophisticated network intrusions, persistence, lateral movement, and data exfiltration. The tools were exploited by groups such as Hunters International and Medusa to evade traditional security controls due to their legitimate status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150808</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Chinese Hackers Actively Exploiting SharePoint 0-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-chinese-hackers-actively-exploiting-sharepoint-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A vulnerability chain dubbed "ToolShell" is actively exploited by Chinese hackers to gain unauthorized access to on-premises SharePoint servers. The vulnerabilities allow for network spoofing and remote code execution, enabling attackers to achieve unauthenticated system access, authenticated access, and execute arbitrary code across networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150832</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Introduces Black Screen of Death and Auto Recovery</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-introduces-black-screen-of-death-and-auto-recovery/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced significant updates to Windows 11's system recovery capabilities, including a redesigned "Black Screen of Death" interface and automated recovery features like Quick Machine Recovery (QMR) aimed at minimizing downtime and improving user experience during system failures. The new features promise to reduce system downtime and automate recovery processes, addressing critical pain points in enterprise environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150803</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Expose Russia’s Most Secretive FSB Spy Network</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-expose-russias-most-secretive-fsb/</link>
      <description>Researchers analyzed open-source intelligence (OSINT) and phaleristics to reveal the structure and operations of the Russian Federal Security Service's (FSB) 16th Center, a unit responsible for signals intelligence (SIGINT), cryptanalysis, and computer network operations (CNO). The study mapped the center's internal architecture, including at least ten departments, and geolocated ten SIGINT facilities across Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150792</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux Introduces Two New Tools for Raspberry Pi to Boost Wi-Fi Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kali-linux-introduces-tools-raspberry-pi-wi-fi-performance/</link>
      <description>The article is about the integration of Nexmon firmware-patching framework into Kali Linux, enabling native monitor-mode and packet-injection capabilities on Raspberry Pi boards. This update streamlines wireless security assessments on popular ARM-based Pi boards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150802</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome High-Severity Vulnerabilities Allow Hackers to Gain Full Control</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-high-severity-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): None; Summary: The latest Chrome update addresses three significant security vulnerabilities, including two high-severity issues involving type confusion errors in V8, Chrome's JavaScript engine. These flaws can allow attackers to manipulate data types, leading to memory corruption and arbitrary code execution, enabling cybercriminals to bypass security measures, steal sensitive information, or install malicious software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150790</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Orders Urgent Patching After Chinese Hackers Exploit SharePoint Flaws in Live Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-orders-urgent-patching-after.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: Two Microsoft SharePoint flaws, CVE-2025-49704 and CVE-2025-49706, have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The vulnerabilities, tracked as ToolShell, enable unauthorized access to on-premise SharePoint servers and are being exploited by Chinese hacking groups like Linen Typhoon and Violet Typhoon since July 7, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-orders-urgent-patching-after.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Warns: SysAid Flaws Under Active Attack Enable Remote File Access and SSRF</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-warns-sysaid-flaws-under-active.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SysAid IT support software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2775, CVE-2025-2776; Summary: Two XXE vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-2775 and CVE-2025-2776, allow for administrator account takeover, file read primitives, and potential remote code execution when chained with other flaws. The vulnerabilities were disclosed by watchTowr Labs researchers in May and addressed in SysAid's on-premise version 24.4.60 build 16 released in early March 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-warns-sysaid-flaws-under-active.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Launches Firefox 141 With Critical Security Fixes – Update Immediately</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mozilla-launches-firefox-141/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8027, CVE-2025-8028, CVE-2025-8034, CVE-2025-8035, CVE-2025-8040; Summary: The vulnerability summary states that Firefox 141 addresses 18 distinct CVEs, including high-impact memory safety bugs and moderate issues in URL handling and sandboxing. The most critical defects fixed include two high-severity flaws in the JavaScript engine, which could lead to arbitrary code execution, cross-origin data leaks, and privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150786</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Injected Malicious Firefox Packages in Arch Linux Repo</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-injected-malicious-firefox-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Arch Linux; CVE(s): None; Summary: Three compromised packages containing Remote Access Trojan (RAT) malware were uploaded to the Arch User Repository (AUR), targeting users seeking alternative Firefox configurations and browsers. The malware was designed to establish persistent remote access capabilities on infected systems, potentially granting attackers comprehensive system access without user knowledge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150781</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Active Exploitation of Microsoft SharePoint Code Injection and Authentication Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-of-microsoft-sharepoint-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint allow attackers to gain unauthorized access and execute code, posing significant risks to enterprise deployments. The vulnerabilities can be chained together to create devastating attack scenarios, enabling malicious actors to view sensitive information and make unauthorized modifications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150776</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma infostealer malware returns after law enforcement disruption</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-returns-after-law-enforcement-disruption/</link>
      <description>The Lumma infostealer malware operation has resumed activities after a massive law enforcement operation in May, which resulted in the seizure of 2,300 domains and parts of its infrastructure. Despite significant disruption, the operators claimed their central server had not been seized and restoration efforts were underway, eventually regaining trust within the cybercrime community.

(Note: Since there is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, I have formatted my response as a summary for a malware operation.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-returns-after-law-enforcement-disruption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Logging for Security and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/cloud-logging-for-security/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of cloud logging and monitoring in enterprise environments. It provides an overview of the different log categories for enterprise environments, including Audit, Compute, Network, Secrets, Cloud-Native Storage, and Kubernetes. The article also highlights the complexities of cloud logging across different cloud service providers (CSPs) such as AWS, Azure, and GCP.

The article emphasizes the need for a holistic approach to cloud logging that balances security, regulatory, and business needs while optimizing costs. It provides best practices for organizations to effectively monitor, secure, and manage their cloud environments.

Overall, this article aims to educate readers on the importance of cloud logging and monitoring in today's digital landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147360</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EFF moves to stop power utility reporting suspected pot growers to cops</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/07/eff-moves-to-stop-power-utility-reporting-suspected-pot-growers-to-cops/</link>
      <description>The article discusses how SMUD's smart meter data analysis program has been used to monitor and potentially identify individuals growing cannabis in their homes. Law enforcement agencies, including the Sacramento Police Department, have requested lists of customers using above a certain threshold of electricity, with disproportionately high penalties levied against Asian property owners who were found to be growing cannabis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/07/eff-moves-to-stop-power-utility-reporting-suspected-pot-growers-to-cops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5062660 update brings new 'Windows Resilience' features</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062660-update-brings-new-windows-resilience-features/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article discusses various updates and changes to Windows 11, including new features, fixes, and improvements. The main updates are:

1. Quick machine recovery: This feature enables automatic detection and fixing of widespread issues on Windows 11 devices using the Windows Recovery Environment (WinRE).
2. Streamlined interface during unexpected restarts: The updated design aligns with Windows 11's visual style and helps users return to work faster.
3. Boolean option for configuring Start menu pins: Administrators can apply Start menu pins once, allowing users to make changes to their pinned layout and have those changes safeguarded.
4. Improvements to Snap in Windows 11, including inline messages and keyboard shortcuts.
5. Fixes for various issues, such as authentication problems, file explorer bugs, graphics recognition, input method editor issues, stability problems, and Windows Firewall errors.

Overall, this article highlights the importance of keeping software up-to-date and secure, as well as the value of auto-recovery tools in mitigating downtime caused by widespread issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062660-update-brings-new-windows-resilience-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 gets new Black Screen of Death, auto recovery tool</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-gets-new-black-screen-of-death-auto-recovery-tool/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft's Windows Resiliency Initiative, which aims to make Windows more stable and self-healing. The initiative includes the replacement of the Blue Screen of Death (BSOD) with a new Black Screen of Death, as well as the introduction of the Quick Machine Recovery feature, which can automatically resolve boot failures without requiring manual intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-gets-new-black-screen-of-death-auto-recovery-tool/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-634: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-634/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7981; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an uninitialized variable in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25475</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-638: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-638/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7990; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the file parsing functionality. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25944</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-639: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-639/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7986; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by parsing VC6 files. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25755</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-640: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-640/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7989; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by parsing out-of-bounds read remote code execution. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of AR files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25943</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-641: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-641/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7987; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required, and the attack can be executed by visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-642: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-642/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7992; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of AR files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25972</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-643: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-643/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7991; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by reading past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25945</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-644: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-644/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7988; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of VC6 files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25862</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-645: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-645/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by parsing out-of-bounds RFA files. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27254</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-629: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-629/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7977; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an out-of-bounds read in the LI file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25354</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-630: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-630/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7982; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an integer overflow before allocating a buffer during LI file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25476</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-631: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-631/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7980; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the VC6 file parsing. User interaction is required, and the flaw results from improper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25465</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-632: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-632/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7978; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to an uninitialized variable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25459</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-633: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-633/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7979; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25463</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-635: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-635/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7983; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25477</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-636: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-636/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7984; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs when parsing AR files due to uninitialized variables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25700</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-637: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-637/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7985; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an integer overflow in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25704</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyote malware abuses Windows accessibility framework for data theft</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coyote-malware-abuses-windows-accessibility-framework-for-data-theft/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new variant of the banking trojan "Coyote" that abuses Microsoft's UI Automation framework (UIA) to identify which banking and cryptocurrency exchange sites are accessed on a device for potential credential theft. The malware, which targets 75 apps primarily in Brazil, uses UIA to extract web addresses from browser tabs or address bars and cross-referenced with a hardcoded list of targeted services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coyote-malware-abuses-windows-accessibility-framework-for-data-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and FBI warn of escalating Interlock ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-and-fbi-warn-of-escalating-interlock-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>CISA and the FBI have warned of increased Interlock ransomware activity targeting businesses and critical infrastructure organizations in double extortion attacks. The advisory provides indicators of compromise (IOCs) collected during investigations, as well as mitigation measures to protect networks against this ransomware gang's attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-and-fbi-warn-of-escalating-interlock-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major European healthcare network discloses security breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-european-healthcare-network-discloses-security-breach/</link>
      <description>AMEOS Group suffered a security breach that may have exposed customer, employee, and partner information. External actors gained unauthorized access to its IT systems and accessed sensitive information.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, but rather a security breach at AMEOS Group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-european-healthcare-network-discloses-security-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scavenger Malware Compromises Popular npm Packages to Target Developers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scavenger-malware-compromises-popular-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Npm package eslint-config-prettier; CVE(s): None; Summary: The npm package eslint-config-prettier was compromised through a phishing email and used to distribute a novel malware dubbed "Scavenger" that targets Windows systems. The malware uses various evasion techniques, including anti-VM checks, anti-antivirus measures, and dynamic resolution of functions using CRC32 hashing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hackers Target Global Airlines to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hackers-target-global-airlines/</link>
      <description>APT39, a state-sponsored hacker collective connected to Iran's Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS), was exposed as operating through the compromised internal systems of Amnban, a cybersecurity company. The breach reveals a sophisticated campaign involving cyber network exploitation (CNE) and preparation for cyber network attacks (CNA), with millions of airline passengers' sensitive personal identifiable information (PII) harvested worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150730</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Links Ongoing SharePoint Exploits to Three Chinese Hacker Groups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-links-ongoing-sharepoint.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53771, CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The exploitation of security flaws in internet-facing SharePoint Server instances has been linked to two Chinese hacking groups, Linen Typhoon and Violet Typhoon, as well as a third China-based threat actor, Storm-2603. The vulnerabilities allow for authentication bypass and remote code execution, leading to the deployment of a web shell and potential data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-links-ongoing-sharepoint.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETQ Reliance RCE Flaw Grants Full SYSTEM Access with a Single Space</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/etq-reliance-rce-flaw-grants-full-system-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hexagon ETQ's ETQ Reliance; CVE(s): 2025-34140, 2025-34141, 2025-34142, 2025-34143; Summary: The Java-based quality management system, ETQ Reliance, has several serious flaws including reflected cross-site scripting (XSS), XML External Entity (XXE) injection, authentication bypass, and remote code execution (RCE). These vulnerabilities were responsibly disclosed, leading to patches in NXG Release 2025.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150713</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-628: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 OCPP Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-628/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25271, ZDI-CAN-26346, ZDI-25-628; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to bypass authentication on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26346</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Target Linux SSH Servers to Deploy SVF Botnet</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-target-linux-ssh-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux servers; CVE(s): None; Summary: Weak SSH credentials on Linux servers are being exploited by threat actors to launch DDoS attacks and cryptocurrency mining. The SVF Botnet malware is used to achieve this, which also incorporates proxy servers for enhanced evasion and has a modular design with customizable attack parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150698</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco: Maximum-severity ISE RCE flaws now exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-maximum-severity-ise-rce-flaws-now-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282, CVE-2025-20337; Summary: Three critical remote code execution vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE are being actively exploited. The flaws allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root without authentication and can lead to gaining a foothold on corporate networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-maximum-severity-ise-rce-flaws-now-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Web3 Phishing Scam Uses Fake AI Platforms to Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-web3-phishing-scam-uses-fake-ai-platforms/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a phishing campaign by the LARVA-208 threat actor group targeting Web3 developers. The attackers use spearphishing links to lure victims into downloading malware disguised as a Realtek HD Audio Driver, which executes PowerShell commands and exfiltrates sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150688</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFake Interview Attack Leverages ClickFix Technique to Deploy GolangGhost Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clickfake-interview-attack-leverages-clickfix-technique/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the "ClickFake Interview" campaign by Lazarus Group, a North Korean state-sponsored hacker outfit. This operation targets job seekers in the cryptocurrency and technology sectors with fake job interviews that lead to malware deployment. The campaign uses the "ClickFix" technique, which exploits human vulnerabilities and bypasses traditional security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150659</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Bans Public Sector from Paying Ransomware Gangs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uk-bans-public-sector-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</link>
      <description>The UK government has announced a comprehensive ban preventing public sector organizations from paying ransom demands to cybercriminals in an effort to disrupt the business model that makes ransomware attacks profitable. The ban aims to protect critical national infrastructure operators, including NHS trusts and schools, by prohibiting ransom payments to criminal groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150696</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Confirms Active Exploits Targeting ISE Flaws Enabling Unauthenticated Root Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-confirms-active-exploits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20337, CVE-2025-20282; Summary: A set of critical-rated vulnerabilities (CVSS scores: 10.0) in Cisco's Identity Services Engine (ISE) and ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to issue commands, execute arbitrary code, or upload and execute files as the root user. The flaws stem from insufficient validation of user-supplied input and lack of file validation checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-confirms-active-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban public sector orgs from paying ransomware gangs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-to-ban-public-sector-orgs-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</link>
      <description>The UK government is planning to ban public sector and critical infrastructure organizations from paying ransoms after ransomware attacks. The proposed legislation aims to target the business model that fuels cybercriminals' activities and makes vital services less attractive targets for ransomware groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-to-ban-public-sector-orgs-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credential Theft and Remote Access Surge as AllaKore, PureRAT, and Hijack Loader Proliferate</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/credential-theft-and-remote-access.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a long-running campaign targeting Mexican organizations with modified versions of AllaKore RAT and SystemBC. The attacks use phishing or drive-by compromises to distribute booby-trapped ZIP archives, which facilitate the deployment of AllaKore RAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/credential-theft-and-remote-access.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Alerts on ISE RCE Vulnerability Actively Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-alerts-on-ise-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282, CVE-2025-20337; Summary: A set of critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities affecting Cisco's Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) products are being actively exploited in the wild. The flaws allow unauthenticated attackers to gain root-level access to vulnerable systems with a CVSS base score of 10.0, and no viable workarounds exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150681</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-adds-four-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various (CrushFTP, Google Chromium ANGLE and GPU, SysAid On-Prem); CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2025-2776, CVE-2025-2775; Summary: Four new vulnerabilities have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to active exploitation. These vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and other organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23659</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert (PME) and EcoStruxure Power Operation (EPO); CVE(s): CVE-2025-6788; Summary: A resource exposure vulnerability exists that exposes TGML diagram resources to unauthorized control, allowing other authenticated users unauthorized access to TGML diagrams. Successful exploitation could provide potentially inappropriate access to TGML diagrams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23666</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxture IT Data Center Expert</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure IT Data Center Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50121, CVE-2025-50122, CVE-2025-50123, CVE-2025-50124, CVE-2025-6438; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities exist in Schneider Electric's EcoStruxure IT Data Center Expert, including OS command injection, insufficient entropy, code injection, server-side request forgery, improper privilege management, and XML external entity reference. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to disrupt operations, access system data, or gain unauthorized file access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23668</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Operation</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Operation; CVE(s): CVE-2023-50447, CVE-2022-45198, CVE-2024-28219, CVE-2023-35945, CVE-2023-44487; Summary: The EcoStruxure Power Operation (EPO) has multiple vulnerabilities including improper neutralization of directives in dynamically evaluated code ('Eval Injection'), integer overflow to buffer overflow, improper handling of highly compressed data (data amplification), out-of-bounds write, and uncontrolled resource consumption. Successful exploitation could result in the loss of system functionality or unauthorized access to system functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23663</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: The two vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23670</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric System Monitor Application</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric System Monitor Application, Harmony Industrial PC series and Pro-face Industrial PC series; CVE(s): CVE-2020-11023; Summary: The vulnerability is a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) issue in the System Monitor Application. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute untrusted code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23667</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuraComm DP-10iN-100-MU</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: DuraComm Corporation SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41425, CVE-2025-48733, CVE-2025-53703; Summary: The SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU power distribution panel contains vulnerabilities that could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information or cause a denial-of-service condition. The vulnerabilities include cleartext transmission of sensitive information, missing authentication for a critical function, and improper neutralization of input during web page generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23664</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Nine Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-releases-nine-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released nine Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 22, 2025. These advisories provide information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits affecting ICS products from various vendors, including DuraComm, Lantronix, Schneider Electric, and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23669</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lantronix Provisioning Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lantronix Provisioning Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7766; Summary: The Lantronix Provisioning Manager contains an improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) Reference vulnerability, which can be exploited to perform cross-site scripting attacks and achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23665</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Advisory Issued on Protecting Against Interlock Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/joint-advisory-issued-protecting-against-interlock-ransomware</link>
      <description>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Agency (CISA) has issued a joint advisory with the FBI, Department of Health and Human Services, and Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center to help protect businesses and critical infrastructure organizations against Interlock ransomware. The advisory provides indicators of compromise, tactics, techniques, and procedures identified through recent FBI investigations, along with recommended mitigations for reducing the risk of Interlock ransomware threat activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23656</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#StopRansomware: Interlock</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-203a</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an advisory on emerging ransomware threats, specifically the Interlock Ransomware gang. The report provides an in-depth analysis of the group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), as well as recommended mitigations and best practices for organizations to prevent and respond to such attacks.

As a cybersecurity analyst, I would categorize this article under "FYSA" since it is not discussing a specific vulnerability or product issue. Instead, it offers valuable insights into the tactics used by the Interlock Ransomware gang and provides guidance on how to improve defenses against these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23643</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Selling macOS 0-Day LPE Exploit on Dark Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-selling-macos-0-day-lpe-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: A threat actor claims to possess a zero-day Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) exploit targeting Apple's macOS operating system, offering the vulnerability for sale at $130,000. The alleged exploit could allow attackers to gain complete administrative control over compromised systems, bypassing Apple's built-in security mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Jena Vulnerability Allows Arbitrary File Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-jena-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Jena; CVEs: CVE-2025-49656, CVE-2025-50151; Summary: Two vulnerabilities in Apache Jena enable administrators to access and create files outside designated server directories, potentially compromising system security. The first vulnerability allows administrative users to create database files outside the intended directory boundaries, while the second vulnerability enables improper file access path validation, allowing administrators to reference and potentially access files anywhere on the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150670</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DCHSpy Android Malware Targets WhatsApp, Call Logs, Audio, and Photos</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-dchspy-android-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the discovery of four novel samples of DCHSpy, an advanced Android surveillanceware attributed to the Iranian threat actor group MuddyWater. The malware harvests sensitive information from infected devices and enables attackers to intercept WhatsApp communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150621</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Scanner Launched to Detect CVE-2025-53770 in SharePoint Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-scanner-to-detect-cve-2025-53770-in-sharepoint-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The vulnerability is an unauthenticated Remote Code Execution flaw affecting on-premise SharePoint deployments that have not been updated with Microsoft's security patches. The scanner, developed by Niels Hofmans, targets the vulnerability and allows administrators to detect exposure without causing damage to the target system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150655</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Sharepoint ToolShell attacks linked to Chinese hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-toolshell-attacks-linked-to-chinese-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Hackers with ties to the Chinese government exploited a zero-day vulnerability chain in Microsoft SharePoint, allowing them to breach dozens of organizations worldwide. The exploit chain, dubbed "ToolShell," provides unauthenticated access to systems and enables malicious actors to execute code over the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-toolshell-attacks-linked-to-chinese-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Sophos Firewall Flaws Allow Pre-Auth RCE</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sophos-firewall-flaws-allow-pre-auth-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6704, CVE-2025-7624, CVE-2025-7382, CVE-2024-13974, CVE-2024-13973; Summary: Multiple critical vulnerabilities were discovered in Sophos Firewall products, including remote code execution flaws and SQL injection vulnerabilities. The most severe flaw allows pre-authentication remote code execution through the Secure PDF eXchange (SPX) feature, while another vulnerability enables remote code execution when a quarantining policy is active for email.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150645</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Advance from SOC Manager to CISO?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-advance-from-soc-manager-to-ciso.html</link>
      <description>This article provides guidance on the practical steps and skills needed to transition from managing a security operations center (SOC) to becoming a chief information security officer (CISO). It highlights the importance of developing strategic and leadership skills beyond technical expertise, as well as effective communication and risk management. The article also emphasizes the need for CISOs to understand the nuances of their role and adapt to different reporting structures and expectations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-advance-from-soc-manager-to-ciso.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Windows Server KB5062557 causes cluster, VM issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-kb5062557-causes-cluster-vm-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2019; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Cluster service on Windows Server 2019 may fail to function correctly after installing the July Windows security update, causing nodes to fail to rejoin the cluster or enter quarantine states, virtual machines to experience multiple restarts, and frequent Event ID 7031 errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-kb5062557-causes-cluster-vm-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Travel Agencies Exploit Cheap Deals to Steal Credit Card Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dark-web-travel-agencies-exploit-cheap-deals/</link>
      <description>Dark web travel agencies have developed into sophisticated organizations using hacked credit card information, compromised loyalty accounts, and fake identities to provide reduced travel services. They exploit popular booking aggregators, adapting quickly to blocked channels through advanced credential harvesting techniques. The article highlights the need for proactive, multi-layered defenses in the hospitality industry to combat these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150595</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Merge Android Malware with Click Fraud Apps to Harvest Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-merge-android-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article describes a campaign of active Android malware that combines brand impersonation with traffic monetization tactics. The malware exploits social engineering and off-market distribution channels to evade traditional security measures, preying on user trust to exfiltrate sensitive data such as login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150557</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wolfSSL Security Update Addresses Apple Trust Store Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wolfssl-security-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: wolfSSL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7394, CVE-2025-7395, CVE-2025-7396; Summary: The vulnerabilities affect users of wolfSSL versions after 5.7.6 and before 5.8.2 who utilize WOLFSSL_SYS_CA_CERTS and WOLFSSL_APPLE_NATIVE_CERT_VALIDATION features on Apple platforms. The most serious vulnerability allows malicious actors to bypass certificate verification processes, while the other two vulnerabilities relate to predictable random number generation and side-channel attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150591</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals from GLOBAL GROUP Target All Platforms with Golang Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-from-global-group-target/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation called GLOBAL GROUP, which is actually a rebranded version of the Mamona RIP and Black Lock ransomware families. The RaaS offers features such as automated negotiations, cross-platform payloads, and lucrative affiliate splits, but it leverages familiar foundations and shared code artifacts from previous ransomware operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150506</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Institutions Under Siege by Greedy Sponge Hackers’ Modified AllaKore RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/financial-institutions-under-siege-by-greedy-sponge-hackers/</link>
      <description>This article is about a threat actor group called Greedy Sponge that has been targeting Mexican organizations with a customized version of the AllaKore Remote Access Trojan (RAT) to steal banking credentials and authentication data. The malware, which can perform keylogging, screenshots, file uploads/downloads, and remote control capabilities, is delivered through spear-phishing and drive-by downloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit SharePoint Zero-Day Since July 7 to Steal Keys, Maintain Persistent Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-sharepoint-zero-day.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint is being actively exploited in the wild, putting thousands of global organizations at risk. The attack chain leverages a remote code execution flaw (CVE-2025-53770) and a spoofing vulnerability (CVE-2025-49706) to gain initial access and escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-sharepoint-zero-day.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Image Builder Vulnerability Grants Root Access to Windows Nodes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kubernetes-image-builder-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kubernetes Image Builder; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7342; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Kubernetes Image Builder allows attackers to gain root access on Windows nodes by exploiting default credentials embedded in virtual machine images. The flaw affects images built with the Nutanix or OVA providers and can be exploited by logging in as the Administrator account, escalating privileges, and potentially compromising the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150543</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Reveals Just 10% Of Employees Drive 73% Of Cyber Risk</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-reveals-just-10-of-employees-drive-73-of-cyber-risk/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a report by Living Security and Cyentia Institute, titled "2025 State of Human Cyber Risk Report", which reveals that human risk in the workforce is concentrated among 10% of employees who account for 73% of risky behavior. The report highlights the importance of managing behavioral risk rather than just systems, and provides insights on how to reduce organizational risk exposure through strategic HRM programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150529</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak Password Enables Ransomware Attack on 158-Year-Old Firm</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weak-password-enables-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a specific vulnerability but highlights the devastating impact of cybersecurity vulnerabilities on British businesses. The case study of KNP, a logistics firm, demonstrates how a single compromised password can lead to catastrophic consequences, including ransomware attacks and data breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150501</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell Data Breach – World Leaks Group Hacks Test Lab Platform</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dell-data-breach/</link>
      <description>The World Leaks extortion group successfully infiltrated Dell Technologies' Customer Solution Centers platform, compromising a demonstration environment used to showcase products to commercial clients. The stolen information consists mainly of synthetic test data, publicly available datasets, and system data, with only an outdated contact list containing minimal operational significance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150496</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN Windows Client Flaw Could Expose User Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/expressvpn-windows-client-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ExpressVPN Windows Desktop Client; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows desktop client (versions 12.97 to 12.101.0.2-beta) had a vulnerability that could leak user connection details, specifically revealing their true IP address and RDP connections to on-network observers or internet service providers, although encryption remained intact. The issue was caused by debug code intended for internal testing but mistakenly shipped in production builds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150492</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Exploitation of Microsoft SharePoint Vulnerabilities: Threat Brief</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/microsoft-sharepoint-cve-2025-49704-cve-2025-49706-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: A set of high-impact vulnerabilities in on-premises Microsoft SharePoint servers allows unauthenticated threat actors to access restricted functionality and run arbitrary commands. The vulnerabilities have been actively exploited, and attackers are bypassing identity controls to gain privileged access and exfiltrate sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147463</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-626: (Pwn2Own) NVIDIA Container Toolkit Environment Variable Handling Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-626/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NVIDIA Container Toolkit by exploiting the handling of environment variables and lack of restrictions on spawning a hook process. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27193</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-627: rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-627/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: rocket.chat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7974; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of rocket.chat, without requiring authentication. The issue is due to incorrect authorization within the web service listening on TCP port 3000 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel announces end of Clear Linux OS project, archives GitHub repos</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/intel-announces-end-of-clear-linux-os-project-archives-github-repos/</link>
      <description>Clear Linux OS has shut down after 10 years, and its user base is recommended to migrate to another distribution for security reasons, as it will no longer receive security patches or updates. The shutdown may be due to low user adoption and high maintenance burden, allowing Intel to focus on other projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/intel-announces-end-of-clear-linux-os-project-archives-github-repos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Deploys Weaponized LNK Files with Cobalt Strike and Metasploit to Target Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ung0002-deploys-weaponized-lnk-files/</link>
      <description>A persistent threat entity, UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002), has been uncovered by Seqrite Labs, targeting critical sectors in Asia with sophisticated multi-stage attacks and evasive intrusion techniques. The group demonstrates adaptability, technical prowess, and a focus on intelligence gathering through espionage-driven operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150443</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolShell: Details of CVEs Affecting SharePoint Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/toolshell-affecting-sharepoint-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Two path traversal vulnerabilities affecting SharePoint Server Subscription Edition, SharePoint Server 2016, and SharePoint Server 2019 allow for unauthenticated remote code execution. Patches have been provided for most versions, but SharePoint Server 2016 remains unpatched, and users are recommended to rotate their machine keys and enable Antimalware Scan Interface (AMSI) as an alternative mitigation measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687e91ad2e0cc100010c33cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeerStealer Malware Spread Through Weaponized .LNK and LOLBin Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/deerstealer-malware-spread-through-weaponized-lnk/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new wave of cyber-attacks that exploit Windows shortcut files (.LNK) and legitimate system utilities (LOLBin/S) to deliver the DeerStealer infostealer. The attacks use highly obfuscated multi-stage chains, leveraging MITRE ATT&amp;CK technique T1218.005, and employ anti-sandbox and anti-VM checks to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150434</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Compromise Popular npm Packages to Steal Maintainers’ Tokens</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-compromise-popular-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm; CVE(s): None; Summary: Phishing campaign targeting npm package maintainers resulted in the compromise of widely used JavaScript tooling libraries. Attackers utilized a typosquatted domain to trick developers into surrendering their authentication tokens, which were then used to publish malicious package versions directly to the npm registry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150429</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of npm Phishing Emails Targeting Developer Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-npm-phishing-emails/</link>
      <description>A highly advanced phishing email targeted npm package maintainers by spoofing the support@npmjs.org address and redirecting users to a malicious site that stole developer credentials. The campaign used unique tokens, semi-targeted approach, and infrastructure abuse to evade detection, highlighting the need for vigilance and proactive reporting to prevent supply chain attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150412</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring denies breach after users report suspicious logins</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ring-denies-breach-after-users-report-suspicious-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ring; CVE(s): None; Summary: A backend update bug is causing unauthorized devices to be displayed as logged into customers' accounts, leading to concerns of a security incident. Customers are reporting unknown devices and countries listed in their Authorized Client Devices list, which cannot be previous logins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ring-denies-breach-after-users-report-suspicious-logins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint vulnerability with 9.8 severity rating under exploit across globe</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/sharepoint-vulnerability-with-9-8-severity-rating-is-under-exploit-across-the-globe/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: Attackers extract the ValidationKey directly from memory or configuration, allowing them to craft fully valid, signed __VIEWSTATE payloads and execute remote commands (RCE) without requiring credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/sharepoint-vulnerability-with-9-8-severity-rating-is-under-exploit-across-the-globe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Use Zoho WorkDrive Folders to Spread Obfuscated PureRAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-use-zoho-workdrive-folders/</link>
      <description>A targeted attack was discovered against a U.S.-based certified public accounting firm using a novel crypter named "Ghost Crypt" to deliver PureRAT, a Remote Access Trojan (RAT). The attackers employed social engineering tactics and leveraged Zoho WorkDrive, a cloud-based file-sharing platform, to distribute malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150406</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT41 Hackers Exploiting Atexec and WmiExec Windows Modules for Malware Deployment</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt41-hackers-exploiting-atexec-and-wmiexec-windows-modules/</link>
      <description>This article reports a sophisticated targeted attack by APT41 against government IT services in the African region. The attackers used various tools and techniques to gain access to systems, including Impacket/WMI usage, DLL sideloading, and C2 domains. The attack was detected through suspicious activity on multiple workstations, and retrospective analysis revealed an IIS web server as the initial entry point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150375</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-625: Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager JobManagmentService Improper Access Control Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-625/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24286; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager, requiring authentication. The issue results from improper access control in the JobManagmentService component, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26062</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Can Exploit Lighthouse Studio RCE Bug to Gain Server Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-can-exploit-lighthouse-studio-rce-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sawtooth Software Lighthouse Studio; CVE(s): CVE-2025-34300; Summary: The Lighthouse Studio survey software contains a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in its Perl CGI scripts, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on hosting servers. This flaw enables attackers to inject Perl code via specially crafted URL parameters, leveraging an eval sink that interprets content enclosed in [% … %] as executable code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150260</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran-Linked DCHSpy Android Malware Masquerades as VPN Apps to Spy on Dissidents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iran-linked-dchspy-android-malware.html</link>
      <description>Android spyware known as DCHSpy has been discovered by cybersecurity researchers at Lookout, which collects sensitive data such as WhatsApp information, accounts, contacts, SMS messages, call logs, files, location, and audio recordings. The malware is believed to be affiliated with the Iranian Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS) and has been distributed via masquerading VPN apps and Starlink-related lures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iran-linked-dchspy-android-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAWA4096 Ransomware Employs WMI Techniques to Delete Backup Snapshots</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kawa4096-ransomware-employs-wmi-techniques/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the KAWA4096 ransomware, a new strain detected in June 2025. It targets entities in the United States and Japan, using multithreaded encryption, network share targeting, and evasion tactics to amplify disruption. The ransomware embeds its configuration within the binary, terminates antivirus processes, and erases Volume Shadow Copies to hinder data recovery efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150351</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-621: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 DHCP Configuration Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-621/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25269, ZDI-CAN-26350, ZDI-25-621; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices without authentication. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call, which can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26350</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-622: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 Configuration Service Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-622/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25268; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the configuration service that listens on TCP port 5001 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26331</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-623: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 Origin Validation Error Firewall Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-623/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25270; Summary: The Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 device has an origin validation error that allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass firewall rules and access another interface without authentication. The vulnerability exists in the configuration of firewall rules and can be exploited by leveraging other vulnerabilities to execute code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26332</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-624: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-624/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100; CVE(s): CVE-2024-25995; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100 devices without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the default routemetric parameter to the config service, resulting from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23328</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Cloaking Tools Help Threat Actors Hide Malicious Domains from Security Scans</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-powered-cloaking-tools-help-threat-actors/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are increasingly using AI-powered cloaking services to evade automated security scanners and prolong the operational lifespan of their infrastructure. These services analyze visitor attributes such as IP geolocation, user-agent strings, and browser entropy to classify and reroute requests, ensuring only targeted human users encounter the payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150320</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked Hackers Launch Targeted Espionage Campaign on African IT Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-linked-hackers-launch-targeted.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a Chinese nation-state hacking group, tracked as APT41, which has launched a new campaign targeting government IT services in the African region. The attackers used hardcoded names of internal services, IP addresses, and proxy servers embedded within their malware to communicate with command-and-control (C2) servers, including a hacked SharePoint server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-linked-hackers-launch-targeted.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN bug leaked user IPs in Remote Desktop sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/expressvpn-bug-leaked-user-ips-in-remote-desktop-sessions/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ExpressVPN; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows client of ExpressVPN had a flaw that caused Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) traffic to bypass the virtual private network (VPN) tunnel, exposing users' real IP addresses. The issue was caused by remnants of debug code used for internal testing being mistakenly included in production builds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/expressvpn-bug-leaked-user-ips-in-remote-desktop-sessions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Recovery Orchestrator users locked out after MFA rollout</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/veeam-recovery-orchestrator-users-locked-out-after-mfa-rollout/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Recovery Orchestrator; CVE(s): None; Summary: The recently released version of Recovery Orchestrator (build 7.2.1.286) blocks Web UI logins after enabling multi-factor authentication (MFA). This issue has been fixed with the release of version 7.2.1.290, and customers who installed the buggy version are advised to contact technical support for assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/veeam-recovery-orchestrator-users-locked-out-after-mfa-rollout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Fix Targets Attacks on SharePoint Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/microsoft-fix-targets-attacks-on-sharepoint-zero-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint Server is actively being exploited to compromise vulnerable organizations, allowing attackers to execute code over the network and steal ASP.NET machine keys. The patch comes amid reports of breaches in U.S. federal and state agencies, universities, and energy companies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71737</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dior begins sending data breach notifications to U.S. customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dior-begins-sending-data-breach-notifications-to-us-customers/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a data breach incident at House of Dior, a French luxury fashion house, which affected U.S. customers' personal information. The breach occurred on January 26, 2025, and was only discovered on May 7, 2025. The compromised database contained full names, contact details, physical addresses, date of birth, passport or government ID number (in some cases), and Social Security Number (in some cases).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dior-begins-sending-data-breach-notifications-to-us-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Keylogger Uses Persistence via Scheduled Tasks to Steal Login Data Undetected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/snake-keylogger-uses-persistence-via-scheduled-tasks/</link>
      <description>Researchers have identified a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Turkish enterprises, particularly defense and aerospace industries. The campaign involves emails masquerading as legitimate contractual documents from Turkish Aerospace Industries (TUSAŞ), which contain malware that steals sensitive data such as credentials, cookies, and financial details without detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150310</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Release PoC Exploit for High-Severity NVIDIA AI Toolkit Bug</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-release-poc-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit (NCT); CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: A severe vulnerability in NCT allows malicious containers to escape isolation and gain root access on host systems. The flaw stems from a misconfiguration in OCI hook handling, affecting NCT versions up to 1.17.7 and NVIDIA GPU Operator up to 25.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150208</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal Listings Target Fujitsu, Baxter Kelly, AGX Financeira, and a Belgian IT Platform</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cybercriminal-listings-target-fujitsu-baxter-kelly-agx-financeira-and-a-belgian-it-platform/</link>
      <description>This article reports on several new listings for unauthorized access sales and data breaches affecting companies across Japan, the U.K., Brazil, and Belgium. The listings include sensitive internal files, Citrix access, customer data, and administrative control over a monitoring system, with prices ranging from $1,500 to $20,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061978</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolShell Campaign: New SharePoint Zero-Day (CVE-2025-53770) Triggers Widespread Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/toolshell-sharepoint-zero-day-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint, identified as CVE-2025-53770, is actively being exploited in targeted attacks. The vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication, gain remote code execution capabilities, and establish persistent access using stolen cryptographic keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061964</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHP PDO Flaw Allows Attackers to Inject Malicious SQL Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/php-pdo-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PHP PDO; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious SQL commands by exploiting weaknesses in PDO's SQL parser. This affects millions of web applications worldwide, even when developers implement prepared statements correctly. Attackers can manipulate PDO's parsing logic through carefully constructed payloads, leading to SQL injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150385</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: SharePoint 0-Day, Chrome Exploit, macOS Spyware, NVIDIA Toolkit RCE and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a summary of various cyber-related incidents, attacks, and trends from around the world. The article discusses malware families like Rainbow Hyena, DiskStation Security, and Katz Stealer; phishing campaigns targeting specific industries or organizations; and large-scale cyber thefts affecting financial institutions and other entities.

There are no explicit discussions about vulnerabilities in software, hardware, or firmware within this article. However, the article does touch upon various cybersecurity concerns and threats that could potentially impact different systems and organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 CrushFTP servers exposed to ongoing hijack attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: All CrushFTP versions below 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23 are vulnerable to hijack attacks that exploit a critical security bug due to mishandled AS2 validation, allowing admin access to the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Role of AI in Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in Zero Trust architecture, highlighting its capabilities in adaptive trust, continuous risk evaluation, and automation. It also emphasizes the importance of human-machine teaming, where AI amplifies human decision-making rather than replacing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Firm Exploits SS7 Flaw to Track User Locations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surveillance-firm-exploits-ss7-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SS7 (Signaling System No. 7) protocol; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated surveillance operation has been discovered exploiting critical vulnerabilities in the global telecommunications infrastructure to track mobile phone users' locations without authorization. The attack leverages weaknesses in the decades-old SS7 protocol that underpins international cellular networks, manipulating the TCAP layer and using an obscure encoding technique called "extended tag encoding" to disguise malicious location tracking requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn 14 Languages from Babbel with this exclusive StackSocial deal</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</link>
      <description>The article is promoting language learning platforms Babbel, uTalk, and Rosetta Stone, offering lifetime subscriptions and discounts. It highlights the features of each platform, such as AI conversation partners and personalized review sessions. The article also includes a free board report deck for CISOs to present cloud security risks and priorities in business terms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell confirms breach of test lab platform by World Leaks extortion group</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</link>
      <description>World Leaks, a rebranded extortion gang, has breached Dell's product demonstration platform and is trying to extort the company into paying a ransom. The stolen data is believed to be synthetic test data used in product demonstrations and trials, with only a very outdated contact list being legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinDCX Hack Leads to $44.2 Million Loss</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coindcx-hack-leads-to-44-2-million-loss/</link>
      <description>CoinDCX, an Indian cryptocurrency exchange, suffered a significant security breach that resulted in approximately $44 million in losses. Despite the incident, customer funds remain secure and unaffected, thanks to the company's segregated account architecture. The investigation is ongoing to identify vulnerabilities, implement additional safety measures, and trace the movement of compromised funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150352</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE‑2025‑37103: Remote Access Risk in Aruba Instant On Access Points Due to Hardcoded Passwords</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve202537103-aruba-instant-on-hardcoded-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, CVE-2025-37102; Summary: The Aruba Instant On access points contain a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-37103) that allows remote access to the device's web interface without authentication due to a hardcoded admin password. This flaw can be exploited to gain administrative access and launch lateral attacks across the internal network, and when combined with CVE-2025-37102, it enables command injection and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061953</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-54309: New CrushFTP Zero-Day Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-54309-new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in CrushFTP allows attackers to gain administrator-level access through the HTTPS interface on unpatched servers, enabling file theft, privilege escalation, and deeper network compromise. The flaw affects versions prior to 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23, and building released after July 1, 2025, contain the fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061943</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AppLocker Flaw Lets Malicious Apps Bypass Security Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-applocker-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft AppLocker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft's AppLocker security feature allows malicious applications to bypass established security restrictions by exploiting a seemingly minor error in the MaximumFileVersion field. Attackers could potentially modify a blocked executable's version number to exceed the configured maximum version, but this would simultaneously break the file's digital signature, making it detectable by systems configured with "signed executables only" policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150306</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Livewire Flaw Puts Millions of Laravel Apps at Risk of RCE Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/livewire-flaw-of-rce-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Livewire; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54068; Summary: A critical remote command execution vulnerability exists in Livewire versions from 3.0.0-beta.1 to 3.6.3, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the server by injecting malicious code through property updates. Exploitation requires only a vulnerable component with default configuration, and no user authentication or interaction is necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on Microsoft SharePoint 0-Day RCE Exploited in Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-microsoft-sharepoint-0-day-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint Server allows unauthorized attackers to execute arbitrary code remotely over a network, potentially giving cybercriminals complete control over affected systems. The flaw stems from deserialization of untrusted data and is actively being exploited in cyberattacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150250</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-Zip Vulnerability Lets Malicious RAR5 Files Crash Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/7-zip-vulnerability-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: 7-Zip; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53816; Summary: A critical denial-of-service vulnerability in 7-Zip's RAR5 decoder allows attackers to crash systems by processing specially crafted RAR5 archive files, leading to memory corruption and system crashes. The vulnerability occurs due to a heap buffer overflow when the decoder attempts to repair corrupted archive items, resulting in writing data beyond allocated buffer boundaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150238</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoisonSeed Hackers Bypass FIDO Keys Using QR Phishing and Cross-Device Sign-In Abuse</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/poisonseed-hackers-bypass-fido-keys.html</link>
      <description>A novel attack technique has been disclosed, allowing threat actors to downgrade Fast IDentity Online (FIDO) key protections by deceiving users into approving authentication requests from spoofed company login portals. The attack exploits a legitimate FIDO feature called cross-device sign-in and does not exploit any flaw in the FIDO implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/poisonseed-hackers-bypass-fido-keys.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoisonSeed Attack Tricks Users into Scanning Malicious MFA QR Codes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poisonseed-attack-scanning-malicious-mfa-qr-codes/</link>
      <description>The PoisonSeed threat group has developed an attack technique that exploits FIDO key cross-device sign-in features, bypassing multifactor authentication (MFA) and allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to protected accounts through social engineering tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150201</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 05:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint 0-Day RCE Flaw Actively Exploited for Full Server Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sharepoint-0-day-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A new SharePoint vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770) is being actively exploited in large-scale attacks worldwide, enabling attackers to gain complete control of on-premise servers without authentication. The exploit chain, dubbed "ToolShell," leverages previously demonstrated Pwn2Own vulnerabilities to achieve remote code execution and steals cryptographic secrets from SharePoint servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150197</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrushFTP 0-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited to Breach Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/crushftp-0-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in CrushFTP servers is being actively exploited by threat actors to compromise systems worldwide. The vulnerability allows attackers to exploit a previously patched issue that remained present in outdated installations, making it critical for organizations to maintain current software versions and implement recommended security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150193</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft releases emergency patches for SharePoint RCE flaws exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-patches-for-sharepoint-rce-flaws-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Two zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-53770 and CVE-2025-53771) were exploited in "ToolShell" attacks to achieve remote code execution on Microsoft SharePoint servers worldwide. The flaws bypassed previous patches and impacted over 54 organizations. Emergency updates have been released for Microsoft SharePoint Subscription Edition, SharePoint 2019, and are still being worked on for SharePoint 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-patches-for-sharepoint-rce-flaws-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Releases Urgent Patch for SharePoint RCE Flaw Exploited in Ongoing Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-releases-urgent-patch-for.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: The exploited vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770) is a remote code execution flaw that arises from the deserialization of untrusted data in on-premise versions of Microsoft SharePoint Server. The newly disclosed spoofing flaw (CVE-2025-53771) allows an authorized attacker to perform spoofing over a network. These flaws are related to two other SharePoint vulnerabilities, and the exploit chain has been patched as part of Microsoft's July 2025 Patch Tuesday update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-releases-urgent-patch-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Coded Credentials Found in HPE Instant On Devices Allow Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hard-coded-credentials-found-in-hpe.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett-Packard Enterprise (HPE) Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, CVE-2025-37102; Summary: The HPE Instant On Access Points have a critical security flaw that allows an attacker to bypass authentication and gain administrative access. Additionally, there is an authenticated command injection flaw in the command-line interface that could be exploited with elevated permissions to run arbitrary commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hard-coded-credentials-found-in-hpe.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,500 Websites Hijacked to Secretly Mine Crypto Using Stealth JavaScript and WebSocket Tactics</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/3500-websites-hijacked-to-secretly-mine.html</link>
      <description>A new attack campaign has compromised over 3,500 websites worldwide with JavaScript cryptocurrency miners, using obfuscated JavaScript, WebSockets, and infrastructure reuse to stay hidden. The malware assesses device capabilities, spawns background Web Workers for mining tasks, and dynamically adjusts mining intensity based on device power without raising alarms.

FYSA: Threat actors are leveraging browser-based cryptojacking attacks, exploiting JavaScript embeds, Google OAuth endpoints, WordPress databases, and plugins to compromise websites and inject malicious code. They use stealthy miners, obfuscation, and infrastructure reuse to stay hidden, prioritizing persistence over resource theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/3500-websites-hijacked-to-secretly-mine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EncryptHub Targets Web3 Developers Using Fake AI Platforms to Deploy Fickle Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/encrypthub-targets-web3-developers.html</link>
      <description>EncryptHub (aka LARVA-208 and Water Gamayun), a financially motivated threat actor, has been attributed to a new campaign targeting Web3 developers with information stealer malware. The attackers use fake AI platforms and trick victims into clicking on meeting links, which ultimately lead to the download of malicious software disguised as a genuine Realtek HD Audio Driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/encrypthub-targets-web3-developers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SharePoint zero-day exploited in RCE attacks, no patch available</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-sharepoint-zero-day-exploited-in-rce-attacks-no-patch-available/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint (CVE-2025-53770) is being actively exploited since July 18th, allowing attackers to steal the MachineKey configuration and inject malicious code. The vulnerability has been chained with two other flaws (CVE-2025-49706 and CVE-2025-49704) to achieve remote code execution. A security update will be released as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-sharepoint-zero-day-exploited-in-rce-attacks-no-patch-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPE warns of hardcoded passwords in Aruba access points</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hpe-warns-of-hardcoded-passwords-in-aruba-access-points/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, None; Summary: Hardcoded login credentials in Aruba Instant On Access Points allow attackers to bypass normal device authentication and access the web interface, enabling administrative access. This vulnerability can be exploited by remote attackers to change settings, install backdoors, capture traffic, or perform lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hpe-warns-of-hardcoded-passwords-in-aruba-access-points/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Microsoft Releases Guidance on Exploitation of SharePoint Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/20/update-microsoft-releases-guidance-exploitation-sharepoint-vulnerabilities</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A vulnerability chain allows unauthorized access to on-premise SharePoint servers through network spoofing and remote code execution (RCE), enabling malicious actors to fully access SharePoint content and execute code over the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23640</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability, CVE-2025-53770 “ToolShell,” to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/20/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-cve-2025-53770-toolshell-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The vulnerability, a remote code execution issue, has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog due to active exploitation. It poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and should be remediated by affected organizations as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23642</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Releases Guidance on Exploitation of SharePoint Vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770)</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/20/microsoft-releases-guidance-exploitation-sharepoint-vulnerability-cve-2025-53770</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in on-premise SharePoint servers enables unauthorized access and allows malicious actors to execute code over the network. The vulnerability is actively being exploited and poses a risk to organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23640</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Unpatched SharePoint Zero-Day Actively Exploited, Breaches 75+ Global Organizations</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-microsoft-sharepoint-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A zero-day flaw in Microsoft SharePoint Server tracked as CVE-2025-53770 (CVSS score: 9.8) allows an unauthorized attacker to execute code over a network through deserialization of untrusted data. The vulnerability is being exploited in a large-scale campaign and has been linked to the previously disclosed CVE-2025-49706.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-microsoft-sharepoint-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware Injected into 6 npm Packages After Maintainer Tokens Stolen in Phishing Attack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malware-injected-into-6-npm-packages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply chain attack targeted popular npm packages via a phishing campaign designed to steal project maintainers' npm tokens. The captured tokens were used to publish malicious versions of the packages, attempting to execute a DLL on Windows machines and potentially allowing remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malware-injected-into-6-npm-packages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Critical CrushFTP Flaw to Gain Admin Access on Unpatched Servers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-critical-crushftp-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to obtain admin access via HTTPS due to mishandled AS2 validation in CrushFTP 10 before 10.8.5 and 11 before 11.3.4_23, when the DMZ proxy feature is not used. This critical flaw has been actively exploited in the wild since July 18, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-critical-crushftp-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat actors downgrade FIDO2 MFA auth in PoisonSeed phishing attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-downgrade-fido2-mfa-auth-in-poisonseed-phishing-attack/</link>
      <description>The PoisonSeed threat actors are bypassing FIDO2 security key protections by abusing the cross-device sign-in feature in WebAuthn to trick users into approving login authentication requests from fake company portals. This attack does not exploit a flaw in FIDO2's implementation but rather uses a legitimate feature that downgrades the FIDO key authentication process. The threat actors can initiate a login flow that relies on cross-device authentication instead of the user's physical FIDO2 key, effectively bypassing security key protections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-downgrade-fido2-mfa-auth-in-poisonseed-phishing-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular npm linter packages hijacked via phishing to drop malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/popular-npm-linter-packages-hijacked-via-phishing-to-drop-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm package eslint-config-prettier; CVE(s): None; Summary: The npm package eslint-config-prettier was compromised after its maintainer fell victim to a phishing attack, allowing the attacker to publish malicious versions of the package that can infect Windows machines. The affected versions are 8.10.1, 9.1.1, 10.1.6, and 10.1.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/popular-npm-linter-packages-hijacked-via-phishing-to-drop-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT"s GPT-5-reasoning-alpha model spotted ahead of launch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-gpt-5-reasoning-alpha-model-spotted-ahead-of-launch/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the upcoming release of OpenAI's GPT-5 model, which may unify breakthroughs from previous models. Additionally, leaks suggest that a new "o3-alpha" model may be released, featuring improved coding and frontend design capabilities. There is no mention of vulnerabilities or cybersecurity threats in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-gpt-5-reasoning-alpha-model-spotted-ahead-of-launch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI, Anthropic, Google may disrupt education market with new AI tools</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-anthropic-google-may-disrupt-education-market-with-new-ai-tools/</link>
      <description>AI companies like OpenAI and Anthropic are developing new AI-based learning tools for students, such as Study Together features that guide the learning process. Google is also testing a similar feature called Guided Learning for Gemini. These tools aim to aid in student learning and potentially disrupt the online education market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-anthropic-google-may-disrupt-education-market-with-new-ai-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New CrushFTP zero-day exploited in attacks to hijack servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks-to-hijack-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-54309 allows attackers to gain administrative access via the web interface on vulnerable servers. The vulnerability affects versions prior to CrushFTP v10.8.5 and v11.3.4_23, which were released around July 1st.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks-to-hijack-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux pulls AUR packages that installed Chaos RAT malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arch-linux-pulls-aur-packages-that-installed-chaos-rat-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Arch User Repository (AUR); CVE(s): None; Summary: The AUR was compromised when a malicious user uploaded three packages containing the CHAOS remote access trojan (RAT). The packages were designed to install the malware on Linux devices, which can be used for cryptocurrency mining, credential harvesting, or cyber espionage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arch-linux-pulls-aur-packages-that-installed-chaos-rat-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 21:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Threat Actors Operate 2,800 Malicious Domains to Distribute Windows Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-threat-actors-operate-2800-malicious-domains/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated threat actor, known as "SilverFox," has been conducting a large-scale malware distribution campaign since at least June 2023, targeting Chinese-speaking individuals and entities. The campaign employs various tactics such as fake application download sites, spurious update prompts, and phishing emails to deliver Windows-specific malware designed for credential theft, financial exploitation, and potential access brokering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150153</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Veeam-Themed Phishing Attack Uses Weaponized WAV File to Target Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-veeam-themed-phishing-attack/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are using voicemail notifications to distribute malware by impersonating Veeam Software. The attack begins with an email containing a WAV file that, upon playback, reveals a scripted call attempting to create urgency around license expiration. The real danger lies in the weaponized nature of the WAV file itself, which can be embedded with malicious code exploiting vulnerabilities in media players or audio processing libraries.

(Note: Since there is no specific vulnerability mentioned, I've summarized the article as a non-vulnerability related cybersecurity content)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150136</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK ties GRU to stealthy Microsoft 365 credential-stealing malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-ties-russian-gru-to-authentic-antics-credential-stealing-malware/</link>
      <description>The Authentic Antics espionage malware attacks are attributed to APT28 (Fancy Bear), a threat actor linked to Russia's military intelligence service (GRU). The malware steals credentials and OAuth 2.0 tokens, allowing access to victim email accounts, and sends stolen data to an attacker-controlled email address using the victim's own Outlook account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-ties-russian-gru-to-authentic-antics-credential-stealing-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft mistakenly tags Windows Firewall error log bug as fixed</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-mistakenly-tags-windows-firewall-error-log-bug-as-fixed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A bug in the Windows Firewall With Advanced Security logs an error message as event ID 2042 every time the device is restarted, but Microsoft states it's not an issue with the Windows Firewall and can be disregarded. The bug was mistakenly marked as fixed in recent updates, and a fix will be released in an upcoming update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-mistakenly-tags-windows-firewall-error-log-bug-as-fixed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma Infostealer Steals Browser Data and Sells It as Logs on Underground Markets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lumma-infostealer-steals-browser-data/</link>
      <description>This article discusses infostealers, specifically the Lumma malware variant, which steals sensitive data from compromised systems. It spreads through phishing operations, social engineering tactics, and malvertising, and is attributed to the Russian-based threat actor Shamel. The malware's ecosystem has been disrupted by a coordinated international effort, but new C2 servers have reemerged, indicating ongoing threat persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150143</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishers have found a way to downgrade—not bypass—FIDO MFA</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-phishers-are-not-bypassing-fido-mfa-at-least-not-yet-heres-why/</link>
      <description>An attacker downgraded FIDO MFA to a weaker form of authentication. The attack is classified as a FIDO downgrade attack, not a bypass, and requires intentional configuration by an admin to fall back to the weaker method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-phishers-are-not-bypassing-fido-mfa-at-least-not-yet-heres-why/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ChatGPT o3-alpha model hints at coding upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/new-chatgpt-o3-alpha-model-hints-at-coding-upgrade/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article mentions OpenAI's o3-alpha model, which features significant coding-related improvements and is capable of designing web pages and creating simple web games. It also hints at the upcoming GPT-5 model, which is expected to unify breakthroughs from different models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/new-chatgpt-o3-alpha-model-hints-at-coding-upgrade/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Surge of Crypto-Jacking Hits Over 3,500 Websites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-surge-of-crypto-jacking/</link>
      <description>The article describes a campaign that infected over 3,500 websites with JavaScript miners, using advanced obfuscation and low-profile execution to evade detection. The miners employ Web Workers to execute mining logic off the main thread, minimizing performance impacts and avoiding traditional red flags like excessive CPU usage or overt network activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150120</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Massistant Tool Secretly Extracts SMS, GPS Data, and Images From Confiscated Phones</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinas-massistant-tool-secretly.html</link>
      <description>Massistant is a mobile forensics tool used by law enforcement authorities in China to gather information from seized mobile devices. It requires physical access to the device and can collect data such as GPS location, SMS messages, images, audio, contacts, and phone services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinas-massistant-tool-secretly.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy Bear Hackers Target Governments and Military Entities with Advanced Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fancy-bear-hackers-target-governments-and-military-entities/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Fancy Bear, a sophisticated Russian cyberespionage collective that has been operational since 2007. They exploit vulnerabilities in office suites, operating systems, and web applications to gain access to targeted organizations. Their tactics include phishing, spearphishing, exploitation of public-facing applications, and command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150128</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Group Hits China, Hong Kong, Pakistan Using LNK Files and RATs in Twin Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ung0002-group-hits-china-hong-kong.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a threat activity cluster tracked as UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002), which has been targeting multiple sectors in China, Hong Kong, and Pakistan. The group uses shortcut files, VBScript, and post-exploitation tools like Cobalt Strike and Metasploit to launch cyber espionage campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ung0002-group-hits-china-hong-kong.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian alcohol retailer WineLab closes stores after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-alcohol-retailer-winelab-closes-stores-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>WineLab, a retail store of the largest alcohol company in Russia, has closed its stores following a cyberattack that is impacting its operations and causing purchase problems to its customers. The attackers requested a ransom payment, but the company declined to engage and won't comply with their demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-alcohol-retailer-winelab-closes-stores-after-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Zero-Days Exploited to Drop MDifyLoader and Launch In-Memory Cobalt Strike Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ivanti-zero-days-exploited-to-drop.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Connect Secure (ICS) appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0282, CVE-2025-22457; Summary: The vulnerabilities in ICS appliances have been weaponized to drop MDifyLoader, which is used to launch Cobalt Strike in memory. The attacks exploit a critical security flaw (CVE-2025-0282) and a stack-based buffer overflow (CVE-2025-22457) that were previously patched by Ivanti in January 2025 and April 2025, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ivanti-zero-days-exploited-to-drop.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Keylogger Bypasses Windows Defender and Uses Scheduled Tasks to Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/snake-keylogger-bypasses-windows-defender/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated phishing operation impersonates Turkish Aerospace Industries (TUSAŞ) to attack Turkish businesses in the defense and aerospace sectors. The campaign distributes malicious emails containing a PE32 executable that delivers a variant of the Snake Keylogger, an information-stealing malware designed to harvest sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150163</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Phobos ransomware decryptor lets victims recover files for free</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phobos-ransomware-decryptor-lets-victims-recover-files-for-free/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phobos and 8Base Ransomware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the release of a free decryptor by the Japanese police for victims of the Phobos and 8Base ransomware operations. The decryptor can recover files encrypted by these operations, including those with extensions such as ".phobos", ".8base", ".elbie", ".faust", and ".LIZARD".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phobos-ransomware-decryptor-lets-victims-recover-files-for-free/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers scanning for TeleMessage Signal clone flaw exposing passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-scanning-for-telemessage-signal-clone-flaw-exposing-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48927, CVE-2025-48928; Summary: The TeleMessage SGNL app allows retrieving usernames, passwords, and other sensitive data due to the exposure of the '/heapdump' endpoint from Spring Boot Actuator without authentication. This vulnerability (CVE-2025-48927) lets an attacker download a full Java heap memory dump, which may contain plaintext usernames, passwords, tokens, and other sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-scanning-for-telemessage-signal-clone-flaw-exposing-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web vs Dark Web: What’s the Real Difference?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/deep-web-vs-dark-web-difference/</link>
      <description>The article explains the difference between the deep web and the dark web. While both are non-indexed by search engines, the deep web is a larger part of the internet that includes private content accessible through standard browsers, whereas the dark web is a smaller subset that uses encryption to maintain anonymity and often hosts illegal or malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New QR Code Attacks Through PDFs Bypass Detection and Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-qr-code-attacks-through-pdfs/</link>
      <description>The article discusses an ongoing phishing campaign called "Scanception" that uses QR code-based delivery mechanisms to distribute credential-harvesting URLs. The campaign involves targeted emails with PDF lures, social engineering tactics, and abuse of trusted services to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150095</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophos Intercept X for Windows Flaws Enable Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophos-intercept-x-for-windows-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13972, CVE-2025-7433, CVE-2025-7472; Summary: Three critical security vulnerabilities were discovered in Sophos Intercept X for Windows, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain system-level privileges. The vulnerabilities affect different components of the software, including the updater, Device Encryption module, and installer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150111</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Sues BadBox 2.0 Botnet Operators Behind 10 Million+ Infected Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-sues-badbox-2-0-botnet-operators/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the BadBox 2.0 botnet, a network of over 10 million insecure devices running Android Open Source Project (AOSP) that were compromised by malware during manufacturing and used for ad fraud schemes and other illicit activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150080</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grafana Flaws Allow User Redirection and Code Execution in Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/grafana-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grafana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6023, CVE-2025-6197; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities were discovered in Grafana's scripted dashboards and organization switching functionality. The first vulnerability is a high-severity cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw that can redirect users to malicious websites and execute arbitrary code, while the second is a medium-severity open redirect flaw that requires specific conditions for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150097</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquiti UniFi Vulnerability Lets Hackers Inject Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ubiquiti-unifi-vulnerability-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti UniFi Access devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27212; Summary: The vulnerability allows malicious actors to inject and execute arbitrary commands on affected systems due to improper input validation within certain UniFi Access devices, carrying a maximum CVSS score of 9.8. It can be exploited by attackers with access to the UniFi Access management network, enabling them to bypass normal security controls and potentially gain unauthorized access to sensitive areas or systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150090</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for Office 365 Gets Enhanced Threat Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-defender-threat-dashboard/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced a new customer-facing dashboard for its email security platform, providing detailed visibility into threat protection effectiveness across organizations. The enhanced dashboard and two comparative benchmarking reports aim to empower organizations with actionable data about their security posture and foster trust through transparency in threat protection capabilities. The initiative recognizes the importance of continuous evaluation of security solutions in today's sophisticated threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150085</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/18/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: The vulnerability, an SQL injection flaw, has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to active exploitation. It poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and requires timely remediation to protect against cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23639</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: CrazyHunter Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-crazyhunter-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the "CrazyHunter" ransomware group, which has been targeting Taiwanese organizations, particularly in the healthcare and technology sectors. The group uses advanced tactics, techniques, and tools (TTPs) such as BYOVD, SharpGPOAbuse, and Prince Ransomware builder to carry out sophisticated attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061922</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERT-UA Discovers LAMEHUG Malware Linked to APT28, Using LLM for Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cert-ua-discovers-lamehug-malware.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on a phishing campaign that delivered a malware codenamed LAMEHUG, attributed with medium confidence to the Russian state-sponsored hacking group tracked asAPT28. The malware uses a large language model (LLM) to generate commands based on textual representation, and supports commands to harvest basic information about the compromised host and search for specific files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cert-ua-discovers-lamehug-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Sues 25 Chinese Entities Over BADBOX 2.0 Botnet Affecting 10M Android Devices</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-sues-25-chinese-entities-over.html</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it reports on Google's legal action against 25 unnamed individuals or entities in China for allegedly operating the BADBOX 2.0 botnet and residential proxy infrastructure, which compromises over 10 million Android devices running open-source software. The botnet is used to conduct large-scale ad fraud and other digital crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-sues-25-chinese-entities-over.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Ivanti Connect Secure Flaws to Deploy Cobalt Strike Beacon</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-ivanti-connect-secure-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Connect Secure; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0282, CVE-2025-22457; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting vulnerabilities in Ivanti Connect Secure to deploy advanced malware, including MDifyLoader and Cobalt Strike Beacon. The attacks use DLL hijacking and side-loading to inject malware into memory, and employ obfuscation and encryption to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150041</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical NVIDIA Container Toolkit Flaw Allows Privilege Escalation on AI Cloud Services</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: The NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains a critical container escape vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-23266, which carries a CVSS score of 9.0 out of 10.0. An attacker could execute arbitrary code with elevated permissions, potentially leading to escalation of privileges, data tampering, information disclosure, and denial-of-service. The vulnerability affects all versions up to and including 1.17.7 and has been addressed in versions 1.17.8 and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Backup to Cyber Resilience: Why IT Leaders Must Rethink Backup in the Age of Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-cyber-resilience-helps-it-defend-against-ransomwa.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of maintaining operations during an incident, especially in light of escalating IT outages and ransomware attacks. It highlights the limitations of traditional backup strategies, which often rely on manual testing and may not account for targeted cyberattacks that aim to destroy recovery infrastructure. The article emphasizes the need for a "resilience-first" approach, which integrates immutable backups, automated testing, and orchestrated recovery playbooks to ensure business continuity even during an attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-cyber-resilience-helps-it-defend-against-ransomwa.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit ClickFix Tactics to Spread NetSupport RAT, Latrodectus, and Lumma Stealer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-clickfix-tactics/</link>
      <description>Attackers are using the ClickFix social engineering technique to distribute malware families like NetSupport RAT, Latrodectus, and Lumma Stealer. This technique tricks users into executing malicious commands by hijacking their clipboard and injecting obfuscated PowerShell scripts or commands that victims unwittingly paste into system interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149986</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Protection Driver Flaw Enables Privilege Escalation and Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lenovo-protection-driver-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4657; Summary: Lenovo's protection driver software contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges, posing significant security risks. The flaw affects Lenovo PC Manager, Lenovo Browser, and Lenovo App Store versions prior to 5.1.110.4231, impacting millions of users worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150016</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI: GPT-5 is coming, "we'll see" if it creates a shockwave</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-gpt-5-is-coming-well-see-if-it-creates-a-shockwave/</link>
      <description>OpenAI's next AI model, GPT-5, is still in development and no release date has been announced. Additionally, the company is planning to upgrade its Operator tool and adding new features to its Image Gen model, including a built-in style feature on ChatGPT. There are also hints about an Operator-like tool being tested on ChatGPT ahead of GPT-5's launch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-gpt-5-is-coming-well-see-if-it-creates-a-shockwave/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Uncovers Scattered Spider Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures in Recent Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-uncovers-scattered-spider-tactics/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the tactics and techniques used by a financially motivated cybercriminal group called Octo Tempest (Scattered Spider, Muddled Libra, UNC3944, or 0ktapus). The group uses advanced social engineering campaigns, phishing attacks, and exploitation of Azure Active Directory environments to gain initial access and pivot to cloud resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149967</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAFFLED: New Technique Targets Web Application Firewall Weaknesses</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/waffled-new-technique-targets-web-application/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various WAF platforms (AWS WAF, Azure WAF, Google Cloud Armor, Cloudflare, and ModSecurity); CVE(s): None; Summary: The WAFFLED attack technique exploits parsing discrepancies in Web Application Firewalls (WAFs) to bypass security measures and compromise the security of millions of websites worldwide. The technique targets three content types (multipart/form-data, application/json, and application/xml) and affects five major WAF platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149970</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit GitHub Accounts to Host Payloads, Tools, and Amadey Malware Plugins</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-github-accounts/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation that employed the Amadey botnet to distribute various payloads. The operation exploited fake GitHub accounts as open directories, bypassing web filtering mechanisms and simplifying distribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149921</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Vodka Maker Beluga Struck by Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beluga-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>Novabev Group, the parent company of Beluga vodka, was hit by a sophisticated ransomware attack on July 14, 2025, causing temporary disruptions to its IT infrastructure and services. The company refused to pay any ransom demands and is working to restore normal operations with the help of external cybersecurity experts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149962</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 08:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Daemon Ex Plist’ Vulnerability Grants Root Access on macOS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/daemon-ex-plist-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27981; Summary: A newly discovered vulnerability in macOS allows attackers to escalate privileges from standard user to root access by exploiting a timing flaw in how the operating system handles daemon configuration files. The vulnerability requires no initial elevated permissions and can be exploited through simple XML modifications, giving attackers complete system control, including disabling System Integrity Protection (SIP), manipulating privacy databases, and installing persistent backdoors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149950</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes 13 ICS Security Advisories on Critical Flaws</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-13-ics-security-advisories/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released thirteen Industrial Control Systems (ICS) security advisories highlighting critical vulnerabilities in operational technology networks across multiple sectors. The advisories warn of potential disruptions to essential infrastructure services, emphasizing the importance of immediate action to prevent exploitation by threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149942</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best XDR (Extended Detection And Response) Solutions 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/best-xdr-solutions/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article presents an analysis of top 10 Extended Detection and Response (XDR) solutions in the market. The review highlights the strengths and approaches of each solution, including their ability to integrate with existing security stacks, detect advanced threats, and streamline incident response.

The XDR solutions reviewed are:

1. Google Chronicle Security Operations
2. Exabeam Fusion XDR
3. Fortinet FortiXDR
4. Sophos XDR
5. Mandiant Security Operations (part of Google Chronicle)
6. Microsoft Azure Sentinel
7. Palo Alto Networks XDR
8. FireEye Helix XDR
9. RSA NetWitness XDR
10. CrowdStrike Falcon XDR

The analysis notes that each solution has its unique strengths and weaknesses, making it essential for organizations to carefully evaluate their specific needs and requirements before selecting an XDR solution.

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the current state of XDR solutions in the market and highlights the importance of choosing a suitable solution to effectively detect and respond to advanced threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=126278</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal App Clone Telemessage App Vulnerability Actively Exploited for Password Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/signal-app-clone-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessageTM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48927; Summary: A critical vulnerability in TeleMessageTM SGNL's legacy configuration of Spring Boot Actuator allows threat actors to steal passwords and sensitive data by exploiting a publicly accessible diagnostic endpoint. The vulnerability affects certain deployments of the secure communications archiving system and has been actively exploited since at least May 5, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149907</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 06:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIND 9 Vulnerabilities Enable Cache Poisoning and Service Disruption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bind-9-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Internet Systems Consortium (ISC) BIND 9; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40776, CVE-2025-40777; Summary: Two critical security vulnerabilities in BIND 9, one allowing cache poisoning attacks and the other causing assertion failures leading to service disruption. These flaws primarily impact DNS resolvers rather than authoritative servers, with potential for redirecting users to malicious websites or intercepting communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149900</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 05:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor Passwords Tattle on AI Hiring Bot Maker Paradox.ai</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/poor-passwords-tattle-on-ai-hiring-bot-maker-paradox-ai/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Paradox.ai; CVE(s): None; Summary: The personal information of millions of people who applied for jobs at McDonald's was exposed after researchers guessed the password ("123456") for Paradox.ai's account. The weak password allowed access to 64 million records, including applicants' names, email addresses, and phone numbers.

FYSA: Threat actors exploited a Paradox.ai administrator in Vietnam's malware-infected device, stealing usernames and passwords for various internal and third-party services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71668</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 01:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 exploited weeks before PoCs as Citrix denied attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-exploited-weeks-before-pocs-as-citrix-denied-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: A critical memory overread vulnerability, dubbed "CitrixBleed 2," allows attackers to send malformed POST requests and leak 127 bytes of memory. The flaw can be exploited to expose sensitive data, hijack sessions, and gain unauthorized access to internal resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-exploited-weeks-before-pocs-as-citrix-denied-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 23:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub abused to distribute payloads on behalf of malware-as-a-service</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/malware-as-a-service-caught-using-github-to-distribute-its-payloads/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a malicious activity campaign called Amadey, which is likely part of a larger Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation. Threat actors behind Amadey are distributing various malware families from fake GitHub repositories onto infected hosts, suggesting they may be serving payloads for other individuals or groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/malware-as-a-service-caught-using-github-to-distribute-its-payloads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware fixes four ESXi zero-day bugs exploited at Pwn2Own Berlin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-fixes-four-esxi-zero-day-bugs-exploited-at-pwn2own-berlin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware ESXi, Workstation, Fusion, and Tools; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41236, CVE-2025-41237, CVE-2025-41238, CVE-2025-41239; Summary: Three of the patched flaws allow programs running in a guest virtual machine to execute commands on the host, while the fourth is an information disclosure. The first three have a severity rating of 9.3 and were exploited as zero-days during Pwn2Own Berlin 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-fixes-four-esxi-zero-day-bugs-exploited-at-pwn2own-berlin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams voice calls abused to push Matanbuchus malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-voice-calls-abused-to-push-matanbuchus-malware/</link>
      <description>The Matanbuchus malware loader is being distributed through social engineering over Microsoft Teams calls impersonating IT helpdesk, allowing attackers to gain initial access and deliver malicious payloads. The latest version, Matanbuchus 3.0, includes enhanced evasion, obfuscation, and post-compromise capabilities, making it a sophisticated threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-voice-calls-abused-to-push-matanbuchus-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-616: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer CATPRODUCT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-616/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6971; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CATPRODUCT files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26975</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
