<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs join ongoing SAP NetWeaver attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-join-ongoing-sap-netweaver-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A maximum-severity vulnerability allows threat actors to gain remote code execution on vulnerable servers. The vulnerability can be exploited without login credentials, potentially leading to complete system compromise. Ransomware gangs, including RansomEXX and BianLian, have joined attacks exploiting this flaw, with evidence of Chinese threat actor involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-join-ongoing-sap-netweaver-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An $8.4 billion money launderer has been operating for years on US soil</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/incorporated-in-us-8-4b-money-launderer-for-chinese-speaking-crypto-scammers/</link>
      <description>Tether, a cryptocurrency, has the ability to freeze payments when it identifies bad actors. Despite this capability, there is no clear evidence that Tether has taken measures to stop Chinese-language crypto scammers and others from using its currency. The article highlights the ongoing struggle against financial crime in the cryptocurrency space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/incorporated-in-us-8-4b-money-launderer-for-chinese-speaking-crypto-scammers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Human Rights Commission leaks docs to search engines</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/australian-human-rights-commission-leaks-docs-to-search-engines/</link>
      <description>The Australian Human Rights Commission (AHRC) disclosed a data breach incident where private documents containing sensitive information, such as names, contact information, health details, and photographs, were leaked online and indexed by major search engines. The breach impacted 670 submissions between specific dates, and AHRC has requested the removal of the files from search engines and disabled web forms to prevent further exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/australian-human-rights-commission-leaks-docs-to-search-engines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xinbi Telegram Market Tied to $8.4B in Crypto Crime, Romance Scams, North Korea Laundering</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/xinbi-telegram-market-tied-to-84b-in.html</link>
      <description>Xinbi Guarantee, a Telegram-based marketplace, has facilitated $8.4 billion in transactions since 2022, offering various illicit services such as technology sales, personal data trading, and money laundering services. The platform's users include vendors selling fake IDs, databases of stolen information, and services for stalking and intimidating targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/xinbi-telegram-market-tied-to-84b-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage Weaponized HTML Files to Deliver Horabot Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-weaponized-html-files/</link>
      <description>A phishing campaign targeting Spanish-speaking users in Latin America has been discovered by FortiGuard Labs. The attack uses malicious HTML files embedded in emails to steal sensitive information and propagate through networks. The campaign is highly sophisticated, using browser redirection tricks, custom string decoding, and PowerShell scripts to evade detection and exfiltrate data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135763</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TA406 Hackers Target Government Entities to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ta406-hackers-target-government-entities/</link>
      <description>TA406, a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor, has launched targeted phishing campaigns against Ukrainian government entities. The attacks aim to gather strategic intelligence on the Russian invasion of Ukraine and assess risks to North Korea's forces assisting Russia. The campaign involves credential harvesting through fake Microsoft security alerts and malware deployment via RAR archives and HTML attachments.

FYSA: TA406's dual-pronged offensive includes credential harvesting through fake Microsoft security alerts and malware deployment via RAR archives and HTML attachments, aiming to gather strategic intelligence on the Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Threat Intelligence Releases Actionable Threat Hunting Technique for Malicious .desktop Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-releases-actionable-threat-hunting-technique/</link>
      <description>Malicious .desktop files were discovered to be a novel attack vector used by threat actors to compromise systems. These files exploit legitimate system processes and use junk code to obfuscate their intent. The files, which typically include sections like [Desktop Entry] with keys such as Name, Comment, Exec, and Icon, can trigger commands that open seemingly innocuous PDFs via Google Drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135719</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Adobe Photoshop Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-adobe-photoshop-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Photoshop; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30324, CVE-2025-30325, CVE-2025-30326; Summary: Three high-severity vulnerabilities in Photoshop 2024 and 2025 allow arbitrary code execution on Windows and macOS systems through memory corruption risks. The flaws involve improper memory management during image file processing and require user interaction via malicious file openings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135681</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe Adobe Illustrator Flaw Allows Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/severe-adobe-illustrator-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Illustrator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30330; Summary: The vulnerability allows arbitrary code execution on affected systems, impacting Windows and macOS versions of Illustrator 2024 and 2025. It could enable attackers to take control of a user's device by tricking them into opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135702</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Linux boot issues on dual-boot Windows systems</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-linux-boot-issues-on-dual-boot-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The August 2024 Windows security updates prevented Linux from booting on dual-boot systems with Secure Boot enabled, due to an SBAT update that blocks UEFI shim bootloaders vulnerable to the CVE-2022-2601 GRUB2 Secure Boot bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-linux-boot-issues-on-dual-boot-windows-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel giant Nucor Corporation facing disruptions after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-corporation-facing-disruptions-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation, the largest steel producer in the US, experienced a cybersecurity incident that forced it to take parts of its network offline and suspend production at multiple locations. The incident has been reported to law enforcement authorities and external cybersecurity experts have been engaged to assist with the investigation. No details about the attack's date or type were provided, including whether data theft or encryption was involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-corporation-facing-disruptions-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Unveil New Mechanism to Track Compartmentalized Cyber Threats</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-mechanism-to-track-compartmentalized-cyber-threats/</link>
      <description>This article introduces the extended Diamond Model for cybersecurity professionals to tackle compartmentalized cyber threats. The model integrates a "Relationship Layer" to contextualize interactions between adversaries, capabilities, infrastructure, and victims, enabling accurate attribution and prevention of erroneous clustering of threat activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135703</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HTTPBot Botnet Rapidly Expands to Target Windows Machines</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-httpbot-botnet-rapidly-expands/</link>
      <description>The HTTPBot Botnet is a novel Trojan developed in the Go programming language that targets Windows machines and uses innovative HTTP-based Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attack methods to target high-value business interfaces. It deploys seven distinct HTTP attack techniques, including randomized User-Agent strings, dynamic URL paths, and cookie replenishment mechanisms to bypass conventional rule-based detection systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135680</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTM360 Identifies Surge in Phishing Attacks Targeting Meta Business Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ctm360-identifies-surge-in-phishing.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a global phishing threat called "Meta Mirage" that targets businesses using Meta's Business Suite. The attackers impersonate official Meta communications, tricking users into handing over sensitive details like passwords and security codes (OTP). The campaign uses fake alerts about policy violations, account suspensions, or urgent verification notices to deceive victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ctm360-identifies-surge-in-phishing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Phishing: Attack Targets Victims With Trusted Sites and Live Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/focused-phishing-attack-targets-victims-with-trusted-sites-and-live-validation/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a real-world phishing incident that showcases advanced tactics used by attackers, including leveraging legitimate infrastructure, precision email validation, and evasive delivery techniques. The attack involved a server-side phishing page that dynamically handled email input and included anti-analysis mechanisms to obstruct analysis efforts. The article highlights the importance of browser-based, zero-day phishing protection and emphasizes the need for security stacks to detect and block phishing pages even on trusted domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/focused-phishing-attack-targets-victims-with-trusted-sites-and-live-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May 2025 Patch Tuesday: 78 Flaws, 5 Exploited, &amp; Critical SAP Fixes</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/may-2025-patch-tuesday-78-flaws-5-exploited-critical-sap-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709, CVE-2025-30397, and others; Summary: Microsoft has released May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates addressing a total of 78 vulnerabilities across its software. Five zero-day vulnerabilities have been confirmed as exploited in the wild, including use-after-free bugs in Windows Desktop Window Manager (DWM) Core Library, Common Log File System (CLFS) driver, and Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock. Other critical vulnerabilities affect Azure, Microsoft Office, and Remote Desktop Client, with some allowing Remote Code Execution (RCE), elevation of privileges, spoofing, or data exposure.

FYSA: Five zero-day vulnerabilities have been confirmed as exploited in the wild, including use-after-free bugs in Windows Desktop Window Manager (DWM) Core Library, Common Log File System (CLFS) driver, and Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock. Threat actors are actively scanning for newly patched bugs and exploiting these vulnerabilities to gain elevated privileges or unauthorized access.

FYSA: This article discusses Microsoft's May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, which address a total of 78 vulnerabilities across its software. The article highlights the importance of prioritizing patch deployment, assessing external exposure, and ensuring continuous visibility into emerging threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060006</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katz Stealer Malware Hits 78+ Chromium and Gecko-Based Browsers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/katz-stealer-malware-hits-78-chromium/</link>
      <description>Katz Stealer is a newly disclosed information-stealing malware that targets Chromium and Gecko-based browsers, extracting sensitive data including credentials, cookies, autofill data, CVV2 codes, OAuth tokens, cryptocurrency wallets, and messaging platform credentials. The malware's customizable build panel with anti-VM safeguards and web-based C2 interface enables threat actors to tailor payloads and manage stolen data, posing a persistent threat to individual and enterprise security postures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135653</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion giant Dior discloses cyberattack, warns of data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fashion-giant-dior-discloses-cyberattack-warns-of-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Dior, a French luxury fashion brand, has disclosed a cybersecurity incident that exposed customer information, including full name, gender, phone number, email address, postal address, purchase history, and preferences. The incident was discovered on May 7, and while account passwords and payment card information were not affected, customers are advised to remain vigilant for phishing attempts and report any brand impersonation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fashion-giant-dior-discloses-cyberattack-warns-of-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Windows Remote Desktop Gateway Allows Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-windows-remote-desktop-gateway/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Remote Desktop Gateway (RDG); CVE(s): CVE-2025-26677, CVE-2025-29831; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities were discovered in the Microsoft RDG service, allowing for denial-of-service (DoS) attacks and remote code execution (RCE), respectively. The vulnerabilities have been patched in Microsoft's May 2025 security update, but unpatched systems are at risk of operational disruption or unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135577</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Microsoft Outlook Flaw Enables Remote Execution of Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-microsoft-outlook-flaw-enables-remote-execution/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Outlook; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32705; Summary: A memory corruption flaw in Microsoft Outlook allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by reading data beyond allocated buffer boundaries. The vulnerability affects all Outlook versions from 2019 to the latest 2025 build and has a low attack complexity, requiring minimal user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135640</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kosovo extradites BlackDB admin to face US cybercrime charges</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kosovo-extradites-blackdb-admin-to-face-us-cybercrime-charges/</link>
      <description>A Kosovo national, Liridon Masurica (also known as @blackdb), has been extradited to the United States and charged with five counts of fraudulent use of unauthorized access devices and one count of conspiracy to commit access device fraud. He is accused of running an online cybercrime marketplace called BlackDB.cc that illegally offered compromised accounts, stolen credit card information, and personally identifiable information (PII) for sale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kosovo-extradites-blackdb-admin-to-face-us-cybercrime-charges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender Vulnerability Allows Unauthorized Privilege Gain</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-defender-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26684; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (CVE-2025-26684) allows authenticated attackers with high privileges to manipulate file names or paths and execute arbitrary code, enabling local privilege escalation attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135622</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Cyberattacks in 2024 Expose 276 Million Patient Records Compromised</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/healthcare-cyberattacks-in-2024/</link>
      <description>The healthcare sector faced an unprecedented wave of cyber threats, with 92% of organizations reporting at least one cyberattack. The attacks resulted in the compromise of over 276 million patient records, with victims of medical identity theft spending an average of 210 hours and $2,500 out-of-pocket to reclaim their identities and mitigate the damage. The campaign involved a sophisticated phishing attack impersonating legitimate medical service providers like Zocdoc, targeting healthcare consumers and employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135633</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit AI and LLM Tools for Offensive Cyber Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-ai-and-llm-tools/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are misusing generative AI and large language models (LLMs) for malicious cyber operations, including exploit generation, malware creation, and bypassing security mechanisms. LLMs like ChatGPT, Claude, and DeepSeek are being weaponized on dark web forums such as Cracked and BreachForums, with a focus on prompt engineering and open-source research for nefarious purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135578</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation-State Actors Target Healthcare Institutions to Sabotage IT and OT Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nation-state-actors-target-healthcare-institutions/</link>
      <description>Nation-state actors are increasingly targeting healthcare institutions worldwide, launching sophisticated cyberattacks that disrupt IT and OT systems, posing a severe threat to patient safety, data integrity, and operational continuity. The attacks involve APTs, ransomware, and zero-day exploits, with motives ranging from geopolitical leverage to economic disruption and psychological warfare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135595</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Tuesday, May 2025 Edition</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/patch-tuesday-may-2025-edition/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-30397; Summary: At least 70 vulnerabilities were fixed in Windows and related products, including five zero-day flaws that are already being exploited. The vulnerabilities include elevation of privilege bugs in the Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) driver and the Desktop Window Manager (DWM) library, as well as a flaw in the Microsoft Scripting Engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71250</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Ammit Breached Drone Supply Chains via ERP in VENOM, TIDRONE Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/earth-ammit-breached-drone-supply.html</link>
      <description>The article describes two related cyber espionage campaigns, VENOM and TIDRONE, attributed to the group Earth Ammit. The campaigns targeted various entities in Taiwan and South Korea, including military, satellite, and technology sectors, with the goal of compromising trusted networks via supply chain attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/earth-ammit-breached-drone-supply.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Hack: Why Offensive Security Training Benefits Your Entire Security Team</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/learning-how-to-hack-why-offensive.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of investing in offensive operations training for cybersecurity teams to stay ahead of evolving threats. It highlights the benefits of such training for various roles within a security team, including detection engineering, triage, remediation, and incident response. The author emphasizes that understanding attacker tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) enables practitioners to better prioritize vulnerabilities, identify malicious activity, and respond more effectively to incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/learning-how-to-hack-why-offensive.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horabot Malware Targets 6 Latin American Nations Using Invoice-Themed Phishing Emails</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/horabot-malware-targets-6-latin.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a new phishing campaign targeting Windows users in Latin American countries with malware called Horabot. The campaign uses crafted emails impersonating invoices or financial documents to trick victims into opening malicious attachments, stealing email credentials, and installing banking trojans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/horabot-malware-targets-6-latin.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized PyPI Package Targets Developers to Steal Source Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-pypi-package-targets-developers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI "solana-token" package; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "solana-token" Python package was discovered to be malicious, targeting developers working with the Solana blockchain. It exhibited characteristics of infostealer malware, including hardcoded URLs referencing command-and-control servers and file-reading behaviors. The primary objective is to steal hardcoded cryptographic secrets, such as private keys or access credentials to cryptocurrency wallets, making it a precursor to potentially devastating breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135544</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Alerts on AD CS Flaw Enabling Remote Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-alerts-on-ad-cs-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS); CVE(s): CVE-2025-29968; Summary: A newly identified vulnerability in AD CS allows authenticated attackers to disrupt critical certificate management operations over a network, enabling denial-of-service (DoS) attacks. The flaw stems from improper input validation and requires valid authentication credentials for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135539</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkCloud Stealer: Comprehensive Analysis of a New Attack Chain That Employs AutoIt</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/darkcloud-stealer-and-obfuscated-autoit-scripting/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the DarkCloud Stealer malware, which is a data-stealing malware that collects and exfiltrates sensitive information such as computer names, usernames, passwords, and credit card details. The malware uses multi-stage payloads and obfuscated AutoIt scripting to evade detection and establish command and control (C2) communications.

FYSA: Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected from DarkCloud Stealer through their Network Security solutions and Cortex line of products, including Advanced WildFire, Cortex XDR, and Cortex XSIAM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=140509</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerabilities in Fortinet and Ivanti Products: Multiple Zero-Day Threats Addressed</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/fortinet-and-ivanti-products-zero-day-threat-addressed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiVoice Enterprise; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A severe remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands via specially crafted HTTP requests, impacting multiple Fortinet products. The flaw is a stack-based buffer overflow that has been actively exploited in zero-day attacks.

Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Neurons for ITSM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22462; Summary: A critical authentication bypass vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to gain administrative access in low-complexity attack scenarios, impacting versions 2023.4, 2024.2, and 2024.3. Patched versions include May 2025 Security Patches for all affected versions.

Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Two vulnerabilities have been exploited in a limited number of attacks, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on exposed systems. Mitigated in EPMM 11.12.0.5, EPMM 12.3.0.2, EPMM 12.4.0.2, and EPMM 12.5.0.1.

FYSA: Hundreds of Ivanti EPMM instances remain exposed online, with the highest numbers in Germany and the United States, highlighting an ongoing trend of attackers exploiting enterprise software flaws to gain deep access into critical systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059996</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit SAP NetWeaver Zero-Day Vulnerability to Target Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-exploit-sap-netweaver-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: The article describes a sophisticated cyber-espionage campaign targeting critical infrastructure worldwide, exploiting an unauthenticated file upload flaw in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer. The vulnerability allows remote code execution (RCE), providing attackers with a gateway to compromise high-value networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135500</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Unveil New Threat-Hunting Techniques to Detect Azure Managed Identity Abuse</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-unveil-new-threat-hunting-techniques/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a research paper by Hunters' Team Axon that presents threat-hunting techniques to identify and prevent the misuse of Azure Managed Identities. The paper provides tools and strategies for detecting suspicious behaviors, tracing compromised identities, and assessing blast radii of permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135478</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows CLFS Zero-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-clfs-zero-day-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32701; Summary: The Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) Driver has two critical security vulnerabilities that allow local privilege escalation and have been confirmed to be actively exploited in the wild. The first vulnerability is due to improper input validation, while the second is a Use-After-Free condition. Both require local access, low attack complexity, and low privileges but can result in complete compromise of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135492</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server Flaw Allows Arbitrary File Writes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-samsung-magicinfo-9-server-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4632; Summary: The MagicINFO 9 Server platform has a critical path traversal vulnerability that allows unauthorized actors to write arbitrary files with system-level privileges. Attackers could exploit this flaw to bypass directory restrictions, create or overwrite critical system files, and potentially implant persistence mechanisms, manipulate firmware images, or disrupt entire digital signage networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135472</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Fixes 78 Flaws, 5 Zero-Days Exploited; CVSS 10 Bug Impacts Azure DevOps Server</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-fixes-78-flaws-5-zero-days.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709; Summary: Five zero-day vulnerabilities have been identified in Microsoft's software lineup, including the Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability (CVE-2025-30397), Microsoft Desktop Window Manager (DWM) Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-30400), Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-32701 and CVE-2025-32706), and Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-32709). These vulnerabilities can lead to remote code execution, privilege escalation, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-fixes-78-flaws-5-zero-days.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Ancillary for WinSock 0-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited to Gain Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-ancillary-for-winsock-0-day-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32709; Summary: The Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock contains a critical privilege escalation vulnerability that allows local attackers with basic user privileges to gain SYSTEM-level access. Attackers can exploit the use-after-free flaw by crafting specific IOCTL requests, enabling arbitrary code execution in kernel space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135423</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Ammit Hackers Deploy New Tools to Target Military Drones</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/earth-ammit-hackers-deploy-new-tools/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the threat actor group Earth Ammit, believed to be associated with Chinese-speaking APTs, which orchestrated two campaigns (VENOM and TIDRONE) targeting Taiwan and South Korea. The group exploited supply chain vulnerabilities, using open-source tools and custom-built malware to maintain persistence and evade attribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135447</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Microsoft Scripting Engine Vulnerability Exposes Systems to Remote Code Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-microsoft-scripting-engine-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Scripting Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397; Summary: A type confusion weakness (CWE-843) allows remote code execution (RCE) attacks over networks by manipulating the engine's memory processes. Attackers can craft malicious scripts that confuse the engine into interpreting memory addresses as executable code segments, enabling arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135408</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Microsoft Office Vulnerabilities Enable Malicious Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-microsoft-office-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30377, CVE-2025-30386, CVE-2025-26629; Summary: Three critical security flaws in Microsoft Office enable remote code execution via use-after-free memory corruption weaknesses. The most severe vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-30377 and CVE-2025-30386, can be exploited without user interaction, while the third vulnerability, CVE-2025-26629, requires user interaction to execute malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135397</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windows RDP Vulnerability Enables Network-Based Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-windows-rdp-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop services; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29966, CVE-2025-29967; Summary: Two critical heap-based buffer overflow flaws affect the Windows Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) and Remote Desktop Gateway (RD Gateway) service, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems over a network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135387</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical 0-Day in Windows DWM Enables Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-0-day-in-windows-dwm/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Desktop Window Manager (DWM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-30400; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers with local access to elevate their privileges on affected systems through a use-after-free memory condition in the DWM component. This zero-day threat has been actively exploited despite no prior public disclosure, and its exploitation grants attackers full control over affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135379</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Patches CVE-2025-32756 Zero-Day RCE Flaw Exploited in FortiVoice Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fortinet-patches-cve-2025-32756-zero.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A critical security flaw (CVE-2025-32756) in FortiVoice, FortiMail, FortiNDR, FortiRecorder, and FortiCamera allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands via crafted HTTP requests. The vulnerability has been exploited in the wild, with threat actors performing device network scans, erasing system crash logs, and enabling fcgi debugging to log credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fortinet-patches-cve-2025-32756-zero.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Patches EPMM Vulnerabilities Exploited for Remote Code Execution in Limited Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ivanti-patches-epmm-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Ivanti EPMM software contains two security flaws that can be chained together to gain remote code execution. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to access protected resources without proper credentials and execute arbitrary code on the target system. Affected versions include 11.12.0.4 and prior, 12.3.0.1 and prior, 12.4.0.1 and prior, and 12.5.0.0 and prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ivanti-patches-epmm-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-288: Fortinet FortiWeb cgi_httpcontentrouting_post Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-288/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25254; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fortinet FortiWeb, requiring authentication to exploit. It occurs in the cgi_httpcontentrouting_post function due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to file operations, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25181</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-289: Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-289/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation ThinManager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3618; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Rockwell Automation ThinManager. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the ThinServer component due to a null pointer dereference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25872</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-290: Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-290/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation ThinManager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3617; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Rockwell Automation ThinManager by creating a symbolic link within the ThinServer component. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25727</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP patches second zero-day flaw exploited in recent attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sap-patches-second-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-recent-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: The article discusses a zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-42999) exploited in recent attacks targeting SAP NetWeaver servers. The flaw was discovered while investigating another unauthenticated file upload vulnerability (CVE-2025-31324) fixed in April. Threat actors were chaining both vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary commands remotely without privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sap-patches-second-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-recent-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
