<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-398: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-398/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49384; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations by creating a symbolic link, which can be used to delete files. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25876</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-399: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-399/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor by exploiting a stack-based buffer overflow. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26026</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-400: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-400/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32412; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data that can result in a read past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26032</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-401: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V10 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-401/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V10; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41413; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists in the parsing of V10 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26028</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-397: Delta Electronics COMMGR Insufficient Randomization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-397/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics COMMGR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3495; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Delta Electronics COMMGR, making it possible for an attacker to exploit the system without requiring a login. The specific flaw exists within the PLC simulator service, which can be exploited through brute force attacks at moderate expense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25049</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sorillus RAT Targets European Organizations Through Tunneling Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sorillus-rat-targets-european-organizations/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malicious infection chain using the Sorillus Remote Access Trojan (RAT) that targets organizations across Europe. The campaign employs invoice-themed phishing emails to deliver the malware, which uses legitimate services like OneDrive and Ngrok to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142610</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Zero-Day CVE-2025-2783 Exploited by TaxOff to Deploy Trinper Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-2783.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2783; Summary: A sandbox escape vulnerability (CVE-2025-2783) in Google Chrome was exploited by threat actor TaxOff to deploy a backdoor codenamed Trinper. The vulnerability had a CVSS score of 8.3 and was used as part of a phishing campaign targeting Russian organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-2783.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scania confirms insurance claim data breach in extortion attempt</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scania-confirms-insurance-claim-data-breach-in-extortion-attempt/</link>
      <description>Scania, a major Swedish manufacturer of heavy trucks and buses, suffered a cybersecurity incident where threat actors used compromised credentials to breach its Financial Services systems and steal insurance claim documents. The attackers emailed several Scania employees, threatening to leak the data online unless their demands were met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scania-confirms-insurance-claim-data-breach-in-extortion-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New KimJongRAT Stealer Uses Weaponized LNK File to Deploy PowerShell-Based Dropper</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-kimjongrat-stealer-uses-weaponized-lnk-file/</link>
      <description>The article discusses new variants of the KimJongRAT stealer malware that emerged in 2019. These variants use a weaponized Windows shortcut (LNK) file as an initial infection vector to deploy multi-stage droppers, aiming to steal sensitive user data, including cryptocurrency wallet extensions and system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142599</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Chaos RAT Variants Targeting Windows and Linux Systems to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-chaos-rat-variants-targeting-windows-and-linux-systems/</link>
      <description>Chaos RAT is a remote administration tool (RAT) that targets both Windows and Linux systems. It spreads through phishing campaigns, utilizing malicious PDF attachments embedded in emails to lure unsuspecting users into initiating the infection process. The malware grants attackers extensive control over infected systems, enabling capabilities such as keylogging, screen capture, file exfiltration, and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142564</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sophisticated Multi-Stage Malware Campaign Uses VBS Files to Execute PowerShell Script</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sophisticated-multi-stage-malware-campaign-uses-vbs-files/</link>
      <description>A multi-stage malware campaign has been discovered, utilizing heavily obfuscated Visual Basic Script (VBS) files to deploy remote access trojans (RATs). The campaign involves a three-stage process of obfuscation, dynamic script generation, and remote payload downloads, highlighting the evolving tactics of modern cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142587</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LangSmith Bug Could Expose OpenAI Keys and User Data via Malicious Agents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/langchain-langsmith-bug-let-hackers.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LangChain's LangSmith platform; CVE(s): None; Summary: The LangSmith platform contains a vulnerability that allows attackers to capture sensitive data, including API keys and user prompts. The vulnerability can be exploited by creating an artificial intelligence (AI) agent with a malicious proxy server, which can then intercept all user communications without the victim's knowledge.

FYSA: Threat actors have released two new variants of WormGPT, powered by xAI Grok and Mistral AI Mixtral, designed to facilitate malicious activities such as creating tailored phishing emails and writing snippets of malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/langchain-langsmith-bug-let-hackers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Weaponized Research Papers Delivering Malware Through Password-Protected Documents</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-weaponized-research-papers-delivering-malware/</link>
      <description>Kimsuky hacking organization is linked to a phishing email campaign targeting individuals with a password-protected HWP document embedded with a malicious OLE object. The attack chain includes the deployment of additional components, including executables and PowerShell scripts, designed to evade detection and establish persistent access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky and Konni APT Groups Lead Active Attacks Targeting East Asia</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-and-konni-apt-groups-lead-active-attacks/</link>
      <description>APT groups Kimsuky, Konni, Sidewinder, and Lazarus have been identified as the most active players in various regions, including East Asia, South Asia, Middle East, and Eastern Europe. These groups are using sophisticated intrusion techniques, spear phishing, and exploiting vulnerabilities to target government agencies, financial institutions, research bodies, and diplomats. The report highlights the need for enhanced threat intelligence and robust security frameworks to counter these persistent and evolving threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142549</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram 'BMO' ads use AI deepfakes to scam banking customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-bmo-ads-use-ai-deepfakes-to-scam-banking-customers/</link>
      <description>Instagram ads impersonating financial institutions like Bank of Montreal (BMO) and EQ Bank (Equitable Bank) are being used to target Canadian consumers with phishing scams and investment fraud. The ads use AI-powered deepfake videos or official branding to drive traffic outside the platform to lookalike illicit domains that are not affiliated with banks, attempting to collect personal information or banking credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-bmo-ads-use-ai-deepfakes-to-scam-banking-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDSpy Threat Actors Exploit Windows LNK Zero-Day Vulnerability to Target Windows System Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xdspy-threat-actors-exploit-windows-lnk-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25373; Summary: The Windows LNKzero-day vulnerability (ZDI-CAN-25373) is exploited by the XDSpy threat actor to target governmental entities in Eastern Europe and Russia. The vulnerability manipulates the Windows Explorer UI to conceal malicious commands through excessive whitespace padding, allowing hidden command execution that evades user interface visibility and third-party parsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Veeam RCE flaw lets domain users hack backup servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-veeam-rce-flaw-lets-domain-users-hack-backup-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121; Summary: Veeam Backup &amp; Replication 12 or later contains a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that can be exploited by authenticated domain users in low-complexity attacks to gain code execution remotely on the Backup Server. The flaw only impacts domain-joined installations and was fixed in version 12.3.2.3617, which was released earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-veeam-rce-flaw-lets-domain-users-hack-backup-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitecore CMS exploit chain starts with hardcoded 'b' password</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sitecore-cms-exploit-chain-starts-with-hardcoded-b-password/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform (XP); CVE(s): None; Summary: A chain of three pre-auth remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities allows attackers to breach and hijack servers without authentication. The vulnerabilities hinge on an internal user with a hardcoded password, a Zip Slip flaw in the Upload Wizard, and a vulnerability in the Sitecore PowerShell Extensions (SPE) module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sitecore-cms-exploit-chain-starts-with-hardcoded-b-password/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 15:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK fines 23andMe for ‘profoundly damaging’ breach exposing genetics data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-fines-23andme-for-profoundly-damaging-breach-exposing-genetics-data/</link>
      <description>The UK's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) fined genetic testing provider 23andMe £2.31 million ($3.12 million) for serious security failings that led to a data breach in 2023, exposing sensitive personal information of thousands of people in the UK and Germany.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-fines-23andme-for-profoundly-damaging-breach-exposing-genetics-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Surface Hub boot issues with emergency update</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-surface-hub-boot-issues-with-emergency-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Surface Hub v1; CVE(s): None; Summary: The June 2025 Windows security update (KB5060533) causes startup failures for some Surface Hub v1 devices running Windows 10, version 22H2, resulting in Secure Boot Violation errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-surface-hub-boot-issues-with-emergency-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to automate IT ticket handling with AI and Tines</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-automate-it-ticket-handling-with-ai-and-tines/</link>
      <description>This article is about a workflow orchestration and AI platform called Tines, specifically highlighting a pre-built ticket-handling workflow developed by Connor Brewer. The workflow aims to streamline IT issue handling by automating routine tasks, reducing manual triage, and enabling analysts to focus on more complex challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-automate-it-ticket-handling-with-ai-and-tines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker steals 1 million Cock.li user records in webmail data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-1-million-cockli-user-records-in-webmail-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cock.li Roundcube webmail platform; CVE(s): CVE-2021-44026; Summary: The Cock.li email hosting provider suffered a data breach after threat actors exploited an old SQL injection vulnerability in its now-retired Roundcube webmail platform, exposing over 1 million user records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-1-million-cockli-user-records-in-webmail-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Fox APT Targets Taiwan with Complex Gh0stCringe and HoldingHands RAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/silver-fox-apt-targets-taiwan-with.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers are warning of a new phishing campaign targeting users in Taiwan with malware families such as HoldingHands RAT and Gh0stCringe. The campaign delivers malware via phishing emails impersonating Taiwan's National Taxation Bureau, using lures related to taxes, invoices, and pensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/silver-fox-apt-targets-taiwan-with.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondTrust Tools RCE Vulnerability Allows Attackers Execute Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beyondtrust-tools-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BeyondTrust; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5309; Summary: The Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA) products from BeyondTrust contain a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected servers via the chat feature. This high-severity issue, tracked as CVE-2025-5309, could have far-reaching consequences for organizations relying on these access management solutions and requires prompt patching or configuration changes to mitigate exploitation risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142578</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerabilities in Sitecore Could Lead to Widespread Enterprise Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerabilities-in-sitecore/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform (XP); CVE(s): CVE-2025-27218, WT-2025-0024, WT-2025-0032, WT-2025-0025; Summary: A series of critical vulnerabilities in Sitecore XP allow for remote code execution and unauthorized access. The most severe vulnerability is a pre-authentication RCE flaw due to unsafe deserialization, while other flaws include hardcoded credentials, path traversal, and unrestricted file uploads. Unpatched systems are exposed to attacks that could lead to data theft, lateral movement, and operational disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142575</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Warns of Scattered Spider Attacks Targeting IT Support Teams at U.S. Insurance Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-warns-of-scattered-spider.html</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a cybercrime group known for using advanced social engineering tactics, has shifted its focus from retailers to insurance companies. The group is believed to have forged an alliance with the DragonForce ransomware cartel and targets organizations with large help desks and outsourced IT functions. To mitigate these attacks, enhanced authentication, rigorous identity controls, access restrictions, and employee verification are recommended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-warns-of-scattered-spider.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Manipulate Search Engines to Push Malicious Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-manipulate-search-engines/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated SEO poisoning operation has been exposed, where hackers manipulate search engine algorithms to push malicious websites to the top of search results. The platform Hacklink allows cybercriminals to buy access to thousands of compromised websites and inject code designed to deceive both users and search engines. This campaign targets high-traffic search terms related to online gambling and pharmaceuticals, artificially boosting the credibility and search ranking of malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142554</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/17/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux Kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A vulnerability in the Linux Kernel, identified as CVE-2023-0386, has been added to CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. This type of vulnerability is a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors and poses significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23527</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Mendix Studio Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Mendix Studio Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40592; Summary: A path traversal vulnerability in the module installation process of Studio Pro allows an attacker to write or modify arbitrary files in directories outside a developer's project directory, which could be exploited by crafting a malicious module and distributing it via the Mendix Marketplace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23520</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuji Electric Smart Editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32412, CVE-2025-41413, CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor is vulnerable to out-of-bounds read, out-of-bounds write, and stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23523</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Five Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/17/cisa-releases-five-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released five Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 17, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories cover specific products from Siemens, LS Electric, Fuji Electric, and Dover Fueling Solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23525</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dover Fueling Solutions ProGauge MagLink LX Consoles</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dover Fueling Solutions ProGauge MagLink LX consoles; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5310; Summary: The ProGauge MagLink LX consoles have a missing authentication vulnerability, allowing an attacker to create, delete, or modify files and potentially execute code remotely. Successful exploitation could result in control of the monitoring device, manipulation of fueling operations, deletion of system configurations, or deployment of malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23524</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LS Electric GMWin 4</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LS Electric GMWin 4; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49848, CVE-2025-49849, CVE-2025-49850; Summary: Successful exploitation of the Out-of-Bounds Write, Out-of-Bounds Read, and Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities in LS Electric GMWin 4 could allow an attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23521</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Forgotten AD Service Accounts Leaving You at Risk?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/are-forgotten-ad-service-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Forgotten Active Directory (AD) service accounts are often overlooked, allowing them to quietly persist with non-expiring or stale passwords. Attackers seek out these forgotten service accounts as they can serve as silent gateways for attack paths and lateral movement across enterprise environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/are-forgotten-ad-service-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp’s Status Tab Set to Feature Ads as Meta Monetizes Platform</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/whatsapps-status-tab-set-to-feature-ads/</link>
      <description>WhatsApp, with over 2 billion monthly active users, is introducing advertisements within its Updates tab, marking a significant shift in monetization. The ads will appear in the Status section, allowing businesses to promote products through ephemeral stories that disappear after 24 hours. Personal messaging remains untouched, and Meta emphasizes that privacy is built into these new features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142541</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Fake Verification Prompt and Clickfix Technique to Deploy Fileless AsyncRAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-fake-verification-prompt-and-clickfix-technique/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are distributing a fileless variant of AsyncRAT remote access Trojan using deceptive tactics such as fake verification prompts. The malware uses obfuscated PowerShell scripts, in-memory execution, and registry persistence to evade detection and maintain covert access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142513</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS Armoury Crate Vulnerability Lets Hackers Gain System-Level Access on Windows</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-armoury-crate-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS Armoury Crate; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3464; Summary: A critical vulnerability in ASUS's Armoury Crate software allows attackers to bypass security controls and gain SYSTEM-level privileges, exposing millions of Windows users to system-level compromise. The flaw can be exploited by creating a hard link from a benign application to a trusted executable, tricking the driver into granting privileged access to malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142520</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Coded 'b' Password in Sitecore XP Sparks Major RCE Risk in Enterprise Deployments</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hard-coded-b-password-in-sitecore-xp.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discloses three security flaws in Sitecore Experience Platform that could be chained to achieve pre-authenticated remote code execution. The vulnerabilities include hard-coded credentials, post-authenticated remote code execution via path traversal, and post-authenticated remote code execution via Sitecore PowerShell Extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hard-coded-b-password-in-sitecore-xp.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backups Are Under Attack: How to Protect Your Backups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-protect-your-backups-from-ransomware-attacks.html</link>
      <description>Ransomware attacks are increasingly targeting backup infrastructure, attempting to cripple recovery capabilities. Threat actors disable backup agents, delete snapshots, modify retention policies, encrypt backup volumes, and exploit vulnerabilities in integrated backup platforms. To defend against this, IT pros should implement a resilient backup strategy that includes isolation, offsite or immutable copies, and regular verification and monitoring of backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-protect-your-backups-from-ransomware-attacks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water Curse Hacker Group Uses 76 GitHub Accounts to Spread Multistage Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/water-curse-hacker-group-uses-76-github-accounts/</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as Water Curse has been linked to a campaign utilizing at least 76 GitHub accounts to distribute malware, targeting a diverse range of victims including cybersecurity professionals. The group's sophisticated attack methodology poses a significant supply chain risk, embedding malicious payloads within seemingly legitimate tools and scripts hosted on GitHub.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142500</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical sslh Vulnerabilities Allow Remote Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sslh-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: sslh; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46807, CVE-2025-46806; Summary: The sslh protocol multiplexer has two critical vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-46807 and CVE-2025-46806, which could allow remote attackers to crash the service or render it unavailable, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) for legitimate users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142511</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-381: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic CreateTrace SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-381/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27495; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the CreateTrace method, which fails to properly validate a user-supplied string before constructing SQL queries, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25911</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-382: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateProject SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-382/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32475; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which can be bypassed to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25912</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-383: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic VerifyUser SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-383/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27539; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the flaw exists within the implementation of the VerifyUser method due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25914</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-384: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic Authenticate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-384/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27540; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the Authenticate method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25913</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-385: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic RestoreFromBackup SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-385/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29905; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by injecting SQL commands through the RestoreFromBackup method. The flaw is due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25923</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-386: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateConnectionVariables SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-386/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30002; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, bypassing authentication and disclosing stored credentials. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25909</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-387: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateProjectConnections SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-387/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30003; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used in SQL queries, enabling attackers to disclose stored credentials and potentially leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25910</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-388: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic ImportDatabase SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-388/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30030; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries, which can be used to disclose stored credentials leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25924</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-389: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateUsers SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-389/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30031; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by exploiting a SQL injection information disclosure vulnerability in the UpdateUsers method, which can be bypassed. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25922</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-390: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateDatabaseSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-390/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30032; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, which can be used to compromise further. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25921</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-391: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateTcmSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-391/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31343; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Although authentication is required, the existing mechanism can be bypassed. The flaw exists in the UpdateTcmSettings method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries, allowing disclosure of stored credentials leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25920</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-392: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateSmtpSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-392/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31349; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic through SQL injection, bypassing authentication. The issue is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which could lead to stored credentials being disclosed and further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25919</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-393: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateBufferingSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-393/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31350; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, by exploiting a SQL injection flaw in the UpdateBufferingSettings method. Authentication is required but can be bypassed, making it possible for an attacker to leverage this issue and disclose sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25918</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-394: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic CreateProject SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-394/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31351; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by bypassing the existing authentication mechanism and leveraging a SQL injection flaw in the CreateProject method, which lacks proper validation of user-supplied strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25917</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-395: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateGateways SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-395/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31352; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, by exploiting a SQL injection issue in the UpdateGateways method due to improper validation of user-supplied strings. Authentication is required but can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25915</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-396: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateOpcSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-396/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31353; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the UpdateOpcSettings method due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25916</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a New KimJongRAT Stealer Variant and Its PowerShell Implementation</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/kimjongrat-stealer-variant-powershell/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an in-depth analysis of a malware campaign, specifically focusing on a PowerShell-based stealer and its various components. The article describes the different stages of the malware's operation, including data extraction from browsers and file systems, as well as interactions with a command-and-control (C2) server.

Key findings include:

1. The malware is designed to extract sensitive information such as browser data, cryptocurrency wallet extensions, and system files.
2. The malware uses various techniques to evade detection, including anti-VM checks and obfuscation of its code.
3. The malware communicates with a C2 server to upload stolen data, download additional payloads, and execute commands.
4. The malware has persistence mechanisms in place, including registry entries and file creation.

The article provides detailed information on the malware's components, including VBScript code, PowerShell scripts, and Base64-encoded payloads. It also discusses the different stages of the malware's operation and its interactions with the C2 server.

Overall, this analysis provides valuable insights into the capabilities and behavior of this particular malware campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143320</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Flodrix Botnet Variant Exploits Langflow AI Server RCE Bug to Launch DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-flodrix-botnet-variant-exploits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: Langflow's missing authentication vulnerability (CVE-2025-3248) allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted HTTP requests, potentially leading to remote code execution. Attackers are exploiting this flaw to deliver the Flodrixbotnet malware and conduct reconnaissance, installing a shell script downloader and eventually launching DDoS attacks over TCP or TOR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-flodrix-botnet-variant-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150K+ Users Affected by Malicious Loan Apps on iOS and Google Play</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/150k-users-affected-by-malicious-loan-apps/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RapiPlata app; CVE(s): None; Summary: The RapiPlata app, posing as a financial service, targeted Colombian users by gaining access to sensitive data such as SMS messages, call logs, calendar events, and installed applications. It exploited permissions under the guise of credit assessment to conduct keyword-based SMS scanning, behavioral data harvesting, and unauthorized exfiltration of personal information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142481</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 09:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploiting Chrome Zero‑Day Vulnerability in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploiting-chrome-zero%e2%80%91day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2783; Summary: The vulnerability arises from an incorrect handle being provided in unspecified circumstances, allowing remote attackers to escape Chrome's sandbox via a malicious file or website. This enables attackers to bypass one of Chrome's core security mechanisms, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution on the victim's machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 08:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TP-Link Router Flaw CVE-2023-33538 Under Active Exploit, CISA Issues Immediate Alert</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/tp-link-router-flaw-cve-2023-33538.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TP-Link; CVE(s): CVE-2023-33538; Summary: The vulnerability is a command injection bug (CVSS score: 8.8) in TP-Link wireless routers that could result in the execution of arbitrary system commands when processing the ssid1 parameter in a specially crafted HTTP GET request, with evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/tp-link-router-flaw-cve-2023-33538.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Devices Under Siege: How Threat Actors Abuse OEM Permissions for Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-threat-actors-abuse-oem-permissions-for-privilege-escalation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting legitimate channels, such as sideloading and OEM permissions, to achieve privilege escalation and gain control over devices. This can occur through malicious apps requesting excessive system access or inheriting elevated privileges. The vulnerability lies in the exploitation of trusted pathways, allowing attackers to bypass Android's standard security model and compromise user privacy settings.

(Note: Since this article is about a cybersecurity-relevant issue rather than a specific vulnerability with CVEs, I responded in the "FYSA" format.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142461</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts: iOS Zero‑Click Flaw Actively Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-ios-zero%e2%80%91click-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The zero-click vulnerability in Apple's ecosystem allowed attackers to compromise iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, and visionOS devices without user interaction. The flaw was triggered by processing maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via iCloud Links, enabling remote code execution and full device compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142469</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCHQ Intern Sentenced to 7 Years for Illegally Copying Secret Files to Smartphone</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gchq-intern-sentenced-to-7-years/</link>
      <description>A former GCHQ intern, Hasaan Arshad, has been sentenced to 7 and a half years in prison for smuggling top secret data out of a secure facility using his mobile phone. The breach was described as a "flagrant violation" of national security protocols, posing a significant risk to the UK's national security efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142445</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeerStealer Malware Deployed Through Exploitation of Windows Run Prompt by Threat Actors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/deerstealer-malware-deployed-through-exploitation/</link>
      <description>DeerStealer malware is being deployed using HijackLoader malware loader, designed to harvest sensitive data including cryptocurrency wallets, browser credentials, VPN details, and instant messenger information. The initial access method, ClickFix, manipulates victims into executing a malicious PowerShell command, setting off a complex attack chain that ultimately delivers DeerStealer as the final payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142438</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Tomcat Flaws Allow Auth Bypass and DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-tomcat-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Software Foundation Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48976, CVE-2025-48988, CVE-2025-49124, CVE-2025-49125; Summary: Four newly discovered vulnerabilities in Apache Tomcat allow for denial-of-service attacks, privilege escalation, installer abuse, and authentication bypass. The flaws affect versions 9.0, 10.1, and 11.0, and administrators are strongly advised to upgrade to patch the issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142439</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Weaponize Langflow Vulnerability to Launch Flodrix Botnet</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-weaponize-langflow-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: A remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-3248) in Langflow, a Python-based AI prototyping framework, is being actively exploited by cybercriminals to deploy the Flodrix botnet. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to craft malicious POST requests embedding harmful code within function decorators or default arguments, granting remote code execution capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142433</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zyxel Devices Under Attack as Hackers Exploit UDP Port RCE Flaw</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zyxel-devices-under-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zyxel; CVE(s): CVE-2023-28771; Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVSS 9.8) affects several Zyxel product lines, including ATP, USG FLEX, VPN series, and ZyWALL/USG, across firmware versions ZLD V4.60 to V5.35 (or V4.73 for ZyWALL/USG). Exploitation involves sending a single, specially crafted IKE packet to UDP port 500, triggering unauthenticated remote code execution, which can potentially seize full control of unpatched devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142426</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Starts Showing Ads on WhatsApp After 6-Year Delay From 2018 Announcement</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-starts-showing-ads-on-whatsapp.html</link>
      <description>WhatsApp is introducing ads in its Status feature, with the company emphasizing that it's built with privacy in mind and only uses limited information to serve ads. The ads will be displayed on the Updates tab and will not access users' personal messages, calls, or groups for targeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-starts-showing-ads-on-whatsapp.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Eyes: Generative AI in China’s Military Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/artificial-eyes-generative-ai-chinas-military-intelligence</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Peoples Liberation Army's (PLA) interest in using generative artificial intelligence (AI) to support military intelligence tasks. The PLA has likely procured generative AI technology and is exploring its applications for intelligence work, including generating open-source intelligence products, processing satellite imagery, and supporting event extraction. The article also highlights potential challenges and risks associated with the PLA's use of generative AI, such as reducing objectivity in intelligence analysis and creating opportunities for counterintelligence organizations to generate convincing but inaccurate information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/artificial-eyes-generative-ai-chinas-military-intelligence</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers switch to targeting U.S. insurance companies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-warns-scattered-spider-hackers-now-target-us-insurance-companies/</link>
      <description>Threat intelligence researchers are warning of hackers breaching multiple U.S. companies in the insurance industry using tactics observed with Scattered Spider activity, a group known for sophisticated social engineering attacks and use of ransomware. The threat actors have a sector-by-sector focus, and the insurance industry should be on high alert.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-warns-scattered-spider-hackers-now-target-us-insurance-companies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals cut fiber-optic lines, causing outage for Spectrum Internet subscribers</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/vandals-cut-fiber-optic-lines-causing-outage-for-spectrum-internet-subscribers/</link>
      <description>There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in this article. Instead, it discusses copper theft and its impact on industries that rely on copper infrastructure, including telephone and internet connectivity. The article highlights the severity of the issue, with examples such as AT&amp;T's experience with fiber line disruptions due to copper theft, and the company's decision to replace copper-based networks with fiber ones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/vandals-cut-fiber-optic-lines-causing-outage-for-spectrum-internet-subscribers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katz Stealer Boosts Credential Theft with System Fingerprinting and Persistence Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/katz-stealer-boosts-credential-theft-with-system/</link>
      <description>Katz Stealer is a sophisticated information-stealing malware-as-a-service (MaaS) that steals sensitive information such as browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallet data, and session tokens from platforms like Discord and Telegram. It uses advanced techniques to evade detection, including in-memory operation, modular payloads, and process hollowing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142381</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS Armoury Crate bug lets attackers get Windows admin privileges</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asus-armoury-crate-bug-lets-attackers-get-windows-admin-privileges/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS Armoury Crate; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3464; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability (CVE-2025-3464) in ASUS Armoury Crate software allows threat actors to escalate their privileges to SYSTEM level on Windows machines, bypassing authorization and granting access to physical memory, I/O ports, and model-specific registers. Exploitation involves creating a hard link from a benign test app to a fake executable, allowing the attacker to gain low-level system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asus-armoury-crate-bug-lets-attackers-get-windows-admin-privileges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Seizes $7.74M in Crypto Tied to North Korea’s Global Fake IT Worker Network</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-seizes-774m-in-crypto-tied-to-north.html</link>
      <description>North Korean IT workers used fake identities and AI tools like OpenAI ChatGPT to bypass due diligence checks and secure freelance jobs at U.S. cryptocurrency companies. They laundered ill-gotten gains through Sim, a North Korean Foreign Trade Bank representative, to further Pyongyang's strategic objectives in violation of sanctions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-seizes-774m-in-crypto-tied-to-north.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post's email system hacked, journalists' accounts compromised</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/washington-posts-email-system-hacked-journalists-accounts-compromised/</link>
      <description>The email accounts of several Washington Post journalists were compromised in a suspected foreign government- sponsored attack, targeting journalists writing about national security and economic policy topics, as well as some who write about China. Advanced persistent threats (APTs) are believed to be behind the attack, which is reminiscent of previous attacks on Microsoft Exchange systems by Chinese hackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/washington-posts-email-system-hacked-journalists-accounts-compromised/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 15:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anubis Ransomware Encrypts and Wipes Files, Making Recovery Impossible Even After Payment</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/anubis-ransomware-encrypts-and-wipes.html</link>
      <description>An emerging ransomware strain named Anubis has been discovered that can encrypt files and permanently erase them, allowing recovery attempts to be impossible. The ransomware features a "wipe mode" that erases files, making recovery even if the ransom is paid impossible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/anubis-ransomware-encrypts-and-wipes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux 2025.2 released with 13 new tools, car hacking updates</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-20252-released-with-13-new-tools-car-hacking-updates/</link>
      <description>Kali Linux 2025.2 has been released, featuring new tools and updates to the car hacking toolkit, including a renamed CAN Arsenal (now CARsenal) and additional hacking tools such as hlcand, VIN Info, CaringCaribou, ICSim, and more. The Kali Menu has also been reorganized to align with the MITRE ATT&amp;CK framework.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kali-linux-20252-released-with-13-new-tools-car-hacking-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoomcar discloses security breach impacting 8.4 million users</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zoomcar-discloses-security-breach-impacting-84-million-users/</link>
      <description>Unauthorized access to Zoomcar's system led to a data breach impacting 8.4 million users, exposing sensitive data including full name, phone number, car registration number, home address, and email address. The company is still evaluating the exact scope and potential impact of the security incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zoomcar-discloses-security-breach-impacting-84-million-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target and Hijack Washington Post Journalists’ Email Accounts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-washington-post-journalists-email-accounts/</link>
      <description>A targeted cyberattack has struck The Washington Post, compromising email accounts of several journalists. The attack appears to have been focused on reporters from national security and economic policy teams, including those covering sensitive topics related to China. Experts warn that this breach poses a significant risk to the integrity of independent journalism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142389</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 13:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archetyp Market Takedown: Operation Deep Sentinel Ends a Major Dark Web Platform</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/archetyp-market-takedown-operation-deep-sentinel/</link>
      <description>International law enforcement agencies took down Archetyp Market, one of the most active darknet marketplaces dedicated to drug trafficking. The operation, led by German authorities and supported by Europol and Eurojust, targeted the platform's infrastructure, administrators, and top vendors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061021</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoomcar Data Breach Exposes Sensitive Details of 8.4 Million Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zoomcar-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVEs: None; Summary: A data breach at Zoomcar Holdings, Inc. has compromised the personal information of approximately 8.4 million users, including user names, phone numbers, car registration numbers, personal addresses, and email addresses. The breach poses risks of identity theft, targeted phishing, and other malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142363</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Deep Sentinel: Authorities Shut Down Darknet Market Archetyp</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/operation-deep-sentinel/</link>
      <description>Authorities successfully dismantled Archetyp Market, a major darknet marketplace, as part of "Operation Deep Sentinel." The takedown marks a significant victory in the fight against cybercrime and the illicit drug trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142359</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERT Ransomware Escalates Attacks on Linux Machines with Weaponized ELF Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bert-ransomware-escalates-attacks-on-linux-machines/</link>
      <description>The BERT ransomware group has expanded its reach from targeting Windows environments to launching attacks on Linux machines, posing a significant risk to global enterprises reliant on Linux for critical infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142327</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Airline WestJet Suffers Cyberattack, Halts App and Web Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/canadian-airline-westjet-suffers-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>WestJet Airlines experiences a significant cybersecurity incident, causing disruptions to its mobile app and internal systems. The airline is working with law enforcement agencies and Transport Canada to investigate the breach, while emphasizing that flight operations remain safe and stable. The incident highlights the growing threat posed by cybercriminals to critical infrastructure and major organizations across Canada.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142287</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shares temp fix for Outlook crashes when opening emails</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-workaround-for-classic-outlook-crashes/</link>
      <description>The article describes a known issue with classic Outlook email client causing it to crash when opening or starting a new message, affecting users in the Monthly Enterprise Channel who updated Outlook for Microsoft 365. A temporary fix is provided until a permanent solution is rolled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-workaround-for-classic-outlook-crashes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy XWorm Malware via Fake Travel Websites to Infect Users’ PCs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-xworm-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign targets vacation planners by imitating Booking.com using phony travel websites. The campaign uses social engineering tactics, including a counterfeit cookie banner, to deploy XWorm, a remote access trojan (RAT).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142303</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/16/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple, Multiple Products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200, CVE-2023-33538; Summary: Two vulnerabilities have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The first is an unspecified vulnerability in Apple products, and the second is a command injection vulnerability affecting TP-Link routers. These vulnerabilities pose significant risks to federal agencies and other organizations if not remediated in a timely manner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean APT Hackers Target Ukrainian Government Agencies to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-apt-hackers-target-ukrainian-government-agencies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The Konni group, a North Korean Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) hacker group, has been observed in a targeted phishing campaign against Ukrainian government agencies, aiming to steal login credentials and distribute malware. The attackers used deceptive tactics, including using Proton Mail accounts and sophisticated Command and Control (C2) communication via PowerShell.

FYSA: This article highlights the shifting focus of North Korean APT groups, such as the Konni group, towards targeting specific government entities and industries, potentially in alignment with strategic alliances. The use of social engineering tactics, including phishing emails and AI-manipulated resumes, underscores the growing sophistication of these threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142296</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: iPhone Spyware, Microsoft 0-Day, TokenBreak Hack, AI Data Leaks and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-iphone-spyware-microsoft-0.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses various cybersecurity-related topics and threats, including malware, phishing attacks, and data breaches. It also highlights the importance of staying private on the internet by learning about real-world methods used by trackers.

Vulnerable Products:

* BrowserVenom: A Windows implant that reconfigures Chromium- and Gecko-based browsing instances to force traffic through a proxy controlled by the threat actors.
* AppleSeed: A known malware delivered as part of a multi-stage infection sequence.
* Kimsuky's Triple Combo: A campaign targeting Facebook, email, and Telegram users in South Korea.

Note: These vulnerabilities are not traditional software or hardware flaws but rather malware or social engineering tactics used to compromise user data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-iphone-spyware-microsoft-0.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playbook: Transforming Your Cybersecurity Practice Into An MRR Machine</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/playbook-transforming-your.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of transitioning from reactive cybersecurity services to ongoing strategic management aligned with business goals. It highlights the benefits for service providers and clients, including increased revenue, stronger resilience, and more predictable outcomes. The article also provides guidance on how service providers can scale their businesses by standardizing workflows, automating processes, and offering tiered services that align with client needs and maturity levels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/playbook-transforming-your.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police seizes Archetyp Market drug marketplace, arrests admin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-seizes-archetyp-market-drug-marketplace-arrests-admin/</link>
      <description>Law enforcement authorities from six countries took down the Archetyp Market, a darknet drug marketplace that operated since May 2020. The market had over 612,000 users and a total transaction volume of over €250 million in Monero cryptocurrency transactions. As part of the joint action codenamed 'Operation Deep Sentinel', investigators seized assets worth €7.8 million from all suspects and arrested several individuals involved with the marketplace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-seizes-archetyp-market-drug-marketplace-arrests-admin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Compromise Discord Invite to Inject Malicious Links Delivering AsyncRAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-compromise-discord-invite-to-inject-malicious-links/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Discord; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors have exploited Discord's invite system to distribute malicious links, ultimately delivering AsyncRAT and other harmful payloads. The attack begins with the manipulation of Discord invite links, using fake domains and social engineering tactics to compromise user accounts and steal sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142253</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrayAlpha Hackers Group Exploits Browser Updates to Deploy PowerNet Loader and NetSupport RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/grayalpha-hacker-group-exploits-browser-updates/</link>
      <description>The article discusses GrayAlpha, a financially motivated threat actor group that overlaps with the FIN7 group. They use custom malware, including PowerNet and MaskBat loaders to decompress and execute NetSupport RAT. The group employs various infection vectors, including fake browser update pages, fraudulent 7-Zip download sites, and an undocumented TAG-124 traffic distribution system (TDS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142240</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 20 Malicious Google Play Apps Steal Users’ Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-google-play-apps-steal-users-login-credentials/</link>
      <description>Malicious Android apps impersonating cryptocurrency wallets were found on the Google Play Store, designed to steal login credentials. The apps prompt users to enter sensitive information, which is then transmitted to attackers, allowing them to drain victims' wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142263</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Purview DLP Now Controls Copilot’s Access to Sensitive Email Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-purview-dlp-now-controls-copilots-access/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is enhancing data security in Microsoft 365 by extending Purview Data Loss Prevention (DLP) controls to Copilot's handling of sensitive email data. Starting January 1, 2025, DLP policies will detect sensitivity labels in emails and restrict Copilot from processing them, ensuring that sensitive information remains protected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142268</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anubis Ransomware Introduces Irreversible File Destruction Feature</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/anubis-ransomware-introduces-irreversible-file/</link>
      <description>Anubis is a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation that combines traditional file encryption with a destructive "wipe mode" feature, permanently erasing file contents. It targets industries like healthcare and construction across regions using sophisticated attack chains, including spear-phishing and command-line execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142215</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Alleged Leaks Hit Vodafone Egypt, SAP Israel, OKX, and T-Mobile US</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/leak-vodafone-egypt-sap-israel-okx-and-t-mobile-us/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are allegedly selling or leaking user data from high-profile companies across telecom, technology, and finance sectors, including Vodafone Egypt, SAP Israel, OKX, and T-Mobile US. The stolen data includes various types of personal information such as names, phone numbers, dates of birth, email addresses, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060986</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: June Windows Server security updates cause DHCP issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-windows-server-security-updates-cause-dhcp-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server; CVE(s): None; Summary: The DHCP service on some Windows Server systems (2016, 2019, 2022, and 2025) freezes after installing the June 2025 security updates, preventing unicast IP address renewals. This issue affects IP renewal for clients and may intermittently stop responding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-windows-server-security-updates-cause-dhcp-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering the Technique of Hiding Images in DNS TXT Entries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uncovering-hiding-images-in-dns-txt-entries/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a novel technique of hiding images inside DNS TXT records by converting them into Base64-encoded text strings and splitting them into chunks. While this approach demonstrates the flexibility of DNS infrastructure, it is not without limitations, including size and rate limits, making it impractical for storing large images.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142243</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 07:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Suffers Major Disruption After API Management Error</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-cloud-suffers-major-disruption/</link>
      <description>Google Cloud experienced an outage due to a critical error in its API management system, affecting millions of users and businesses worldwide. The incident was caused by an invalid automated quota update that propagated globally, causing 503 errors across various services. The recovery process was complicated by the scale of the failure, with some regions experiencing prolonged issues due to database overload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142233</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI Package Masquerades as Chimera Module to Steal AWS, CI/CD, and macOS Data</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/malicious-pypi-package-masquerades-as.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: chimera-sandbox-extensions; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious package named chimera-sandbox-extensions was discovered on PyPI, which masquerades as a helper module for Chimera Sandbox. The package can steal sensitive information such as credentials, configuration data, and environment variables from infected machines, and sends the gathered data to an external domain.

FYSA: Malicious packages on npm and PyPI have been identified, capable of executing remote code and downloading additional payloads. These packages, including eslint-config-airbnb-compat, ts-runtime-compat-check, solder, and @mediawave/lib, have been taken down from their respective package registries. Additionally, credential stealers, cryptocurrency drainers, cryptojackers, and clippers are targeting the cryptocurrency and blockchain development ecosystem.

(Note: The article does not contain any other cybersecurity-relevant content besides the vulnerabilities mentioned above.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/malicious-pypi-package-masquerades-as.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Backup Services Flaw Allows Hackers to Gain Elevated Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-backup-services-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM Backup, Recovery, and Media Services for i; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33108; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in IBM's BRMS software allows users with limited privileges to execute arbitrary code with elevated system access, potentially compromising the entire host operating system. The flaw arises from an unqualified library call within the software, allowing malicious actors to redirect calls to their own code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142226</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIA Ecuador Keyless Entry Systems Vulnerability Faces Major Theft Threat</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kia-ecuador-keyless-entry-systems-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: KIA; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6029; Summary: The keyless entry systems (KES) used in Kia vehicles across Ecuador are vulnerable to theft due to outdated "learning code" technology. Attackers can intercept and replay the fixed code transmitted by aftermarket key fobs, granting unauthorized access to the vehicle. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.4, classified as "critical".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142218</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT's AI coder Codex now lets you choose the best solution</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-ai-coder-codex-now-lets-you-choose-the-best-solution/</link>
      <description>The article discusses updates and new features in OpenAI's Codex, an AI agent that assists with coding tasks. Notably, Codex can now generate multiple responses simultaneously for a single task, allowing users to explore different solutions and pick the best approach. Additionally, keyboard shortcuts and a page to explore them have been added, along with other updates such as improved network access restrictions handling and increased setup script duration limits for Pro, Team, and Business users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-ai-coder-codex-now-lets-you-choose-the-best-solution/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 19:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Search gets an upgrade as OpenAI takes aim at Google</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-search-gets-an-upgrade-as-openai-takes-aim-at-google/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenAI's updates to its ChatGPT Search, including improved quality and comprehensive responses. It also mentions the company's efforts to improve the AI model's ability to follow instructions and reduce repetitive responses. Additionally, the article touches on Tines' guide to modern IT automation and some other unrelated news about ChatGPT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-search-gets-an-upgrade-as-openai-takes-aim-at-google/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 15:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 46,000 Grafana instances exposed to account takeover bug</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-46-000-grafana-instances-exposed-to-account-takeover-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grafana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4123; Summary: The open-source platform Grafana has a client-side open redirect vulnerability that allows executing malicious plugins and account takeover. The vulnerability was discovered by Alvaro Balada and patched in security updates released on May 21, but more than a third of all instances reachable over the public internet remain unpatched.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-46-000-grafana-instances-exposed-to-account-takeover-bug/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 14:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WestJet investigates cyberattack disrupting internal systems</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/westjet-investigates-cyberattack-disrupting-internal-systems/</link>
      <description>WestJet is investigating a cybersecurity incident that has disrupted access to some internal systems and the WestJet app, with users unable to log in. The extent of the breach and its cause are unclear, but the company's operation continues to run safely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/westjet-investigates-cyberattack-disrupting-internal-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 17:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anubis ransomware adds wiper to destroy files beyond recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/anubis-ransomware-adds-wiper-to-destroy-files-beyond-recovery/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Anubis Ransomware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Anubis ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation has added a wiper module that destroys targeted files, making recovery impossible even if the ransom is paid. The wiper erases all file contents, reducing their sizes to 0 KB while keeping the filenames and structure intact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/anubis-ransomware-adds-wiper-to-destroy-files-beyond-recovery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 14:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 users want these five features back</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-users-want-these-five-features-back/</link>
      <description>There are no cybersecurity-relevant topics or vulnerabilities discussed in this article. The article is focused on user feedback and feature requests for the Windows 11 operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-users-want-these-five-features-back/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 14:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord Invite Link Hijacking Delivers AsyncRAT and Skuld Stealer Targeting Crypto Wallets</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/discord-invite-link-hijacking-delivers.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Discord; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Discord's invitation system allows attackers to hijack expired or deleted invite links and silently redirect unsuspecting users to malicious servers. The issue enables attackers to reuse custom vanity invite links, allowing them to claim previously expired or deleted permanent invite codes for their own malicious servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/discord-invite-link-hijacking-delivers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 02:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-380: Trend Micro Maximum Security Platinum Host Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-380/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Maximum Security Platinum Host Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49385, ZDI-CAN-25877, ZDI-25-380; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Maximum Security by creating a symbolic link within the Platinum Host Service. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete files and execute arbitrary code as SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25877</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 19:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google links massive cloud outage to API management issue</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-links-massive-cloud-outage-to-api-management-issue/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a service outage that affected Google Cloud and various third-party platforms. The root cause was an API management issue due to invalid data, which caused 503 errors in external API requests. The impact was widespread, with many services disrupted or brought down for over three hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-links-massive-cloud-outage-to-api-management-issue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord flaw lets hackers reuse expired invites in malware campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/discord-flaw-lets-hackers-reuse-expired-invites-in-malware-campaign/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Discord; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers are hijacking expired or deleted Discord invite links to redirect users to malicious sites that deliver remote access trojans and information-stealing malware. The campaign relies on a flaw in the Discord invitation system, allowing attackers to reuse expired temporary invite codes and deleted permanent invite codes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/discord-flaw-lets-hackers-reuse-expired-invites-in-malware-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 16:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux 2025.2 Released: New Tools, Smartwatch and Car Hacking Added</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kali-linux-2025-2/</link>
      <description>Kali Linux has released its second major update of 2025, Kali Linux 2025.2, which includes a restructured menu organized according to the MITRE ATT&amp;CK framework, upgraded desktop environments, and new tools such as smartwatch Wi-Fi injection and car hacking toolset. The update also enhances Active Directory reconnaissance with BloodHound Community Edition and adds 13 new tools to its network repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142196</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arsen Launches AI-Powered Vishing Simulation to Help Organizations Combat Voice Phishing at Scale</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/arsen-launches-ai-powered-vishing-simulation-to-help-organizations-combat-voice-phishing-at-scale/</link>
      <description>Arsen, a cybersecurity startup, has released a new Vishing Simulation module to train employees against voice phishing (vishing) attacks. The AI-powered tool simulates realistic phone-based social engineering attacks, adapting dynamically to employee responses and handling objections or hesitation with lifelike dialogue. The module is designed to help organizations identify risk exposure and train employees to respond confidently and securely in real-time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142186</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 269,000 Websites Infected with JSFireTruck JavaScript Malware in One Month</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-269000-websites-infected-with.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have observed a large-scale campaign compromising legitimate websites with malicious JavaScript injections using the "JSFireTruck" technique, which obfuscates code using only a limited set of characters. The injected code redirects victims to malicious URLs that can deliver malware, exploits, or malvertising if they come from specific search engines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-269000-websites-infected-with.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Fixes Critical RCE Bugs in Apex Central &amp; TMEE PolicyServer</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/trend-micro-fixes-rce-apex-central-tmee-policyserver/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49219, CVE-2025-49220; Summary: Two critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerabilities were found in Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise 2019 and SaaS versions), allowing unauthenticated RCE with a CVSS score of 9.8, posing a severe risk to enterprise environments.

Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption PolicyServer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49212, CVE-2025-49213, CVE-2025-49216, CVE-2025-49214, CVE-2025-49211, CVE-2025-49215, CVE-2025-49218; Summary: Eight vulnerabilities were found in Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption PolicyServer versions prior to 6.0.0.4013, including four critical RCE bugs and an authentication bypass issue, with a CVSS score of 9.8, enabling attackers to gain admin-level control or escalate privileges.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060973</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIST Releases New Guide – 19 Strategies for Building Zero Trust Architectures</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nist-releases-new-guide/</link>
      <description>The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) has released guidance for implementing Zero Trust Architectures (ZTAs), providing 19 real-world implementation models, technical configurations, and best practices developed through a four-year collaboration with 24 industry partners. This guide helps organizations implement ZTAs using commercially available technologies, eliminating implicit trust by continuously verifying every access request through policy engines and dynamic authentication mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142174</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Framework Flaw Enables Remote File Disclosure via “Content‑Disposition” Header</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/spring-framework-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware Spring Framework; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41234; Summary: A medium-severity RFD vulnerability (CVE-2025-41234) in VMware's Spring Framework allows attackers to execute malicious code by exploiting improperly configured Content-Disposition headers and unsanitized user input. The vulnerability arises when applications use non-ASCII characters derived from unsanitized user input, allowing attackers to craft HTTP responses that trick users into downloading files with executable extensions containing malicious commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142161</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: KB5060533 update triggers boot errors on Surface Hub v1 devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-kb5060533-update-triggers-boot-errors-on-surface-hub-v1-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: Surface Hub v1 devices running Windows 10, version 22H2, with the KB5060533 June 2025 Windows security update installed may experience Secure Boot errors and fail to start due to an invalid signature detected. A mitigation was released on July 11, 2025, to prevent additional devices from encountering this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-kb5060533-update-triggers-boot-errors-on-surface-hub-v1-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms auth issues affecting Microsoft 365 users</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-auth-issues-affecting-microsoft-365-users/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is investigating an ongoing incident causing errors with some Microsoft 365 authentication features, including self-service password resets and adding MFA sign-in methods. The issue affects customers in the Asia Pacific, Europe, the Middle East, and Africa, resulting in "we're sorry, we ran into a problem" or "no methods available" errors while setting up MFA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-auth-issues-affecting-microsoft-365-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victoria’s Secret restores critical systems after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/victorias-secret-restores-critical-systems-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Victoria's Secret has restored all critical systems impacted by a May 24 security incident, which forced the company to shut down corporate systems and its e-commerce website. The incident is believed to have no material impact on its yearly fiscal results, despite ongoing expenses related to the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/victorias-secret-restores-critical-systems-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender Spoofing Flaw Enables Privilege Escalation and AD Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-defender-spoofing/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Defender for Identity; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26685; Summary: A spoofing vulnerability in Microsoft Defender for Identity (MDI) allows unauthenticated attackers to capture Net-NTLM hashes of critical Directory Service Accounts, potentially compromising Active Directory environments. The flaw exploits MDI's Lateral Movement Paths feature and has been actively addressed in May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142159</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections of the Israel-Iran Conflict on the Cyber World</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/reflections-of-israel-iran-conflict-cyber-world/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the escalation of tensions between Israel and Iran following a series of airstrikes by Israel against Iranian nuclear enrichment sites, missile facilities, and military leaders' homes. Cyber activity has already begun, with groups like Moses Staff, Team Insane Pakistan, and DieNet posting messages and threatening attacks on Israeli infrastructure. Iranian cyber units are also expected to mobilize, potentially targeting government systems, communication infrastructure, or strategic industries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060957</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Cloud Cam Flaw Allows Attackers to Intercept and Modify Network Traffic</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/amazon-cloud-cam-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Cloud Cam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6031; Summary: The Amazon Cloud Cam devices, which reached end-of-life (EOL) status in December 2022, contain a critical vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass SSL pinning during device pairing, enabling man-in-the-middle attacks and network traffic manipulation. This flaw enables credential harvesting, device spoofing, and network compromise, and no patches will be released for the EOL product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142148</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acer Control Center Flaw Lets Attackers Run Malicious Code as Elevated User</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/acer-control-center-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Acer ControlCenter; CVE(s): 2025-5491; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the ACCSvc.exe service allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM privileges via a misconfigured Windows Named Pipe. The issue stems from insecure permissions on the pipe exposed by the service, which can be exploited to deploy malware and perform lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142147</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Gangs Exploit Unpatched SimpleHelp Flaws to Target Victims with Double Extortion</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ransomware-gangs-exploit-unpatched.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM); CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, CVE-2024-57728, and CVE-2024-57726; Summary: Ransomware actors are targeting unpatched versions of SimpleHelp RMM instances to compromise customers of an unnamed utility billing software provider. The vulnerabilities can lead to information disclosure, privilege escalation, and remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ransomware-gangs-exploit-unpatched.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers Beware – Sophisticated Phishing Scams Exploit GitHub Device Code Flow to Hijack Tokens</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophisticated-phishing-scams-exploit-github-device-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers are exploiting GitHub's OAuth 2.0 Device Code Flow to trick developers into surrendering access to their code repositories and CI/CD pipelines, posing a substantial risk to intellectual property and facilitating large-scale supply chain attacks. The attack involves social engineering, generating device codes, and retrieving OAuth tokens, allowing attackers to exfiltrate private code, manipulate workflows, and initiate supply chain attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142082</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM is the New SOC: Shifting from Monitoring Alerts to Measuring Risk</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ctem-is-new-soc-shifting-from.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of traditional Security Operations Centers (SOCs) in dealing with modern threats and proposes a new approach called Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM). CTEMs shifts the focus from detecting alerts to managing risk by identifying critical assets, potential attack paths, and eliminating vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ctem-is-new-soc-shifting-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashiCorp Nomad ACL Lookup Flaw Allows Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hashicorp-nomad-acl-lookup/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HashiCorp Nomad; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4922; Summary: The Nomad workload orchestration tool contains a critical security flaw that allows attackers to bypass namespace restrictions and escalate privileges via improper ACL policy enforcement. This vulnerability enables privilege escalation, policy shadowing, and data exfiltration attacks with low complexity and high potential impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142113</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatched IT Tool Opens Door – Hackers Breach Billing Software Firm via SimpleHelp RMM</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-breach-billing-software-firm-via-simplehelp-rmm/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) platform; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727; Summary: The SimpleHelp RMM platform contains a path traversal vulnerability that allows attackers to access files or directories outside the intended web root, potentially exposing sensitive data or enabling further network compromises. The vulnerability has been exploited by ransomware actors since January 2025, targeting organizations with unpatched instances of SimpleHelp RMM versions 5.5.7 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142072</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare: Outage not caused by security incident, data is safe</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-outage-not-caused-by-security-incident-data-is-safe/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a service outage experienced by Cloudflare, which lasted almost 2.5 hours and affected multiple edge computing and AI services. The root cause was a failure in the Workers KV underlying storage infrastructure due to an outage from a third-party cloud provider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-outage-not-caused-by-security-incident-data-is-safe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphite Spyware Uses iOS Zero-Click Flaw to Target Journalists</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/graphite-spyware-uses-ios-zero-click-flaw-to-target-journalists/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple iMessage; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The vulnerability allowed for zero-click attacks on iPhones running iOS 18.2.1, exploiting a logic flaw in processing malicious iCloud links containing images/videos. The attack required no user interaction and was patched in iOS 18.3.1 (February 2025).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142112</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless Tokens in the Cloud: Exploitation and Detections</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/serverless-authentication-cloud/</link>
      <description>The article appears to be a technical analysis of serverless computing and its associated security implications. It discusses various cloud platforms, including AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure, and highlights potential vulnerabilities and risks related to the use of serverless identities and tokens.

The article provides detailed information on how attackers can exploit these credentials to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions within cloud environments. It also offers recommendations for securing serverless computing environments, such as implementing posture management and runtime monitoring protections, restricting access to IMDS, and using robust input validation and sanitization techniques.

Overall, the article is informative and provides valuable insights into the security implications of serverless computing, but it does not specifically discuss a vulnerability in any product or service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143156</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fog Ransomware Uses Pentesting Tools to Steal Data and Launch Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fog-ransomware-uses-pentesting-tools/</link>
      <description>Fog ransomware attacks have been linked to the use of open-source penetration testing tools, such as GC2, Adaptix, and Stowaway, and legitimate employee monitoring software like Syteca. The attackers used these tools to conduct reconnaissance, establish persistence, and exfiltrate data before deploying Fog ransomware, marking a new trend in cybercrime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142061</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tycoon 2FA: An Evolving Phishing Kit Powering PhaaS Threats</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/tycoon-2fa-an-evolving-phishing-kit-phaas-threats/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tycoon 2FA; CVE(s): None; Summary: Tycoon 2FA is a Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) kit that enables attackers to bypass Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) by stealing session cookies. It uses a reverse proxy to insert itself between the victim and the legitimate service, allowing attackers to capture sensitive information during a seemingly normal login process. The kit has undergone regular updates since its emergence in 2023, introducing new tactics to evade detection and boost its effectiveness.

FYSA: Tycoon 2FA is an active danger that continuously evolves, adapting to security measures and remaining a formidable tool for cybercriminals. Its ease of use, ability to evade security tools, and adaptability make it a popular choice for attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060930</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSFireTruck Obfuscation Helps Cybercriminals Hijack Trusted Sites with Malicious JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jsfiretruck-obfuscation-helps-cybercriminals-hijack/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated cyber attack campaign has been discovered, where threat actors compromise legitimate websites to inject obfuscated JavaScript code. This enables them to quietly redirect unsuspecting visitors to malicious sites capable of delivering malware or executing exploits. Over 200,000 webpages were compromised in just one month, underscoring the evolving tactics used by attackers to exploit trusted domains for nefarious purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142051</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Unveiled for Windows Disk Cleanup Elevation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poc-exploit-windows-disk-cleanup/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Disk Cleanup Utility (cleanmgr.exe); CVE(s): CVE-2025-21420; Summary: The vulnerability enables attackers to execute malicious code with SYSTEM privileges through DLL sideloading and a directory traversal technique. The flaw stems from cleanmgr.exe's failure to validate DLL loading paths and mitigate symbolic link attacks, allowing attackers to exploit path interception vulnerabilities to load unsigned DLLs and gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142056</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Outage Hits Google Cloud and Linked Cloudflare Services, Thousands Affected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/major-outage-hits-google-cloud-and-linked/</link>
      <description>The article discusses two concurrent outages at Cloudflare and Google due to infrastructure failures, highlighting vulnerabilities in modern cloud dependencies. The outages had widespread impacts on critical services, underscoring the fragility of interconnected internet ecosystems. The incidents exposed risks in vendor lock-in and centralized dependencies, with both companies committing to postmortems and implementing changes to improve resilience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142054</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenBreak Exploit Tricks AI Models Using Minimal Input Changes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tokenbreak-exploit-tricks-ai-models/</link>
      <description>TokenBreak is a novel attack technique that exploits tokenization strategies in AI text classification models to bypass detection. It manipulates input text by inserting characters to create tokenization divergence between the model and its target, allowing attackers to evade detection while preserving meaning for the end target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142053</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebDAV Remote Code Execution 0-Day Actively Exploited — PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/webdav-0-day-poc-released/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WebDAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft's Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) protocol allows remote code execution via manipulated .url shortcut files. The flaw has been actively exploited by the Stealth Falcon APT group since March 2025, enabling attackers to hijack legitimate Windows tools like iediagcmd.exe and execute malicious payloads from attacker-controlled WebDAV servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142052</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Zero-Click Flaw in Messages Exploited to Spy on Journalists Using Paragon Spyware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apple-zero-click-flaw-in-messages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Messages app; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: A logic issue in the Messages app allowed for zero-click exploitation of maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via an iCloud Link, targeting civil society members with sophisticated cyber attacks. The vulnerability was actively exploited and patched on February 10, 2025, as part of various iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, and visionOS updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apple-zero-click-flaw-in-messages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrayAlpha Uses Diverse Infection Vectors to Deploy PowerNet Loader and NetSupport RAT</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/grayalpha-uses-diverse-infection-vectors-deploy-powernet-loader-netsupport-rat</link>
      <description>Insikt Group identified new infrastructure associated with GrayAlpha, a threat actor that overlaps with FIN7. The newly discovered infrastructure includes domains used for payload distribution and additional IP addresses believed to be tied to GrayAlpha. The group uses three primary infection vectors: fake browser update pages, fake 7-Zip download sites, and the TDS TAG-124 network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/grayalpha-uses-diverse-infection-vectors-deploy-powernet-loader-netsupport-rat</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside a Dark Adtech Empire Fed by Fake CAPTCHAs</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/inside-a-dark-adtech-empire-fed-by-fake-captchas/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a dark adtech industry that allows malicious actors to bypass moderation on social media platforms and spread disinformation. The industry relies on domain cloaking services, which hide the true nature of websites from search engines, allowing them to remain online longer than they would otherwise. The industry also uses push monetization services, which pay affiliates to drive signups for various schemes, including online dating services. The article highlights the connections between VexTrio, LosPollos, and other malicious traffic distribution systems (TDSs), which are operated by Russian organized crime groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=69927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming to Apple OSes: A seamless, secure way to import and export passkeys</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/apple-previews-new-import-export-feature-to-make-passkeys-more-interoperable/</link>
      <description>Apple has introduced a new process for securely transferring credentials between apps, which is more secure than traditional methods and eliminates the risk of credential leaks. The system uses a standardized data format built with the FIDO Alliance to move data between apps, providing a modern and secure way to manage credentials. This development aims to improve the usability of passkeys and potentially alleviate issues related to password management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/apple-previews-new-import-export-feature-to-make-passkeys-more-interoperable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Exploiting Expired Discord Invite Links to Deploy Multi-Stage Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-exploiting-expired-discord-invite-links/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Discord; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign exploits a little-known flaw in Discord's invitation system, allowing attackers to hijack expired or deleted invite links and redirect users to malicious servers. The attack chain delivers powerful malware that targets cryptocurrency assets, stealing browser credentials, Discord tokens, and cryptocurrency wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141963</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro fixes critical vulnerabilities in multiple products</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-six-critical-flaws-on-apex-central-endpoint-encryption-policyserver/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central and Endpoint Encryption (TMEE) PolicyServer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49212, CVE-2025-49213, CVE-2025-49216, CVE-2025-49217; Summary: Multiple critical-severity remote code execution and authentication bypass vulnerabilities were identified in Trend Micro's Apex Central and Endpoint Encryption (TMEE) PolicyServer products. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to execute arbitrary code as SYSTEM without requiring login or fully bypass login and perform admin-level actions without credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-six-critical-flaws-on-apex-central-endpoint-encryption-policyserver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit DeepSeek-R1 Popularity to Target Windows Device Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-deepseek-r1-popularity/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated cyberattack campaign is targeting users seeking to download the language model DeepSeek-R1, exploiting malvertising and phishing tactics to distribute previously unknown malware, BrowserVenom. The malware hijacks victims' web traffic, steals sensitive information, and updates browser settings for persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141942</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud and Cloudflare hit by widespread service outages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-cloud-and-cloudflare-hit-by-widespread-service-outages/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare and Google Cloud are investigating ongoing outages affecting multiple services across regions, including Cloudflare Zero Trust WARP connectivity issues and authentication failures. The incidents appear to be impacting various online services and platforms, with Downdetector reporting tens of thousands of reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-cloud-and-cloudflare-hit-by-widespread-service-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenPGP.js Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Bypass Message Signature Verification</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/openpgp-js-vulnerability-allows-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenPGP.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47934; Summary: A critical vulnerability in OpenPGP.js (versions 5.0.1 to 5.11.2 and 6.0.0-alpha.0 to 6.1.0) allows attackers to spoof message signatures, potentially undermining the trust model of public key cryptography. The flaw enables attackers to manipulate signed or signed-and-encrypted messages so that they appear to be validly signed by a trusted party even when the underlying data has been maliciously altered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141930</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Defender Bypass Using PowerShell and Registry Edits in CyberEYE RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-defender-bypass-using-powershell-and-registry-edits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: CyberEye is a remote access trojan (RAT) that uses Telegram as its command-and-control (C2) infrastructure. It has sophisticated capabilities, including keyloggers, file grabbers, clipboard hijackers, and persistence mechanisms, making it easy for attackers to customize payloads and evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141878</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know thyself, know thy environment</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/know-thyself-know-thy-environment/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various software (catdoc, Parallel, NVIDIA, High-Logic FontCreator); CVE(s): None; Summary: Several vulnerabilities were disclosed across various software products, including catdoc which posed an exception as the vendor was unreachable. These vulnerabilities highlight risks in widely used software, potentially exposing systems to attacks such as privilege escalation, memory corruption, and data leaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">684ad31518508e0001bb2cd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sites Turned Weapon: How VexTrio and Affiliates Run a Global Scam Network</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/wordpress-sites-turned-weapon-how.html</link>
      <description>VexTrio ViperTraffic Distribution Service (TDS) is a sophisticated cybercriminal operation distributing malicious content through smartlinks and push notifications. The operation involves multiple TDS services, including Help TDS and Disposable TDS, which redirect victims to scam infrastructure. VexTrio's malware actors are often linked to Russian-connected infrastructure, and the company's operations have been compromised by DNS threat intelligence firm Qurium.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/wordpress-sites-turned-weapon-how.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphite spyware used in Apple iOS zero-click attacks on journalists</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/graphite-spyware-used-in-apple-ios-zero-click-attacks-on-journalists/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Paragon's Graphite spyware platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The Graphite spyware platform was used to launch zero-click attacks against at least two journalists' Apple iOS devices. The attack exploited a zero-day vulnerability in the processing of maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via an iCloud Link, allowing remote code execution without any interaction from the target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/graphite-spyware-used-in-apple-ios-zero-click-attacks-on-journalists/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AitM Phishing Attacks on Microsoft 365 and Google Aimed at Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/aitm-phishing-attacks-on-microsoft-365-and-google-aimed/</link>
      <description>A dramatic escalation in phishing attacks leveraging Adversary-in-the-Middle (AiTM) techniques has swept across organizations worldwide. These attacks use sophisticated reverse proxy servers to intercept user credentials and session cookies in real-time, bypassing even advanced security measures like Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA). Threat actors are constantly refining their methods to evade detection, employing various tactics such as HTML and SVG attachments, QR codes, and encrypted scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneLogin AD Connector Vulnerabilities Expose Authentication Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/onelogin-ad-connector-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OneLogin Active Directory (AD)Connector; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in OneLogin's AD Connector service allowed malicious actors to obtain authentication credentials, impersonate users, and access sensitive applications. The flaw was exploited by obtaining AWS credentials hard-coded in logs and using them to forge valid JSON Web Tokens (JWTs), enabling unauthorized access to enterprise applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141838</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Using Bat Files to Deploy Quasar RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-using-bat-files/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Quasar Remote Access Trojan (RAT) campaign that uses strong obfuscation and anti-sandbox techniques to evade detection. The malware infection begins with a batch script attached to a seemingly harmless document, which downloads an obfuscated second-stage file from a remote server. The malware then checks for virtual drives commonly used by sandboxes and kills itself if detected, making automated analysis difficult.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password-spraying attacks target 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-spraying-attacks-target-80-000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts/</link>
      <description>The TeamFiltration pentesting framework has been used by threat actor UNK_SneakyStrike to target over 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID accounts at hundreds of organizations worldwide. The campaign used AWS servers across multiple regions and exploited vulnerabilities in Office 365 API for account enumeration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-spraying-attacks-target-80-000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>137,000 SoftBank Customers Affected by Data Leak from Third-Party Vendor</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/137000-softbank-customers-affected/</link>
      <description>The article discusses SoftBank's approach to data security, highlighting the importance of comprehensive policies, employee training, and technical safeguards. It also emphasizes the need for robust data protection frameworks to prevent data leaks and breaches, particularly in outsourcing contexts. Additionally, the article touches on regulatory compliance and the evolving nature of cybersecurity threats in the telecommunications industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141961</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple GitLab Vulnerabilities Expose Users to Complete Account Takeover Risks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-gitlab-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4278, CVE-2025-2254, CVE-2025-5121, CVE-2025-0673, CVE-2025-1516, CVE-2025-1478, CVE-2024-9512, CVE-2025-5195, CVE-2025-5982; Summary: GitLab has released urgent security updates to address multiple high-severity vulnerabilities that could allow attackers to take over user accounts, inject malicious code, and disrupt services. The vulnerabilities include account takeover via injected HTML, cross-site scripting, injecting malicious CI/CD jobs, and denial-of-service attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TokenBreak Attack Bypasses AI Moderation with Single-Character Text Changes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-tokenbreak-attack-bypasses-ai.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Large Language Models (LLMs); CVE(s): None; Summary: The TokenBreak attack technique can bypass LLMs' safety and content moderation guardrails by manipulating input text with single character changes. This manipulation causes the tokenizer to split the text differently, allowing malicious input to be classified as legitimate, potentially leading to prompt injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-tokenbreak-attack-bypasses-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Resolves Windows Server 2025 Restart Bug Disrupting Active Directory Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-resolves-windows-server/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26647, None; Summary: The vulnerability affects Windows Server 2025 domain controllers, causing authentication failures and network connectivity problems. The issue occurs when security update KB5055523 changes how domain controllers validate certificates used for Kerberos authentication, requiring certificates to chain to an issuing certificate authority (CA) in the NTAuth store. The problem is resolved with the June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141944</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge now offers secure password deployment for businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-now-offers-secure-password-deployment-for-businesses/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced the general availability of a new feature for Microsoft Edge, allowing administrators to deploy encrypted shared passwords to specific user groups in enterprise environments. This feature aims to minimize the risk of unauthorized access by ensuring that employees do not accidentally share passwords with unintended recipients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-now-offers-secure-password-deployment-for-businesses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Run on Secret Accounts — Learn How to Secure Them in This Webinar</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ai-agents-run-on-secret-accounts-learn.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the growing threat of non-human identities (NHI) created by AI agents, chatbots, and automation scripts. These invisible identities, such as API keys, service accounts, and OAuth tokens, are powerful and unsecured, allowing attackers to move laterally through cloud infrastructure, deploy malware, and exfiltrate data without triggering alerts. The article emphasizes the need for new strategies to secure these NHIs, citing traditional IAM tools as insufficient for this task.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ai-agents-run-on-secret-accounts-learn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privilege Escalation in PAN-OS Web Interface Allows Admin Users to Perform Root Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/privilege-escalation-in-pan-os-web/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS operating system; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4231; Summary: A medium-severity command injection vulnerability (CVE-2025-4231) in the management web interface of PAN-OS allows authenticated administrative users to escalate privileges and execute commands as the root user, potentially compromising the entire firewall system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141935</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab patches high severity account takeover, missing auth issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-patches-high-severity-account-takeover-missing-auth-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4278, CVE-2025-5121, CVE-2025-2254, CVE-2025-0673; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities in GitLab's DevSecOps platform allow attackers to take over accounts, inject malicious jobs, and exploit cross-site scripting and denial of service flaws. Successful exploitation requires authenticated access with a GitLab Ultimate license.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-patches-high-severity-account-takeover-missing-auth-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command Injection Flaw in Palo Alto PAN-OS Allows Root-Level Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/flaw-in-palo-alto-pan-os/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4230; Summary: A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges, enabling file system modifications, unauthorized service disruptions, and lateral network movement. The vulnerability impacts PAN-OS versions 10.x and 11.x, and is exploitable locally without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141919</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: DragonForce Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-dragonforce-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the DragonForce Ransomware group, which has emerged as a significant threat in the cyber landscape. The group is known for its aggressive double extortion tactics, using both custom and borrowed tools to steal data, encrypt systems, and pressure victims into paying ransoms. The article provides an overview of the group's operations, including their use of leaked ransomware builders, advanced evasion techniques, and organized affiliate model. It also highlights the importance of proactive defense and intelligence gathering in detecting and stopping DragonForce attacks before they cause harm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100048798</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Cybersecurity Advisory on SimpleHelp RMM Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/12/cisa-releases-cybersecurity-advisory-simplehelp-rmm-vulnerability</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, None; Summary: Ransomware actors exploited an unpatched path traversal vulnerability (CVE-2024-57727) in SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) versions 5.5.7 and earlier to compromise customers of a utility billing software provider, resulting in service disruptions and double extortion incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23511</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Actors Exploit Unpatched SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management to Compromise Utility Billing Software Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-163a</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM); CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727; Summary: Ransomware actors are leveraging unpatched instances of SimpleHelp RMM, specifically versions 5.5.7 and earlier, to compromise customers. The vulnerability, CVE-2024-57727, is a path traversal vulnerability that allows attackers to access downstream customers' networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23510</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM products; CVE(s): CVE-2024-41797; Summary: The vulnerability is an incorrect authorization check that allows an authenticated remote attacker with "guest" role to invoke an internal "do system" command exceeding their privileges. This could allow the execution of certain low-risk actions, including clearing the local system log.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23500</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Connector for CygNet</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-09</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Connector for CygNet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4417, CVE-2025-4418; Summary: Cross-site scripting and improper validation of integrity check value vulnerabilities exist in PI Connector for CygNet Versions 1.6.14 and prior, allowing an attacker to persist arbitrary code or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23506</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Energy Services</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens G5DFR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40585; Summary: The vulnerability, due to incorrect default permissions, allows an attacker to gain remote control of the G5DFR component and tamper with outputs from the device. Successful exploitation could result in unauthorized access and manipulation of the device's outputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23503</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40567, CVE-2025-40568, CVE-2025-40569; Summary: The "Load Rollback" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains an incorrect authorization check vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with a "guest" role to make the affected product roll back to a previous configuration. Additionally, the "Load Configuration from Local PC" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains a race condition vulnerability that allows an authenticated remote attacker to load an attacker-controlled configuration instead of the legitimate one. The third vulnerability is a race condition that occurs when a legitimate administrator invokes the "Load Configuration from Local PC" functionality and the attacker wins the race. Successful exploitation requires that a legitimate administrator invokes the functionality and the attacker wins the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23501</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTZOptics and Other Pan-Tilt-Zoom Cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-10</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PTZOptics PT30X-SDI/NDI-xx before firmware 6.3.40; CVE(s): CVE-2024-8956, CVE-2024-8957; Summary: The camera is vulnerable to insufficient authentication and OS command injection issues, allowing an attacker to leak sensitive data, execute arbitrary commands, and access the admin web interface using hard-coded credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23507</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Data Archive</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Data Archive, AVEVA PI Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-44019, CVE-2025-36539; Summary: The products are vulnerable to an uncaught exception that can be exploited by an authenticated user to shut down necessary subsystems and cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23504</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SIMATIC S7-1500 CPU Family</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-05</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be a collection of multiple Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) from various sources, including Linux kernel, GnuTLS, OpenSSH, and others. Each CVE has its own unique characteristics, such as CVSS score, vector string, and description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23502</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0133; Summary: A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway and portal features of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user's browser when they click on a specially crafted link, potentially leading to phishing attacks and credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23499</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Ten Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/12/cisa-releases-ten-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None listed; CVE(s): None; Summary: CISA released 10 ICS advisories on June 12, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding industrial control systems. The advisories cover various products from Siemens and AVEVA, and users are encouraged to review them for technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23508</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Tecnomatix Plant Simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Tecnomatix Plant Simulation; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32454; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process by reading past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23498</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Web API</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-08</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Web API; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2745; Summary: A cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in AVEVA PI Web API versions 2023 SP1 and prior, allowing an authenticated attacker to persist arbitrary JavaScript code that can be executed by users who disable content security policy protections. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to disable content security policy protections, leading to potential attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23505</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Apex One Zero-Day Vulnerability Enables Attackers to Inject Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/trend-micro-apex-one-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49154, CVE-2025-49155, CVE-2025-49156, CVE-2025-49157, CVE-2025-49158; Summary: Five critical vulnerabilities in Trend Micro's Apex One endpoint security platform allow attackers to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges on affected systems. The most severe vulnerability, CVE-2025-49154, allows local attackers to overwrite key memory-mapped files, while the fifth vulnerability, CVE-2025-49155, enables remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141901</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Click AI Vulnerability Exposes Microsoft 365 Copilot Data Without User Interaction</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/zero-click-ai-vulnerability-exposes.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365 Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32711; Summary: The EchoLeak vulnerability is a zero-click AI vulnerability that allows attackers to exfiltrate sensitive data from Microsoft 365 Copilot's context without user interaction. It requires no customer action and has been already addressed by Microsoft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/zero-click-ai-vulnerability-exposes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Human Identities: How to Address the Expanding Security Risk</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/non-human-identities-how-to-address.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the risks and challenges associated with non-human identities (machine identities), such as service accounts, API keys, bots, automation, and workload identities. It emphasizes that traditional secrets managers do not address the full lifecycle of NHI governance, leading to a high risk of secrets leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/non-human-identities-how-to-address.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Advertise Advanced MaaS Botnet with Blockchain C2 on Hacking Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-advertise-advanced-maas-botnet/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the alleged sale of a sophisticated Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) botnet that combines legitimate development frameworks with cutting-edge evasion techniques. The botnet leverages Node.js runtime, blockchain-based command and control infrastructure, and modern web technologies to create a highly resilient and scalable malicious platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141879</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 24H2 emergency update fixes Easy Anti-Cheat BSOD issue</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-24h2-emergency-update-fixes-easy-anti-cheat-bsod-issue/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has released an emergency Windows 11 24H2 update (KB5063060) to address an incompatibility issue causing system restarts and blue screens of death (BSOD) errors on systems with Easy Anti-Cheat, a popular anti-cheating service used by hundreds of multiplayer games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-24h2-emergency-update-fixes-easy-anti-cheat-bsod-issue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSFireTruck: Exploring Malicious JavaScript Using JSF*ck as an Obfuscation Technique</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/malicious-javascript-using-jsfiretruck-as-obfuscation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various websites; CVE(s): None; Summary: A large-scale campaign has been compromising legitimate websites with injected, obfuscated JavaScript code. The code uses the JSFireTruck technique to hide its true purpose and redirect users to malicious URLs, potentially leading to malware downloads or other harmful activities.

FYSA: This campaign is widespread and has infected many websites, making it a significant threat. Malware authors use this technique to make code analysis more difficult, and website administrators must keep their web servers up-to-date with the latest security updates and analyze their web servers for any signs of infection or compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142866</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Launch Coordinated Attack on Apache Tomcat Manager from 400 Unique IPs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/launch-coordinated-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): None; Summary: GreyNoise Intelligence has identified a significant coordinated attack campaign targeting Apache Tomcat Manager interfaces across the globe. The campaign involves nearly 400 unique IP addresses conducting large-scale reconnaissance and access attempts, with security experts warning that such broad scanning activities often precede more targeted exploitation attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141853</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fog ransomware attack uses unusual mix of legitimate and open-source tools</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fog-ransomware-attack-uses-unusual-mix-of-legitimate-and-open-source-tools/</link>
      <description>Fog ransomware operation uses an uncommon toolset, including open-source pentesting utilities and a legitimate employee monitoring software called Syteca. The toolset includes tools like Stowaway, SMBExec, GC2, Adapt2x C2, Process Watchdog, PsExec, Impacket SMB, 7-Zip, MegaSync, and FreeFileSync utilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fog-ransomware-attack-uses-unusual-mix-of-legitimate-and-open-source-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Campaign Targets Entra ID User Accounts Using Pentesting Tool for Account Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-campaign-targets-entra-id-user-accounts/</link>
      <description>A large-scale Account Takeover (ATO) campaign, internally tracked as UNK_SneakyStrike, has been discovered by Proofpoint Threat Intelligence. The campaign targets Microsoft Entra ID user accounts across global organizations, using the open-source penetration testing framework TeamFiltration to target over 80,000 user accounts and compromise sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141805</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows SMB Client Zero-Day Vulnerability Exploited via Reflective Kerberos Relay Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-smb-client-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33073; Summary: The "Reflective Kerberos Relay Attack" allows low-privileged Active Directory users to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM on domain-joined Windows systems that do not enforce SMB signing. The attack exploits advanced techniques such as authentication coercion, SPN confusion, and Kerberos ticket relay, resulting in SYSTEM-level access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141825</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0-Click Vulnerability in Microsoft 365 Copilot Exposes Sensitive Data via Teams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerability-in-microsoft-365-copilot/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365 Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32711; Summary: A zero-click vulnerability, dubbed "EchoLeak", was discovered in Microsoft 365 Copilot's Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) system, allowing attackers to automatically exfiltrate sensitive information without user interaction. The vulnerability exploits an "LLM Scope Violation" and affects the processing of organizational data, including emails, documents, and conversations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141813</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise to Rotate ScreenConnect Code Signing Certificates Due to Security Risks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/connectwise-to-rotate-screenconnect.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability stems from ScreenConnect storing configuration data in an unsigned area of the installer, which could create an insecure design pattern. The company is releasing an update to improve configuration data management and rotating digital code signing certificates due to security concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/connectwise-to-rotate-screenconnect.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Secure: INTERPOL’s Global Infostealer Crackdown Takes Down 20,000 Malicious IPs and Domains</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/operation-secure-interpols-infostealer-takes-down-20000-ips-domains/</link>
      <description>INTERPOL's Operation Secure resulted in the dismantling of 20,000 malicious IPs and domains, seizure of 41 servers, and arrest of 32 suspects, with a focus on taking down cybercriminal networks trafficking in stolen information. The operation involved intelligence gathering, analysis, and precise actions by law enforcement agencies across Asia and the South Pacific.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060908</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nytheon AI Tool Gaining Traction on Hacking Forums for Malicious Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nytheon-ai-tool-gaining-traction/</link>
      <description>Nytheon AI is a comprehensive suite of open-source large language models (LLMs) that offers a single interface for uncensored model inference. The platform's multimodal ingestion pipeline and API-driven automation create a dynamic threat landscape, posing substantial risks to organizations and individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141787</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Comprehensive Guide to Safeguard Network Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-comprehensive-guide-to-safeguard/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released comprehensive guidance to help organizations protect their network edge devices and appliances from foreign adversaries. The guidance addresses the growing threat landscape targeting firewalls, routers, VPN gateways, IoT devices, internet-facing servers, and OT systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141786</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 06:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID Accounts Targeted Using Open-Source TeamFiltration Tool</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-80000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeamFiltration; CVE(s): None; Summary: The open-source penetration testing framework TeamFiltration is being misused by threat actors in a large-scale account takeover campaign called UNK_SneakyStrike. The tool, designed to enumerate and breach Microsoft Entra ID accounts, has been used to target over 80,000 user accounts across hundreds of organizations' cloud tenants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-80000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 05:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT o3 API 80% price drop has no impact on performance</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-o3-api-80-percent-price-drop-has-no-impact-on-performance/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenAI's price reduction of its ChatGPT o3 API model, which has no visible impact on performance. Additionally, it mentions the introduction of a new o3-pro model for $200 Pro subscribers and plans to combine multiple models into GPT-5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-o3-api-80-percent-price-drop-has-no-impact-on-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
