<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatched IT Tool Opens Door – Hackers Breach Billing Software Firm via SimpleHelp RMM</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-breach-billing-software-firm-via-simplehelp-rmm/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) platform; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727; Summary: The SimpleHelp RMM platform contains a path traversal vulnerability that allows attackers to access files or directories outside the intended web root, potentially exposing sensitive data or enabling further network compromises. The vulnerability has been exploited by ransomware actors since January 2025, targeting organizations with unpatched instances of SimpleHelp RMM versions 5.5.7 and earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142072</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare: Outage not caused by security incident, data is safe</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-outage-not-caused-by-security-incident-data-is-safe/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a service outage experienced by Cloudflare, which lasted almost 2.5 hours and affected multiple edge computing and AI services. The root cause was a failure in the Workers KV underlying storage infrastructure due to an outage from a third-party cloud provider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-outage-not-caused-by-security-incident-data-is-safe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphite Spyware Uses iOS Zero-Click Flaw to Target Journalists</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/graphite-spyware-uses-ios-zero-click-flaw-to-target-journalists/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple iMessage; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The vulnerability allowed for zero-click attacks on iPhones running iOS 18.2.1, exploiting a logic flaw in processing malicious iCloud links containing images/videos. The attack required no user interaction and was patched in iOS 18.3.1 (February 2025).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142112</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless Tokens in the Cloud: Exploitation and Detections</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/serverless-authentication-cloud/</link>
      <description>The article appears to be a technical analysis of serverless computing and its associated security implications. It discusses various cloud platforms, including AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure, and highlights potential vulnerabilities and risks related to the use of serverless identities and tokens.

The article provides detailed information on how attackers can exploit these credentials to access sensitive data or perform unauthorized actions within cloud environments. It also offers recommendations for securing serverless computing environments, such as implementing posture management and runtime monitoring protections, restricting access to IMDS, and using robust input validation and sanitization techniques.

Overall, the article is informative and provides valuable insights into the security implications of serverless computing, but it does not specifically discuss a vulnerability in any product or service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143156</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fog Ransomware Uses Pentesting Tools to Steal Data and Launch Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fog-ransomware-uses-pentesting-tools/</link>
      <description>Fog ransomware attacks have been linked to the use of open-source penetration testing tools, such as GC2, Adaptix, and Stowaway, and legitimate employee monitoring software like Syteca. The attackers used these tools to conduct reconnaissance, establish persistence, and exfiltrate data before deploying Fog ransomware, marking a new trend in cybercrime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142061</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSFireTruck Obfuscation Helps Cybercriminals Hijack Trusted Sites with Malicious JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jsfiretruck-obfuscation-helps-cybercriminals-hijack/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated cyber attack campaign has been discovered, where threat actors compromise legitimate websites to inject obfuscated JavaScript code. This enables them to quietly redirect unsuspecting visitors to malicious sites capable of delivering malware or executing exploits. Over 200,000 webpages were compromised in just one month, underscoring the evolving tactics used by attackers to exploit trusted domains for nefarious purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142051</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Unveiled for Windows Disk Cleanup Elevation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poc-exploit-windows-disk-cleanup/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Disk Cleanup Utility (cleanmgr.exe); CVE(s): CVE-2025-21420; Summary: The vulnerability enables attackers to execute malicious code with SYSTEM privileges through DLL sideloading and a directory traversal technique. The flaw stems from cleanmgr.exe's failure to validate DLL loading paths and mitigate symbolic link attacks, allowing attackers to exploit path interception vulnerabilities to load unsigned DLLs and gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142056</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Outage Hits Google Cloud and Linked Cloudflare Services, Thousands Affected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/major-outage-hits-google-cloud-and-linked/</link>
      <description>The article discusses two concurrent outages at Cloudflare and Google due to infrastructure failures, highlighting vulnerabilities in modern cloud dependencies. The outages had widespread impacts on critical services, underscoring the fragility of interconnected internet ecosystems. The incidents exposed risks in vendor lock-in and centralized dependencies, with both companies committing to postmortems and implementing changes to improve resilience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142054</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenBreak Exploit Tricks AI Models Using Minimal Input Changes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tokenbreak-exploit-tricks-ai-models/</link>
      <description>TokenBreak is a novel attack technique that exploits tokenization strategies in AI text classification models to bypass detection. It manipulates input text by inserting characters to create tokenization divergence between the model and its target, allowing attackers to evade detection while preserving meaning for the end target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142053</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebDAV Remote Code Execution 0-Day Actively Exploited — PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/webdav-0-day-poc-released/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WebDAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft's Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) protocol allows remote code execution via manipulated .url shortcut files. The flaw has been actively exploited by the Stealth Falcon APT group since March 2025, enabling attackers to hijack legitimate Windows tools like iediagcmd.exe and execute malicious payloads from attacker-controlled WebDAV servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142052</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Zero-Click Flaw in Messages Exploited to Spy on Journalists Using Paragon Spyware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apple-zero-click-flaw-in-messages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Messages app; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: A logic issue in the Messages app allowed for zero-click exploitation of maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via an iCloud Link, targeting civil society members with sophisticated cyber attacks. The vulnerability was actively exploited and patched on February 10, 2025, as part of various iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, and visionOS updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apple-zero-click-flaw-in-messages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside a Dark Adtech Empire Fed by Fake CAPTCHAs</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/inside-a-dark-adtech-empire-fed-by-fake-captchas/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a dark adtech industry that allows malicious actors to bypass moderation on social media platforms and spread disinformation. The industry relies on domain cloaking services, which hide the true nature of websites from search engines, allowing them to remain online longer than they would otherwise. The industry also uses push monetization services, which pay affiliates to drive signups for various schemes, including online dating services. The article highlights the connections between VexTrio, LosPollos, and other malicious traffic distribution systems (TDSs), which are operated by Russian organized crime groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=69927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming to Apple OSes: A seamless, secure way to import and export passkeys</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/apple-previews-new-import-export-feature-to-make-passkeys-more-interoperable/</link>
      <description>Apple has introduced a new process for securely transferring credentials between apps, which is more secure than traditional methods and eliminates the risk of credential leaks. The system uses a standardized data format built with the FIDO Alliance to move data between apps, providing a modern and secure way to manage credentials. This development aims to improve the usability of passkeys and potentially alleviate issues related to password management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/apple-previews-new-import-export-feature-to-make-passkeys-more-interoperable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Exploiting Expired Discord Invite Links to Deploy Multi-Stage Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-exploiting-expired-discord-invite-links/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Discord; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign exploits a little-known flaw in Discord's invitation system, allowing attackers to hijack expired or deleted invite links and redirect users to malicious servers. The attack chain delivers powerful malware that targets cryptocurrency assets, stealing browser credentials, Discord tokens, and cryptocurrency wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141963</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro fixes critical vulnerabilities in multiple products</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-six-critical-flaws-on-apex-central-endpoint-encryption-policyserver/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central and Endpoint Encryption (TMEE) PolicyServer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49212, CVE-2025-49213, CVE-2025-49216, CVE-2025-49217; Summary: Multiple critical-severity remote code execution and authentication bypass vulnerabilities were identified in Trend Micro's Apex Central and Endpoint Encryption (TMEE) PolicyServer products. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to execute arbitrary code as SYSTEM without requiring login or fully bypass login and perform admin-level actions without credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trend-micro-fixes-six-critical-flaws-on-apex-central-endpoint-encryption-policyserver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit DeepSeek-R1 Popularity to Target Windows Device Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-deepseek-r1-popularity/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated cyberattack campaign is targeting users seeking to download the language model DeepSeek-R1, exploiting malvertising and phishing tactics to distribute previously unknown malware, BrowserVenom. The malware hijacks victims' web traffic, steals sensitive information, and updates browser settings for persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141942</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud and Cloudflare hit by widespread service outages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-cloud-and-cloudflare-hit-by-widespread-service-outages/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare and Google Cloud are investigating ongoing outages affecting multiple services across regions, including Cloudflare Zero Trust WARP connectivity issues and authentication failures. The incidents appear to be impacting various online services and platforms, with Downdetector reporting tens of thousands of reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/google-cloud-and-cloudflare-hit-by-widespread-service-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenPGP.js Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Bypass Message Signature Verification</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/openpgp-js-vulnerability-allows-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenPGP.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47934; Summary: A critical vulnerability in OpenPGP.js (versions 5.0.1 to 5.11.2 and 6.0.0-alpha.0 to 6.1.0) allows attackers to spoof message signatures, potentially undermining the trust model of public key cryptography. The flaw enables attackers to manipulate signed or signed-and-encrypted messages so that they appear to be validly signed by a trusted party even when the underlying data has been maliciously altered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141930</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Defender Bypass Using PowerShell and Registry Edits in CyberEYE RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-defender-bypass-using-powershell-and-registry-edits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: CyberEye is a remote access trojan (RAT) that uses Telegram as its command-and-control (C2) infrastructure. It has sophisticated capabilities, including keyloggers, file grabbers, clipboard hijackers, and persistence mechanisms, making it easy for attackers to customize payloads and evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141878</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know thyself, know thy environment</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/know-thyself-know-thy-environment/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various software (catdoc, Parallel, NVIDIA, High-Logic FontCreator); CVE(s): None; Summary: Several vulnerabilities were disclosed across various software products, including catdoc which posed an exception as the vendor was unreachable. These vulnerabilities highlight risks in widely used software, potentially exposing systems to attacks such as privilege escalation, memory corruption, and data leaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">684ad31518508e0001bb2cd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sites Turned Weapon: How VexTrio and Affiliates Run a Global Scam Network</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/wordpress-sites-turned-weapon-how.html</link>
      <description>VexTrio ViperTraffic Distribution Service (TDS) is a sophisticated cybercriminal operation distributing malicious content through smartlinks and push notifications. The operation involves multiple TDS services, including Help TDS and Disposable TDS, which redirect victims to scam infrastructure. VexTrio's malware actors are often linked to Russian-connected infrastructure, and the company's operations have been compromised by DNS threat intelligence firm Qurium.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/wordpress-sites-turned-weapon-how.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphite spyware used in Apple iOS zero-click attacks on journalists</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/graphite-spyware-used-in-apple-ios-zero-click-attacks-on-journalists/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Paragon's Graphite spyware platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The Graphite spyware platform was used to launch zero-click attacks against at least two journalists' Apple iOS devices. The attack exploited a zero-day vulnerability in the processing of maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via an iCloud Link, allowing remote code execution without any interaction from the target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/graphite-spyware-used-in-apple-ios-zero-click-attacks-on-journalists/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AitM Phishing Attacks on Microsoft 365 and Google Aimed at Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/aitm-phishing-attacks-on-microsoft-365-and-google-aimed/</link>
      <description>A dramatic escalation in phishing attacks leveraging Adversary-in-the-Middle (AiTM) techniques has swept across organizations worldwide. These attacks use sophisticated reverse proxy servers to intercept user credentials and session cookies in real-time, bypassing even advanced security measures like Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA). Threat actors are constantly refining their methods to evade detection, employing various tactics such as HTML and SVG attachments, QR codes, and encrypted scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneLogin AD Connector Vulnerabilities Expose Authentication Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/onelogin-ad-connector-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OneLogin Active Directory (AD)Connector; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in OneLogin's AD Connector service allowed malicious actors to obtain authentication credentials, impersonate users, and access sensitive applications. The flaw was exploited by obtaining AWS credentials hard-coded in logs and using them to forge valid JSON Web Tokens (JWTs), enabling unauthorized access to enterprise applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141838</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Using Bat Files to Deploy Quasar RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-using-bat-files/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Quasar Remote Access Trojan (RAT) campaign that uses strong obfuscation and anti-sandbox techniques to evade detection. The malware infection begins with a batch script attached to a seemingly harmless document, which downloads an obfuscated second-stage file from a remote server. The malware then checks for virtual drives commonly used by sandboxes and kills itself if detected, making automated analysis difficult.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password-spraying attacks target 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-spraying-attacks-target-80-000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts/</link>
      <description>The TeamFiltration pentesting framework has been used by threat actor UNK_SneakyStrike to target over 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID accounts at hundreds of organizations worldwide. The campaign used AWS servers across multiple regions and exploited vulnerabilities in Office 365 API for account enumeration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/password-spraying-attacks-target-80-000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>137,000 SoftBank Customers Affected by Data Leak from Third-Party Vendor</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/137000-softbank-customers-affected/</link>
      <description>The article discusses SoftBank's approach to data security, highlighting the importance of comprehensive policies, employee training, and technical safeguards. It also emphasizes the need for robust data protection frameworks to prevent data leaks and breaches, particularly in outsourcing contexts. Additionally, the article touches on regulatory compliance and the evolving nature of cybersecurity threats in the telecommunications industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141961</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple GitLab Vulnerabilities Expose Users to Complete Account Takeover Risks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-gitlab-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4278, CVE-2025-2254, CVE-2025-5121, CVE-2025-0673, CVE-2025-1516, CVE-2025-1478, CVE-2024-9512, CVE-2025-5195, CVE-2025-5982; Summary: GitLab has released urgent security updates to address multiple high-severity vulnerabilities that could allow attackers to take over user accounts, inject malicious code, and disrupt services. The vulnerabilities include account takeover via injected HTML, cross-site scripting, injecting malicious CI/CD jobs, and denial-of-service attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TokenBreak Attack Bypasses AI Moderation with Single-Character Text Changes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-tokenbreak-attack-bypasses-ai.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Large Language Models (LLMs); CVE(s): None; Summary: The TokenBreak attack technique can bypass LLMs' safety and content moderation guardrails by manipulating input text with single character changes. This manipulation causes the tokenizer to split the text differently, allowing malicious input to be classified as legitimate, potentially leading to prompt injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-tokenbreak-attack-bypasses-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Resolves Windows Server 2025 Restart Bug Disrupting Active Directory Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-resolves-windows-server/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26647, None; Summary: The vulnerability affects Windows Server 2025 domain controllers, causing authentication failures and network connectivity problems. The issue occurs when security update KB5055523 changes how domain controllers validate certificates used for Kerberos authentication, requiring certificates to chain to an issuing certificate authority (CA) in the NTAuth store. The problem is resolved with the June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141944</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge now offers secure password deployment for businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-now-offers-secure-password-deployment-for-businesses/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced the general availability of a new feature for Microsoft Edge, allowing administrators to deploy encrypted shared passwords to specific user groups in enterprise environments. This feature aims to minimize the risk of unauthorized access by ensuring that employees do not accidentally share passwords with unintended recipients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-edge-now-offers-secure-password-deployment-for-businesses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Run on Secret Accounts — Learn How to Secure Them in This Webinar</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ai-agents-run-on-secret-accounts-learn.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the growing threat of non-human identities (NHI) created by AI agents, chatbots, and automation scripts. These invisible identities, such as API keys, service accounts, and OAuth tokens, are powerful and unsecured, allowing attackers to move laterally through cloud infrastructure, deploy malware, and exfiltrate data without triggering alerts. The article emphasizes the need for new strategies to secure these NHIs, citing traditional IAM tools as insufficient for this task.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ai-agents-run-on-secret-accounts-learn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privilege Escalation in PAN-OS Web Interface Allows Admin Users to Perform Root Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/privilege-escalation-in-pan-os-web/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS operating system; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4231; Summary: A medium-severity command injection vulnerability (CVE-2025-4231) in the management web interface of PAN-OS allows authenticated administrative users to escalate privileges and execute commands as the root user, potentially compromising the entire firewall system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141935</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab patches high severity account takeover, missing auth issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-patches-high-severity-account-takeover-missing-auth-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4278, CVE-2025-5121, CVE-2025-2254, CVE-2025-0673; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities in GitLab's DevSecOps platform allow attackers to take over accounts, inject malicious jobs, and exploit cross-site scripting and denial of service flaws. Successful exploitation requires authenticated access with a GitLab Ultimate license.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gitlab-patches-high-severity-account-takeover-missing-auth-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command Injection Flaw in Palo Alto PAN-OS Allows Root-Level Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/flaw-in-palo-alto-pan-os/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4230; Summary: A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges, enabling file system modifications, unauthorized service disruptions, and lateral network movement. The vulnerability impacts PAN-OS versions 10.x and 11.x, and is exploitable locally without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141919</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: DragonForce Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-dragonforce-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the DragonForce Ransomware group, which has emerged as a significant threat in the cyber landscape. The group is known for its aggressive double extortion tactics, using both custom and borrowed tools to steal data, encrypt systems, and pressure victims into paying ransoms. The article provides an overview of the group's operations, including their use of leaked ransomware builders, advanced evasion techniques, and organized affiliate model. It also highlights the importance of proactive defense and intelligence gathering in detecting and stopping DragonForce attacks before they cause harm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100048798</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Cybersecurity Advisory on SimpleHelp RMM Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/12/cisa-releases-cybersecurity-advisory-simplehelp-rmm-vulnerability</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, None; Summary: Ransomware actors exploited an unpatched path traversal vulnerability (CVE-2024-57727) in SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) versions 5.5.7 and earlier to compromise customers of a utility billing software provider, resulting in service disruptions and double extortion incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23511</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Actors Exploit Unpatched SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management to Compromise Utility Billing Software Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-163a</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM); CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727; Summary: Ransomware actors are leveraging unpatched instances of SimpleHelp RMM, specifically versions 5.5.7 and earlier, to compromise customers. The vulnerability, CVE-2024-57727, is a path traversal vulnerability that allows attackers to access downstream customers' networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23510</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM products; CVE(s): CVE-2024-41797; Summary: The vulnerability is an incorrect authorization check that allows an authenticated remote attacker with "guest" role to invoke an internal "do system" command exceeding their privileges. This could allow the execution of certain low-risk actions, including clearing the local system log.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23500</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Connector for CygNet</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-09</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Connector for CygNet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4417, CVE-2025-4418; Summary: Cross-site scripting and improper validation of integrity check value vulnerabilities exist in PI Connector for CygNet Versions 1.6.14 and prior, allowing an attacker to persist arbitrary code or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23506</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Energy Services</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens G5DFR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40585; Summary: The vulnerability, due to incorrect default permissions, allows an attacker to gain remote control of the G5DFR component and tamper with outputs from the device. Successful exploitation could result in unauthorized access and manipulation of the device's outputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23503</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SCALANCE and RUGGEDCOM products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40567, CVE-2025-40568, CVE-2025-40569; Summary: The "Load Rollback" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains an incorrect authorization check vulnerability. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with a "guest" role to make the affected product roll back to a previous configuration. Additionally, the "Load Configuration from Local PC" functionality in the web interface of affected products contains a race condition vulnerability that allows an authenticated remote attacker to load an attacker-controlled configuration instead of the legitimate one. The third vulnerability is a race condition that occurs when a legitimate administrator invokes the "Load Configuration from Local PC" functionality and the attacker wins the race. Successful exploitation requires that a legitimate administrator invokes the functionality and the attacker wins the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23501</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTZOptics and Other Pan-Tilt-Zoom Cameras</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-10</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PTZOptics PT30X-SDI/NDI-xx before firmware 6.3.40; CVE(s): CVE-2024-8956, CVE-2024-8957; Summary: The camera is vulnerable to insufficient authentication and OS command injection issues, allowing an attacker to leak sensitive data, execute arbitrary commands, and access the admin web interface using hard-coded credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23507</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Data Archive</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Data Archive, AVEVA PI Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-44019, CVE-2025-36539; Summary: The products are vulnerable to an uncaught exception that can be exploited by an authenticated user to shut down necessary subsystems and cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23504</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SIMATIC S7-1500 CPU Family</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-05</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be a collection of multiple Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs) from various sources, including Linux kernel, GnuTLS, OpenSSH, and others. Each CVE has its own unique characteristics, such as CVSS score, vector string, and description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23502</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0133; Summary: A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway and portal features of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user's browser when they click on a specially crafted link, potentially leading to phishing attacks and credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23499</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Ten Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/12/cisa-releases-ten-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None listed; CVE(s): None; Summary: CISA released 10 ICS advisories on June 12, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding industrial control systems. The advisories cover various products from Siemens and AVEVA, and users are encouraged to review them for technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23508</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Tecnomatix Plant Simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Tecnomatix Plant Simulation; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32454; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process by reading past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23498</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Web API</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-162-08</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Web API; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2745; Summary: A cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in AVEVA PI Web API versions 2023 SP1 and prior, allowing an authenticated attacker to persist arbitrary JavaScript code that can be executed by users who disable content security policy protections. Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to disable content security policy protections, leading to potential attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23505</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Apex One Zero-Day Vulnerability Enables Attackers to Inject Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/trend-micro-apex-one-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49154, CVE-2025-49155, CVE-2025-49156, CVE-2025-49157, CVE-2025-49158; Summary: Five critical vulnerabilities in Trend Micro's Apex One endpoint security platform allow attackers to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges on affected systems. The most severe vulnerability, CVE-2025-49154, allows local attackers to overwrite key memory-mapped files, while the fifth vulnerability, CVE-2025-49155, enables remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141901</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Click AI Vulnerability Exposes Microsoft 365 Copilot Data Without User Interaction</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/zero-click-ai-vulnerability-exposes.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365 Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32711; Summary: The EchoLeak vulnerability is a zero-click AI vulnerability that allows attackers to exfiltrate sensitive data from Microsoft 365 Copilot's context without user interaction. It requires no customer action and has been already addressed by Microsoft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/zero-click-ai-vulnerability-exposes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Human Identities: How to Address the Expanding Security Risk</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/non-human-identities-how-to-address.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the risks and challenges associated with non-human identities (machine identities), such as service accounts, API keys, bots, automation, and workload identities. It emphasizes that traditional secrets managers do not address the full lifecycle of NHI governance, leading to a high risk of secrets leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/non-human-identities-how-to-address.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Advertise Advanced MaaS Botnet with Blockchain C2 on Hacking Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-advertise-advanced-maas-botnet/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the alleged sale of a sophisticated Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) botnet that combines legitimate development frameworks with cutting-edge evasion techniques. The botnet leverages Node.js runtime, blockchain-based command and control infrastructure, and modern web technologies to create a highly resilient and scalable malicious platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141879</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 24H2 emergency update fixes Easy Anti-Cheat BSOD issue</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-24h2-emergency-update-fixes-easy-anti-cheat-bsod-issue/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has released an emergency Windows 11 24H2 update (KB5063060) to address an incompatibility issue causing system restarts and blue screens of death (BSOD) errors on systems with Easy Anti-Cheat, a popular anti-cheating service used by hundreds of multiplayer games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-24h2-emergency-update-fixes-easy-anti-cheat-bsod-issue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSFireTruck: Exploring Malicious JavaScript Using JSF*ck as an Obfuscation Technique</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/malicious-javascript-using-jsfiretruck-as-obfuscation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various websites; CVE(s): None; Summary: A large-scale campaign has been compromising legitimate websites with injected, obfuscated JavaScript code. The code uses the JSFireTruck technique to hide its true purpose and redirect users to malicious URLs, potentially leading to malware downloads or other harmful activities.

FYSA: This campaign is widespread and has infected many websites, making it a significant threat. Malware authors use this technique to make code analysis more difficult, and website administrators must keep their web servers up-to-date with the latest security updates and analyze their web servers for any signs of infection or compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142866</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Launch Coordinated Attack on Apache Tomcat Manager from 400 Unique IPs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/launch-coordinated-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): None; Summary: GreyNoise Intelligence has identified a significant coordinated attack campaign targeting Apache Tomcat Manager interfaces across the globe. The campaign involves nearly 400 unique IP addresses conducting large-scale reconnaissance and access attempts, with security experts warning that such broad scanning activities often precede more targeted exploitation attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141853</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fog ransomware attack uses unusual mix of legitimate and open-source tools</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fog-ransomware-attack-uses-unusual-mix-of-legitimate-and-open-source-tools/</link>
      <description>Fog ransomware operation uses an uncommon toolset, including open-source pentesting utilities and a legitimate employee monitoring software called Syteca. The toolset includes tools like Stowaway, SMBExec, GC2, Adapt2x C2, Process Watchdog, PsExec, Impacket SMB, 7-Zip, MegaSync, and FreeFileSync utilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fog-ransomware-attack-uses-unusual-mix-of-legitimate-and-open-source-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Campaign Targets Entra ID User Accounts Using Pentesting Tool for Account Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-campaign-targets-entra-id-user-accounts/</link>
      <description>A large-scale Account Takeover (ATO) campaign, internally tracked as UNK_SneakyStrike, has been discovered by Proofpoint Threat Intelligence. The campaign targets Microsoft Entra ID user accounts across global organizations, using the open-source penetration testing framework TeamFiltration to target over 80,000 user accounts and compromise sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141805</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows SMB Client Zero-Day Vulnerability Exploited via Reflective Kerberos Relay Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-smb-client-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33073; Summary: The "Reflective Kerberos Relay Attack" allows low-privileged Active Directory users to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM on domain-joined Windows systems that do not enforce SMB signing. The attack exploits advanced techniques such as authentication coercion, SPN confusion, and Kerberos ticket relay, resulting in SYSTEM-level access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141825</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0-Click Vulnerability in Microsoft 365 Copilot Exposes Sensitive Data via Teams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerability-in-microsoft-365-copilot/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365 Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32711; Summary: A zero-click vulnerability, dubbed "EchoLeak", was discovered in Microsoft 365 Copilot's Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) system, allowing attackers to automatically exfiltrate sensitive information without user interaction. The vulnerability exploits an "LLM Scope Violation" and affects the processing of organizational data, including emails, documents, and conversations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141813</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise to Rotate ScreenConnect Code Signing Certificates Due to Security Risks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/connectwise-to-rotate-screenconnect.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability stems from ScreenConnect storing configuration data in an unsigned area of the installer, which could create an insecure design pattern. The company is releasing an update to improve configuration data management and rotating digital code signing certificates due to security concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/connectwise-to-rotate-screenconnect.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Secure: INTERPOL’s Global Infostealer Crackdown Takes Down 20,000 Malicious IPs and Domains</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/operation-secure-interpols-infostealer-takes-down-20000-ips-domains/</link>
      <description>INTERPOL's Operation Secure resulted in the dismantling of 20,000 malicious IPs and domains, seizure of 41 servers, and arrest of 32 suspects, with a focus on taking down cybercriminal networks trafficking in stolen information. The operation involved intelligence gathering, analysis, and precise actions by law enforcement agencies across Asia and the South Pacific.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060908</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 07:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nytheon AI Tool Gaining Traction on Hacking Forums for Malicious Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nytheon-ai-tool-gaining-traction/</link>
      <description>Nytheon AI is a comprehensive suite of open-source large language models (LLMs) that offers a single interface for uncensored model inference. The platform's multimodal ingestion pipeline and API-driven automation create a dynamic threat landscape, posing substantial risks to organizations and individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141787</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Comprehensive Guide to Safeguard Network Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-comprehensive-guide-to-safeguard/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released comprehensive guidance to help organizations protect their network edge devices and appliances from foreign adversaries. The guidance addresses the growing threat landscape targeting firewalls, routers, VPN gateways, IoT devices, internet-facing servers, and OT systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141786</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 06:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 80,000 Microsoft Entra ID Accounts Targeted Using Open-Source TeamFiltration Tool</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-80000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeamFiltration; CVE(s): None; Summary: The open-source penetration testing framework TeamFiltration is being misused by threat actors in a large-scale account takeover campaign called UNK_SneakyStrike. The tool, designed to enumerate and breach Microsoft Entra ID accounts, has been used to target over 80,000 user accounts across hundreds of organizations' cloud tenants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-80000-microsoft-entra-id-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 05:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT o3 API 80% price drop has no impact on performance</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-o3-api-80-percent-price-drop-has-no-impact-on-performance/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenAI's price reduction of its ChatGPT o3 API model, which has no visible impact on performance. Additionally, it mentions the introduction of a new o3-pro model for $200 Pro subscribers and plans to combine multiple models into GPT-5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-o3-api-80-percent-price-drop-has-no-impact-on-performance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predator Still Active, with New Client and Corporate Links Identified</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/predator-still-active-new-links-identified</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an analysis of the Predator spyware product and its connections to Intellexa Consortium. The report discusses the continued use of Predator despite widespread media attention and sanctions targeting Intellexa.

The article highlights the adoption of new tactics by Predator operators to evade detection, including the use of new domains and IP addresses. It also mentions the connection between Predator infrastructure and corporate entities associated with the Intellexa Consortium, specifically FoxITech s.r.o., a Czech company based in Krnov.

The report suggests that public exposure, sanctions, and related measures have likely imposed operational costs on Intellexa, driving efforts to increase the complexity of corporate structures, making operations harder to trace and disrupt. The continued spread of Predator and similar spyware products presents a significant risk to a broad range of organizations and individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/predator-still-active-new-links-identified</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartAttack uses smartwatches to steal data from air-gapped systems</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/smartattack-uses-smartwatches-to-steal-data-from-air-gapped-systems/</link>
      <description>SmartAttack is a novel attack that uses smartwatches as covert ultrasonic signal receivers to exfiltrate data from physically isolated (air-gapped) systems. The attack involves malware modulating audio signals on an air-gapped computer's speaker, which can be detected by a nearby smartwatch microphone and transmitted via Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, or cellular connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/smartattack-uses-smartwatches-to-steal-data-from-air-gapped-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-360: Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Uncontrolled Search Path Element Arbitrary Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-360/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro, Worry-Free Business Security; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49487; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL, which loads an unsecured configuration file from a certain location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23056</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-361: Trend Micro Password Manager Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-361/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Password Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48443; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Password Manager, requiring low-privileged code execution and an administrator's install action. The specific flaw exists within the product installer, enabling arbitrary file deletion and privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25574</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-362: Trend Micro Apex One Data Loss Prevention Uncontrolled Search Path Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-362/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49155; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent by loading a DLL from an uncontrolled search path. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24571</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-363: Trend Micro Apex One Virus Scan Engine Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-363/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49156; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent by creating a symbolic link within the VsapiNT.sys kernel module. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution and configure the product for non-default malware remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24973</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-364: Trend Micro Apex One Damage Cleanup Engine Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-364/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49157, ZDI-CAN-25273; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25273</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-365: Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent ntrmv Uncontrolled Search Path Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-365/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49158; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One Security Agent by exploiting the product's uninstaller, which executes a program from an unsecured location. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution and then persuade an administrator to uninstall the Security Agent in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25771</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-366: Trend Micro Apex Central GetReportDetailView Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-366/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49219; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25286</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-367: Trend Micro Apex Central ConvertFromJson Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-367/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49220; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central without authentication. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25495</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-368: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption BuildEnterpriseSearchString SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-368/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49211, ZDI-CAN-25528, ZDI-25-368; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption by bypassing the existing authentication mechanism. It exists within the implementation of the BuildEnterpriseSearchString method due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25528</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-369: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption PolicyValueTableSerializationBinder Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-369/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49212; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption without authentication. The issue exists within the PolicyValueTableSerializationBinder class due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25507</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-370: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption PolicyServerWindowsService Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-370/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49213, ZDI-CAN-25506, ZDI-25-370; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the PolicyServerWindowsService class due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data leading to deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25506</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-371: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption DeserializeFromBase64String Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-371/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49212; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption by deserializing untrusted data. The existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed, and the attack can be executed in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25518</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-372: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption GetGroupFilteredUsers SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-372/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49215; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption, bypassing authentication. The issue exists in the implementation of the GetGroupFilteredUsers method and results from improper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to gain elevated access to resources normally protected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25527</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-373: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption DbAppDomain Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-373/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49216; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption, without requiring authentication. The issue is due to an improper implementation of an authentication algorithm in the DbAppDomain service, which can be exploited to gain access to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25519</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-374: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption ValidateToken Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-374/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49217; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the ValidateToken method, which lacks proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25505</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-375: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption ProcessWhereClause SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-375/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49218; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Endpoint Encryption, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The flaw exists in the ProcessWhereClause method's lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, allowing attackers to escalate privileges to normally protected resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25526</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-376: (Pwn2Own) Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet Improper Certificate Validation Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-376/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti Networks; AI Bullet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23118; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet cameras. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to bypass authentication on the system due to improper certificate validation in the ubnt_avclient component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25666</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-377: (Pwn2Own) Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet Improper Neutralization of Escape Sequences Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-377/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti Networks; AI Bullet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23119; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet cameras. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the processing of DHCP packet options due to insufficient neutralization of special characters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25603</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-378: (Pwn2Own) Ubiquiti Networks UniFi Console Missing Authentication for Critical Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-378/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti Networks UniFi Console; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23116, ZDI-CAN-25588, ZDI-25-378; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected UniFi Console devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the handling of bridge device adoption requests. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication and disclose credentials for accessing connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25588</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-379: (Pwn2Own) Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet Insufficient Firmware Update Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-379/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23117; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Ubiquiti Networks AI Bullet Cameras, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The specific flaw exists within the handling of firmware updates, resulting from the lack of proper validation of firmware update packages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25589</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 22:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erie Insurance confirms cyberattack behind business disruptions</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/erie-insurance-confirms-cyberattack-behind-business-disruptions/</link>
      <description>Erie Insurance and Erie Indemnity Company have disclosed a weekend cyberattack causing business disruptions and platform outages on their website, affecting over 6 million active policies. The company detected "unusual network activity" on June 7, 2025, and is working with law enforcement to investigate the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/erie-insurance-confirms-cyberattack-behind-business-disruptions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-359: Microsoft Visual Studio initializeCommand Insufficient UI Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-359/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Visual Studio; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47959; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Visual Studio. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists in the handling of the devcontainer.json file and can be exploited to execute code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26586</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpol Dismantles 20,000 Malicious IPs and Domains Tied to 69 Malware Variants</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/interpol-dismantles-20000-malicious-ips-and-domains-tied/</link>
      <description>INTERPOL's Operation Secure has seen the takedown of over 20,000 malicious IP addresses and domains associated with infostealer malware. The operation involved law enforcement agencies across 26 countries, leveraging advanced threat intelligence from leading cybersecurity firms to produce Cyber Activity Reports. The operation resulted in the seizure of 41 servers, confiscation of over 100 GB of data, and 32 arrests made globally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141720</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 40,000 Internet-Connected Cameras Exposed, Streaming Live Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-40000-internet-connected-cameras-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Surveillance Cameras; CVE(s): None; Summary: Bitsight TRACE has discovered over 40,000 security cameras openly accessible on the internet, streaming live footage from various locations, including homes, offices, factories, and datacenter rooms. The exposure allows anyone with a web browser and basic technical knowledge to access the feeds without authentication or sophisticated hacking, leaving millions vulnerable to surveillance, espionage, and privacy invasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141765</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Secure Boot Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Install Malware in PC and Server Boot Processes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-secure-boot-vulnerability-allows-attackers-to-install-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: DT Research, Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI); CVE(s): CVE-2025-3052; Summary: A memory corruption flaw enables attackers to execute unsigned code during the early boot phase, bypassing Secure Boot protections and potentially compromising the entire device. The vulnerability allows an attacker to set an NVRAM variable called IhisiParamBuffer to an arbitrary memory address, granting them an arbitrary memory write primitive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141758</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise to Update Code Signing Certificates for ScreenConnect, Automate, and RMM</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/connectwise-to-update-code-signing-certificates/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability but rather announces upcoming security updates for ScreenConnect, ConnectWise Automate, and ConnectWise RMM. The updates include rotating code signing certificates and improving configuration data management to ensure the integrity of software installations and updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141752</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Malware Authors Targeting Cloud Environments with ELF Binaries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/linux-malware-authors-targeting-cloud-environments/</link>
      <description>A worrying trend has been observed by Unit 42, Palo Alto Networks' threat intelligence division, where threat actors are increasingly creating and modifying Linux Executable and Linkable Format (ELF) malware to attack cloud infrastructure. Five evolving ELF-based malware families have been identified, including NoodleRAT, Winnti (Linux variants), SSHdInjector, Pygmy Goat, and AcidPour. Each family has seen at least two significant codebase updates in the past year and has been observed in the wild at least 20 times, indicating active development and deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141746</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-340: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial Technician API Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-340/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel; MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5822; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial charging stations. An attacker must first obtain a low-privileged authorization token in order to exploit this vulnerability, which is caused by incorrect authorization within the implementation of the Autel Technician API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26325</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-341: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial Serial Number Exposed Dangerous Method Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-341/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5823; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial EV chargers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the implementation of the Autel Technician API due to an exposed dangerous method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26351</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-342: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial PIN Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-342/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel; MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): ZDI-25-342, ZDI-CAN-26352; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication on affected installations of Autel's MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial charging stations. The issue is due to the lack of authentication prior to accessing functionality, which can lead to credential disclosure and further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26352</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-343: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial Origin Validation Error Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-343/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5824, ZDI-CAN-26353, ZDI-25-343; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial by insufficiently validating the origin of commands. An attacker must first obtain the ability to pair a malicious Bluetooth device with the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to bypass authentication on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26353</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-344: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial Firmware Downgrade Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-344/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5825; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial charging stations by exploiting the lack of proper validation of a firmware image during the upgrade process. An attacker must first pair a malicious Bluetooth device with the target system to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26354</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-345: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial ble_process_esp32_msg Misinterpretation of Input Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-345/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5826, ZDI-CAN-26368, ZDI-25-345; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to inject arbitrary AT commands on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial charging stations without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the ble_process_esp32_msg function due to misinterpretation of input data, which can be exploited to execute AT commands in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26368</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-346: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial ble_process_esp32_msg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-346/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5827, ZDI-CAN-26369; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial EV chargers without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the ble_process_esp32_msg function due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing attackers to execute code in the device's context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26369</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-347: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial wLength Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-347/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5828; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial EV chargers without authentication. The flaw exists in the handling of USB frame packets and results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer, allowing an attacker to execute code in the device's context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26328</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-348: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial autocharge Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-348/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel; Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5829; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial EV chargers without authentication. It exists within the handling of JSON messages and is caused by a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer, allowing for remote code execution in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26330</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-349: (Pwn2Own) Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial DLB_SlaveRegister Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-349/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5830; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autel MaxiCharger AC Wallbox Commercial EV chargers without authentication. The flaw exists in the handling of DLB_SlaveRegister messages due to insufficient validation of user-supplied data, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26327</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-350: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Root Filesystem Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-350/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5833; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to bypass authentication on affected Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX devices without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the operating system's configuration, resulting from insufficient protection for the root file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26077</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-351: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Missing Immutable Root of Trust in Hardware Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-351/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5834; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges, executing arbitrary code in the context of the boot process. The issue arises from a lack of a properly configured hardware root of trust within the application system-on-chip (SoC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26078</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-352: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Software Update Signing Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-352/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5832; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX devices without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the software update verification process, which lacks validation of all data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26079</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-353: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth Packet Handling Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-353/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5475; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Sony XAV-AX8500 devices by exploiting an integer overflow in Bluetooth packet handling. The attacker must first pair a malicious device with the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26283</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-354: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth L2CAP Protocol Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-354/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5477; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected devices by exploiting a heap-based buffer overflow in the Bluetooth L2CAP protocol. An attacker must pair a malicious device with the target system to exploit this vulnerability, and Sony has issued an update to correct it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26286</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-355: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth SDP Protocol Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-355/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5478; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sony XAV-AX8500 devices without authentication. The issue results from an integer overflow in the Bluetooth SDP protocol due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26288</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-356: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth AVCTP Protocol Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-356/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5479; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sony XAV-AX8500 devices by exploiting a heap-based buffer overflow in the Bluetooth AVCTP protocol. An attacker must pair a malicious Bluetooth device with the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which affects the length validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26290</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-357: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth Improper Isolation Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-357/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5476; Summary: The Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth device has an improper isolation authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication without requiring any further interaction. The issue is due to the lack of L2CAP channel isolation in the implementation of ACL-U links, enabling attackers to exploit this flaw and gain unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26284</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-358: (Pwn2Own) Sony XAV-AX8500 Bluetooth ERTM Channel Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-358/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sony XAV-AX8500; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5820; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected Sony XAV-AX8500 devices without requiring authentication, exploiting a flaw in the implementation of Bluetooth ERTM channel communication due to improper channel data initialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26285</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-click AI data leak flaw uncovered in Microsoft 365 Copilot</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zero-click-ai-data-leak-flaw-uncovered-in-microsoft-365-copilot/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365 Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32711; Summary: A zero-click AI vulnerability, dubbed EchoLeak, allows attackers to exfiltrate sensitive data from a user's context without interaction. The vulnerability was fixed server-side in May and no real-world exploitation has been observed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/zero-click-ai-data-leak-flaw-uncovered-in-microsoft-365-copilot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Black Basta Members Use Microsoft Teams and Python Scripts in 2025 Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/former-black-basta-members-use.html</link>
      <description>Former Black Basta ransomware operation members are using Teams phishing and email bombing to establish persistent access to target networks, with some attacks leveraging Python script execution and others using Quick Assist and AnyDesk for remote desktop sessions. Additionally, the article discusses various ransomware groups' tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including Scattered Spider's "one-to-many" approach, Qilin's exploitation of Fortinet vulnerabilities, and Interlock's use of NodeSnake JavaScript RAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/former-black-basta-members-use.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insyde UEFI Application Vulnerability Enables Digital Certificate Injection Through NVRAM Variable</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/insyde-uefi-application-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Insyde H2O UEFI firmware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-XXXX; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Insyde H2O UEFI firmware allows attackers to bypass Secure Boot protections by injecting malicious digital certificates via an unprotected NVRAM variable. This flaw exposes millions of devices to pre-boot malware and kernel-level rootkits that evade traditional security monitoring, enabling three primary attack vectors including bypassing Secure Boot, neutralizing Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) or antivirus (AV) systems, and opening the door to supply chain attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141738</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlook Vulnerability Allows Remote Execution of Arbitrary Code by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/outlook-vulnerability-allows-remote-execution/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Outlook; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47176; Summary: The vulnerability enables attackers to execute arbitrary code via a local file handling issue. Attackers with low privileges and local access can manipulate the process to execute arbitrary code by manipulating special characters or path sequences in file or attachment names, potentially compromising data confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141726</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers exploited Windows WebDav zero-day to drop malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stealth-falcon-hackers-exploited-windows-webdav-zero-day-to-drop-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: The Windows WebDav RCE vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-33053, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code remotely from a controlled WebDAV server without dropping malicious files locally. This vulnerability was exploited by the APT group 'Stealth Falcon' in zero-day attacks against defense and government organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stealth-falcon-hackers-exploited-windows-webdav-zero-day-to-drop-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft creates separate Windows 11 24H2 update for incompatible PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-creates-separate-windows-11-24h2-update-for-incompatible-pcs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on a compatibility issue affecting some Windows 11 24H2 systems, causing them to be incompatible with the initial security update released during Patch Tuesday. A revised update will be rolled out to affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-creates-separate-windows-11-24h2-update-for-incompatible-pcs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brute-force attacks target Apache Tomcat management panels</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brute-force-attacks-target-apache-tomcat-management-panels/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): None; Summary: A coordinated campaign of brute-force attacks using hundreds of unique IP addresses targets Apache Tomcat Manager interfaces exposed online. The attacks do not exploit any specific vulnerability, but rather attempt to gain access to Tomcat services over the Internet by trying login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brute-force-attacks-target-apache-tomcat-management-panels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Task Scheduler Flaw Allows Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-task-scheduler-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Task Scheduler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33067; Summary: A critical elevation of privilege vulnerability allows attackers to gain elevated privileges on affected systems, bypassing normal user restrictions and compromising the integrity of the operating system. The flaw occurs when the software does not properly restrict, assign, or manage privileges, allowing attackers to perform actions outside their intended level of authority. Exploitation requires local access to the target system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141673</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Common Log File System Driver Flaw Allows Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-common-log-file-system-driver-flaw-allows-attackers-to-escalate-privileges/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32713; Summary: The Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) driver contains a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability that allows local attackers to escalate privileges to SYSTEM-level access. Attackers can exploit this by triggering a heap overflow via crafted log operations, corrupting adjacent memory structures, and gaining NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM privileges without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141670</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Secure disrupts global infostealer malware operations</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/operation-secure-disrupts-global-infostealer-malware-operations/</link>
      <description>Operation Secure, a global law enforcement action, targeted infostealer malware infrastructure across 26 countries, resulting in 32 arrests, data seizures, and server takedowns. The operation focused on disrupting groups that steal financial and personal data through widespread infections, leading to the takedown of over 20,000 malicious IPs/domains and seizure of 41 servers supporting info-stealers operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/operation-secure-disrupts-global-infostealer-malware-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>295 Malicious IPs Launch Coordinated Brute-Force Attacks on Apache Tomcat Manager</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/295-malicious-ips-launch-coordinated.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): None; Summary: A "coordinated brute-force activity" has been observed targeting Apache Tomcat Manager interfaces. The activity was seen on June 5, 2025, and involved 295 unique IP addresses engaging in brute-force attempts against exposed Tomcat services at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/295-malicious-ips-launch-coordinated.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>catdoc zero-day, NVIDIA, High-Logic FontCreator and Parallel vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/catdoc-zero-day-nvidia-high-logic-fontcreator-and-parallel-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Cisco Talos has disclosed three zero-day vulnerabilities in catdoc and other software products, including Parallel, NVIDIA cuobjdump, and High-Logic FontCreator. The vulnerabilities have been patched by their respective vendors except for the catdoc zero-day vulnerabilities which were patched by a Cisco researcher due to an inability to reach the vendor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">683dd4475919a600012bd788</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes unreachable Windows Server domain controllers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-unreachable-windows-server-domain-controllers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some Windows Server 2025 domain controllers may become unreachable after a restart and trigger app or service failures due to incorrect network traffic management. This issue can be mitigated by applying the KB5060842 update or temporarily restarting the network adapter using PowerShell until the update is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-unreachable-windows-server-domain-controllers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June 2025 Patch Tuesday Fixes 67 Flaws &amp; 2 Zero-Days; Critical Ivanti IWC Updates</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/june-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-67-flaws-2-zero-days/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: Two zero-days were disclosed in June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates. One (CVE-2025-33053) allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted WebDAV URL, which was actively exploited by Stealth Falcon, an advanced persistent threat group. The second (CVE-2025-33073) is a Windows SMB client vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to elevate privileges to SYSTEM level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060890</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Microsoft Office Vulnerabilities Enable Remote Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-office-vulnerabilities-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47162, CVE-2025-47953, CVE-2025-47164, and CVE-2025-47167; Summary: Four critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities were disclosed in Microsoft Office's June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, affecting document parsing logic, memory management, and file validation. Exploitation can grant attackers full system control, compromising confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141669</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Windows Server auth issues caused by April updates</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-server-auth-issues-caused-by-april-updates/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26647; Summary: The April 2025 security updates caused authentication problems on Windows Server domain controllers, affecting Windows Server 2016, Windows Server 2019, Windows Server 2022, and Windows Server 2025. This issue is linked to a high-severity vulnerability that can let authenticated attackers escalate privileges remotely by exploiting an improper input validation weakness in Windows Kerberos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-server-auth-issues-caused-by-april-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoreDNS Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Exhaust Server Memory via Amplification Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coredns-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CoreDNS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47950; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in CoreDNS's DNS-over-QUIC (DoQ) implementation allows remote attackers to crash DNS servers through stream amplification attacks, enabling OOM crashes in memory-constrained environments and bypassing authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141662</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERPOL Dismantles 20,000+ Malicious IPs Linked to 69 Malware Variants in Operation Secure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/interpol-dismantles-20000-malicious-ips.html</link>
      <description>INTERPOL's Operation Secure resulted in the takedown of 79% of malicious IP addresses, seizure of servers and data, and arrests of suspects linked to illegal cyber activities. The operation targeted information-stealing malware variants, with a focus on disrupting command-and-control servers hosting phishing, online fraud, and social media scams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/interpol-dismantles-20000-malicious-ips.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why DNS Security Is Your First Defense Against Cyber Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/why-dns-security-is-your-first-defense.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of securing the Domain Name System (DNS) as it plays a critical role in nearly every online interaction, making it an attractive target for cyber attackers. It highlights common DNS-based attacks such as DNS spoofing, hijacking, and tunneling, which can disrupt services, compromise sensitive data, or silently spy on users. The article also emphasizes the need to secure DNS traffic through monitoring, controlling, and encrypting queries, citing ClouDNS as an example of a provider that combines speed, reliability, and built-in security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/why-dns-security-is-your-first-defense.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache CloudStack Flaw Allows Attackers to Execute Privileged Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-cloudstack-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache CloudStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26521, CVE-2025-47713, CVE-2025-30675, CVE-2025-47849, CVE-2025-22829; Summary: Five critical security vulnerabilities were found in Apache CloudStack, including a privilege escalation flaw allowing Domain Admins to reset admin passwords and a vulnerability that enables attackers to impersonate the cluster creator. Upgrading to version 4.19.3.0 or 4.20.1.0 is recommended to remediate these issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141655</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinoTrack GPS Devices Vulnerable to Remote Vehicle Control via Default Passwords</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sinotrack-gps-devices-vulnerable-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SinoTrack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5484, CVE-2025-5485; Summary: Two vulnerabilities in SinoTrack GPS devices allow an attacker to access device profiles without authorization, enabling remote functions on connected vehicles such as tracking locations and disconnecting power to the fuel pump. The flaws stem from weak authentication using a default password and a numerical identifier printed on the receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sinotrack-gps-devices-vulnerable-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Lean Security Model: 5 Lessons from River Island</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-build-lean-security-model-5.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses how River Island, a UK fashion retailer, implemented a lean security model using Intruder's exposure management platform. This allowed their small team of three to improve visibility, respond faster to threats, and empower others across the business to fix vulnerabilities. The approach involves adopting continuous network monitoring, consolidating security tools, and automating vulnerability scanning and remediation processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-build-lean-security-model-5.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPE Aruba Network Flaw Exposes Sensitive Data to Potential Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hpe-aruba-network-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Networking Private 5G Core Platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37100; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in the API implementation of the Private 5G Core Platform allows unauthorized access to sensitive system files, posing a risk to enterprise confidentiality and infrastructure integrity. Exploitation can occur remotely with valid credentials or authentication to the system, enabling attackers to download protected system files containing sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141640</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patches 67 Vulnerabilities Including WEBDAV Zero-Day Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-patches-67-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WEBDAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A remote code execution flaw in Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WEBDAV) has been weaponized in real-world attacks, allowing an attacker to execute malware by deceiving users into clicking on a specially crafted URL. The vulnerability, rated Critical, can be triggered by manipulating the working directory and is exploited through a .url file that launches iediagcmd.exe, which then executes another payload called Horus Loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-patches-67-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insyde UEFI Flaw Enables Digital Certificate Injection via NVRAM Variable</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/insyde-uefi-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Insyde H2O UEFI firmware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4275; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the SecureFlashCertData NVRAM variable allows attackers to inject malicious digital certificates and bypass Secure Boot protections, enabling pre-boot execution of unsigned code. This flaw enables severe risks to enterprise and consumer devices, allowing for persistence across reboots and OS reinstalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141634</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Chrome Flaws Enable Remote Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-chrome-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5958, CVE-2025-5959; Summary: The Stable channel of Google Chrome has been updated to version 137.0.7151.103 for Windows and Mac, and 137.0.7151.103 for Linux. Two high-severity security vulnerabilities have been addressed: a use-after-free condition in the Chrome Media component (CVE-2025-5958) that can lead to arbitrary code execution or denial-of-service attacks, and a type confusion vulnerability in the V8 JavaScript engine (CVE-2025-5959) that can be leveraged for remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141625</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Tuesday, June 2025 Edition</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/patch-tuesday-june-2025-edition/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: The article reports on multiple vulnerabilities in Microsoft Windows operating systems and software. One vulnerability, CVE-2025-33053, is a remote code execution flaw in the Windows implementation of WebDAV, which has already been exploited. Another vulnerability, CVE-2025-33073, is an elevation of privilege flaw in the SMB client, which can grant attackers SYSTEM-level control over a vulnerable PC.

FYSA: Several cybersecurity-relevant details are highlighted in the article, including the exploitation of a zero-day flaw and public proof-of-concept code for another flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71465</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-332: Microsoft Windows Installer Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-332/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33075; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by abusing the Windows Installer service. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this flaw, which can be used to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26710</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-333: Microsoft Windows Installer Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-333/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32714; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the Windows Installer service that uses an unsecured location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26487</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-334: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Gateway Service Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-334/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Gateway Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30394; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Microsoft Windows, without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the Remote Desktop Gateway service due to a null pointer dereference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26776</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-335: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-335/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43575; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC by writing past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26342</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-336: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Collab Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-336/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43573; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the handling of Collab objects due to lack of validating object existence prior to operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26590</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-337: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-337/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47112; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data that can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26777</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-338: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Collab Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-338/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43574; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Collab objects and can be exploited by not validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26593</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-339: JupyterLab Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-339/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jupyter; JupyterLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30167; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of JupyterLab. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and it is triggered only when a target user makes use of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25932</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DanaBot malware operators exposed via C2 bug added in 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/danabot-malware-operators-exposed-via-c2-bug-added-in-2022/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: DanaBot Malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in the DanaBot malware operation introduced in June 2022 allowed security researchers to gain insight into the malware's internal operations and the people behind it, leading to the identification, indictment, and dismantling of their operations. The "DanaBleed" flaw was a memory leak that exposed private data, including threat actor details, backend infrastructure, and victim data, for over three years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/danabot-malware-operators-exposed-via-c2-bug-added-in-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday for June 2025 — Snort rules and prominent vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-june-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32710, CVE-2025-29828, CVE-2025-33071, CVE-2025-47172, CVE-2025-47162, CVE-2025-47164, CVE-2025-47167, CVE-2025-47953; Summary: The vulnerabilities affect various Microsoft Windows services and applications, including Remote Desktop Services, Schannel (Secure Channel), KDC Proxy service, Microsoft Office, and SharePoint server. They are remote code execution (RCE) or elevation of privilege vulnerabilities with varying attack complexities and exploitation likelihoods.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6848785af23a7100010e4c1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise rotating code signing certificates over security concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-rotating-code-signing-certificates-over-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise (various products); CVE(s): None; Summary: ConnectWise is rotating the digital code signing certificates used to sign ScreenConnect, Automate, and RMM executables due to concerns raised by a third-party security researcher about how certain configuration data can be abused by threat actors. The action is unrelated to any security incidents, including a nation-state cyberattack suffered last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-rotating-code-signing-certificates-over-security-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Secure Boot flaw lets attackers install bootkit malware, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-secure-boot-flaw-lets-attackers-install-bootkit-malware-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3052; Summary: A Secure Boot bypass vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-3052, allows attackers with admin rights to modify a user-writable NVRAM variable and disable Secure Boot, enabling the installation of bootkit malware. The flaw affects nearly every system that trusts Microsoft's "UEFI CA 2011" certificate, which is widely used in modern systems utilizing UEFI firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-secure-boot-flaw-lets-attackers-install-bootkit-malware-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Windows WebDAV 0-Day RCE Vulnerability Actively Exploited in The Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-windows-webdav-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft Windows allows remote code execution through manipulation of a system's working directory. The flaw was actively exploited by the advanced persistent threat (APT) group Stealth Falcon, who used it to deliver malicious files and inject shellcode into legitimate system processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141611</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found in the wild: 2 Secure Boot exploits. Microsoft is patching only 1 of them.</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/unearthed-in-the-wild-2-secure-boot-exploits-microsoft-patches-only-1-of-them/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers with brief physical access to a device can boot it up in IGEL and modify the boot loader to install malware. This vulnerability allows bypassing Secure Boot protections, potentially loading an untrusted OS on systems that trust the Microsoft 3rd Party UEFI CA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/unearthed-in-the-wild-2-secure-boot-exploits-microsoft-patches-only-1-of-them/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday June 2025 – 66 Vulnerabilities Patched Including 2 Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-june-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the WebDAV component of Windows was actively exploited and a publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerability in the SMB client allowed for elevation of privilege. The vulnerabilities could be exploited to execute arbitrary code or gain SYSTEM-level privileges, making timely patching essential.

Note: There are 66 vulnerabilities patched in total, but only these two specific vulnerabilities are mentioned as zero-days with exploitation details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141601</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Highlights the Internet as the Primary Threat to Industrial Automation Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-highlights-the-internet-as-the-primary-threat/</link>
      <description>According to Kaspersky ICS CERT, the internet is the primary source of threats to operational technology (OT) infrastructure worldwide, with 21.9% of Industrial Control System (ICS) computers encountering malicious objects in the first quarter of 2025. The report highlights regional disparities in cybersecurity maturity, with Africa and South-East Asia facing heightened exposure to internet-based threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141568</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Releases Patch Fixing 254 Vulnerabilities, Closing High-Severity Security Gaps</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/adobe-releases-patch-fixing-254.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe; CVEs: CVE-2025-47110, CVE-2025-43585, None (for others); Summary: Adobe patched 254 security flaws in its software products, primarily affecting Experience Manager and Commerce/Magento. The vulnerabilities, including a critical reflected XSS flaw and an improper authorization issue, could lead to arbitrary code execution, privilege escalation, or security feature bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/adobe-releases-patch-fixing-254.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Details on How to Manage Your Digital Footprint</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-to-manage-your-digital-footprint/</link>
      <description>ESET highlights the importance of digital footprints, emphasizing both their benefits (personalized marketing, professional branding) and risks (privacy breaches, identity theft). The article stresses the need for robust strategies to manage and secure one's online presence, including regular audits, adjusting privacy settings, and leveraging advanced security tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141538</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover 20+ Configuration Risks, Including Five CVEs, in Salesforce Industry Cloud</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-uncover-20-configuration.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Salesforce Industry Cloud; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43697, CVE-2025-43698, CVE-2025-43699, CVE-2025-43700, CVE-2025-43701; Summary: Over 20 configuration-related risks were found in Salesforce Industry Cloud, exposing sensitive data to unauthorized parties. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to bypass security controls and extract sensitive customer or employee information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-uncover-20-configuration.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5060533 cumulative update released with 7 changes, fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5060533-cumulative-update-released-with-7-changes-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The KB5060533 cumulative update for Windows 10 22H2 and Windows 10 21H2 fixes seven zero-day vulnerabilities, including bringing seconds back to the time shown in the Calendar flyout, enhancing the Rich Calendar feature, and fixing issues with GDI/GDI+, Mobile Operator Profiles, and WinSaS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5060533-cumulative-update-released-with-7-changes-fixes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP NetWeaver Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-netweaver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP; CVE(s): 3600840; Summary: A critical vulnerability with a CVSS score of 9.6 in the SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP's Remote Function Call (RFC) framework allows authenticated attackers to bypass standard authorization checks and escalate privileges, potentially granting access to critical system functions and data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft June 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes exploited zero-day, 66 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-exploited-zero-day-66-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: Microsoft fixed two zero-day vulnerabilities in its June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates. The first is a Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WEBDAV) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability (CVE-2025-33053), which was actively exploited before the patch was available. The second is a Windows SMB Client Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-33073), which allows attackers to gain SYSTEM privileges on vulnerable devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-exploited-zero-day-66-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5060842 and KB5060999 cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060842-and-kb5060999-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the release of Windows 11 KB5060842 and KB5060999 cumulative updates for versions 24H2 and 23H2, which include fixes for 66 security vulnerabilities. The updates also introduce new features such as improved Windows Search, enhanced digital accessibility with AI-powered image descriptions in Narrator, and management of Energy Saver settings through group policies and MDM configurations using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060842-and-kb5060999-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Instagram Growth Tools Stealing Login Credentials and Sending Them to Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-instagram-growth-tools-stealing-login-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: imad213 (Python package); CVE(s): None; Summary: The malicious Python package imad213, posing as an Instagram growth tool, tricks users into surrendering their credentials. Upon execution, it initiates a remote check and prompts users for their Instagram login details, saving them locally in plaintext. The malware then broadcasts these credentials to a network of Turkish bot services, which pose as legitimate platforms with professional interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141553</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean APT Hackers Target Users on Social Media to Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-apt-hackers-target-users/</link>
      <description>This article reports a highly sophisticated Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) campaign orchestrated by the North Korean state-sponsored hacking group Kimsuky, targeting individuals in South Korea through social media, email, and Telegram. The attackers use social engineering and tailored content to exploit trust, and employ a multi-stage infiltration strategy involving malicious files, decoy PDFs, and malware designed to bypass signature-based detection tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141545</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN6 Uses AWS-Hosted Fake Resumes on LinkedIn to Deliver More_eggs Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fin6-uses-aws-hosted-fake-resumes-on.html</link>
      <description>FIN6 is a financially motivated threat actor that uses fake resumes hosted on Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure to deliver the More_eggs malware. The group initiates contact with recruiters through LinkedIn and Indeed, posing as job seekers, and then delivers phishing messages that lead to malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fin6-uses-aws-hosted-fake-resumes-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook to block more risky attachments used in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-outlook-to-block-more-risky-attachments-used-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Microsoft will block .library-ms and .search-ms file types in Outlook Web and the new Outlook for Windows starting next month to enhance security and prevent exploitation of Windows vulnerabilities. The blocked file types are rarely used, but may affect organizations that rely on them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-outlook-to-block-more-risky-attachments-used-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Dept. of Transportation breached, 300k crash records stolen</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/texas-dept-of-transportation-breached-300k-crash-records-stolen/</link>
      <description>The Texas Department of Transportation (TxDOT) suffered a data breach after a threat actor downloaded 300,000 crash records from its database using compromised credentials. The exposed data includes full names, physical addresses, driver's license numbers, and other information, which elevates the risk for social engineering, scamming, and phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/texas-dept-of-transportation-breached-300k-crash-records-stolen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN6 hackers pose as job seekers to backdoor recruiters’ devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fin6-hackers-pose-as-job-seekers-to-backdoor-recruiters-devices/</link>
      <description>FIN6 hacking group impersonates job seekers to target recruiters, using social engineering campaigns to deliver "More Eggs" malware-as-a-service JavaScript backdoor for credential theft, system access, and ransomware deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fin6-hackers-pose-as-job-seekers-to-backdoor-recruiters-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Workspace Control hardcoded key flaws expose SQL credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-workspace-control-hardcoded-key-flaws-expose-sql-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Workspace Control (IWC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-5353, CVE-2025-22455, CVE-2025-22463; Summary: The IWC solution has three high-severity hardcoded key vulnerabilities that can lead to privilege escalation and system compromise following successful exploitation. Two flaws allow local authenticated attackers to decrypt stored SQL credentials, while the third enables decryption of the stored environment password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-workspace-control-hardcoded-key-flaws-expose-sql-credentials/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Heroku outage impacts web platforms worldwide</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-heroku-outage-impacts-web-platforms-worldwide/</link>
      <description>Heroku is experiencing a widespread outage that has lasted over six hours, affecting developers' ability to log in and use the platform. The outage impacts various services and websites, including SolarWinds, which cannot ingest logs due to the issue. Heroku has not yet provided details on the root cause or when services will be restored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-heroku-outage-impacts-web-platforms-worldwide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Workspace Control Vulnerability Lets Attackers Remotely Exploit To Steal the Credential</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-workspace-control-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Workspace Control; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5353, CVE-2025-22463, CVE-2025-22455; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Ivanti Workspace Control prior to 10.19.10.0 allow local authenticated attackers to decrypt stored SQL credentials and environment passwords due to hardcoded cryptographic keys. Successful exploitation could lead to severe consequences, including unauthorized access to critical systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141554</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust-based Myth Stealer Malware Spread via Fake Gaming Sites Targets Chrome, Firefox Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rust-based-myth-stealer-malware-spread.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): None; Summary: Myth Stealer is a Rust-based information stealer that steals passwords, cookies, and autofill information from Chromium- and Gecko-based browsers. It's distributed through fake gaming websites and online forums, and attempts to terminate running processes associated with web browsers before exfiltrating stolen data to a remote server or Discord webhook. The malware contains anti-analysis techniques such as string obfuscation and system checks using filenames and usernames.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rust-based-myth-stealer-malware-spread.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is a data-breach time bomb, reveals new report</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ai-is-a-data-breach-time-bomb-reveals-new-report/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with AI, cloud environments, and SaaS apps. It highlights that 99% of organizations have sensitive data unnecessarily exposed to AI tools, and no organization was fully prepared for AI. The report emphasizes the importance of implementing effective security measures to prioritize data protection.

Note: There are no specific vulnerabilities mentioned in this article, but it focuses on the risks associated with AI and data exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ai-is-a-data-breach-time-bomb-reveals-new-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Persist in Using ConnectWise ScreenConnect Tool to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-persist-in-using-connectwise-screenconnect-tool/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise ScreenConnect; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers are exploiting a vulnerability in ScreenConnect versions 23.9.7 and prior, deploying malicious payloads, particularly targeting financial organizations, using phishing emails with invoice themes to trick users into downloading harmful executables. The exploitation involves signed malicious droppers, likely tied to the CHAINVERB backdoor associated with the UNC5952 threat group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141498</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI working to fix ChatGPT outage affecting users worldwide</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/openai-working-to-fix-chatgpt-outage-affecting-users-worldwide/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article reports on an ongoing outage impacting OpenAI's ChatGPT, causing errors and latency for users worldwide. The issue has been identified as a root cause and the company is working to implement a mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/openai-working-to-fix-chatgpt-outage-affecting-users-worldwide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe SAP NetWeaver Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Bypass Authorization Checks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/severe-sap-netweaver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): 3600840 (9.6), 3609271 (8.8), 3606484 (8.5), 3560693 (8.2), 3610006 (7.5), 3590887 (5.8); Summary: The June Patch Day from SAP addresses nineteen security patches, including critical vulnerabilities that can allow attackers to bypass authorization controls and escalate privileges across multiple enterprise systems. The most severe vulnerability affects the RFC framework in SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP, enabling authenticated attackers to bypass standard authorization controls and achieve privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141512</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-49113: Critical Roundcube Vulnerability Enables RCE Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-49113-roundcube-vulnerability-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49113; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-49113, affects all Roundcube versions before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x up to 1.6.10, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands on targeted systems after successful authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060866</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New SharePoint Phishing Campaigns Employing Deceptive Lick Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sharepoint-phishing-campaigns/</link>
      <description>Phishing campaigns leveraging Microsoft SharePoint to bypass modern detection systems have been identified, exploiting inherent trust users place in the platform. These attacks disguise phishing URLs as legitimate file-sharing links, tricking users into accessing credential-harvesting pages or downloading malware, and evade endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools and email security gateways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141482</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISPConfig Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation to Superadmin and PHP Code Injection Exploit</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ispconfig-vulnerability-allows-privilege-escalation-to-superadmin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ISPConfig version 3.2.12p1; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to escalate their privileges to that of a superadmin and execute arbitrary PHP code remotely, posing a serious risk to affected systems. Attackers can manipulate HTTP parameters when using the client_add and users_edit features, creating a client account with admin privileges, then modifying or assuming the identity of the superadmin user (ID 1), granting unrestricted access to the ISPConfig instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141481</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Lovable’s Security Policies Allows Malicious Code Injection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-lovables-security-policies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lovable; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability affects Lovable's AI-powered development platform, exposing sensitive user data and enabling malicious code injection across hundreds of applications. It stems from the platform's client-driven architecture and lack of proper Row Level Security (RLS) configurations, allowing unauthorized access to database contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141460</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/10/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24016, CVE-2025-33053; Summary: Two new vulnerabilities were added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog by CISA due to evidence of active exploitation. The vulnerabilities are a Wazuh Server Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability and a Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability. These types of vulnerabilities pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and all organizations are urged to prioritize timely remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23494</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinoTrack GPS Receiver</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-160-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SinoTrack Equipment; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5484, CVE-2025-5485; Summary: Weak authentication and observable response discrepancy vulnerabilities in all known SinoTrack devices allow an attacker to access device profiles without authorization through the common web management interface, enabling remote functions on connected vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/10/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories by CISA, providing information on current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23493</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670, 650, SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-160-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670, Relion 650, SAM600-IO Series; CVE(s): CVE-2022-4304; Summary: A timing-based side channel exists in the OpenSSL RSA decryption implementation, allowing an attacker to decrypt application data in transit by sending a large number of trial messages for decryption. This vulnerability affects all RSA padding modes: PKCS#1 v1.5, RSA-OEAP and RSASVE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23491</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroDicom DICOM Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-160-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MicroDicom DICOM Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5943; Summary: The DICOM Viewer suffers from an out-of-bounds write vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with user interaction. Successful exploitation could lead to the execution of arbitrary code on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23492</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five plead guilty to laundering $36 million stolen in investment scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/five-plead-guilty-to-laundering-36-million-stolen-in-investment-scams/</link>
      <description>Five men from China, the United States, and Turkey pleaded guilty to their involvement in an international crime ring and laundering nearly $37 million stolen from U.S. victims in cryptocurrency investment scams carried out from Cambodia. The scam involved accomplices reaching out to targets via unsolicited social media, phone calls, text messages, and online dating services to gain their trust, promoting fraudulent digital asset investments and falsely claiming that the victims' funds' value increased after they tricked them into investing, when, in fact, their money was stolen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/five-plead-guilty-to-laundering-36-million-stolen-in-investment-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Threat in Your Stack: Why Non-Human Identity Management is the Next Cybersecurity Frontier</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-threat-in-your-stack-why-non.html</link>
      <description>Non-human identities (NHIs), including application secrets, API keys, service accounts, and OAuth tokens, have increased in recent years due to the expanding array of apps and services. NHIs introduce unique risks and management challenges that security leaders must address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-threat-in-your-stack-why-non.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on Erlang/OTP SSH Server RCE Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-erlang-otp-ssh-server-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP SSH server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: The Erlang/OTP SSH server implementation has a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-32433) that allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands without authentication, bypassing standard security controls. This flaw enables unauthenticated remote code execution and is actively exploited in the wild, posing significant risks to organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141432</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Authorities Bust Cybercriminals Posing as Microsoft Tech Support</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-posing-as-microsoft-tech-support/</link>
      <description>The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) launched an operation targeting a tech support scam network impersonating Microsoft, resulting in the arrest of six key operatives and the shutdown of two illicit call centers. The operation was a result of international collaboration between the CBI, Japan's Cybercrime Control Center, National Police Agency, and Microsoft's Digital Crimes Unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141461</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Actors Exploit SoraAI’s Popularity &amp; GitHub to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-actors-exploit-soraais-popularity-github/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malware campaign that uses OpenAI's Sora video generation model as a social engineering tactic to distribute information-stealing malware. The attack chain involves multiple stages, including downloading malicious batch files and executing Python scripts, which target sensitive data such as browser cookies, passwords, and system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141441</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher Found Flaw to Discover Phone Numbers Linked to Any Google Account</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researcher-found-flaw-to-discover-phone.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Google's account recovery feature allowed attackers to brute-force a user's recovery phone number, potentially exposing their accounts to privacy and security risks. The exploit required several steps, including leaking the display name via Looker Studio, running the forgot password flow, and brute-forcing the phone number against the username recovery endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researcher-found-flaw-to-discover-phone.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Linux Binaries in Targeted Cloud Operations</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/elf-based-malware-targets-cloud/</link>
      <description>Unit 42 researchers have identified a growing threat to cloud security: Linux Executable and Linkage Format (ELF) files that threat actors are developing to target cloud infrastructure. The article highlights the types of malicious binaries that threat actors are developing for use in attacks against Linux-based environments, including backdoors, droppers, remote access Trojans (RATs), data wipers, and vulnerability-exploiting binaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142727</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware Deployment Campaigns: ‘Librarian Ghouls’ APT Group Targets Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/librarian-ghouls-apt-group-targets-organizations/</link>
      <description>The Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group "Librarian Ghouls" has been actively targeting organizations across Russia and the CIS with sophisticated malware deployment campaigns, utilizing targeted phishing emails as their primary infection vector. They employ legitimate third-party software to mask their activities and hinder detection, deploying remote access tools, stealing sensitive credentials, and installing crypto-mining malware like XMRig on compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141411</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP Security Patch Day: 14 Vulnerabilities Resolved Across Various Products</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-security-patch-day-14-vulnerabilities-resolved/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-42989 (Critical), CVE-2025-42982 (High), CVE-2025-23192 (High), CVE-2025-42977 (Medium), CVE-2025-42994, CVE-2025-42995, and CVE-2025-42996 (Medium); Summary: SAP's June 10, 2025 Security Patch Day addressed 14 vulnerabilities across the enterprise software portfolio, including a Critical vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP allowing unauthorized access to sensitive system functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141405</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploitation of Critical Wazuh Server RCE Vulnerability Leads to Mirai Variant Deployment</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploitation-of-critical-wazuh-server-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wazuh; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24016, CVE-2023-1389 (TP-Link Archer AX21), CVE-2017-17215 (Huawei HG532); Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Wazuh servers, identified as CVE-2025-24016 with a CVSS score of 9.9, allows attackers to execute arbitrary Python code via maliciously crafted JSON payloads. The vulnerability has been weaponized by two distinct botnets to propagate variants of the notorious Mirai malware, targeting primarily Internet of Things (IoT) devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141375</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Stealer Rises, Android 0-Day for Sale, EDF Leak Exposed</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/fusion-stealer-rises-android-0-day-for-sale-edf-leak-exposed/</link>
      <description>The article highlights several concerning cybercriminal offerings on the dark web, including an alleged Android 0-day exploit, a stealer tool called Fusion Stealer, unauthorized VPN access to a US healthcare provider, admin panel access for multiple South American FinTech companies, and a massive alleged leak of EDF Energy's customer database. These discoveries emphasize the persistent and evolving threat landscape facing organizations and individuals worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060851</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensata Technologies Faces Disruption Due to Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sensata-technologies-faces-disruption/</link>
      <description>The article reports a significant cybersecurity incident at Sensata Technologies, involving an external system breach that compromised personal information of hundreds of individuals. The breach remained undetected for nearly two months before being discovered on May 23, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141366</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability in DanaBot Malware C2 Server Leaks Threat Actor Usernames and Crypto Keys</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerability-in-danabot-malware-c2-server/</link>
      <description>A severe vulnerability in the command-and-control (C2) infrastructure of the DanaBot malware has been discovered, allowing for the exposure of usernames and cryptographic keys used by malicious operators. This breach could provide cybersecurity defenders with a rare glimpse into the inner workings of DanaBot operations and enable more effective disruption of this persistent banking trojan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141390</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
