<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:06:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti warns of critical Neurons for ITSM auth bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Neurons for ITSM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22462, CVE-2025-22460; Summary: The vulnerability (CVE-2025-22462) is a critical authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to gain administrative access to unpatched systems in low-complexity attacks. Ivanti also patched a default credentials security flaw (CVE-2025-22460) in its Cloud Services Appliance (CSA) that can let local authenticated attackers escalate privileges on vulnerable systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked APTs Exploit SAP CVE-2025-31324 to Breach 581 Critical Systems Worldwide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A critical security flaw in SAP NetWeaver is being exploited by multiple China-nexus nation-state actors to target critical infrastructure networks. The vulnerability allows for remote code execution and has been used to deploy web shells, reverse shells, and backdoors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Intel CPU flaws leak sensitive data from privileged memory</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intel CPUs; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45332; Summary: A "Branch Privilege Injection" flaw in modern Intel CPUs allows attackers to leak sensitive data from memory regions allocated to privileged software. The vulnerability, tracked under CVE-2024-45332, is a race condition on the branch predictor subsystem and affects all Intel CPUs from the 9th generation onward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI Package Posing as Solana Tool Stole Source Code in 761 Downloads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Python Package Index (PyPI) repository had a malicious package named solana-token that was designed to steal source code and developer secrets. When installed, it attempts to exfiltrate data from the developer's machine to a hard-coded IP address, suggesting a target on developers creating their own blockchains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft will update Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has extended its support for Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028, allowing users to continue receiving security updates and using the applications without having to upgrade to Windows 11 immediately. The decision comes as many users are reluctant to switch due to requirements such as TPM 2.0 support. The company will also provide updates beyond October 2025 for Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) and Long-Term Servicing Branch (LTSB) releases, catering to specialized devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increase Red Team Operations 10X with Adversarial Exposure Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of traditional red team engagements in identifying critical security gaps and proposes an alternative approach called Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV). AEV combines Breach and Attack Simulation (BAS) and Automated Penetration Testing to provide continuous, scalable, and automated offensive testing. This approach allows for repeatable and on-demand testing, enabling faster remediation, continuous benchmarking, and the agility to respond to new threats without waiting for the next audit or assessment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks &amp; Spencer Confirms Customer Data Breach in Recent Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/marks-spencer-confirms-customer-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A cyber attack against Marks &amp; Spencer (M&amp;S) has compromised customer personal data, including names, dates of birth, telephone numbers, home addresses, and online order histories. The attackers used a "double extortion" method, exfiltrating sensitive data and encrypting company systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135277</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;S says customer data stolen in cyberattack, forces password resets</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</link>
      <description>Marks and Spencer (M&amp;S) confirmed a cyberattack occurred on April 22, 2025, involving DragonForce ransomware affiliates using the Scattered Spider social engineering tactic. The attackers stole sensitive customer information, including full names, email addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, dates of birth, online order history, household information, and "masked" payment card details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Workplace Apps Flaws Allow Hackers to Gain Elevated Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zoom-workplace-apps-flaws-allow-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zoom Workplace Apps; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30663, CVE-2025-30664, CVE-2025-30665, CVE-2025-30666, CVE-2025-46785; Summary: The Zoom Workplace Apps contain seven newly discovered vulnerabilities, including a high-severity Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability that could lead to privilege escalation when exploited successfully. The vulnerabilities include improper neutralization of special elements, NULL pointer dereference, and buffer over-read flaws, which could potentially allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, elevate privileges, or cause denial of service conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135248</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Published for macOS Sandbox Escape Vulnerability (CVE-2025-31258)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/macos-sandbox-escape-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31258; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-31258, is a sandbox escape flaw that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code outside application sandbox constraints. It affects macOS Ventura 13.4 through Sonoma 14.2 and can be exploited by launching a malicious app, which could grant read/write access to protected directories like ~/Library and limited command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135083</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Hackers Caught Exploiting Old Routers as Proxy Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/four-hackers-caught-exploiting-old-routers/</link>
      <description>The article reports a global cybercrime scheme that hijacked outdated wireless routers to create malicious proxy networks, generating over $46 million by selling access to infected devices. The scheme exploited security vulnerabilities in older-model routers and allowed the hackers to covertly reconfigure them and resell access through subscription-based platforms.

FYSA: Threat actors targeted residential and business routers, including devices in Oklahoma, by exploiting security vulnerabilities to install malicious firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135172</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents that autonomously trade cryptocurrency aren’t ready for prime time</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/ai-agents-that-autonomously-trade-cryptocurrency-arent-ready-for-prime-time/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ChatGPT, Gemini; CVE(s): None; Summary: An untrusted user can plant false memories in the long-term conversation memory of ChatGPT or similar LLM-based agents, causing the chatbot to send all user input to an attacker-controlled channel. This vulnerability was demonstrated through a proof-of-concept attack that abused the built-in conversation memory feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/ai-agents-that-autonomously-trade-cryptocurrency-arent-ready-for-prime-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F5 BIG-IP Vulnerability Allows Remote Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/f5-big-ip-vulnerability-allows-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: F5; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31644; Summary: The vulnerability allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary system commands, bypassing security boundaries, by exploiting an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint and BIG-IP TMOS Shell command. This can enable attackers to create or delete files, execute system commands, and create a significant security bypass mechanism with a CVSS v3.1 score of 8.7 and a CVSS v4.0 score.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135092</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Launches Supply Chain Attacks on UK Retail Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scattered-spider-launches-supply-chain-attacks/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider is a financially motivated threat actor targeting UK retail organizations with sophisticated social engineering and technical exploitation tactics. They leverage third-party vendor dependencies, seasonal vulnerabilities, and advanced techniques like cloud exploitation and endpoint detection evasion to gain initial access and persist within networks. Their attacks often involve ransomware deployment, victim communication pressure, and data exfiltration tools, posing a significant risk to high-impact targets during critical sales periods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135217</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Service Suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache HTTP Server, Hitachi Energy Service Suite; CVEs: CVE-2022-26377, CVE-2023-31122, and others (see below); CVSS scores: 5.3-8.7.

A comprehensive list of vulnerabilities affecting the Apache HTTP Server and Hitachi Energy Service Suite has been published. The affected products are versions prior to 2.4.55. The listed CVEs include:

* CVE-2022-26377: An inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP request smuggling') vulnerability in mod_proxy_ajp that allows an attacker to smuggle requests to the AJP server it forwards requests to.
* CVE-2023-31122: Another inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP request smuggling') vulnerability in mod_proxy_ajp that also allows an attacker to smuggle requests to the AJP server it forwards requests to.

The other CVEs listed include:

* CVE-2022-37436
* CVE-2023-43622
* CVE-2022-28614
* CVE-2022-28330

These vulnerabilities have been assigned CVSS scores ranging from 5.3 to 8.7, indicating varying levels of severity.

Recommendations:

1. Update to version 9.8.1.4 or later.
2. Implement security practices and firewall configurations to help protect process control networks from external attacks.
3. Ensure that process control systems are physically protected from unauthorized personnel, have no direct connections to the Internet, and are separated from other networks by a firewall system with a minimal number of exposed ports.

No known public exploitation specifically targeting these vulnerabilities has been reported to CISA at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23352</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy MACH GWS Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy MACH GWS products; CVE(s): CVE-2024-4872, CVE-2024-3980, CVE-2024-3982, CVE-2024-7940; Summary: The MACH GWS product contains multiple vulnerabilities that allow an attacker to inject code, read or modify files, hijack user sessions, or access exposed ports without authentication. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could result in a range of impacts, including the ability to access or modify system files or other critical files, hijack user sessions, or inject code towards persistent data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23354</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650/SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650/SAM600-IO Series; CVE(s): CVE-2023-4518; Summary: A buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability exists in the input validation of GOOSE messages, allowing an attacker to reboot the device and cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23353</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABB Automation Builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ABB Automation Builder; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3394, CVE-2025-3395; Summary: Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource vulnerabilities in Automation Builder allow an attacker to overrule user management. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized access and changes to automation projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23355</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Abuse PyInstaller to Deploy Stealthy macOS Infostealer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-abuse-pyinstaller-to-deploy-stealthy/</link>
      <description>A novel macOS infostealer that exploits PyInstaller has been identified. The malware uses strings like ‘_MEIPASS’ to indicate embedded archives extracted at runtime and orchestrates malicious logic through PyInstaller's bootloader. It exhibits nefarious behaviors including AppleScript dialogs coercing user passwords, system volume mutting, and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135204</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake Defense in the Age of AI</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deepfake-defense-in-age-of-ai.html</link>
      <description>AI-generated social engineering attacks are increasingly sophisticated and prevalent, utilizing large language models (LLMs) to impersonate trusted individuals. Attackers use voice phishing (vishing) tactics to automate social engineering at scale, posing a significant threat to trust in virtual collaboration platforms.

FYSA: Threat actors are leveraging generative AI to impersonate trusted individuals, automating social engineering tactics and driving a surge in voice phishing attacks. This trend is fueled by the convergence of AI-driven deception, virtual collaboration tools that assume trust, and defenses that rely on probability rather than proof.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deepfake-defense-in-age-of-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Konni APT Targets Ukraine with Malware to track Russian Invasion Progress</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/north-korean-konni-apt-targets-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>The North Korea-linked threat actor, Konni APT, has been attributed to a phishing campaign targeting government entities in Ukraine. The goal of the campaign is to collect intelligence on the "trajectory of the Russian invasion." The threat group, also known as Opal Sleet, Osmium, TA406, and Vedalia, has a history of targeting entities in South Korea, the United States, and Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/north-korean-konni-apt-targets-ukraine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PupkinStealer Targets Windows Users to Steal Browser Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pupkinstealer-targets-windows-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PupkinStealer; CVE(s): None; Summary: A newly identified information-stealing malware, PupkinStealer, targets Windows users by stealing sensitive data including browser credentials, desktop documents, and full-screen screenshots. It uses Telegram's Bot API for data exfiltration and relies on social engineering tactics to trick victims into executing the malicious file. The malware can pilfer login credentials from Chromium-based browsers, hijack Telegram sessions, extract authentication tokens from Discord clients, and capture desktop screenshots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135176</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeated Firmware Key-Management Failures Undermine Intel Boot Guard and UEFI Secure Boot</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/repeated-firmware-key-management-failures/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: UEFI firmware ecosystem; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3052, None; Summary: The security of the UEFI firmware ecosystem has been questioned due to persistent cryptographic key management issues. Private keys have been exposed and unpatched vulnerabilities affecting millions of devices across vendors like Lenovo, MSI, Gigabyte, and Supermicro have been found. These issues leave systems open to pre-OS malware and bootkit attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135145</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INE Security Alert: Top 5 Takeaways from RSAC 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ine-security-alert-top-5-takeaways-from-rsac-2025/</link>
      <description>INE Security provides comprehensive training and certification programs to address top cybersecurity priorities, including AI security, multi-cloud vulnerabilities, zero-trust architecture, crisis response, and continuous skill development. The company's platform offers hands-on labs, cutting-edge technology, and world-class instructors to help teams develop the expertise needed to address modern cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135179</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Flags Hidden Functionality Flaw in TeleMessage TM SGNL on KEV List</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-flags-hidden-functionality-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage TM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47729; Summary: A critical hidden functionality vulnerability in TeleMessage's archiving backend exposes cleartext copies of user messages, enabling unauthorized access to sensitive communications. The flaw persists even if end-to-end encryption is implemented at the application layer, violating zero-trust principles. Organizations have until June 2, 2025, to apply vendor-provided mitigations or discontinue TM SGNL usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135166</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Flags Hidden Functionality Flaw in TeleMessage TM SGNL on KEV List</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-flags-hidden-functionality-flaw-in-telemessage/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage TM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47729; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthorized access to sensitive communications by retaining unencrypted message copies within the archiving infrastructure. This flaw enables exploitation of zero-trust principles, and CISA has given organizations until June 2, 2025, to apply vendor-provided mitigations or discontinue usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135166</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus One-Click Flaw Exposes Users to Remote Code Execution Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-one-click-flaw-exposes-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462 (8.4), CVE-2025-3463 (9.4); Summary: A critical vulnerability in ASUS DriverHub allowed attackers to execute arbitrary code with administrator privileges by visiting a specially crafted website, bypassing origin checking mechanisms. The vulnerability originated from an inadequate domain validation mechanism, allowing any website with a matching subdomain pattern to download and execute malicious files without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135127</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus One-Click Flaw Exposes Users to Remote Code Execution Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-one-click-flaw-exposes-users-to-remote-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462 (8.4), CVE-2025-3463 (9.4); Summary: A critical security vulnerability in ASUS DriverHub software allowed attackers to execute arbitrary code with administrator privileges through a simple web visit, bypassing origin checking mechanisms. The exploit chain permitted attackers to compromise systems running the ASUS driver management utility by visiting a specially crafted domain, and was patched within 10 days of being reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135127</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining a new methodology for modeling and tracking compartmentalized threats</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/compartmentalized-threat-modeling/</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be an analysis of a cyberattack campaign that involved multiple attackers and various tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The authors utilize the extended Diamond Model to clarify the distinct activities and roles of these attackers across different stages of the attack kill chain.

The article discusses a campaign dubbed "ToyMaker" that spanned six days, during which an initial access group compromised a server, exfiltrated credentials, and deployed a proprietary backdoor. Subsequently, a second wave of attacks began three weeks later, attributed to Cactus ransomware. The authors present several hypotheses regarding the relationship between the two waves of activity, ultimately concluding that the initial access group (ToyMaker) provided initial access for the Cactus group.

The article highlights various TTPs and indicators of compromise (IOCs) observed during the investigation, including differences in tools and infrastructure used by the two attacker groups. The authors' analysis suggests that there was a handoff of access between the initial access group and the ransomware actor, with shared stolen credentials facilitating the transition.

In summary, this article presents an in-depth analysis of a complex cyberattack campaign involving multiple attackers and TTPs, highlighting the importance of understanding the relationships between different attack groups and their TTPs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68093d6e0264c50001a1da04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining IABs: Impacts of compartmentalization on threat tracking and modeling</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/redefining-initial-access-brokers/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a threat analysis and modeling piece focused on initial access brokers (IABs) and their categories: financially motivated IABs (FIA), state-sponsored IABs (SIA), and opportunistic IABs (OIA). The authors provide an in-depth examination of the characteristics, tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), as well as the interactions between these different types of IAGs. The article aims to provide a clearer understanding of how IAGs operate within the broader threat landscape and how this information can be used for improved intrusion analysis and attribution.

The main focus of the article is on the differences between FIA, SIA, and OIA groups, highlighting their motivations, target selection, toolsets, and collaboration levels. The authors also provide real-world examples to illustrate these concepts and demonstrate how understanding these categories can aid in threat modeling and analysis.

In summary, this article does not discuss a vulnerability but rather delves into the realm of threat analysis and modeling, providing valuable insights into the world of initial access brokers and their various forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68093e340264c50001a1da12</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Remote IT Job Fraud Scheme Involving North Korean Nationals</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-uncover-remote-it-job-fraud-scheme/</link>
      <description>North Korean nationals have been indicted for orchestrating a scheme to secure remote IT jobs at American companies and nonprofits using stolen identities, funneling at least $88 million USD to the North Korean government over six years. The operation employed tactics such as fake companies, malware infections, and remote access software, with signs of coordination and tradecraft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135109</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Leverage Unpatched Output Messenger 0‑Day to Deliver Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-leverage-unpatched-output/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Srimax Output Messenger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27920, CVE-2025-27921; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the Output Messenger Server Manager allows authenticated attackers to upload malicious files directly into the server's startup directory. The vulnerability can be exploited to deliver malicious payloads, collect sensitive user data, and exfiltrate information from compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135093</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Strike 4.11.1 Released With SSL Checkbox Fix</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cobalt-strike-4-11-1-released-with-ssl-checkbox-fix/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cobalt Strike; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cobalt Strike 4.11.1 addresses several critical issues, including a module stomping issue that caused system crashes, resolves problems with the "Enable SSL" checkbox functionality, and adds clearer deprecation warnings for stomp reflective loaders. The update also ensures more stable operation during penetration testing activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135073</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moldovan Police Arrest Suspect in €4.5M Ransomware Attack on Dutch Research Agency</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/moldovan-police-arrest-suspect-in-45m.html</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability. It reports on law enforcement efforts to combat ransomware attacks, including the arrest of a suspect in Moldova and the targeting of suspected core members of a cybercrime group behind DoppelPaymer ransomware attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/moldovan-police-arrest-suspect-in-45m.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Releases Security Patches to Fix Critical Data Exposure Flaws</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apple-releases-security-patches/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS Sequoia 15.5; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31250, CVE-2025-31209, CVE-2025-31256, CVE-2025-31242, CVE-2025-31220, CVE-2025-31251, CVE-2025-31233, CVE-2025-31235, CVE-2025-31246, CVE-2025-31240, CVE-2025-24213, CVE-2025-31219, CVE-2024-8176, CVE-2025-31244, CVE-2025-31258, CVE-2025-31218, CVE-2025-31249, CVE-2025-31224, CVE-2025-24274, CVE-2025-31259; Summary: Apple released critical security updates for macOS Sequoia 15.5 addressing over 40 vulnerabilities across various system components, including kernel-level memory corruption risks, app sandbox escapes, and unauthorized access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135063</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Türkiye Hackers Exploited Output Messenger Zero-Day to Drop Golang Backdoors on Kurdish Servers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/turkiye-hackers-exploited-output.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Srimax Output Messenger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27920, CVE-2025-27921; Summary: A zero-day directory traversal vulnerability (CVE-2025-27920) in Output Messenger's version 2.0.62 allowed remote attackers to access or execute arbitrary files. The issue was exploited by the Marbled Dust threat group as part of a cyber espionage attack campaign, which also involved a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability (CVE-2025-27921).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/turkiye-hackers-exploited-output.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS DriverHub flaw let malicious sites run commands with admin rights</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asus-driverhub-flaw-let-malicious-sites-run-commands-with-admin-rights/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462, CVE-2025-3463; Summary: The ASUS DriverHub driver management utility had a critical remote code execution flaw that allowed malicious sites to execute commands on devices with the software installed. The flaw was due to poor validation of commands sent to the DriverHub background service and could be exploited by spoofing the Origin Header and using the UpdateApp endpoint to download and run .exe files from ".asus.com" URLs without user confirmation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asus-driverhub-flaw-let-malicious-sites-run-commands-with-admin-rights/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 upgrade block lifted after Safe Exam Browser fix</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-upgrade-block-lifted-after-safe-exam-browser-fix/</link>
      <description>Microsoft removed an upgrade block that prevented some Safe Exam Browser users from installing the Windows 11 2024 Update due to incompatibility issues. The issue was resolved by updating the Safe Exam Browser app before upgrading systems to Windows 11 24H2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-upgrade-block-lifted-after-safe-exam-browser-fix/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma Stealer Upgraded with PowerShell Tools and Advanced Evasion Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lumma-stealer-upgraded-with-powershell-tools/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolution of Lumma Stealer malware, which uses sophisticated PowerShell tools and advanced evasion tactics to deceive users. It targets sensitive data such as passwords, session tokens, cryptocurrency wallets, and personal information. The malware uses social engineering, exploiting user trust in CAPTCHA challenges, and executes malicious PowerShell commands, often leading to devastating data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134985</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Noodlophile Malware Spreads Through Fake AI Video Generation Platforms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-noodlophile-malware-spreads-through-fake-ai-video/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals have launched a new malware campaign using fake AI video generation platforms as a lure, targeting users by exploiting their enthusiasm for AI-powered content creation tools. The malware, dubbed Noodlophile Stealer, harvests browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and other sensitive data, and may also deploy a remote access trojan (RAT) like XWorm to gain deeper control over compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134958</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky Hacker Group Deploys New Phishing Techniques and Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-hacker-group-deploys-new-phishing-techniques/</link>
      <description>The North Korean state-sponsored APT group Kimsuky has been active since at least 2012, targeting nations like South Korea, Japan, and the United States with sophisticated cyber espionage campaigns. The article details Kimsuky's latest attack vector, which employs phishing, malware deployment, and obfuscation techniques to evade detection and penetrate sensitive systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134940</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT37 Hackers Use Weaponized LNK Files and Dropbox for Command-and-Control Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt37-hackers-use-weaponized-lnk-files-and-dropbox/</link>
      <description>APT37, a North Korean state-sponsored hacking group, launched a spear phishing campaign targeting activists focused on North Korean issues. The attackers exploited legitimate cloud services like Dropbox as command-and-control (C2) infrastructure and delivered malicious shortcut (LNK) files via phishing emails to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134904</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers now testing ClickFix attacks against Linux targets</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-now-testing-clickfix-attacks-against-linux-targets/</link>
      <description>A new ClickFix attack campaign has been spotted targeting Windows, Linux, and macOS systems, using social engineering tactics to trick users into running console commands that install malware. The attacks are attributed to the Pakistan-linked threat group APT36 (aka "Transparent Tribe").</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-now-testing-clickfix-attacks-against-linux-targets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Output Messenger flaw exploited as zero-day in espionage attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/output-messenger-flaw-exploited-as-zero-day-in-espionage-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Output Messenger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27920; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-27920) in the LAN messaging application, a directory traversal vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive files or deploy malicious payloads. The vulnerability was exploited by the Marbled Dust group to attack Output Messenger users linked to the Kurdish military in Iraq and gain access to sensitive data, impersonate users, and cause operational disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/output-messenger-flaw-exploited-as-zero-day-in-espionage-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moldova arrests suspect linked to DoppelPaymer ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/moldova-arrests-suspect-linked-to-doppelpaymer-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather reports on the detention of a suspect linked to DoppelPaymer ransomware attacks targeting Dutch organizations. The suspect remains in custody and legal procedures are underway for extradition to the Netherlands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/moldova-arrests-suspect-linked-to-doppelpaymer-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Linux Firewall IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194 Released: What’s New!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ipfire-2-29-core-update-194/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): expat 2.7.1 (fixing CVE-2024-8176), xz 5.8.1 (fixing CVE-2025-31115); Summary: IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194 includes security enhancements, performance improvements, and new features to safeguard networks, including updates for expat (fixing CVE-2024-8176) and xz (fixing CVE-2025-31115).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135019</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google to pay $1.375 billion to settle Texas data privacy violations</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/google-to-pay-1375-billion-to-settle-texas-data-privacy-violations/</link>
      <description>Google has agreed to a $1.375 billion settlement with the state of Texas over allegations it collected and used biometric data without consent, impacting millions of Texans; this settlement marks one of the highest recoveries against Google nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/google-to-pay-1375-billion-to-settle-texas-data-privacy-violations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage DDoS Attacks as Smokescreens for Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-ddos-attacks/</link>
      <description>DDoS attacks have evolved from being simple denial-of-service tools to sophisticated smokescreens masking more insidious breaches. Threat actors orchestrate high-volume traffic floods to distract security teams while executing quieter, surgical operations within the same infrastructure. This emerging pattern exploits both technical and human vulnerabilities during incident response, requiring a paradigm shift in defense strategies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134892</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Browser Extensions Pose Critical Security Risk, A New Report Reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/majority-of-browser-extensions-pose-critical-security-risk-a-new-report-reveals/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the risks associated with browser extensions in enterprise environments. It highlights that 99% of employees have browser extensions installed, which creates a significant threat surface. Many extensions have extensive permissions to sensitive data, and some are published anonymously or are outdated/unmanaged, making trust verification challenging and increasing security risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/majority-of-browser-extensions-pose-critical-security-risk-a-new-report-reveals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-Year-Old Proxy Botnet Network Dismantled After Exploiting 1,000 Unpatched Devices Each Week</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/20-year-old-proxy-botnet-network/</link>
      <description>A 20-year-old criminal proxy network was disrupted through a joint operation. The botnet exploited an average of 1,000 unique IoT and end-of-life devices weekly, turning them into proxies for malicious actors. The network enabled illicit activities such as ad fraud, DDoS attacks, and data exploitation, with over half the infected devices located in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134851</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
