<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:00:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware kingpin “Stern” apparently IDed by German law enforcement</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/german-police-say-theyve-identified-trickbot-ransomware-kingpin/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the cybersecurity threat actor known as "Stern", who is allegedly linked to Russia's intelligence apparatus and has been involved in ransomware attacks. According to experts, Stern's organization, Trickbot and Conti, has been highly effective due to its strong operational security and ability to remain hidden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/german-police-say-theyve-identified-trickbot-ransomware-kingpin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Linux Flaws Allow Password Hash Theft via Core Dumps in Ubuntu, RHEL, Fedora</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-linux-flaws-allow-password-hash.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubuntu, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Fedora; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5054, CVE-2025-4598; Summary: Two race condition bugs in apport and systemd-coredump allow local attackers to obtain sensitive information, including password hashes, by exploiting SUID programs and gaining read access to core dumps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-linux-flaws-allow-password-hash.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DoJ Seizes 4 Domains Supporting Cybercrime Crypting Services in Global Operation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-doj-seizes-4-domains-supporting.html</link>
      <description>This article is about a multinational law enforcement operation that took down an online cybercrime syndicate offering crypting services to threat actors. The operation seized four domains and associated servers, including AvCheck[.]net, Cryptor[.]biz, and Crypt[.]guru, which now display a seizure notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-doj-seizes-4-domains-supporting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US “insider threat” cybersecurity worker arrested… as insider threat</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/us-insider-threat-cybersecurity-worker-arrested-as-insider-threat/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article describes the story of Laatsch, a DIA employee who allegedly leaked classified information to an unknown contact. The FBI tracked down and arrested him after tracing his digital footprints, including his email accounts and IP addresses, which were linked to his residence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/us-insider-threat-cybersecurity-worker-arrested-as-insider-threat/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers are exploiting critical flaw in vBulletin forum software</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-flaw-in-vbulletin-forum-software/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: vBulletin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48827, CVE-2025-48828; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities, an API method invocation and a remote code execution (RCE) via template engine abuse, affecting vBulletin versions 5.0.0 through 5.7.5 and 6.0.0 through 6.0.3 when running on PHP 8.1 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-flaw-in-vbulletin-forum-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft now testing Notepad text formatting in Windows 11</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-now-testing-notepad-text-formatting-in-windows-11/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Microsoft's updates and new features in the Windows 11 Notepad application, including text formatting support for Markdown-style input. Additionally, it mentions the introduction of AI-powered text summarization and generation features, as well as other minor updates. There is no mention of a vulnerability or cybersecurity threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-now-testing-notepad-text-formatting-in-windows-11/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Exploit Microsoft Entra Billing Roles to Escalate Privileges in Organizational Environments</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-exploit-microsoft-entra-billing-roles/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID and Azure environments; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers can exploit lesser-known billing roles to escalate privileges within organizational tenants by creating and controlling Azure subscriptions in external tenants where they hold no direct administrative rights. This vulnerability allows for unauthorized reconnaissance, persistence, and potential privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139826</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police takes down AVCheck site used by cybercriminals to scan malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-takes-down-avcheck-antivirus-site-used-by-cybercriminals/</link>
      <description>The article reports on the takedown of AVCheck, a service used by cybercriminals to test whether their malware is detected by commercial antivirus software. This service was seized as part of Operation Endgame, an international law enforcement operation aimed at disrupting ransomware attacks and related infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-takes-down-avcheck-antivirus-site-used-by-cybercriminals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany doxxes Conti ransomware and TrickBot ring leader</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-doxxes-conti-ransomware-and-trickbot-ring-leader/</link>
      <description>Vitaly Nikolaevich Kovalev, leader of the Trickbot and Conti cybercrime gangs, is suspected of being a 36-year-old Russian. The article discusses his involvement in malware operations, including Trickbot, Bazarloader, SystemBC, IcedID, Ryuk, Conti, and Diavol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-doxxes-conti-ransomware-and-trickbot-ring-leader/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Google Apps Script to Host Phishing Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-google-apps-script/</link>
      <description>The Cofense Phishing Defense Center has uncovered a sophisticated phishing campaign that uses Google Apps Script to host deceptive pages. The attack leverages the trust users have in Google's platform to trick recipients into divulging sensitive information. Threat actors exploit this trust by embedding malicious content within a reputable domain, making it a particularly insidious form of social engineering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139809</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dadsec Hacker Group Uses Tycoon2FA Infrastructure to Steal Office365 Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dadsec-hacker-group-uses-tycoon2fa-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>This article reports a large-scale phishing campaign orchestrated by the hacker group Storm-1575 (also known as "Dadsec"), using a Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platform called Tycoon2FA. The campaign targets Microsoft 365 users, aiming to harvest credentials through meticulously crafted phishing pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139769</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Weaponized AI Tool Installers Infect Devices with Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-ai-tool-installers-infect-devices/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of malicious threats masquerading as legitimate AI tool installers, targeting users and businesses across multiple industries. The threats include CyberLock ransomware, Lucky_Gh0$t ransomware, and Numero malware, which exploit the growing popularity of AI solutions to compromise sensitive data and undermine trust in genuine AI tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139750</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your AI Notetaker Might Be a Liability: Insights from Stealer Logs</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/ai-notetaker-liability-insights-stealer-logs/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with AI-powered notetaking tools, highlighting the potential for sensitive data breaches and privacy issues. It emphasizes the importance of careful implementation, secure storage, and robust access controls to mitigate these risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060523</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pure Crypter Uses Multiple Evasion Methods to Bypass Windows 11 24H2 Security Features</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pure-crypter-uses-multiple-evasion-methods/</link>
      <description>Pure Crypter is a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) loader used by threat actors to deploy information stealers like Lumma and Rhadamanthys. It has demonstrated adaptability in evading Microsoft's security enhancements in Windows 11 24H2, including bypassing Process Hollowing-based injection using a patch of the NtManageHotPatch API in memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139738</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New EDDIESTEALER Malware Bypasses Chrome's App-Bound Encryption to Steal Browser Data</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/eddiestealer-malware-uses-clickfix.html</link>
      <description>A novel Rust-based information stealer dubbed EDDIESTEALER is distributed using the ClickFix social engineering tactic, compromising legitimate websites with malicious JavaScript payloads that prompt site visitors to execute a PowerShell script, ultimately deploying the infostealer. The malware harvests sensitive data such as credentials, browser information, and cryptocurrency wallet details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/eddiestealer-malware-uses-clickfix.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Exploit Microsoft Entra Billing Roles to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploit-microsoft-entra/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical security gap in Microsoft Entra B2B guest accounts allows external guest users to gain powerful control over Azure environments by leveraging billing roles and creating new subscriptions without explicit administrative privileges. This behavior is not a software bug but rather an architectural design choice, enabling guests to spin up new subscriptions and move them into target tenants, opening potential attack vectors for attackers who become subscription Owners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139787</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Exposure Management Right: Insights from 500 CISOs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/getting-exposure-management-right-insights-from-500-cisos/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the importance of exposure management in cybersecurity, highlighting the growing complexity of attack surfaces and the need for a strategic approach to managing vulnerabilities. It also emphasizes the need for prioritizing exposures based on their impact rather than solely focusing on exploitability.

FYSA: The article provides insights from Pentera's 4th Pentesting report, which reveals that despite increased pentesting efforts, attackers are still able to breach systems. It highlights the importance of exposure management in reducing cyber risk and emphasizes the need for a proactive approach to managing vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/getting-exposure-management-right-insights-from-500-cisos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Reveals Techniques for Defending Against Evolving AiTM Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-reveals-techniques/</link>
      <description>This article highlights the escalating sophistication of phishing attacks, particularly focusing on Adversary-in-the-Middle (AiTM) techniques. It emphasizes the importance of adopting phishing-resistant, passwordless authentication methods like passkeys, complementing MFA with risk-based Conditional Access policies, and user awareness training to recognize social engineering lures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139719</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Dark Web Markets</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/top-10-dark-web-markets/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the top 10 dark web markets, highlighting their features, categories, and user bases. These markets facilitate the trade of illegal goods and services, including drugs, stolen data, malware, and counterfeit documents. Despite frequent law enforcement takedowns and exit scams, new platforms continue to emerge with stronger security measures, making it harder to shut them down entirely. The article also highlights SOCRadar's Dark Web Report, which scans various sources to identify mentions of a company, employees, or assets on the dark web.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100045356</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Icinga 2 Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Obtain Valid Certificates</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-icinga-2-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Icinga 2; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48057; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Icinga 2's VerifyCertificate() function allows attackers to obtain valid certificates from the Icinga Certificate Authority, potentially impersonating trusted nodes and compromising monitoring environments. The flaw affects installations built with OpenSSL versions older than 1.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139725</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Gh0st RAT to Hijack Internet Café Systems for Crypto Mining</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-gh0st-rat-to-hijack-internet-cafe/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Korean Internet café management programs; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers have been targeting internet cafés in South Korea since 2022, exploiting specialized management software to install malicious tools for cryptocurrency mining. The attackers use Gh0st RAT and its droppers to seize control of systems and deploy the T-Rex CoinMiner to mine cryptocurrencies like Ethereum and RavenCoin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139701</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Security Update for 22H2 &amp; 23H2 May Cause Recovery Errors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-security-update-for-22h2-23h2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The KB5058405 security update has caused significant boot failures in some users running Windows 11 versions 22H2 and 23H2, especially in enterprise and virtual environments. Affected systems display a recovery error with code 0xc0000098 referencing the ACPI.sys file, which is essential for power management and device configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139724</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Study Uncovers Multiple Vulnerabilities in WeChat and IM Apps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerabilities-in-wechat/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WeChat; CVE(s): CVE-2019-11932, CVE-2023-41064, CVE-2023-4863; Summary: A single WeChat message can be leveraged for persistent client-side attacks. Attackers can exploit lax URL validation to craft malicious links, and file processing vulnerabilities allow remote code execution. Additionally, built-in browser components, such as the XWEB engine, are vulnerable to known issues like CVE-2023-41064 and CVE-2023-4863 in the libwebp component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139723</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICI NetFax Server Flaws Allow Attackers to Execute Remote Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mici-netfax-server-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MICI Network Co., Ltd's NetFax Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48045, CVE-2025-48046, and CVE-2025-48047; Summary: The NetFax Server has three severe vulnerabilities allowing attackers to gain root-level access through a chain of authenticated attacks. The flaws include default administrative credentials exposed in cleartext, stored SMTP passwords exposed, and improper input sanitization leading to remote code execution as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139636</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked Hackers Exploit SAP and SQL Server Flaws in Attacks Across Asia and Brazil</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-hackers-exploit-sap-and.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: The article discusses a critical unauthenticated file upload vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver (CVE-2025-31324) exploited by the China-linked threat actor Earth Lamia. The vulnerability allows attackers to establish a reverse shell and gain control of infrastructure under their control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-hackers-exploit-sap-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use AI-Generated Videos on TikTok to Spread Info-Stealing Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-ai-generated-videos-on-tiktok/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting TikTok to distribute information-stealing malware, using AI-generated videos posing as tutorials for unlocking pirated software. The campaign uses social engineering and advanced technology like AI to trick unsuspecting viewers into executing malicious PowerShell commands, leading to the download of malware strains such as Vidar and StealC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139685</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: NightSpire Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-nightspire-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NightSpire Ransomware; CVE(s): CVE-2024-55591; Summary: NightSpire is a financially motivated ransomware group that employs double extortion tactics, encrypting data after exfiltration. They target small to medium-sized enterprises across multiple industries and countries, exploiting public-facing vulnerabilities like CVE-2024-55591.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060476</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the "Department of No" to a "Culture of Yes": A Healthcare CISO's Journey to Enabling Modern Care</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-department-of-no-to-culture-of-yes.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges faced by healthcare organizations in balancing security requirements with the need for frictionless care delivery. It highlights the importance of integrating security and IT operations to enable a culture of yes, where security is no longer seen as a barrier but rather an enabler of modern healthcare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-department-of-no-to-culture-of-yes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized PyPI Package Executes Supply Chain Attack to Steal Solana Private Keys</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-pypi-package-executes-supply-chain-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Python Package Index (PyPI); CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious package named semantic-types was discovered in PyPI, which deploys a covert key-stealing payload targeting Solana blockchain developers. The attack leverages a backdoor that silently exfiltrates private keys, posing a severe risk to developer environments and CI/CD pipelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139644</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel Malware Evades Detection by Skipping PE Header in Windows</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/novel-malware-evades-detection-by-skipping-pe-header/</link>
      <description>Researchers have identified a new strain of malware that bypasses traditional detection mechanisms by omitting the Portable Executable (PE) header in Windows environments. This innovative evasion tactic makes many signature-based and heuristic analysis tools ineffective, allowing the malware to load its malicious payload directly into memory without relying on a structured PE header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139625</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safari Flaw Exploited by BitM Attack to Steal User Login Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/safari-flaw-exploited-by-bitm/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple (browser-agnostic); CVE(s): None; Summary: A new type of phishing attack, known as Fullscreen Browser-in-the-Middle (BitM) attacks, uses the Fullscreen API to create convincing overlays that mask browser interface elements, making malicious activity nearly undetectable. The attack works by tricking users into clicking a malicious link or button, which triggers a remote browser session and allows attackers to capture credentials and sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139638</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next.js Dev Server Vulnerability Leads to Developer Data Exposure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/next-js-dev-server-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Next.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48068; Summary: The Next.js framework has a vulnerability (CVE-2025-48068) that allows attackers to exploit the development server via Cross-site WebSocket Hijacking (CSWSH), exposing sensitive application source code. The issue is fixed in version 15.2.2, but developers must upgrade and configure their environments securely to mitigate the risk of similar exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139637</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Cisco IOS XE Flaw Permits Arbitrary File Upload — PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-xe-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20188; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Cisco IOS XE Wireless LAN Controllers (WLCs) allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files and potentially execute commands as root, granting full control over affected devices. The flaw arises from a hard-coded JSON Web Token (JWT) used in the Out-of-Band AP Image Download feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139592</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean IT Workers Exploit Legitimate Software and Network Tactics to Evade EDR</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-it-workers-exploit-legitimate-software/</link>
      <description>A North Korean IT worker infiltrated a Western organization using a remote-control system that exploited legitimate software and network protocols. The attacker used WebSockets for C2 communication and ARP packets for decentralized command propagation, making it difficult to detect with traditional EDR systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139607</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rust-Based InfoStealer Uses Fake CAPTCHA to Deliver EDDIESTEALER</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-rust-based-infostealer-uses-fake-captcha/</link>
      <description>A newly discovered infostealer, EDDIESTEALER, is spreading through social engineering tactics involving fake CAPTCHA verification pages. The malware, built in Rust, steals sensitive data such as credentials, browser information, and cryptocurrency wallet details by executing PowerShell scripts on Windows systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139597</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Sanctions Funnull for $200M Romance Baiting Scams Tied to Crypto Fraud</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-sanctions-funnull-for-200m-romance.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Philippines-based company, Funnull Technology Inc., and its administrator Liu Lizhi, who were sanctioned by the U.S. Department of Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) for providing infrastructure to conduct romance baiting scams that led to massive cryptocurrency losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-sanctions-funnull-for-200m-romance.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise Hit by Advanced Cyberattack: Internal Data at Risk</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/connectwise-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise ScreenConnect; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3935; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-3935) was exploited by a nation-state actor to execute remote code via ViewState code injection, leveraging unsafe deserialization in the ASP.NET framework. The vulnerability allowed attackers with privileged system-level access to execute arbitrary code on the server, and was fixed with the release of version 25.2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139588</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Tomcat CGI Servlet Flaw Enables Security Constraint Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-tomcat-cgi-servlet-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Software Foundation Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46701; Summary: A vulnerability in Apache Tomcat's CGI servlet (CVE-2025-46701) allows attackers to bypass security constraints by manipulating the case of characters in the pathInfo portion of a URL, potentially granting unauthorized access to restricted CGI resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139576</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentinelOne Recovers: Platform Back Online After Extended Outage</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sentinelone-recovers/</link>
      <description>SentinelOne experienced a significant platform outage that disrupted access to its commercial customer consoles worldwide, affecting the Management Console and managed response services. The incident was caused by a technical issue within the platform's infrastructure, not a cyberattack or security breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139556</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise Hit by Cyberattack; Nation-State Actor Suspected in Targeted Breach</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/connectwise-hit-by-cyberattack-nation.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a reported cyber attack on ConnectWise's ScreenConnect software that may have been perpetrated by a nation-state threat actor. While the exact details are unclear, the company has engaged Google Mandiant for forensic analysis and notified affected customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/connectwise-hit-by-cyberattack-nation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Disrupts Influence Ops Targeting Romania, Azerbaijan, and Taiwan with Fake Personas</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-disrupts-influence-ops-targeting.html</link>
      <description>Meta disrupted three covert influence operations originating from Iran, China, and Romania during Q1 2025. The campaigns targeted various platforms, including Meta's services, TikTok, X, and YouTube, using fake accounts, off-platform websites, and AI-generated profile photos. Threat actors leveraged proxy IP infrastructure to conceal their origin and coordination, posting content related to news, current events, and politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-disrupts-influence-ops-targeting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Sanctions Cloud Provider ‘Funnull’ as Top Source of ‘Pig Butchering’ Scams</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/u-s-sanctions-cloud-provider-funnull-as-top-source-of-pig-butchering-scams/</link>
      <description>The U.S. government imposed sanctions on Funnull Technology Inc., a Philippines-based company, for facilitating virtual currency investment scams known as "pig butchering," resulting in over $200 million in financial losses to Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71387</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla releases Firefox 139.0.1 update to fix artifacts on Nvidia GPUs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/mozilla-releases-firefox-13901-update-to-fix-artifacts-on-nvidia-gpus/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Firefox 139.0.1 update fixes graphical artifacts caused by re-enabled DirectComposition path behavior in Firefox 139, which exposed a graphics driver bug on NVIDIA cards under Windows 10, resulting in flickering or flashing videos and webpages. The issue was caused by the removal of a block list that prevented Firefox from using DirectComposition on mixed-refresh NVIDIA setups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/software/mozilla-releases-firefox-13901-update-to-fix-artifacts-on-nvidia-gpus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Authenticator now warns to export passwords before July cutoff</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-authenticator-now-warns-to-export-passwords-before-july-cutoff/</link>
      <description>Microsoft Authenticator app is deprecating its password autofill feature, prompting users to export their saved passwords or switch to Microsoft Edge. The change will occur in July 2025, with a gradual phase-out starting June 2025 for saving new passwords and ending August 2025 for accessing saved passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-authenticator-now-warns-to-export-passwords-before-july-cutoff/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-311: (Pwn2Own) Sonos Era 300 Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-311/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sonos Era 300; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1051; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Sonos Era 300 speakers without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the processing of ALAC data due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25865</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-310: Linux Kernel ksmbd Session Setup Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-310/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux Kernel; CVE(s): ZDI-25-310, ZDI-CAN-26505; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Linux Kernel by dereferencing a null pointer in the handling of preauth hashes. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, but only systems with ksmbd enabled are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26505</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise breached in cyberattack linked to nation-state hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-breached-in-cyberattack-linked-to-nation-state-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise ScreenConnect; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3935; Summary: A high-severity ViewState code injection bug (CVE-2025-3935) allowed threat actors with privileged system-level access to steal secret machine keys, enabling remote code execution on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-breached-in-cyberattack-linked-to-nation-state-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Nifty[.]com Infrastructure in Sophisticated Phishing Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-nifty-com-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have orchestrated a multi-wave phishing campaign between April and May 2025, leveraging the legitimate infrastructure of Nifty[.]com, a prominent Japanese Internet Service Provider (ISP), to execute their attacks. The campaign used trusted domains, abusing free consumer accounts on Nifty[.]com, and employed various techniques such as HTML padding, display name spoofing, and flawless AI-generated grammar to evade traditional filters. The attack highlights the limitations of legacy email security systems and underscores the need for advanced behavioral analysis and anomaly detection to combat sophisticated phishing attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139489</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new author has appeared</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/a-new-author-has-appeared/</link>
      <description>None, as this is not an article about a vulnerability or cybersecurity-relevant content. The article appears to be a newsletter introduction by a cybersecurity analyst who has recently joined Cisco Talos and discusses their background in anthropology and technical writing. They also provide information on emerging threats and offer insights into the human side of cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">683744165919a600012bd73e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PureHVNC RAT Uses Fake Job Offers and PowerShell to Evade Security Defenses</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/purehvnc-rat-uses-fake-job-offers-and-powershell/</link>
      <description>A new malware campaign delivering the PureHVNC Remote Access Trojan (RAT) has been identified by Netskope Threat Labs. The campaign leverages fake job offers and advanced technical evasion methods to bypass security defenses, resulting in full system access for attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139472</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interlock Ransomware Uses NodeSnake RAT for Persistent Access to Corporate Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/interlock-ransomware-uses-nodesnake-rat/</link>
      <description>NodeSnake, a Remote Access Trojan (RAT), has been used to compromise two UK-based universities. The malware, likely operated by the ransomware group Interlock, demonstrates advanced capabilities for persistent access and network infiltration, including long-term persistence, system reconnaissance, and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139501</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat actors abuse Google Apps Script in evasive phishing attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-abuse-google-apps-script-in-evasive-phishing-attacks/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using the "Google Apps Script" development platform to host phishing pages that appear legitimate and steal login credentials. The phishing pages are designed to look like a legitimate login screen, and the attackers use email masquerading as an invoice to trick recipients into handing over sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-abuse-google-apps-script-in-evasive-phishing-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Safari exposes users to fullscreen browser-in-the-middle attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apple-safari-exposes-users-to-fullscreen-browser-in-the-middle-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): None; Summary: A weakness in Apple's Safari web browser allows threat actors to exploit the fullscreen browser-in-the-middle (BitM) technique, making guardrails less visible and tricking users into typing sensitive data in an attacker-controlled window. The attack abuses the Fullscreen API, which is not properly alerted to users on Safari, unlike Firefox and Chromium-based browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apple-safari-exposes-users-to-fullscreen-browser-in-the-middle-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Target AI Users with Malware-Loaded Installers Posing as Popular Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cybercriminals-target-ai-users-with.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various AI tools (OpenAI ChatGPT, InVideo AI, and others); CVE(s): None; Summary: Fake installers for popular AI tools are being used as lures to propagate various threats, including CyberLock ransomware, Lucky_Gh0$t ransomware, and Numero malware. The fake installers claim to offer free access to the tool for the first year, with a monthly subscription of $95 thereafter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cybercriminals-target-ai-users-with.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sanctions firm linked to cyber scams behind $200 million in losses</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-company-linked-to-hundreds-of-thousands-of-cyber-scam-sites/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Treasury Department has sanctioned Funnull Technology, a Philippines-based company, and its administrator Liu Lizhi for facilitating virtual currency investment scams linked to over $200 million in losses for Americans. The company is responsible for generating numerous unique domain names and providing hosting services to cybercriminals, enabling them to host malicious websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-company-linked-to-hundreds-of-thousands-of-cyber-scam-sites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache InLong JDBC Vulnerability Enables Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-inlong-jdbc-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache InLong; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27522; Summary: A moderate-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-27522, allows threat actors to bypass security mechanisms in the InLong JDBC component, potentially leading to unauthorized data manipulation or information disclosure. The vulnerability occurs when the system fails to validate or sanitize incoming serialized objects, allowing attackers to craft malicious payloads that can trigger unintended behaviors such as arbitrary file reading or code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139474</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals exploit AI hype to spread ransomware, malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybercriminals-exploit-ai-hype-to-spread-ransomware-malware/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using AI tools as lures to infect victims with malicious payloads, including a PowerShell-based ransomware called CyberLock and a new malware named Numero. The malware is delivered via fake AI tool websites and can encrypt files or render Windows systems unusable.

FYSA: Threat actors linked to lesser-known ransomware and malware projects are now using AI tools as lures to infect unsuspecting victims with malicious payloads, including info-stealer malware operators and ransomware operations attempting to breach corporate networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cybercriminals-exploit-ai-hype-to-spread-ransomware-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal IP Set to Make Its Debut at Infosecurity Europe 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/criminal-ip-set-to-make-its-debut-at-infosecurity-europe-2025/</link>
      <description>The article announces Criminal IP's participation in Infosecurity Europe 2025, a major cybersecurity conference in Europe. The platform will showcase its AI-powered threat intelligence solutions and engage with security professionals to accelerate its entry into the European market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139478</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers are mapping your attack surface—are you?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-are-mapping-your-attack-surface-are-you/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of Attack Surface Management (ASM) in understanding an organization's digital footprint. It highlights how attackers use ASM to map out a target's infrastructure, and emphasizes the need for defenders to do the same to stay secure. The article promotes Sprocket Security's ASM tool as a solution to provide visibility into an attack surface, prioritize exposure by real-world risk, and close gaps before adversaries exploit them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/attackers-are-mapping-your-attack-surface-are-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 File Explorer Vulnerability Enables NTLM Hash Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-file-explorer-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24071; Summary: A vulnerability in Windows File Explorer allows attackers to capture NTLM authentication hashes by tricking users into extracting a malicious ZIP archive. The flaw exploits Windows Explorer's automatic file processing and can be exploited to gain access to networks for lateral movement or offline cracking of NTLM hashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139389</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Partner Hackers Leverage Fake AI, VPN, and Crypto Sites to Target macOS and Windows Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dark-partner-hackers-leverage-fake-ai-vpn-and-crypto-sites/</link>
      <description>The "Dark Partners" group has launched a sophisticated malware campaign targeting both macOS and Windows users through deceptive websites impersonating well-known AI, VPN, and software brands. The campaign delivers either the Poseidon Stealer (macOS) or PayDay Loader (Windows) malwares, designed for data theft and further propagation, after capturing user information and exploiting trust in popular brands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139426</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windows RAT Evades Detection for Weeks Using Corrupted DOS and PE Headers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-windows-rat-evades-detection-for.html</link>
      <description>Malware with corrupted DOS and PE headers was discovered by Fortinet's researchers, which challenges analysis efforts. The malware is a remote access trojan (RAT) that captures screenshots, enumerates system services, and acts as a server for incoming client connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-windows-rat-evades-detection-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fullscreen BitM Attack Discovered by SquareX Exploits Browser Fullscreen APIs to Steal Credentials in Safari</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fullscreen-bitm-attack-discovered-by-squarex/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Safari's Fullscreen API allows attackers to create a convincing Browser-in-the-Middle (BitM) attack that tricks victims into divulging credentials and sensitive information. The attack works by displaying a legitimate login page of an enterprise SaaS app in a fullscreen BitM window, making it difficult for users to notice the suspicious URL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139442</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alarming Rise of Cyber Threats in the NFT and Cryptocurrency Space</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cyber-threats-in-the-nft-and-cryptocurrency-space/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the growing cyber threats targeting the NFT and cryptocurrency space, with attackers focusing on emerging markets and major platforms like Binance and Coinbase. Phishing is a major concern, with 75% of phishing sites using HTTPS to mimic well-known platforms, highlighting the need for proactive security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060459</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Microsoft Entra Connect Update Replaces Legacy Login Methods</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-entra-connect-update/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the rapidly emerging field of quantum computing, highlighting its potential to revolutionize industries by solving complex problems. It explains key concepts such as qubits, superposition, entanglement, and quantum algorithms, providing a basic understanding of the technical landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139388</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PumaBot Hijacks IoT Devices via SSH Brute-Force for Persistent Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-pumabot-hijacks-iot-devices/</link>
      <description>PumaBot is a sophisticated malware that targets IoT devices with exposed SSH ports, exploiting weak security configurations to gain unauthorized access and establish persistent control. The malware uses brute-force attacks, self-updates via encrypted channels, and employs obfuscation techniques to evade detection, posing a severe risk to individual users and large-scale network infrastructures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139410</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Argo CD Flaw Exposes Kubernetes Clusters to Full Resource Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-argo-cd-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Argo CD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47933, GHSA-2hj5-g64g-fp6p; Summary: A critical cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Argo CD's repository URL handling mechanism allows attackers to inject malicious URLs that execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of authenticated users, enabling session hijacking or unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139387</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Cloudflare Tunnels to Launch Stealthy Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-cloudflare-tunnels/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cloudflare, Cloudflared; CVE(s): None; Summary: Adversaries have been exploiting Cloudflared, a legitimate tunneling tool by Cloudflare, to orchestrate stealthy cyberattacks. The vulnerability lies in the exploitation of Cloudflared's capabilities for maintaining persistent access in compromised environments, using it as a beachhead for lateral movement within networks after gaining initial entry through methods like VPN breaches or RDP exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139399</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santesoft Sante DICOM Viewer Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-148-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Santesoft, Sante DICOM Viewer Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5307; Summary: The vulnerability is an out-of-bounds read that could allow an attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code. A local attacker could exploit this issue to potentially disclose information and execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23440</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SiPass</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-148-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) and ACC-AP; CVE(s): CVE-2022-31807; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to upload a maliciously modified firmware onto the device, either locally or remotely. It is caused by improper verification of cryptographic signatures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23436</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Five Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/29/cisa-releases-five-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released five Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on May 29, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories aim to inform users and administrators of technical details and mitigations for the affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23441</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instantel Micromate</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-148-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Instantel Micromate; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1907; Summary: The Micromate device lacks authentication on its configuration port, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to execute commands and access the device's configuration. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized changes or data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23439</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consilium Safety CS5000 Fire Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-148-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Consilium Safety CS5000 Fire Panel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41438, CVE-2025-46352; Summary: The CS5000 Fire Panel is vulnerable to exploitation due to an insecure default account and a hard-coded password on the VNC server. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain high-level access to the device, potentially putting it into a non-functional state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23438</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SiPass Integrated</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-148-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SiPass integrated; CVE(s): CVE-2022-31812; Summary: The vulnerability is an out-of-bounds read past the end of an allocated buffer in affected server applications, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to create a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23437</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victoria’s Secret takes down website after security incident</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/victorias-secret-takes-down-website-after-security-incident/</link>
      <description>Victoria's Secret has taken down its website and some store services due to an ongoing security incident. The company is working to restore operations, but no further details are available on the nature of the incident or whether it was related to other recent attacks targeting retailers in the UK and US.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/victorias-secret-takes-down-website-after-security-incident/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT41 Targets Governments with New TOUGHPROGRESS Malware Using Google Calendar for C2</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/apt41-toughprogress-malware-google-calendar/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: APT41 (Chinese state-sponsored cyber threat group); CVE(s): None; Summary: APT41, a Chinese state-sponsored cyber threat group, has launched an advanced cyber campaign targeting multiple government organizations. The campaign uses novel malware dubbed TOUGHPROGRESS, which leverages Google Calendar as a stealthy Command and Control (C2) channel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060441</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UTG-Q-015 Hackers Launch Massive Brute-Force Attacks on Government Web Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/utg-q-015-hackers-launch-massive-brute-force-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2021-38647, CVE-2017-12611, CVE-2017-9805, CVE-2023-48022; Summary: The UTG-Q-015 hacker group has escalated their malicious activities, targeting government and enterprise web servers with brute-force scanning and blasting campaigns. They have exploited 0day and Nday vulnerabilities, including the listed CVEs, to launch attacks on high-value targets such as blockchain platforms, financial institutions, and AI research servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139367</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Dedicated SIEM &amp; SOAR Guide for Cybersecurity Professionals</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-releases-dedicated-siem-soar-guide/</link>
      <description>The article discusses best practices for Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) log ingestion, emphasizing the importance of prioritizing high-value log sources, filtering out noise, and ensuring compatibility across diverse systems. It also highlights the role of log instrumentation in applications and provides examples of AQL queries for querying SIEM data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139360</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Dell PowerStore T Vulnerability Allows Full System Compromise</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dell-powerstore-t-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dell PowerStore T; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36572, None; Summary: A series of vulnerabilities in the PowerStore T family can be exploited by malicious actors to compromise affected systems. The most critical proprietary issue involves the use of hard-coded credentials within the PowerStore image file, allowing a low-privileged attacker with remote access and knowledge of these credentials to gain unauthorized access, potentially exposing sensitive system resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139359</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce Exploits SimpleHelp Flaws to Deploy Ransomware Across Customer Endpoints</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/dragonforce-exploits-simplehelp-flaws.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, CVE-2024-57728, and CVE-2024-57726; Summary: Threat actors exploited multiple security flaws in SimpleHelp to gain access to an MSP's deployment, ultimately leading to data exfiltration and ransomware attacks on downstream customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/dragonforce-exploits-simplehelp-flaws.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Reveals Key TCP SYN Patterns for Detecting Malicious Activity</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-research-reveals-key-tcp-syn-patterns/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a study by NETSCOUT that analyzed TCP SYN segments captured by honeypot systems. The research identifies trends and anomalies in network traffic that could signal potential threats, including variability in IPv4 TTL values, suspicious patterns in TCP header lengths, and correlations between header lengths, window sizes, and sequence numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139352</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victoria’s Secret Website Taken Offline After Cybersecurity Breach</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/victorias-secret-websit/</link>
      <description>Victoria's Secret has taken its US website offline and suspended some in-store services following a major cybersecurity incident. The company has not disclosed the exact nature of the breach or whether customer data was compromised. Industry analysts note that the timing aligns with common tactics among cybercriminals, who often launch attacks during holidays when IT staff coverage is reduced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139318</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals camouflaging threats as AI tool installers</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/fake-ai-tool-installers/</link>
      <description>Talos has discovered multiple threats masquerading as AI tool installers, including the ransomware CyberLock, Lucky_Gh0$t, and a newly-discovered malware called "Numero". These threats are disguised as legitimate AI solutions and are targeting businesses in various industries. Threat actors are using SEO-poisoning tactics to manipulate search engine rankings and distribute these fraudulent installers through platforms like Telegram or social media messengers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6835f4ab9e70410001050ded</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Windows 11 might fail to start after installing KB5058405</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-might-fail-to-start-after-installing-kb5058405/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some Windows 11 systems (22H2 and 23H2) may fail to start after installing the KB5058405 cumulative update, displaying a "0xc0000098" recovery error in ACPI.sys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-might-fail-to-start-after-installing-kb5058405/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Spear-Phishing Campaign Targets Financial Executives with NetBird Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-spear-phishing-campaign-targets-financial-executives/</link>
      <description>Trellix detected a sophisticated spear-phishing campaign targeting CFOs and finance executives across various industries. The campaign uses social engineering, legitimate tools like NetBird and OpenSSH, and custom math CAPTCHA to evade security defenses. It creates a persistent backdoor on victims' networks for lateral movement and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139337</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ChoiceJacking Exploit Targets Android and iOS via Infected Charging Ports</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/choicejacking-exploit-android-and-ios/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various mobile devices from multiple vendors; CVE(s): CVE-2024-43085, CVE-2024-20900; Summary: ChoiceJacking is a new class of USB-based attacks that compromises Android and iOS devices by exploiting the dual-use nature of USB ports. The attack bypasses user consent and allows unauthorized data access, with three distinct techniques manipulating USB protocols and input channels to trick devices into allowing access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139317</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodpecker: Red Teaming Tool Targets AI, Kubernetes, and API Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/woodpecker-red-teaming-tool/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: Operant AI has released Woodpecker, an open-source automated red teaming engine designed to make advanced security testing accessible to organizations of all sizes. This tool automates red teaming across three critical domains (Kubernetes Security, API Security, and AI Security) and simulates over 50% of the OWASP Top 10 threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139316</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data broker LexisNexis discloses data breach affecting 364,000 people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-broker-lexisnexis-discloses-data-breach-affecting-364-000-people/</link>
      <description>LexisNexis Risk Solutions has disclosed a data breach that affected over 364,000 individuals. The breach occurred when an unknown threat actor stole personal information from GitHub using a compromised company account. The stolen information includes names, contact details, Social Security numbers, driver's license numbers, and dates of birth, but financial information was not accessed or stolen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-broker-lexisnexis-discloses-data-breach-affecting-364-000-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Assessment of the Alleged United Airlines SMS Data Leak</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/assessment-of-alleged-united-airlines-sms-data-leak/</link>
      <description>A Russian hacker platform posted a claimed data leak involving United Airlines, allegedly exposing 272 million records. The SMS messages shared included flight details and URLs that resolved to legitimate United Airlines service pages. However, the presence of "FakeDLR" markers in the samples raises questions about their authenticity, as they are typically associated with internal test environments or simulated traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060429</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Botnet Targets ASUS Routers by Injecting Malicious SSH Keys</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-botnet-targets-asus-routers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS routers; CVE(s): CVE-2023-39780; Summary: The campaign compromises over 9,000 ASUS routers by using brute-force attacks, authentication bypasses, and a known command injection vulnerability (CVE-2023-39780) to gain unauthorized access. The attackers establish persistence by enabling SSH access on a non-standard port and insert their own SSH public key for remote access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139302</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious WordPress Plugin Disguised as Java Update Infects Site Visitors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-wordpress-plugin-disguised-as-java-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Yoast SEO; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious plugin masquerading as "Yoast SEO" injects a deceptive JavaScript into WordPress websites, targeting non-admin users and generating a fake "Java Update" pop-up to trick visitors into downloading harmful software. The ultimate goal is to download a malicious executable file from an suspicious domain, allowing the malware to monitor system processes and detect new activity, including sending notifications to the attacker via Telegram.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139291</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 07:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Hackers Turn Google Calendar Into Command Hub Using TOUGHPROGRESS Malware, Google Alerts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-hackers-turn-google-calendar-into-command-hub/</link>
      <description>APT41 (HOODOO) has been uncovered to be behind a sophisticated malware campaign dubbed "TOUGHPROGRESS", which exploits a compromised government website and leverages Google Calendar as a command and control (C2) hub to manage compromised systems. The campaign involves spear-phishing, LNK files disguised as PDFs, encrypted payloads, and advanced evasion techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139279</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 06:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical OneDrive Flaw Lets Malicious Websites Access All Your Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-onedrive-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft OneDrive File Picker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The OneDrive File Picker has a vulnerability that allows popular web applications to gain full read access to users' entire OneDrive accounts due to excessive OAuth permissions and insecure token management. This design flaw enables apps like ChatGPT, Slack, Trello, and ClickUp to potentially read every file and folder in the user's OneDrive account without explicit permission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139293</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 06:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese APT41 Exploits Google Calendar for Malware Command-and-Control Operations</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-apt41-exploits-google-calendar.html</link>
      <description>APT41, a Chinese state-sponsored threat actor, used malware called TOUGHPROGRESS that leverages Google Calendar for command-and-control (C2) to target multiple government entities and organizations. The malware uses stealth and evasion techniques, including memory-only payloads, encryption, compression, and control flow obfuscation, to carry out specific functions such as process hollowing and injecting the final payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-apt41-exploits-google-calendar.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100,000 WordPress Sites at Risk from Critical CVSS 10.0 Vulnerability in Wishlist Plugin</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/over-100000-wordpress-sites-at-risk.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TI WooCommerce Wishlist; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47577; Summary: The TI WooCommerce Wishlist plugin for WordPress contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability (CVE-2025-47577) that allows attackers to upload malicious files, including PHP files, which could lead to remote code execution. The vulnerability affects all versions of the plugin below and including 2.9.2, and there is currently no patch available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/over-100000-wordpress-sites-at-risk.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058481 update brings seconds back to calendar flyout</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058481-update-brings-seconds-back-to-calendar-flyout/</link>
      <description>This article is about the release of an optional cumulative update (KB5058481) for Windows 10 22H2. The update brings back seconds to the time display in the calendar flyout and includes several other changes, such as enhanced Rich Calendar features and fixes for various issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058481-update-brings-seconds-back-to-calendar-flyout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5058499 update rolls out new Share and Click to Do features</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058499-update-rolls-out-new-share-and-click-to-do-features/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various changes and fixes made available in Windows 11 KB5058499 update. This update includes 30 new features and fixes, addressing issues such as blurry CJK text at 96 DPI, unresponsive game titles after upgrading to 24H2, and improved performance for multi-user, multi-lingual, and remote desktop usage.

The article also highlights various new features, including the ability to make last-minute edits on images shared through Windows Share, an in-product experience for voice access, and improved accessibility settings. Additionally, it mentions that some fixes are available immediately with the KB5058502 update, which addresses issues such as blue screen errors after resuming from sleep or hybrid-booting.

There is no discussion of vulnerabilities (software, hardware, or firmware) in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058499-update-rolls-out-new-share-and-click-to-do-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Asus routers are being hit with stealthy, persistent backdoors</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/thousands-of-asus-routers-are-being-hit-with-stealthy-persistent-backdoors/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Asus routers; CVE(s): CVE-2023-39780; Summary: The vulnerability allows for the execution of system commands and is exploited by backdooring the devices, potentially allowing attackers to access the device. The attack vector is detected through SSH settings in the configuration panel or system logs indicating access from specific IP addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/thousands-of-asus-routers-are-being-hit-with-stealthy-persistent-backdoors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT41 malware abuses Google Calendar for stealthy C2 communication</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apt41-malware-abuses-google-calendar-for-stealthy-c2-communication/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new malware named 'ToughProgress' used by the Chinese APT41 hacking group, which exploits Google Calendar for command-and-control (C2) operations. The malware uses a legitimate cloud service to communicate with the attacker, making it difficult to detect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apt41-malware-abuses-google-calendar-for-stealthy-c2-communication/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 22:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-309: (Pwn2Own) Canon imageCLASS MF656Cdw sfpcmAuthenticateSecAdmin Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-309/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Canon imageCLASS MF656Cdw; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2146; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Canon imageCLASS MF656Cdw printers without authentication. The issue exists within the sfpcmAuthenticateSecAdmin function due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a stack-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25779</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PumaBot botnet brute forces SSH credentials to breach devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-pumabot-botnet-brute-forces-ssh-credentials-to-breach-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a newly discovered Go-based Linux botnet malware named PumaBot that targets specific IoT devices by brute-forcing SSH credentials. The malware receives a list of target IPs from its command-and-control (C2) server and attempts to perform brute-force login attempts on port 22 for open SSH access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-pumabot-botnet-brute-forces-ssh-credentials-to-breach-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 19:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interlock ransomware gang deploys new NodeSnake RAT on universities</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interlock-ransomware-gang-deploys-new-nodesnake-rat-on-universities/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the NodeSnake remote access trojan (RAT) deployed by the Interlock ransomware gang against educational institutions. NodeSnake establishes persistence, collects metadata, and exfiltrates data to a command-and-control server, allowing real-time shell interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interlock-ransomware-gang-deploys-new-nodesnake-rat-on-universities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan Arrests 21 in ‘Heartsender’ Malware Service</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/pakistan-arrests-21-in-heartsender-malware-service/</link>
      <description>Pakistani authorities arrested 21 individuals accused of operating "Heartsender," a spam and malware dissemination service that allegedly operated for over a decade. The group's tools were connected to losses exceeding $50 million in the United States, with European authorities investigating additional cases. The operation was marketed as "Fully Un-Detectable" (Fud) and primarily used to run business email compromise schemes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71337</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanubis Android Malware Harvests Banking Credentials and Executes Remote Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zanubis-android-malware-harvests-banking-credentials/</link>
      <description>The Zanubis Android banking Trojan has evolved into a sophisticated threat targeting financial institutions, virtual cards, and cryptocurrency wallets. It uses various techniques to evade detection, including obfuscation, encryption, and social engineering tactics, allowing it to steal data, intercept two-factor authentication codes, and execute remote commands without user awareness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139155</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hacker Pleads Guilty in $19 Million Robbinhood Ransomware Attack on Baltimore</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/iranian-hacker-pleads-guilty-in-19.html</link>
      <description>A 37-year-old Iranian national, Sina Gholinejad (aka Sina Ghaaf), has pleaded guilty to involvement in an international ransomware and extortion scheme using the Robbinhood ransomware. The scheme caused significant disruptions and tens of millions in losses, including to the City of Greenville, North Carolina, and the City of Baltimore, Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/iranian-hacker-pleads-guilty-in-19.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Are Turning Ordinary Citizens Into Money Mules in a New ‘Rent-a-Bank-Account’ Scam</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-are-turning-ordinary-citizens/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting individuals by transforming them into unwitting money mules through a sophisticated fraud known as the "rent-a-bank-account" scam. The scam involves fraudsters enticing people with promises of quick cash in exchange for temporarily "lending" their bank accounts, resulting in severe criminal charges and financial risks for the victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139179</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botnet hacks 9,000+ ASUS routers to add persistent SSH backdoor</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/botnet-hacks-9-000-plus-asus-routers-to-add-persistent-ssh-backdoor/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS; CVE(s): CVE-2023-39780; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to add their own SSH public key and enable the SSH daemon to listen on a non-standard TCP port, enabling backdoor access to the device even after reboots and firmware updates. This is exploited by the AyySSHush botnet to compromise over 9,000 ASUS routers, including models RT-AC3100, RT-AC3200, and RT-AX55.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/botnet-hacks-9-000-plus-asus-routers-to-add-persistent-ssh-backdoor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Partners cybercrime gang fuels large-scale crypto heists</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dark-partners-cybercrime-gang-fuels-large-scale-crypto-heists/</link>
      <description>The "Dark Partner" threat actors are using a network of fake AI, VPN, and crypto software download sites to deliver Poseidon (macOS) and Lumma (Windows) infostealers and malware loaders like Payday. These malware tools steal cryptocurrency and sensitive data, which is likely sold on the cybercriminal market.

FYSA: The "Dark Partner" threat actors are using a network of fake AI, VPN, and crypto software download sites to conduct crypto theft attacks worldwide. The sites impersonate popular apps, including at least 37 apps and tools, some of which use generative AI technology to create illustrations and videos. The malware delivered by these sites includes Poseidon Stealer for macOS and Lumma Stealer for Windows, as well as Payday Loader for Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dark-partners-cybercrime-gang-fuels-large-scale-crypto-heists/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worldwide Operation Shuts Down Hundreds of Ransomware Servers and Domains, Ending Key Attack Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/operation-shuts-down-hundreds-of-ransomware-servers/</link>
      <description>International law enforcement agencies, including Europol and Eurojust, have conducted a historic operation called Operation Endgame to disrupt the global ransomware ecosystem. The operation targeted critical infrastructure, dismantling approximately 300 servers and neutralizing 650 malicious domains worldwide, as well as seizing cryptocurrency worth EUR 3.5 million. The effort also resulted in the issuance of international arrest warrants for 20 high-value targets believed to be key players in providing initial access services to ransomware operators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139146</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Blocked 2 million Malicious App &amp; $9 Billion in Fraudulent Transactions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apple-blocked-2-million-malicious-app/</link>
      <description>Apple has thwarted over $9 billion in fraudulent transactions across its App Store platform, with a focus on multilayered security approaches to combat evolving threats from deceptive apps and payment scams. The company's efforts include proactive and reactive measures, such as human oversight, automated detection systems, and termination of developer accounts engaged in fraudulent activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139131</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czech Republic Blames China-Linked APT31 Hackers for 2022 Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/czech-republic-blames-china-linked.html</link>
      <description>The article reports a malicious cyber campaign targeting the Czech Ministry of Foreign Affairs, attributed to a state-sponsored threat actor tracked as APT31. The attack is believed to have occurred since 2022 and affected an institution designated as critical infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/czech-republic-blames-china-linked.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce Ransomware Actors Exploits RMM Tools to Gain Access to Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dragonforce-ransomware-actors-exploits-rmm-tools/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp (MSP's remote monitoring and management tool); CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, CVE-2024-57728, CVE-2024-57726; Summary: A targeted attack exploited multiple vulnerabilities in SimpleHelp to deploy DragonForce ransomware across endpoints and exfiltrate sensitive data. The attackers gained unauthorized access to the MSP's RMM tool, which was used as a conduit for the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139122</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Lamia Hackers Exploits Vulnerabilities in Web Applications to Attack Multiple Industries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/earth-lamia-hackers-exploits-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Earth Lamia, an Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group with a China-nexus, has been targeting organizations across Brazil, India, and Southeast Asia since 2023. They use SQL injection vulnerabilities to infiltrate SQL servers and exploit known flaws in public-facing systems, employing tactics like DLL sideloading and privilege escalation tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139101</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evertz SDN Vulnerabilities Enable Unauthenticated Arbitrary Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/evertz-sdn-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Evertz; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4009; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-4009) in Evertz's Software Defined Video Network (SDVN) product line allows unauthenticated remote code execution, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary system commands as root. The flaw affects multiple Evertz devices and puts global media operations at risk due to the lack of authentication mechanism in the web administration interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139226</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian APT28 Hackers Attacking NATO-aligned Organizations to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-apt28-hackers-attacking-nato-aligned-organizations/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2023-23397 (Microsoft Outlook), CVE-2023-20273 (Cisco ASA/FTD devices); Summary: APT28, a GRU-backed threat actor, is conducting cyber espionage campaigns against NATO-aligned organizations, using tactics like spear phishing, password spraying, and exploiting known vulnerabilities. Their primary objective is to steal sensitive data, with potential for future supply chain disruption and business continuity threats during geopolitical tensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139046</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XenServer Windows VM Tools Flaw Enables Attackers to Run Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xenserver-windows-vm-tools-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix XenServer VM Tools for Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27462, CVE-2025-27463, and CVE-2025-27464; Summary: The vulnerabilities allow attackers to execute arbitrary unprivileged code within a guest Windows VM and escalate privileges, potentially gaining SYSTEM-level access. Affected platforms include Windows VMs running on XenServer 8.4 and Citrix Hypervisor 8.2 CU1 LTSR, with all supported versions before 9.4.1 being vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139115</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechia blames China for Ministry of Foreign Affairs cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/czechia-blames-china-for-ministry-of-foreign-affairs-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The article reveals that the Chinese-backed APT31 hacking group was behind cyberattacks targeting the Czech Republic's Ministry of Foreign Affairs and critical infrastructure organizations. This is part of a broader trend of malicious cyber activities linked to China, which has been condemned by the European Union and NATO allies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/czechia-blames-china-for-ministry-of-foreign-affairs-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Weaponize Fake AI-Themed Websites to Deliver Python-based infostealers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-weaponize-fake-ai-themed-websites/</link>
      <description>A malicious campaign orchestrated by UNC6032 has been distributing malware targeting users through fake AI video generator websites and social media ads. The malware steals sensitive data, facilitates information theft, and exfiltrates it via Telegram API or TCP connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139006</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zscaler to Acquire Red Canary, Enhancing AI-Powered Security Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zscaler-to-acquire-red-canary-enhancing-ai-powered-security-operations/</link>
      <description>Zscaler, a cloud security company, is acquiring Red Canary, a Managed Detection and Response (MDR) provider. The combined entity aims to integrate AI-driven Zero Trust Exchange platform with Red Canary's advanced threat detection and response capabilities, transforming security operations by detecting, analyzing, and responding to cyber threats at unprecedented speed and accuracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139121</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>251 Malicious IPs Target Cloud-Based Device Exploiting 75 Exposure Points</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/251-malicious-ips/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): CVE-2018-15961, CVE-2017-5638, CVE-2015-1427, CVE-2022-26134, CVE-2014-6271; Summary: A coordinated scanning operation was detected by GreyNoise on May 8, targeting 75 known exposure points across the internet. The campaign exploited various technologies, including Adobe ColdFusion, Apache Struts, Elasticsearch, Atlassian Confluence, and Bash, using a mix of exploit attempts and reconnaissance activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=139112</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce Exploits SimpleHelp Flaws in Targeted MSP Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dragonforce-exploits-simplehelp-msp-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57726 (CVSS 9.9), CVE-2024-57727 (CVSS 7.5), CVE-2024-57728 (CVSS 7.2); Summary: The vulnerability in SimpleHelp, a popular Remote Monitoring and Management tool, allowed attackers to exploit three severe vulnerabilities, including privilege escalation, path traversal, and arbitrary file upload flaws, which enabled the deployment of ransomware across multiple client environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060406</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft OneDrive File Picker Flaw Grants Apps Full Cloud Access — Even When Uploading Just One File</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-onedrive-file-picker-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft OneDrive File Picker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The OneDrive File Picker has a security flaw that allows websites to access a user's entire cloud storage content if successfully exploited. This is due to overly broad OAuth scopes and misleading consent screens, which could lead to customer data leakage and violation of compliance regulations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-onedrive-file-picker-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft introduces new Windows backup tool for businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-introduces-new-windows-backup-tool-for-businesses/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced Windows Backup for Organizations, a new tool simplifying backups and making the transition to Windows 11 easier. The tool helps back up and restore user settings after resetting or reimaging devices, reducing migration overhead and minimizing user disruption. It is available for Microsoft Entra joined Windows 10 or Windows 11 systems during limited public preview.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-introduces-new-windows-backup-tool-for-businesses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Weaponizing DCOM to Harvest Credentials on Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-weaponizing-dcom-to-harvest-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting Component Object Model (COM) and Distributed Component Object Model (DCOM) to harvest credentials on Windows systems without deploying payloads or triggering common security alerts. This attack vector, detailed in the RemoteMonologue tool, allows attackers to coerce NTLM authentications and capture user and machine account credentials, posing a significant challenge to organizations not on the latest Windows versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138970</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VenomRAT Malware Introduces New Tools for Password Theft and Stealthy Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/venomrat-malware-introduces-new-tools/</link>
      <description>A malicious cyber campaign using VenomRAT Remote Access Trojan (RAT) and other malware components has been uncovered. The campaign uses phishing tactics to distribute malware through a fake Bitdefender download page, with the goal of stealing credentials and compromising systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138953</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SilentWerewolf Attack Combines Legitimate Tools with Code Obfuscation for Stealthy Infiltration</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silentwerewolf-attack-combines-legitimate-tools/</link>
      <description>The SilentWerewolf threat actor has employed advanced phishing techniques to infiltrate organizations in Russia and Moldova, using social engineering tactics, obfuscation methods, and DLL side-loading to evade detection. They have demonstrated exceptional technical prowess, blending legitimate tools with sophisticated evasive measures to trick users into executing malicious files and initiate a complex infection chain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138934</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PumaBot Botnet Targets Linux IoT Devices to Steal SSH Credentials and Mine Crypto</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-pumabot-botnet-targets-linux-iot.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a botnet called PumaBot that targets embedded Linux-based IoT devices. The malware uses brute-force attacks against SSH instances to gain access and deliver additional malware. It then sets up persistence and executes commands received from a command-and-control (C2) server, allowing it to survive reboots and disguise itself as a legitimate system file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-pumabot-botnet-targets-linux-iot.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging FormBook Malware Threatens Windows Users with Complete System Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/emerging-formbook-malware-threatens-windows-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2017-11882; Summary: FormBook malware targets Microsoft Windows users by enabling attackers to gain full remote control over a victim's computer. The malware delivers payload through phishing emails and uses sophisticated anti-analysis methods, evasion techniques, and process hollowing to maintain persistence on compromised systems. It can collect sensitive information, execute files, download additional malware, or even reboot/power off the device, demonstrating its potential for complete system domination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138922</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft wants Windows to update all software on your PC</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-wants-windows-to-update-all-software-on-your-pc/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced a new update orchestration platform built on the existing Windows Update infrastructure, aiming to unify updating systems for all apps, drivers, and system components on Windows systems. The platform allows developers and IT product teams to onboard their updates via Windows Runtime (WinRT) APIs or PowerShell commands, providing a consistent notification experience and centralized app update history in the Settings app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-wants-windows-to-update-all-software-on-your-pc/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Infection to Access: A 24-Hour Timeline of a Modern Stealer Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-infection-to-access-24-hour.html</link>
      <description>Stealer malware is no longer just stealing passwords, but also stealing live sessions, allowing attackers to hijack enterprise sessions in less than 24 hours. The malware extracts browser cookies, saved credentials, session tokens, and crypto wallets, and exfiltrates data to Telegram bots or command-and-control servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-infection-to-access-24-hour.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Circulate Over 93 Billion Stolen User Cookies on the Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/circulate-over-stolen-cookies-dark-web/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the vulnerability of web cookies, which are small text files stored on devices by websites. Cookies can be used for tracking and data theft, with malicious programs like infostealers, trojans, and keyloggers harvesting cookie data from browser storage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138999</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimo Hackers Exploit CVE-2025-32432 in Craft CMS to Deploy Cryptominer and Proxyware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/mimo-hackers-exploit-cve-2025-32432-in.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Craft CMS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32432; Summary: A remote code execution flaw in Craft CMS allows an attacker to deploy payloads, including cryptocurrency miners and residential proxyware. The vulnerability was patched in versions 3.9.15, 4.14.15, and 5.6.17, but threat actors have exploited it to obtain unauthorized access and deploy malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/mimo-hackers-exploit-cve-2025-32432-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Ransomware Operator Arrested for Attacks on Government and Private Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/robinhood-ransomware-operator-arrested/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): "None"; Summary: The article describes the Robbinhood ransomware campaign that targeted U.S. cities, corporations, and healthcare organizations from January 2019 to March 2024. The attackers used sophisticated evasion techniques, including exploiting a vulnerable Gigabyte driver (CVE-2018-19320), to disable endpoint security software at the kernel level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138997</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Executive Guide on SIEM and SOAR Platforms for Rapid Threat Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-releases-executive-guide/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) and Security Orchestration, Automation, and Response (SOAR) platforms in organizational cybersecurity strategies. It highlights their benefits, including enhanced visibility, accelerated detection, and swift responses to threats, as well as the need for skilled personnel, ongoing tuning, and clear governance to ensure success.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138998</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple blocked over $9 billion in App Store fraud in five years</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-blocked-over-9-billion-in-apap-store-fraud-since-2020/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Apple's efforts to prevent fraudulent activity on the App Store, including blocking transactions, rejecting malicious apps, and terminating developer accounts. It also highlights Apple's success in preventing suspicious transactions and removing fraudulent ratings and reviews from the App Store.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-blocked-over-9-billion-in-apap-store-fraud-since-2020/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 10:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCRadar Named One of the 100 Most Loved Workplaces by Newsweek</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/socradar-named-one-of-the-100-most-loved-workplaces-by-newsweek/</link>
      <description>The article is about SOCRadar's recognition as one of Newsweek's 100 Most Loved Workplaces, highlighting the company's culture of innovation, growth, and inclusivity. The recognition emphasizes the importance of creating a workplace where employees feel valued and supported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060366</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Browser-in-the-Middle' Attacks Steal Sessions in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-browser-in-middle-attacks-steal.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses Browser-in-the-Middle (BiTM) attacks, which involve criminals controlling data flow between a victim's browser and a target service. This attack allows criminals to capture, record, and alter data exchange, making it possible for them to intercept usernames and passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-browser-in-middle-attacks-steal.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>251 Amazon-Hosted IPs Used in Exploit Scan Targeting ColdFusion, Struts, and Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/251-amazon-hosted-ips-used-in-exploit.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a coordinated cloud-based scanning activity that targeted 75 distinct "exposure points" earlier this month. The scanning efforts ranged from exploitation attempts for known CVEs to probes for misconfigurations and other weak points in web infrastructure, indicating that the threat actors were looking indiscriminately for any susceptible system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/251-amazon-hosted-ips-used-in-exploit.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATLAB, Serving Over 5 Million Users, Hit by Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/matlab-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses a ransomware attack that occurred at MathWorks, the developer of MATLAB and Simulink. The incident affected both customer-facing and internal IT systems, resulting in the unavailability of several online applications and internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138950</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes ICS Advisories Highlighting New Vulnerabilities and Exploits</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-ics-advisories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) Tool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26383; Summary: The ICU Tool contains a vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-26383, which can lead to memory leakage and exposure of sensitive data such as user credentials or cryptographic materials. An attacker with access to the affected system could potentially obtain unauthorized access or tamper with access control settings in sensitive environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138949</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Security Patch Addresses High-Severity Vulnerabilities Enabling Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-security-patch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5063, CVE-2025-5280, CVE-2025-5283; Summary: This update includes 11 security fixes, including use-after-free vulnerabilities in Compositing and libvpx, out-of-bounds write vulnerability in V8 JavaScript engine, and inappropriate implementation flaws in APIs like Background Fetch, FileSystemAccess, and Messages. These vulnerabilities could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, corrupt memory, or crash the browser if left unpatched.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138947</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Interaction libvpx Flaw in Firefox Allows Attackers to Run Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zero-interaction-libvpx-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5264, CVE-2025-5265, CVE-2025-5263, CVE-2025-5266, CVE-2025-5268, CVE-2025-5272, CVE-2025-5270, CVE-2025-5271, CVE-2025-5267; Summary: Mozilla Firefox 139 addresses several critical and moderate security vulnerabilities, including a double-free bug in the libvpx encoder that could lead to memory corruption and arbitrary code execution, as well as multiple flaws in the "Copy as cURL" developer tool feature and other issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138933</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INE Security And RedTeam Hacker Academy Announce Partnership To Advance Cybersecurity Skills In The Middle East</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ine-security-and-redteam-hacker-academy-partnership/</link>
      <description>INE Security and RedTeam Hacker Academy have formed a strategic partnership to accelerate INE's expansion in the Middle East and Africa (MEA) region, enhancing cybersecurity training capabilities across the market. The partnership aims to address the growing cybersecurity skills gap and empower the next generation of cybersecurity professionals in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138974</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Blocks $9 Billion in Fraud Over 5 Years Amid Rising App Store Threats</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/apple-blocks-9-billion-in-fraud-over-5.html</link>
      <description>Apple has taken measures to prevent fraudulent transactions, terminating developer accounts and rejecting submissions due to fraud concerns. The company also blocked illegitimate apps, stopped attempts to install unauthorized apps, and removed malicious content from its App Store charts and search results. These efforts have prevented over $9 billion in fraudulent transactions over the past five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/apple-blocks-9-billion-in-fraud-over-5.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce ransomware abuses SimpleHelp in MSP supply chain attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dragonforce-ransomware-abuses-simplehelp-in-msp-supply-chain-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, CVE-2024-57728, CVE-2024-57726; Summary: The DragonForce ransomware operation exploited a chain of older SimpleHelp vulnerabilities to breach a managed service provider's system and steal data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dragonforce-ransomware-abuses-simplehelp-in-msp-supply-chain-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce ransomware abuses MSP’s SimpleHelp RMM to encrypt customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dragonforce-ransomware-abuses-msps-simplehelp-rmm-to-encrypt-customers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SimpleHelp; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57727, CVE-2024-57728, and CVE-2024-57726; Summary: The DragonForce ransomware operation exploited a chain of older SimpleHelp vulnerabilities to breach a managed service provider's system, steal data, and deploy encryptors on downstream customers' systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dragonforce-ransomware-abuses-msps-simplehelp-rmm-to-encrypt-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian pleads guilty to RobbinHood ransomware attacks, faces 30 years</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iranian-pleads-guilty-to-robbinhood-ransomware-attacks-faces-30-years/</link>
      <description>Sina Gholinejad, an Iranian national, has pleaded guilty to participating in the Robbinhood ransomware operation that targeted U.S. cities and organizations over a five-year period, breaching networks, stealing data, and encrypting devices to extort millions of dollars. The operation often used administrator accounts or vulnerabilities to access victim networks and demanded payment through Tor dark web sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iranian-pleads-guilty-to-robbinhood-ransomware-attacks-faces-30-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Self-Spreading Malware Infects Docker Containers to Mine Dero Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-self-spreading-malware-infects.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Docker API; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new malware campaign is targeting misconfigured Docker API instances, transforming them into a cryptocurrency mining botnet. The attack propagates through worm-like capabilities to infect other exposed Docker instances and creates malicious containers to launch external attacks and spread the malware further.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-self-spreading-malware-infects.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Fake DocuSign Notifications to Steal Corporate Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-fake-docusign-notifications/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are leveraging the trusted reputation of DocuSign to deploy sophisticated phishing campaigns that harvest corporate credentials, infiltrate networks, and execute financial fraud. These attacks often employ social engineering tactics, such as mimicking legitimate DocuSign "envelopes" or using QR code attachments to deceive users into compromising their security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138905</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GRU-Backed APT28 is Waging Cyber War on NATO’s Digital Frontlines</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/gru-backed-apt28-cyber-war-on-nato/</link>
      <description>APT28, a GRU-backed threat actor, is conducting a campaign targeting critical infrastructure, government entities, and NATO-aligned organizations, particularly those supporting Ukraine. The campaign uses various tactics such as spear phishing, password spraying, exploitation of public-facing apps, and living-off-the-land binaries to gain initial access, maintain persistence, and evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060340</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Every CVE Deserves a Fire Drill: Focus on What’s Exploitable</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/not-every-cve-deserves-a-fire-drill-focus-on-whats-exploitable/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of traditional vulnerability prioritization methods, such as CVSS and EPSS, which score vulnerabilities based on technical factors but don't consider an organization's specific environment or controls. It proposes a new approach called exposure validation, which tests whether a vulnerability is actually exploitable in an organization's actual environment. This approach uses safe, non-destructive tools to simulate attacks and assess the risk of exploitation, taking into account factors such as existing controls and the importance of affected systems. The article highlights the benefits of this approach, including reducing the noise of false positives, improving prioritization, and increasing the effectiveness of security teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/not-every-cve-deserves-a-fire-drill-focus-on-whats-exploitable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Calls on Organizations to Adopt SIEM and SOAR Solutions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/government-calls-on-organizations-to-adopt-siem-and-soar-solutions/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of a comprehensive series of publications by international cybersecurity agencies to guide organizations in implementing and prioritizing Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) and Security Orchestration, Automation, and Response (SOAR) platforms. The resources aim to help executives and practitioners navigate modern cyber defense complexities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138803</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Clone Antivirus Site to Spread Venom RAT and Steal Crypto Wallets</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cybercriminals-clone-antivirus-site-to_4.html</link>
      <description>The article reports a new malicious campaign using a fake website advertising Bitdefender antivirus software to dupe victims into downloading the Venom RAT remote access trojan. The campaign targets individuals for financial gain by compromising their credentials, crypto wallets, and potentially selling access to their systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cybercriminals-clone-antivirus-site-to_4.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress TI WooCommerce Wishlist Plugin Flaw Puts Over 100,000 Websites at Risk of Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wordpress-ti-woocommerce-wishlist-plugin-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TI WooCommerce Wishlist; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47577; Summary: The TI WooCommerce Wishlist plugin contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-47577, allowing attackers to upload malicious files and achieve remote code execution. This flaw affects all versions prior to 2.9.2, with no patched version currently available, and requires the WC Fields Factory plugin to be active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138886</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Alerts on Void Blizzard Hackers Targeting Telecommunications and IT Sectors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-alerts-on-void-blizzard-hackers/</link>
      <description>A Russian-affiliated threat actor tracked as Void Blizzard, also known as LAUNDRY BEAR, has been conducting cyberespionage operations targeting NATO member states and Ukraine since at least April 2024. The group's tactics include password spraying, stolen credentials, and adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) spear phishing campaigns, posing a heightened risk to nations supporting Ukraine militarily or through humanitarian aid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138869</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Fake OneNote Login to Capture Office365 and Outlook Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-onenote-login/</link>
      <description>A persistent phishing campaign targeting Italian and U.S. users has been uncovered, utilizing free cloud platforms and Telegram bots for credential harvesting and data exfiltration. The attackers lack advanced technical skills but use a consistent exfiltration mechanism, relying on Telegram bot-based command-and-control infrastructure. The campaign's focus is on access brokering, selling harvested credentials to other cybercriminals, rather than direct exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138802</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATLAB dev confirms ransomware attack behind service outage</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mathworks-blames-ransomware-attack-for-ongoing-outages/</link>
      <description>MathWorks, a developer of mathematical computing software, has experienced a ransomware attack that caused an ongoing service outage. The attack affected the company's IT systems and online applications, leading to issues with account creation and login.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mathworks-blames-ransomware-attack-for-ongoing-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Craft CMS Vulnerability to Inject Cryptocurrency Miner Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-craft-cms-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Craft Content Management System (CMS); CVE(s): CVE-2025-32432; Summary: The Craft CMS has a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-32432, which allows unauthenticated attackers to deploy malicious payloads, including cryptocurrency miners and proxyware. The vulnerability affects versions 3.0.0-RC1 to 5.6.17 and has been under active exploitation since its discovery in mid-February 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138851</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT36 and Sidecopy Hackers Target India’s Critical Infrastructure with Malware Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt36-and-sidecopy-hackers-target-indias-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a state-sponsored Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) campaign called Operation Sindoor, orchestrated by Pakistan-aligned threat groups APT36 and Sidecopy. The campaign targeted Indian critical sectors using spear phishing, malicious scripts, website defacements, and data leaks, with the goal of destabilizing national operations through cyber espionage and hybrid warfare tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138834</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Notepad Introduces AI-Powered Writing with Copilot Integration</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-notepad-copilot/</link>
      <description>Microsoft's Notepad, Paint, and Snipping Tool are integrating generative AI features, allowing users to generate text, code, and images with prompts. This introduces concerns about data privacy, compliance, and potential exposure of sensitive information, as well as the need for robust access controls, regular audits, and clear policies to mitigate risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138801</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Cybergroup Toufan Targets Organizations to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-cybergroup-toufan-targets-organizations/</link>
      <description>Cyber Toufan, an ideologically driven group, has orchestrated over 100 breaches targeting Israeli groups, focusing on critical sectors like government, defense, finance, and infrastructure. They exploit weak or reused credentials, poor cybersecurity hygiene, and lack of multi-factor authentication (MFA) to gain initial access and execute stealthy lateral movement using native tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138806</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Velvet Chollima APTHackers Target Government Officials Using Weaponized PDFs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/velvet-chollima-apthackers-target-government-officials/</link>
      <description>The DPRK-linked Velvet Chollima APT group has launched a sophisticated cyberattack campaign targeting South Korean government officials, NGOs, government agencies, media organizations across multiple continents. The attack uses spear-phishing emails with weaponized PDF attachments and a novel social engineering tactic called "ClickFix" to trick users into running PowerShell commands as administrators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138792</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-146-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Johnson Controls Inc. iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26383; Summary: The ICU tool leaks memory, which could result in unintended exposure of unauthorized data. Successful exploitation may allow an attacker to gain access to memory leaked from the ICU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23434</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases One Industrial Control Systems Advisory</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/27/cisa-releases-one-industrial-control-systems-advisory</link>
      <description>CISA released one Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisory on May 27, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues and vulnerabilities surrounding ICS. The advisory is related to the Johnson Controls iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) Tool, but no further details are provided in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23435</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Guidance for SIEM and SOAR Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/27/new-guidance-siem-and-soar-implementation</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released new guidance for organizations on procuring and implementing Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) and Security Orchestration, Automation, and Response (SOAR) platforms. The guidance aims to help executives and practitioners enhance their organization's cybersecurity framework by improving visibility into network activities, detecting cyber threats quickly, and streamlining incident response processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23432</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Breach 20+ NGOs Using Evilginx Phishing via Fake Microsoft Entra Pages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-breach-20-ngos-using.html</link>
      <description>A Russia-affiliated threat actor known as Void Blizzard (aka Laundry Bear) has been attributed to "worldwide cloud abuse" since at least April 2024. The group targets organizations important to Russian government objectives, including those in government, defense, transportation, media, NGOs, and healthcare sectors in Europe and North America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-breach-20-ngos-using.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Drive-By Downloads: How to Stay Protected</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/the-rise-of-drive-by-downloads-how-to-stay-protected/</link>
      <description>Drive-by downloads are a type of cyber attack that installs harmful software on a device without the user's knowledge or permission. The attack takes advantage of vulnerabilities within old browsers, plugins, or trusted sites and can install malware payloads quickly and silently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060321</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Quickly Fixes Firefox Vulnerabilities from Pwn2Own 2025 with Urgent Patches</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mozilla-quickly-fixes-firefox-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4918, CVE-2025-4919; Summary: Two zero-day exploits were demonstrated against Mozilla Firefox's content process at Pwn2OwnBerlin, targeting the browser's JavaScript engine. The vulnerabilities allowed out-of-bounds memory access and raised the risk of remote code execution and sensitive data exposure. However, neither exploit succeeded in escaping Firefox's sandbox, a critical security boundary designed to prevent attackers from gaining full control over the user's system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138744</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Void Blizzard cyberspies linked to Dutch police breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-void-blizzard-cyberspies-linked-to-dutch-police-breach/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Russian-backed cyberespionage group, Void Blizzard, which has been linked to a September 2024 Dutch police security breach. The attackers stole work-related contact information of multiple officers using a pass-the-cookie attack and infostealer malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-void-blizzard-cyberspies-linked-to-dutch-police-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents and the Non‑Human Identity Crisis: How to Deploy AI More Securely at Scale</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ai-agents-and-nonhuman-identity-crisis.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with the increasing use of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in enterprise environments. Non-human identities (NHIs), such as machine identities, service accounts, and AI agents, are overwhelming corporate clouds, making it difficult to manage secrets effectively. The article highlights five actionable controls to reduce AI-related NHI risk: auditing and cleaning up data sources, centralizing NHI management, preventing secrets leaks in LLM deployments, improving logging security, and restricting AI data access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ai-agents-and-nonhuman-identity-crisis.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adidas Customer Information Compromised Through Third-Party Vendor</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/adidas-customer-information-compromised/</link>
      <description>A third-party customer service provider of Adidas was compromised by cybercriminals, exposing contact information of customers who interacted with the help desk. The breach did not involve sensitive information such as passwords or payment details, but may have exposed names, email addresses, phone numbers, and possibly home addresses and birthdates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138743</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Vulnerabilities in Hardy Barth EV Station Allow Unauthenticated Network Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerabilities-hardy-barth-ev-station/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hardy Barth eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 and cPP2 charging stations; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27803, CVE-2025-27804, CVE-2025-48413, CVE-2025-48414, CVE-2025-48415, CVE-2025-48416, CVE-2025-48417; Summary: The eCharge Hardy Barth cPH2 and cPP2 charging stations have been found to have several critical security flaws, including missing authentication, OS command injection, hard-coded OS backdoor user, undocumented web interface credentials, USB backdoor, SSH backdoor, and hard-coded TLS certificates. These vulnerabilities can be exploited to compromise the system, exfiltrate sensitive data, disrupt charging operations, and launch man-in-the-middle attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138742</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver RAT Malware Employs New Anti-Virus Bypass Techniques to Execute Malicious Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silver-rat-malware-employs-new-anti-virus-bypass-techniques/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a newly identified malware strain called Silver RAT, which is a remote access trojan (RAT) that leverages anti-virus bypass techniques to evade detection and compromise Windows-based systems. It uses process hollowing, dynamic API resolution, and obfuscated code execution to remain undetected, making it difficult for security tools to detect its behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138753</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover macOS ‘AppleProcessHub’ Stealer: TTPs and C2 Server Details Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-uncover-macos-appleprocesshub-stealer/</link>
      <description>AppleProcessHub malware has been identified as an information-stealing malware designed to infiltrate Apple systems and exfiltrate sensitive user data. The malware employs advanced tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) to evade detection and establish persistent communication with command-and-control (C2) servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138692</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 10:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIMP Image Editor Vulnerability Allows Remote Attackers to Execute Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gimp-image-editor-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GIMP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2760, CVE-2025-2761; Summary: Two high-severity vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-2760 and CVE-2025-2761) were discovered in GIMP image editing software, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with user privileges. The vulnerabilities impact users who open malicious image files or visit compromised websites, and can lead to remote code execution, data exposure, malware installation, or persistent system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138701</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employees Searching Payroll Portals on Google Tricked Into Sending Paychecks to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/employees-searching-payroll-portals-on.html</link>
      <description>Threat hunters have exposed a novel campaign that uses search engine optimization (SEO) poisoning techniques to target employee mobile devices and facilitate payroll fraud. The attackers use fake login pages to access the employee payroll portal and redirect paychecks into accounts under their control, exploiting weaknesses in home office routers and mobile networks to mask their traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/employees-searching-payroll-portals-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Server emergency update fixes Hyper-V VM freezes, restart issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-server-emergency-update-fixes-hyper-v-vm-freezes-restart-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses an emergency update from Microsoft to address a known issue causing some Hyper-V virtual machines with Windows Server 2022 to freeze or restart unexpectedly, mainly affecting Azure confidential VMs. The issue is fixed by the KB5061906 cumulative update for Windows Server 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-server-emergency-update-fixes-hyper-v-vm-freezes-restart-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat and AMD Team Up to Boost AI Processing Power and Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/red-hat-and-amd-team-up-to-boost-ai/</link>
      <description>This article is about a strategic collaboration between Red Hat and AMD to revolutionize artificial intelligence (AI) workloads. The partnership aims to simplify access to validated GPU Operators for enterprise users by integrating AMD Instinct GPUs within Red Hat OpenShift AI, a Kubernetes-based platform for building and scaling AI/ML models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138682</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android Malware GhostSpy Grants Attackers Full Control Over Infected Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-android-malware-ghostspy-grants-attackers/</link>
      <description>GhostSpy is a high-risk Android malware that employs advanced evasion, persistence, and surveillance techniques to seize control over infected devices. It has capabilities such as keylogging, bypassing banking app protections, screen capture, audio/video recording, GPS tracking, SMS interception, and unauthorized financial transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138665</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adidas warns of data breach after customer service provider hack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/adidas-warns-of-data-breach-after-customer-service-provider-hack/</link>
      <description>Adidas disclosed a data breach where an unauthorized party hacked a third-party customer service provider and stole some customers' data. The stolen information did not include payment-related information or passwords, but only contact information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/adidas-warns-of-data-breach-after-customer-service-provider-hack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SiPass Flaw Allows Remote Attackers to Cause DoS Conditions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/siemens-sipass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SiPass integrated; CVE(s): CVE-2022-31812; Summary: A critical out-of-bounds read vulnerability (CVE-2022-31812) affects all SiPass integrated versions before V2.95.3.18, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to trigger a denial of service condition and disrupting access control operations for organizations relying on SiPass for physical security management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138663</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 08:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arm Mali GPU Vulnerability Enables Bypass of MTE and Arbitrary Kernel Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/arm-mali-gpu-vulnerability-enables-bypass-of-mte/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Arm Mali GPU driver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0072; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Arm Mali GPU driver (CVE-2025-0072) allows a malicious Android app to bypass the Memory Tagging Extension (MTE) and achieve arbitrary kernel code execution. The exploit manipulates queue-&gt;phys fields to point to newly allocated GPU memory pages while maintaining user-space mappings to previously freed pages, creating a use-after-free scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138641</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit HTTP/2 Flaw to Launch Arbitrary Cross-Site Scripting Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-http-2-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple web infrastructure products; CVE(s): None; Summary: A study by Tsinghua University and Zhongguancun Laboratory has discovered critical vulnerabilities in modern web infrastructure related to HTTP/2 serverpush and Signed HTTP Exchange (SXG) features. These vulnerabilities can be exploited to bypass the Same-Origin Policy, allowing attackers to push malicious resources that are treated as legitimate by the browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138640</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Are Calling Your Office: FBI Alerts Law Firms to Luna Moth’s Stealth Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-are-calling-your-office-fbi.html</link>
      <description>The FBI has warned of social engineering attacks by criminal extortion actor Luna Moth targeting law firms over two years, using IT-themed calls and callback phishing emails to gain remote access to systems or steal sensitive data. The attackers have shifted tactics, now posing as employees from the company's IT department to gain access to devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-are-calling-your-office-fbi.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical GitHub MCP Server Vulnerability Allows Unauthorized Access to Private Repositories</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-github-mcp-server-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub MCP integration; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the GitHub MCP integration allows attackers to manipulate a user's agent via a malicious GitHub Issue, coercing it into leaking sensitive information from private repositories. The exploit occurs when an attacker crafts a malicious issue in a user's public repository, embedding a prompt injection payload that triggers a toxic agent flow and exposes private data through autonomously created pull requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138619</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Linked Hackers Target Tajikistan Government with Weaponized Word Documents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russia-linked-hackers-target-tajikistan.html</link>
      <description>This article describes a spear-phishing campaign conducted by the Russia-aligned threat actor TAG-110 targeting Tajikistan using macro-enabled Word templates as an initial payload. The attack chain is a departure from the threat actor's previously documented use of an HTML Application (.HTA) loader dubbed HATVIBE, and the goal is likely to gather intelligence for influencing regional politics or security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russia-linked-hackers-target-tajikistan.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Google Meet Pages Are Exploited to Deliver PowerShell Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-google-meet-exploited/</link>
      <description>A new wave of cyberattacks, dubbed ClickFix, exploits user trust in Google Meet by deploying fake meeting pages that trick victims into running malicious PowerShell commands. The attack bypasses traditional security measures and targets Windows and macOS systems, ultimately leading to the download and execution of a remote access trojan (RAT).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138622</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteobridge Web Interface Vulnerability Let Attackers Inject Commands Remotely</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/meteobridge-web-interface-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MeteoBridge; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4008; Summary: The MeteoBridge firmware has a severe command injection vulnerability (CVE-2025-4008) in versions 6.1 and below, allowing remote, unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. The vulnerability resides in the CGI shell script accessible at /cgi-bin/template.cgi, which processes user input without proper sanitization, making it vulnerable to command injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138552</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Reportedly Selling Over 500 Stolen Crypto Databases on Dark-Web Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-reportedly-selling-over-500-stolen-crypto-databases/</link>
      <description>A threat actor is allegedly selling a ZIP archive containing over 500 compromised databases related to cryptocurrency platforms. The leaked data reportedly includes user information, wallet details, balances, transaction histories, and email addresses connected to the accounts. This breach highlights the need for enhanced security measures in the crypto industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138561</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Deep Research Now Integrates with Dropbox and OneDrive to Retrieve Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chatgpt-deep-research-now-integrates-with-dropbox-and-onedrive/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the beta feature "Deep Research Connectors" in ChatGPT, which allows users to access and analyze live data from third-party applications such as Dropbox, Microsoft OneDrive, GitHub, Microsoft SharePoint, and Box directly within ChatGPT's interface. This integration aims to streamline workflows by embedding search and analysis functionalities into a single platform, while adhering to strict privacy protocols and offering varying levels of access based on subscription plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138509</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Issues on Silent Ransom Group Using Fake IT Support Calls to Target Victims</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fbi-issues-on-silent-ransom-group/</link>
      <description>The Silent Ransom Group (SRG) has shifted its tactics to impersonate IT department employees through unsolicited phone calls to trick individuals into granting remote access to their systems. SRG targets organizations across multiple sectors, including medical and insurance industries, using socially engineered phishing schemes to install remote access software and steal sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138497</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake DigiYatra Apps Target Indian Users to Steal Financial Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-digiyatra-apps-target-indian-users/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have been exploiting India's digital public infrastructure by setting up a deceptive phishing site, digiyatra[.]in, impersonating the DigiYatra Foundation. The site is designed to harvest personal user data and has been flagged by ThreatWatch360 as a potential threat to unauthorized data collection, public deception, and reputational damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138533</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katz Stealer Targets Chrome, Edge, Brave, and Firefox to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/katz-stealer-targets-chrome-edge-brave-and-firefox/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Katz Stealer; CVE(s): None; Summary: Katz Stealer is a credential-stealing malware-as-a-service that targets popular web browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, communication platforms, email clients, and gaming platforms. It conducts extensive system reconnaissance and data theft by extracting saved passwords, cookies, and session tokens, and employs advanced evasion mechanisms to avoid detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138480</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 Malicious npm Packages Exfiltrate Hostnames, IP Addresses, and DNS Server Details</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/60-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple malicious packages in the npm registry; CVE(s): None; Summary: A threat actor has published 60 malicious packages in the npm registry, which embed a covert script that gathers sensitive system data during the npm install process. The harvested data is exfiltrated to a Discord webhook, enabling real-time tracking of infected systems across Windows, macOS, and Linux environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138445</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy Database Client Tools on Targeted Systems to Exfiltrate Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-database-client-tools/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybersecurity experts have observed an increase in data breaches where threat actors are using legitimate database client tools such as DBeaver, Navicat, and sqlcmd to steal sensitive information. These tools, often used by administrators for database management, blend into normal system operations, making detection challenging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138406</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 70 Malicious npm and VS Code Packages Found Stealing Data and Crypto</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/over-70-malicious-npm-and-vs-code.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: As many as 60 malicious npm packages have been discovered, including 20 packages under three different accounts. The packages install with an executable script that targets Windows, macOS, or Linux systems and includes basic sandbox-evasion checks. The harvested information is transmitted to a Discord webhook, enabling a threat actor to chart the network and identify high-value targets.

FYSA: Threat actors have been discovered abusing open-source repositories for malware distribution, including malicious npm packages, Microsoft's Visual Studio Code (VS Code) Marketplace, and GitHub. The threats include supply chain attacks at scale, phishing campaigns, and cryptocurrency wallet credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/over-70-malicious-npm-and-vs-code.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpSuccessor PoC Released to Weaponize Windows Server 2025 BadSuccessor Flaw</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sharpsuccessor-poc-released/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): CVE-2025-XXXX; Summary: A privilege escalation vulnerability in the delegated Managed Service Account (dMSA) feature allows attackers to compromise Active Directory domains using tools like SharpSuccessor. The attack chain exploits default configurations and improper validation of the msDS-ManagedAccountPrecededByLink attribute during dMSA migration, enabling attackers to create a malicious dMSA object, manipulate Kerberos tickets, and gain Domain Admin privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138544</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle TNS Flaw Exposes System Memory to Unauthorized Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oracle-tns-flaw-exposes-system-memory-to-unauthorized-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30733; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote attackers to access sensitive system memory, including environment variables and connection data, by exploiting a memory leak in the Oracle Database Server's RDBMS Listener. The flaw affects Oracle Database Server versions 19.3–19.26, 21.3–21.17, and 23.4–23.7, with a CVSS 3.1 Base Score of 6.5, indicating a medium severity risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138521</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google claims users find ads in AI search 'helpful'</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-claims-users-find-ads-in-ai-search-helpful/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's introduction of ads in their AI mode and AI Overviews, claiming that users find them helpful. However, critics argue that ads can be misleading or disrupt the flow of content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-claims-users-find-ads-in-ai-search-helpful/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI plans to ship an interesting ChatGPT product by 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-plans-to-ship-an-interesting-chatgpt-product-by-2026/</link>
      <description>OpenAI is planning to release a new product by 2026 that combines their ChatGPT technology with hardware, allowing users to use AI natively. This could potentially expand the reach of AI-powered services beyond just apps and websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-plans-to-ship-an-interesting-chatgpt-product-by-2026/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
