<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:02:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPi package hides RAT malware, targets Discord devs since 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-hides-rat-malware-targets-discord-devs-since-2022/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious Python package named "discordpydebug" was discovered on the Python Package Index (PyPI) after over three years. The package, which masqueraded as an error logger utility, could be used to backdoor Discord developers' systems and provide attackers with data theft and remote code execution capabilities, downloaded over 11,000 times since its upload in March 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-hides-rat-malware-targets-discord-devs-since-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE software engineer’s computer infected by info-stealing malware</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses potential security lapses by the Department of Governmental Employee (DOGE) and CISA, including public exposure of sensitive information due to weak credentials and operational security gaffes. Critics suggest that the leaks may be intentional, potentially benefiting specific individuals or groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IT help desk kindly requests you read this newsletter</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/the-it-help-desk-kindly-requests-you-read-this-newsletter/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of being cautious when receiving instructions or requests from individuals claiming to be authorities, as attackers often impersonate authoritative figures to trick victims into taking actions that benefit the attackers. It also highlights the need for threat hunting and the use of different approaches to identify potential threats early on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">681c9fb9f292a20001d3a4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Ubiquiti UniFi Protect Camera Allows Remote Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ubiquiti-unifi-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23123, CVE-2025-23164; Summary: Critical vulnerabilities in UniFi Protect surveillance ecosystem allow attackers to hijack cameras, execute malicious code remotely, and maintain unauthorized access to video feeds. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2025-23123) is a heap buffer overflow that can trigger remote code execution with full control over affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133917</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IXON VPN Client Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation for Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ixon-vpn-client-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IXON VPN Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26168, CVE-2025-26169; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in the IXON VPN client allows local privilege escalation attacks, enabling non-privileged users to gain root or SYSTEM-level access on Windows, Linux, and macOS systems. The flaw stems from improper handling of temporary configuration files, which can be exploited by replacing legitimate files with malicious versions containing arbitrary commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133994</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS Software SISF Vulnerability Could Enable Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-software-sisf-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CSCwk04230, CSCvq14413, CSCvo13585, CSCwj88828; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending specifically crafted DHCPv6 packets to targeted devices with SISF enabled, forcing the device to reload and disrupting network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seamless AI Communication: Microsoft Azure Adopts Google’s A2A Protocol</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-azure-integrates-googles-a2a-protocol/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft's support for the Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol, an open standard enabling seamless communication between AI agents across platforms, clouds, and organizational boundaries. The goal is to address the growing demand for interoperable AI systems in enterprise environments, with potential applications in areas such as customer service escalation, IT incident resolution, and supply chain management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134082</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radware Cloud Web App Firewall Flaw Allows Attackers to Bypass Security Filters</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/radware-cloud-web-app-firewall-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Radware Cloud Web Application Firewall (WAF); CVE(s): CVE-2024-56523, CVE-2024-56524; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in Radware's WAF allow attackers to bypass security filters and deliver malicious payloads to protected web applications. The first vulnerability exploits the WAF's failure to properly validate HTTP GET requests containing extraneous data, while the second vulnerability stems from improper input sanitization when processing requests containing non-alphanumeric characters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134145</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Reveals How to Spot Fake Calls Demanding Payment for ‘Missed Jury Duty’</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eset-reveals-how-to-spot-fake-calls-demanding-payment/</link>
      <description>Scammers are using fake government officials to demand payment for "missed jury duty" over phone and email. They use tactics like threatening language, phishing emails/texts, and requests for personal information. To protect yourself, do not engage with suspicious calls or emails, be skeptical of unsolicited communications, and never share personal or financial details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134208</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickidler employee monitoring software abused in ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kickidler-employee-monitoring-software-abused-in-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kickidler; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Kickidler employee monitoring software was exploited by ransomware operators to track victim activity, harvest credentials, and conduct reconnaissance. The attackers used the software to capture keystrokes, take screenshots, and create videos of the screen, enabling them to identify off-site cloud backups and obtain necessary passwords without being detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kickidler-employee-monitoring-software-abused-in-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38,000+ FreeDrain Subdomains Found Exploiting SEO to Steal Crypto Wallet Seed Phrases</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/38000-freedrain-subdomains-found.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses two separate cryptocurrency phishing operations, dubbed FreeDrain and Inferno Drainer. FreeDrain uses SEO manipulation, free-tier web services, and layered redirection techniques to target cryptocurrency wallets, while Inferno Drainer employs advanced anti-detection tactics and single-use smart contracts to bypass wallet security mechanisms and steal funds.

FYSA: The article highlights the sophistication of threat actors in conducting large-scale phishing operations, leveraging various platforms and tools to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/38000-freedrain-subdomains-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections of the India–Pakistan Kashmir Escalation on the Cyber World</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/india-pakistan-kashmir-escalation-on-cyber-world/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the escalation of a military standoff between India and Pakistan in Kashmir, with both sides engaging in physical clashes and online attacks. Hacktivist groups from both countries have begun to align their operations, launching website defacements, Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks, and leaking stolen data. The article highlights the growth of cyber activity related to India over the years, including hacktivist campaigns, Dark Web mentions, and sales of stolen information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059892</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VC giant Insight Partners confirms investor data stolen in breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vc-giant-insight-partners-confirms-investor-data-stolen-in-breach/</link>
      <description>A venture capital firm, Insight Partners, has confirmed that a cyberattack occurred on January 16, 2025, resulting in the theft of sensitive employee and limited partner data. The incident was caused by a "sophisticated social engineering attack" and may have exposed various types of information, including fund details, personal data, and banking information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vc-giant-insight-partners-confirms-investor-data-stolen-in-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Turn the Tables: Scamming the Scammers in Telegram’s PigButchering Scheme</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scamming-the-scammers-in-telegrams-pigbutchering-scheme/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have developed an innovative approach to combat "PigButchering" scams on Telegram, which involves cultivating false relationships with victims and deceiving them at the opportune moment. The operation involved creating faux personas, executing a sting operation, gathering intelligence, and siphoning off funds from the scammers' wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134177</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Spam Campaign Leverages Remote Monitoring Tools to Exploit Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-spam-campaign-leverages-remote-monitoring-tools/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated spam campaign targeting Portuguese-speaking users in Brazil has been uncovered by Cisco Talos, exploiting commercial remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools to gain unauthorized access to victims' systems. The attackers use deceptive tactics to distribute malicious installers disguised as legitimate files related to Brazil's electronic invoice system, NF-e.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134127</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Attack Exploits X/Twitter Ad URL Feature to Deceive Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-attack-exploits-x-twitter-ad-url-feature/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Twitter; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Twitter's advertising display URL feature allows attackers to manipulate the platform's URL display mechanism, presenting a legitimate-looking link while redirecting users to a malicious cryptocurrency scam site. The exploit involves an inconsistent User Agent string and metadata retrieval process, allowing attackers to create a preview card that displays a trusted domain, masking the true, harmful landing page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134075</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess Which Browser Tops the List for Data Collection!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/which-browser-tops-the-list-for-data-collection/</link>
      <description>Google Chrome has emerged as the most data-intensive web browser among 10 popular browsers, collecting 20 different types of user data, including personal contact information, financial details, location data, and browsing history. Its dominance in the market, with a combined 90% share with Safari, raises concerns about users' privacy and highlights the need for evaluation of browser choices to prioritize security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134093</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall Patches 3 Flaws in SMA 100 Devices Allowing Attackers to Run Code as Root</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/sonicwall-patches-3-flaws-in-sma-100.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA 100; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32819, CVE-2025-32820, CVE-2025-32821; Summary: A remote authenticated attacker can chain these vulnerabilities to elevate privileges, make a sensitive system directory writable, and write an executable file to a system directory, resulting in root-level remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/sonicwall-patches-3-flaws-in-sma-100.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Leads April 2025 Ransomware Spike with 45 Breaches Using NETXLOADER Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/qilin-leads-april-2025-ransomware-spike.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors with ties to Qilin ransomware family have leveraged malware SmokeLoader and a previously undocumented .NET compiled loader, NETXLOADER, as part of a campaign observed in November 2024. The loaders are used to deploy additional malicious payloads, including Agenda ransomware, and are protected by .NET Reactor version 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/qilin-leads-april-2025-ransomware-spike.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Big Balls Ransomware Leverages Open-Source Tools and Custom Scripts for Multi-Stage Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/doge-big-balls-ransomware-leverages-open-source-tools/</link>
      <description>The article describes a highly complex ransomware variant called "DOGE Big Balls," which incorporates political statements and taunts in its payloads. The ransomware's infection chain utilizes custom PowerShell scripts, open-source tools, vulnerable driver exploits, and red team frameworks, with frequent updates to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google links new LostKeys data theft malware to Russian cyberspies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-links-new-lostkeys-data-theft-malware-to-russian-cyberspies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the ColdRiver hacking group, a Russian state-backed threat actor that has been using new LostKeys malware to steal files in espionage attacks targeting Western governments, journalists, think tanks, and non-governmental organizations. The malware is delivered through social engineering attacks, such as ClickFix, which tricks targets into running malicious PowerShell scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-links-new-lostkeys-data-theft-malware-to-russian-cyberspies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) Emerges as a Leading Framework for Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/raas-emerges-as-a-leading-framework/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the rise of Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) frameworks, which have enabled even less-skilled actors to orchestrate sophisticated attacks. The article highlights the shift towards cross-platform attacks, data exfiltration, and double or triple extortion tactics, as well as the increase in average ransom demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133995</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hackers Posing as Model Agency to Target Victims</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hackers-posing-as-model-agency/</link>
      <description>Unit 42 has exposed a covert operation likely orchestrated by Iranian cyber actors that involves a fraudulent website designed to impersonate the Hamburg-based Mega Model Agency, with malicious JavaScript code aimed at harvesting detailed visitor data. The campaign suggests preparation for targeted social engineering and potentially aims to harvest credentials or deliver malware to specific victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134012</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian COLDRIVER Hackers Deploy LOSTKEYS Malware to Steal Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-coldriver-hackers-deploy-lostkeys-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated malware called LOSTKEYS, attributed to the Russian government-backed threat actor COLDRIVER. The malware is designed to exfiltrate files and harvest system information from targeted individuals and organizations, particularly those linked to Ukraine or Western governments. It uses a complex multi-stage infection chain, including CAPTCHA lures and PowerShell code execution, to evade detection and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133897</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven Fake Vulnerability Reports Flooding Bug Bounty Platforms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-driven-fake-vulnerability-reports/</link>
      <description>AI-generated bogus vulnerability reports, or "AI slop," are flooding bug bounty platforms, mimicking technical jargon convincingly enough to pass initial scrutiny but crumble under expert analysis. These fraudulent submissions rely on systemic vulnerabilities within bug bounty programs and can erode trust, divert resources from addressing genuine vulnerabilities, and potentially dismantle the bug bounty model.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Bookings Vulnerability Allows Unauthorized Changes to Meeting Details</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-bookings-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Bookings; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Microsoft Bookings allows unauthorized modification of meeting details, posing risks such as phishing, calendar manipulation, and information leakage. The flaw arises from inadequate input validation and sanitization in several key fields used by Microsoft Bookings, allowing malicious actors to inject arbitrary HTML content into confirmation emails, Teams invitations, and attached ICS files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134115</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nmap 7.96 Released with Enhanced Scanning Capabilities and Updated Libraries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nmap-7-96-launches/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is about the release of Nmap 7.96, a network mapping and security auditing tool. The update brings improvements such as parallel forward DNS resolution, upgraded core libraries, new scripting capabilities, and enhanced compatibility across platforms, especially for Windows users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134099</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS XE Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Gain Elevated Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-xe-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20197, CVE-2025-20198, CVE-2025-20199, among others; Summary: The IOS XE Software has multiple privilege escalation vulnerabilities that could allow attackers with existing high-level device access to gain root privileges, jeopardizing enterprise networks. Insufficient input validation in the command-line interface (CLI) of IOS XE Software enables attackers to supply crafted input and escalate their privileges to root on the underlying system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134088</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric CC-Link IE TSN</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-128-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Link IE TSN Analog-Digital Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN Digital-Analog Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN FPGA module, and CC-Link IE TSN Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3511; Summary: A remote attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending specially crafted UDP packets. The affected products are CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, Analog-Digital Converter module, Digital-Analog Converter module, FPGA module, and Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23329</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horner Automation Cscape</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-128-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Horner Automation Cscape; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4098; Summary: The out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Horner Automation Cscape, version 10.0 (10.0.415.2) SP1, allows an attacker to disclose information and execute arbitrary code with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23327</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy RTU500 Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-128-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy RTU500 series; CVE(s): CVE-2023-5767, CVE-2023-5768, CVE-2023-5769; Summary: The RTU500 series products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting and denial-of-service conditions due to improper neutralization of input during web page generation and incomplete or incorrectly received APDU frame layout. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute cross-site scripting or trigger a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23328</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Five Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/08/cisa-releases-five-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released five Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on May 8, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories are meant for users and administrators to review technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23331</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixmeo OsiriX MD</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-128-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Pixmeo OsiriX MD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27578, CVE-2025-31946, CVE-2025-27720; Summary: The OsiriX MD product is vulnerable to use-after-free and clear-text transmission of sensitive information, allowing attackers to cause memory corruption, denial-of-service conditions, or steal credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23330</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe Vulnerabilities in Cisco &amp; SonicWall Expose Systems to RCE, DoS, and More: Patch Now</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cisco-sonicwall-expose-systems-to-rce-dos-and-more/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20188, CVE-2025-32433; Summary: A series of critical and high-severity vulnerabilities were disclosed in Cisco's latest advisories, affecting key network infrastructure and security appliances. The vulnerabilities include unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) flaws, privilege escalation paths, command injection issues, and other impactful bugs that threaten system integrity and availability.

FYSA: Several prominent platforms are affected by the vulnerabilities, including Catalyst 9800-CL Wireless Controllers, Catalyst 9800 Embedded Wireless Controllers for 9300, 9400, and 9500 switches, and Embedded Wireless Controllers on Catalyst Access Points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059872</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall urges admins to patch VPN flaw exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-urges-admins-to-patch-vpn-flaw-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall Secure Mobile Access (SMA) appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32819, CVE-2025-32820, and CVE-2025-32821; Summary: The three security flaws can be chained by attackers to gain remote code execution as root and compromise vulnerable instances. Successful exploitation of the first vulnerability allows threat actors to delete the primary SQLite database, reset the password of the default SMA admin user, and log in as admin to the SMA web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-urges-admins-to-patch-vpn-flaw-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LockBit Hacked: 60,000 Bitcoin Addresses Leaked</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/lockbit-hacked-60000-bitcoin-addresses-leaked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): CVE-2024-4577; Summary: The article reports that a vulnerability in PHP 8.1.2 (CVE-2024-4577) may have been used as an entry point for the attack on LockBit's Dark Web panel, allowing hackers to run code remotely and deface the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059861</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Tools Alone Don't Protect You — Control Effectiveness Does</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/security-tools-alone-dont-protect-you.html</link>
      <description>According to the Gartner report, misconfiguration of technical security controls is a leading cause for the continued success of attacks. Organizations are beginning to understand that having an average of 43 cybersecurity tools in place does not necessarily mean they have effective security controls. The article discusses the importance of continuous validation and tuning of security tools to ensure their effectiveness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/security-tools-alone-dont-protect-you.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MirrorFace Targets Japan and Taiwan with ROAMINGMOUSE and Upgraded ANEL Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/mirrorface-targets-japan-and-taiwan.html</link>
      <description>The nation-state threat actor "MirrorFace" (also known as Earth Kasha) has been observed deploying malware called ROAMINGMOUSE as part of a cyber espionage campaign directed against government agencies and public institutions in Japan and Taiwan. The attack starts with spear-phishing emails that deliver a ZIP file containing a malware-laced Excel document, which is then used to launch the ANEL backdoor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/mirrorface-targets-japan-and-taiwan.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spam campaign targeting Brazil abuses Remote Monitoring and Management tools</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/spam-campaign-targeting-brazil-abuses-rmm-tools/</link>
      <description>Cisco Talos identified a spam campaign targeting Brazilian users with commercial remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools since at least January 2025. The campaign uses the Brazilian electronic invoice system, NF-e, as a lure to entice users into clicking hyperlinks and accessing malicious content hosted in Dropbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6818d82110aae200012af087</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 10:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS, XE, and XR Vulnerability Allows Remote Device Reboots</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-xe-and-xr-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20154; Summary: The Cisco IOS, IOS XE, and IOS XR software contains a critical vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by forcing devices to reboot remotely. The flaw stems from improper handling of Two-Way Active Measurement Protocol (TWAMP) control packets, which can cause full system reloads on IOS/IOS XE devices or crashes of the ipsla_ippm_server process on IOS XR devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134002</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenCTI: Free Cyber Threat Intelligence Platform for Security Experts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/opencti-free-cyber-threat-intelligence-platform/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenCTI, a free and open-source platform for managing and analyzing cybersecurity threat intelligence. It provides robust capabilities for structuring, storing, and visualizing technical and non-technical information, including integrations with popular tools like MISP, TheHive, and MITRE ATT&amp;CK.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133987</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Using ClickFix Fake CAPTCHA to Deploy New LOSTKEYS Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-using-clickfix-fake.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new malware called LOSTKEYS, attributed to the Russia-linked threat actor COLDRIVER. LOSTKEYS is capable of stealing files from a hard-coded list of extensions and directories, as well as sending system information and running processes to the attacker. The malware was observed in attacks on current and former advisors to Western governments and militaries, journalists, think tanks, and NGOs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-using-clickfix-fake.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LockBit Ransomware Group Breached: Internal Chats and Data Leaked Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lockbit-ransomware-group-breached/</link>
      <description>LockBit ransomware group, once considered one of the world's most prolific cyber extortion rings, has been breached by attackers, leading to the leak of operational data and internal chats. The exposed database includes sensitive information such as Bitcoin wallet addresses, negotiation chat logs, and plaintext passwords for 75 LockBit administrators and affiliates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133883</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 05:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS XE Wireless Controllers Vulnerability Lets Attackers Seize Full Control</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-xe-wireless-controllers-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco IOS XE Wireless LAN Controllers; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20188; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Out-of-Band AP Image Download feature of Cisco IOS XE Software for WLCs allows unauthenticated remote attackers to gain full control of affected devices, enabling arbitrary file upload, path traversal, and execution of system commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133873</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 05:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Patches CVE-2025-20188 (10.0 CVSS) in IOS XE That Enables Root Exploits via JWT</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cisco-patches-cve-2025-20188-100-cvss.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20188; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-20188, is a maximum-severity flaw in Cisco's IOS XE Wireless Controller that allows an unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, perform path traversal, and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. The feature must be enabled on the device for exploitation to occur; it is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cisco-patches-cve-2025-20188-100-cvss.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 04:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LockBit ransomware gang hacked, victim negotiations exposed</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-ransomware-gang-hacked-victim-negotiations-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MySQL; CVE(s): CVE-2024-4577; Summary: The vulnerability is a critical and actively exploited remote code execution flaw in PHP 8.1.2, which was running on the server that stored the LockBit ransomware gang's affiliate panel database. This vulnerability allows for remote code execution on servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lockbit-ransomware-gang-hacked-victim-negotiations-exposed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the US-China AI Gap</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/measuring-the-us-china-ai-gap</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I analyzed the provided article and found that it is an in-depth report on China's AI ecosystem, its growth, and investment trends. The report highlights the country's efforts to become a leader in artificial intelligence research and development.

The report provides detailed information about China's AI-related investments, including government-led initiatives and private-sector funding. It also touches upon the country's semiconductor industry, which is crucial for supporting its AI ecosystem.

From a cybersecurity perspective, this report does not specifically discuss vulnerabilities or threats. Instead, it focuses on the broader landscape of AI development in China and its potential implications for the global AI market.

However, one could argue that the rapid growth and investment in China's AI sector may potentially increase the risk of AI-powered cyberattacks or data breaches if security measures are not adequately implemented to protect against these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/measuring-the-us-china-ai-gap</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistani Firm Shipped Fentanyl Analogs, Scams to US</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/pakistani-firm-shipped-fentanyl-analogs-scams-to-us/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be an investigative report on a network of ghostwriting, logo design, and academic cheating services that are allegedly scamming individuals out of thousands of dollars. The report details the connections between various companies and individuals involved in these operations, including their use of Google Ads to promote their services. The article also discusses the difficulties faced by victims who attempt to seek justice through legal means.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=70782</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp provides no cryptographic management for group messages</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/whatsapp-provides-no-cryptographic-management-for-group-messages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WhatsApp; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in WhatsApp's group messaging feature allows a user to add someone to an existing group without their consent, potentially resulting in sensitive information being sent to unauthorized individuals. The weakness is likely to be exploited only in extraordinary cases, but it's still a good reason for groups trading sensitive messages to avoid using the app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/whatsapp-provides-no-cryptographic-management-for-group-messages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have reached the “severed fingers and abductions” stage of the crypto revolution</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/we-have-reached-the-severed-fingers-and-abductions-stage-of-the-crypto-revolution/</link>
      <description>No vulnerability mentioned; article discusses instances of physical violence and intimidation used by criminals to steal cryptocurrency assets from victims, highlighting the risks associated with publicly displaying one's wealth online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/we-have-reached-the-severed-fingers-and-abductions-stage-of-the-crypto-revolution/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
