<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky Hacker Group Deploys New Phishing Techniques and Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-hacker-group-deploys-new-phishing-techniques/</link>
      <description>The North Korean state-sponsored APT group Kimsuky has been active since at least 2012, targeting nations like South Korea, Japan, and the United States with sophisticated cyber espionage campaigns. The article details Kimsuky's latest attack vector, which employs phishing, malware deployment, and obfuscation techniques to evade detection and penetrate sensitive systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134940</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT37 Hackers Use Weaponized LNK Files and Dropbox for Command-and-Control Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt37-hackers-use-weaponized-lnk-files-and-dropbox/</link>
      <description>APT37, a North Korean state-sponsored hacking group, launched a spear phishing campaign targeting activists focused on North Korean issues. The attackers exploited legitimate cloud services like Dropbox as command-and-control (C2) infrastructure and delivered malicious shortcut (LNK) files via phishing emails to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134904</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers now testing ClickFix attacks against Linux targets</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-now-testing-clickfix-attacks-against-linux-targets/</link>
      <description>A new ClickFix attack campaign has been spotted targeting Windows, Linux, and macOS systems, using social engineering tactics to trick users into running console commands that install malware. The attacks are attributed to the Pakistan-linked threat group APT36 (aka "Transparent Tribe").</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-now-testing-clickfix-attacks-against-linux-targets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Output Messenger flaw exploited as zero-day in espionage attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/output-messenger-flaw-exploited-as-zero-day-in-espionage-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Output Messenger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27920; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-27920) in the LAN messaging application, a directory traversal vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to access sensitive files or deploy malicious payloads. The vulnerability was exploited by the Marbled Dust group to attack Output Messenger users linked to the Kurdish military in Iraq and gain access to sensitive data, impersonate users, and cause operational disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/output-messenger-flaw-exploited-as-zero-day-in-espionage-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moldova arrests suspect linked to DoppelPaymer ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/moldova-arrests-suspect-linked-to-doppelpaymer-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather reports on the detention of a suspect linked to DoppelPaymer ransomware attacks targeting Dutch organizations. The suspect remains in custody and legal procedures are underway for extradition to the Netherlands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/moldova-arrests-suspect-linked-to-doppelpaymer-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Linux Firewall IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194 Released: What’s New!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ipfire-2-29-core-update-194/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): expat 2.7.1 (fixing CVE-2024-8176), xz 5.8.1 (fixing CVE-2025-31115); Summary: IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194 includes security enhancements, performance improvements, and new features to safeguard networks, including updates for expat (fixing CVE-2024-8176) and xz (fixing CVE-2025-31115).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135019</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google to pay $1.375 billion to settle Texas data privacy violations</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/google-to-pay-1375-billion-to-settle-texas-data-privacy-violations/</link>
      <description>Google has agreed to a $1.375 billion settlement with the state of Texas over allegations it collected and used biometric data without consent, impacting millions of Texans; this settlement marks one of the highest recoveries against Google nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/google-to-pay-1375-billion-to-settle-texas-data-privacy-violations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage DDoS Attacks as Smokescreens for Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-ddos-attacks/</link>
      <description>DDoS attacks have evolved from being simple denial-of-service tools to sophisticated smokescreens masking more insidious breaches. Threat actors orchestrate high-volume traffic floods to distract security teams while executing quieter, surgical operations within the same infrastructure. This emerging pattern exploits both technical and human vulnerabilities during incident response, requiring a paradigm shift in defense strategies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134892</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Browser Extensions Pose Critical Security Risk, A New Report Reveals</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/majority-of-browser-extensions-pose-critical-security-risk-a-new-report-reveals/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the risks associated with browser extensions in enterprise environments. It highlights that 99% of employees have browser extensions installed, which creates a significant threat surface. Many extensions have extensive permissions to sensitive data, and some are published anonymously or are outdated/unmanaged, making trust verification challenging and increasing security risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/majority-of-browser-extensions-pose-critical-security-risk-a-new-report-reveals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-Year-Old Proxy Botnet Network Dismantled After Exploiting 1,000 Unpatched Devices Each Week</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/20-year-old-proxy-botnet-network/</link>
      <description>A 20-year-old criminal proxy network was disrupted through a joint operation. The botnet exploited an average of 1,000 unique IoT and end-of-life devices weekly, turning them into proxies for malicious actors. The network enabled illicit activities such as ad fraud, DDoS attacks, and data exploitation, with over half the infected devices located in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134851</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“PupkinStealer” – .NET Malware Steals Browser Data and Exfiltrates via Telegram</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pupkinstealer-net-malware-steals-browser-data/</link>
      <description>PupkinStealer is a new information-stealing malware that targets sensitive user data, including browser credentials, personal files, session information from messaging platforms, and desktop screenshots. It uses the Telegram Bot API to exfiltrate stolen data to attacker-controlled servers with minimal traceability. The malware operates by initiating multiple asynchronous tasks upon execution, targeting Chromium-based browsers, scanning the victim's desktop for files, and harvesting Telegram and Discord tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134828</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishing Campaign Uses Blob URLs to Bypass Email Security and Avoid Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/phishing-campaign-uses-blob-urls/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have identified a sophisticated phishing tactic that leverages Blob URIs to deliver credential phishing pages directly to users' inboxes, evading traditional email security measures. The attack chain begins with a phishing email that slips past Secure Email Gateways (SEGs) and uses legitimate intermediary sites like onedrive.live.com to render malicious HTML content, making it nearly impossible to analyze remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134796</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS Patches DriverHub RCE Flaws Exploitable via HTTP and Crafted .ini Files</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/asus-patches-driverhub-rce-flaws.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462, CVE-2025-3463; Summary: Two security flaws in ASUS DriverHub allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution. The first flaw is an origin validation error vulnerability (CVE-2025-3462) and the second is an improper certificate validation vulnerability (CVE-2025-3463). An attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities by tricking a user into visiting a crafted domain and executing a malicious file using the "AsusSetup.exe" binary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/asus-patches-driverhub-rce-flaws.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware Tools Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Modify Files and Launch Malicious Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-tools-vulnerability-allows-attackers-to-modify-files/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware Tools; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22247; Summary: The VMware Tools insecure file handling vulnerability (CVE-2025-22247) allows non-administrative users to manipulate files within guest virtual machines, enabling unauthorized file operations. The vulnerability affects multiple versions of VMware Tools across different operating systems, with a CVSS base score of 6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134900</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Zero-Day Exploits, Developer Malware, IoT Botnets, and AI-Powered Scams</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/weekly-recap-zero-day-exploits.html</link>
      <description>The article appears to be a collection of cybersecurity news and updates from various sources. It covers topics such as ransomware attacks, phishing scams, data breaches, and other cyber threats. There are no specific software, hardware, or firmware vulnerabilities discussed in this article.

However, the article does mention some general security tips and best practices, such as uniting code, cloud, and SOC security to eliminate hidden gaps, building a legally defensible cyber defense program, and blocking AI bots from scraping websites. These tips aim to provide readers with actionable advice on how to improve their overall cybersecurity posture.

Overall, the article serves as a general cybersecurity news roundup, providing readers with information on the latest threats and trends in the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/weekly-recap-zero-day-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update to How CISA Shares Cyber-Related Alerts and Notifications</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/12/update-how-cisa-shares-cyber-related-alerts-and-notifications</link>
      <description>CISA (Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency) is changing how it announces cybersecurity updates and releases new guidance, shifting focus from the Cybersecurity Alerts &amp; Advisories webpage to urgent information on emerging threats or major cyber activity. The changes aim to ensure critical information gets attention and is easier to find.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23334</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QatarRat Tool Emerges, GST Data Sold, and LockBit Gets Breached</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/qatarrat-tool-emerges-gst-data-sold-and-lockbit-breach/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LockBit; CVE(s): CVE-2024-4577; Summary: A PHP 8.1.2 vulnerability (CVE-2024-4577) was exploited to hack LockBit's dark web panel, exposing a MySQL database containing nearly 60,000 Bitcoin addresses, affiliate credentials, ransom negotiations, and internal tools.

FYSA: The article highlights threat actors selling malware, including a new multi-functional RAT named QatarRat, and stolen data from India's GST portal. Additionally, crypto stealer logs targeting wallet users are being sold, underscoring ongoing threats across malware, finance, and government sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059927</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Persistence Problem: Why Exposed Credentials Remain Unfixed—and How to Change That</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/the-persistence-problem-why-exposed.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the persistence of exposed company secrets in public GitHub repositories, with many credentials remaining valid for years after detection. This creates an expanding attack surface that organizations often fail to address due to limited visibility, operational complexity, and technical limitations.

FYSA: Threat actors can exploit exposed database credentials to exfiltrate or corrupt data, while cloud keys grant access to infrastructure, code, and customer data. Organizations should prioritize rapid remediation and adopt modern secrets management practices, including short-lived, dynamic credentials and automation, to reduce the risks posed by exposed secrets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/the-persistence-problem-why-exposed.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Update Adds Erlang/OTP SSH Exploit and OPNSense Scanner</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/metasploit-update-erlang-opnsense-scanner/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP SSH servers; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: The Erlang/OTP SSH Pre-Auth Root RCE exploit targets a critical pre-authentication vulnerability in Erlang-based SSH servers, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root by sending crafted SSH packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134862</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 09:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Researchers Use Mach IPC to Uncover Sandbox Escape Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mach-ipc-to-uncover-sandbox-escape-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Project Zero researchers, macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The researchers discovered new sandbox escape vulnerabilities in macOS using Mach Interprocess Communication (IPC) mechanisms-core components of Apple's operating system. The vulnerabilities allow crafted messages to cause out-of-bounds memory access, potentially enabling privilege escalation and sandbox escapes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134804</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Hide Undetectable Ransomware Inside JPG Images</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/undetectable-ransomware-inside-jpg-images/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new ransomware attack method that exploits JPEG image files to deliver fully undetectable (FUD) ransomware. The attack involves embedding malicious code within standard JPG images, which activates a multi-stage attack when the victim opens the image, including downloading the ransomware executable and encrypting the victim's files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134792</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Legacy Protocols in Microsoft Entra ID to Bypass MFA and Conditional Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-legacy-protocols-in-microsoft-entra-id/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: The campaign exploited outdated legacy authentication protocols, including BAV2ROPC, SMTP AUTH, POP3, and IMAP4, to bypass modern security measures like MFA and Conditional Access. Attackers targeted legacy endpoints like Exchange Online and the Microsoft Authentication Library, exploiting OAuth legacy flows, password authentication, basic authentication, and legacy Exchange protocols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134763</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Abuse Copilot AI in SharePoint to Steal Passwords and Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-abuse-copilot-ai-in-sharepoint/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a vulnerability where attackers can exploit AI agents embedded in SharePoint sites to bypass traditional security controls, extract passwords, and access restricted files. Attackers can manipulate these agents by framing malicious queries as legitimate security audits, allowing them to evade detection and gain unauthorized access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134731</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defendnot: A Tool That Disables Windows Defender by Registering as Antivirus</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/defendnot-a-tool-that-disables-windows-defender/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "defendnot" tool uses undocumented Windows Security Center APIs to disable Windows Defender by registering itself as a third-party antivirus solution. It achieves this by utilizing the Windows Security Center (WSC) service and performing signature verification, DLL characteristic checks, and other security checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134710</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitel SIP Phone Flaws Allow Attackers to Inject Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitel-sip-phone-flaws-allow-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47188, CVE-2025-47187; Summary: A pair of vulnerabilities in Mitel's 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones could enable attackers to execute arbitrary commands or upload malicious files to compromised devices, posing significant risks to enterprise communication systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134738</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake AI Tools Used to Spread Noodlophile Malware, Targeting 62,000+ via Facebook Lures</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-ai-tools-used-to-spread.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using fake AI-powered tools as lures to entice users into downloading an information stealer malware dubbed Noodlophile. The malware harvests browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallet information, and other sensitive data, and in some cases, bundles with a remote access trojan for persistent access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-ai-tools-used-to-spread.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams to Safeguard Meetings by Blocking Screen Snaps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-blocking-screen-snaps/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing a "Prevent Screen Capture" feature for Teams, which will block unauthorized screenshots and recordings during virtual meetings. When activated, any attempt to take a screenshot will result in the meeting window going completely black, leaving only system notifications visible in the captured image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134749</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Exploit Method Extracts Microsoft Entra Tokens Through Beacon</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-exploit-method-extracts-microsoft-entra-tokens/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel exploit method uses Beacon Object Files (BOFs) to extract Microsoft Entra tokens from compromised endpoints, including non-domain-joined or BYOD devices. The technique bypasses traditional detection mechanisms and expands access to high-value targets, posing significant risks to enterprise cloud environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134720</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Code Published for Linux nftables Security Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poc-code-for-linux-nftables-security-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux; CVE(s): CVE-2024-26809; Summary: The Linux nftables firewall subsystem contains a high-severity double-free vulnerability that allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code. The flaw resides in the pipapo set implementation, which can be exploited by deleting a set marked as "dirty" while it's still dirty, leading to repeated deallocations of memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134711</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth 6.1 enhances privacy with randomized RPA timing</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-61-enhances-privacy-with-randomized-rpa-timing/</link>
      <description>The Bluetooth Special Interest Group (SIG) has announced Bluetooth Core Specification 6.1, which improves device privacy by randomizing Resolvable Private Address (RPA) updates between 8 and 15 minutes (default), allowing custom values between 1 second to 1 hour. This makes tracking harder due to the lack of pattern in value selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-61-enhances-privacy-with-randomized-rpa-timing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is finally adding Download as PDF for Deep Research</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-finally-adding-download-as-pdf-for-deep-research/</link>
      <description>The article discusses upcoming features for ChatGPT, including the ability to save reports as PDFs and a new GitHub connector for Teams subscribers. Additionally, it mentions various benchmarks and releases related to OpenAI's GPT-4.1 models. No cybersecurity-specific information is provided in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-finally-adding-download-as-pdf-for-deep-research/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iClicker site hack targeted students with malware via fake CAPTCHA</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iclicker-hack-targeted-students-with-malware-via-fake-captcha/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: iClicker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The iClicker website was compromised by a ClickFix attack that displayed a fake CAPTCHA prompt to trick students and instructors into installing malware on their devices. The attack used social engineering tactics to execute PowerShell scripts, which could have installed malware or stolen sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iclicker-hack-targeted-students-with-malware-via-fake-captcha/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 14:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated PhaaS Phish Toolkits are Now Genetrating Realistic Fake Phishing Pages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/phishing-scams-on-the-rise-with-sophisticated-phaas/</link>
      <description>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) toolkits are being used to generate convincing replicas of legitimate websites in real-time, enhancing the effectiveness of credential-harvesting campaigns. These toolkits allow attackers to tailor phishing pages instantly for any target organization and evade detection by human users and automated security systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134535</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Azure and Power Apps Vulnerabilities Allow Attackers to Exploit RCE</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-azure-and-power-apps-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure cloud services and Power Apps platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29813, CVE-2025-29827, CVE-2025-29972, CVE-2025-47733; Summary: Four critical security vulnerabilities were patched in Microsoft's Azure cloud services and Power Apps platform. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2025-29813) could allow attackers to escalate privileges or access sensitive information by exploiting improper handling of pipeline job tokens within Visual Studio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134283</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Detecting Backdoors in Enterprise Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/detecting-backdoors-enterprise-networks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware vCenter Server; CVE(s): CVE-2024-38812; Summary: A critical remote code execution flaw (CVE-2024-38812) was exploited in a backdoor attack, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to systems and potentially remain undetected for months while exfiltrating sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134680</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Windows Endpoints Using Group Policy Objects (GPOs): A Configuration Guide</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/securing-windows-endpoints-using-group-policy-objects-gpos-a-configuration-guide/</link>
      <description>This article is a guide on how to effectively use Group Policy Objects (GPOs) for endpoint security in Windows environments. It provides best practices for designing and implementing GPOs to manage and enforce security settings, including structuring Active Directory, configuring password policies, application control, and firewall settings, and maintaining audit logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134295</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth Core 6.1 Released – What’s New!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bluetooth-6-1-unveiled/</link>
      <description>The Bluetooth SIG has transitioned to a bi-annual release cadence, focusing on rapid iteration and market responsiveness. This shift aims to empower developers with more efficient integration of enhancements, reducing the gap between standardization and real-world implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134458</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams will soon block screen capture during meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-teams-will-soon-block-screen-capture-during-meetings/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new feature in Microsoft Teams that prevents users from capturing screenshots of sensitive information shared during meetings. The feature will turn the meeting window black if someone tries to take a screenshot, protecting the sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-teams-will-soon-block-screen-capture-during-meetings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome 137 Integrates Gemini Nano AI to Combat Tech Support Scams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-137-integrates-gemini-nano-ai/</link>
      <description>Google has integrated its Gemini Nano large language model (LLM) into Chrome 137 to detect and block tech support scams in real-time. The on-device AI analysis evaluates webpage content for deceptive patterns, generating security signals for Google's Safe Browsing service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134423</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Employee Computer Infected with Malware and Leaked Data Found Info-Stealer Logs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/doge-employee-credentials-exposed-in-multiple-info-stealer-leaks/</link>
      <description>This article reports on the unauthorized access to sensitive government systems, including the Federal Emergency Management Agency's core financial management platform, by Kyle Schutt, a 37-year-old DOGE employee. The article highlights systemic cybersecurity challenges within federal agencies, specifically the reliance on password-based authentication and the need for multi-factor authentication (MFA) and layered defense approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134393</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CISOs Must Prioritize Cybersecurity Culture in Remote Work</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybersecurity-culture-in-remote-work/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of building a strong cybersecurity culture in remote work environments. It highlights that Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs) must go beyond traditional technical responsibilities and foster a security-first mindset among remote employees. The article provides five practical steps for CISOs to build this culture, including developing remote-specific security policies, delivering ongoing training, encouraging open communication, recognizing good security behavior, and turning mistakes into learning opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=132248</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake AI video generators drop new Noodlophile infostealer malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-ai-video-generators-drop-new-noodlophile-infostealer-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a new information-stealing malware family called 'Noodlophile,' which uses fake AI-powered video generation tools to distribute the malware. The malware targets data stored on web browsers, steals account credentials, session cookies, tokens, and cryptocurrency wallet files, and exfiltrates stolen data via a Telegram bot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-ai-video-generators-drop-new-noodlophile-infostealer-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Uses Advanced AI to Combat Sophisticated Online Scams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-chrome-uses-ai/</link>
      <description>Google has integrated artificial intelligence into its cybersecurity toolkit to shield users from financial and data theft scams. The company has unveiled AI-driven initiatives across Search, Chrome, and Android, aimed at counteracting increasingly sophisticated scams. The advancements include AI classifiers capable of analyzing vast web content datasets, identifying emerging scam patterns, and neutralizing coordinated campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea’s OtterCookie Malware Added a New Feature to Attack Windows, Linux, and macOS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-koreas-ottercookie-malware/</link>
      <description>WaterPlum, a North Korea-linked attack group, has been targeting financial institutions, cryptocurrency operators, and FinTech companies globally since 2023. They have utilized various malware tools, including BeaverTailand InvisibleFerret, Contagious Interview, and their latest tool, OtterCookie, which has undergone rapid updates and evolved through multiple versions (v1 to v4) with enhanced capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134226</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Pays $1.375 Billion to Texas Over Unauthorized Tracking and Biometric Data Collection</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-pays-1375-billion-to-texas-over.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses two lawsuits against Google related to unauthorized tracking and collection of user data, including geolocation, incognito searches, and biometric data. The company has agreed to pay Texas $1.4 billion to settle the suits, which marks one of the largest privacy-related settlements in history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-pays-1375-billion-to-texas-over.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Shuts Down eXch Over $1.9B Laundering, Seizes €34M in Crypto and 8TB of Data</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/germany-shuts-down-exch-over-19b.html</link>
      <description>The German Federal Criminal Police Office (BKA) seized the online infrastructure and shut down eXch, a cryptocurrency exchange accused of money laundering and operating a criminal trading platform. The operation allegedly allowed users to conceal financial flows without implementing anti-money laundering measures, with an estimated $1.9 billion worth of assets transferred since its launch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/germany-shuts-down-exch-over-19b.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Brief: CVE-2025-31324</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/threat-brief-sap-netweaver-cve-2025-31324/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A critical vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver's Visual Composer Framework (version 7.50) allows unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files, leading to remote code execution and system compromise. The vulnerability is exploited by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to the /developmentserver/metadatauploader endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=140450</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ascension says recent data breach affects over 430,000 patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ascension-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-430-000-patients/</link>
      <description>A data breach disclosed by Ascension, a private healthcare system in the US, affected over 430,000 patients, exposing personal and healthcare information. The breach was caused by a former business partner's vulnerability in third-party software used by the partner, which was exploited in a widespread Clop ransomware attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ascension-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-430-000-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome to use on-device AI to detect tech support scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-to-use-on-device-ai-to-detect-tech-support-scams/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's implementation of a new Chrome security feature that uses the Gemini Nano large-language model to detect and block tech support scams while browsing the web. This feature analyzes web pages in real-time to detect scam signals, and if malicious intent is confirmed, it displays a warning message informing the user of the risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-to-use-on-device-ai-to-detect-tech-support-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dismantles botnet selling hacked routers as residential proxies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-dismantles-botnet-selling-hacked-routers-as-residential-proxies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various router models from Linksys and Cisco; CVE(s): None; Summary: A botnet infected thousands of routers worldwide, including older wireless internet routers, with malware since at least 2004. The compromised devices were used to build two networks of residential proxies (Anyproxy and 5socks) which were sold as proxy servers on the dark web, allowing unauthorized access to be sold for malicious activities such as ad fraud, DDoS attacks, brute forcing, or exploiting victim's data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-dismantles-botnet-selling-hacked-routers-as-residential-proxies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
