<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-847: NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T TorchSerializer Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-847/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T TorchSerializer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23296; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T by deserializing untrusted data. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27210</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-848: NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T secure_server Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-848/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23296; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NVIDIA Isaac-GR00T, without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the secure_server method and can be exploited to access functionality, allowing an attacker to bypass authentication on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27209</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-849: (Pwn2Own) NVIDIA Triton Inference Server SharedMemoryManager Error Message Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-849/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Triton Inference Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23320; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NVIDIA Triton Inference Server without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the SharedMemoryManager class, which outputs an error message containing sensitive information that can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27181</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-850: (Pwn2Own) NVIDIA Triton Inference Server LoadFromSharedMemory Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-850/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Triton Inference Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23333; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. It exists within the LoadFromSharedMemory function due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27249</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-851: (Pwn2Own) NVIDIA Triton Inference Server IPC Push Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-851/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Triton Inference Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23318, ZDI-CAN-27250, ZDI-25-851; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NVIDIA Triton Inference Server without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the processing of IPC messages and can be exploited by crafting an IPC Push request that triggers a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27250</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Unveils Enhanced Features to Empower Defenders and Strengthen AI Security</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-unveils-enhanced-features-to-empower-defenders/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Google Cloud's advancements in AI-powered cybersecurity, including proactive vulnerability detection, automated threat intelligence processing, and workload optimization. The updates focus on securing AI ecosystems, leveraging artificial intelligence to elevate organizational defenses, and providing features such as Sensitive Data Protection, Model Armor, and Security Command Center's AI Protection solution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157866</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Impersonate as Google Support to Sniff Out Your Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-impersonate-as-google-support/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using social engineering tactics to impersonate Google support agents, posing as regional accents to manipulate victims into approving fraudulent account recovery prompts. This tactic exploits Google's legitimatetwo-factor authentication(2FA) and recovery workflows, allowing attackers to bypass standard user-initiated processes and gain control of the account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157859</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple fixes new zero-day flaw exploited in targeted attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-emergency-updates-fix-new-actively-exploited-zero-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43300; Summary: The Image I/O framework contains an out-of-bounds write weakness that allows attackers to cause memory corruption, potentially leading to remote code execution. This vulnerability was exploited in "extremely sophisticated attacks" against targeted individuals and has been patched with improved bounds checking in various Apple operating systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/apple/apple-emergency-updates-fix-new-actively-exploited-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuirkyLoader: A New Malware Loader Spreading Infostealers and Remote Access Trojans (RATs)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/quirkyloader-a-new-malware-loader-spreading-infostealers/</link>
      <description>QuirkyLoader is a sophisticated loader malware that distributes various families of malware (Agent Tesla, AsyncRAT, FormBook, MassLogger, Remcos, Rhadamanthys, Snake Keylogger) through spam emails. The malware uses DLL side-loading and process hollowing to evade detection and inject payloads into processes like AddInProcess32.exe, InstallUtil.exe, or aspnet_wp.exe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157847</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOM-Based Extension Clickjacking Exposes Popular Password Managers to Credential and Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/dom-based-extension-clickjacking.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various password manager plugins for web browsers; CVE(s): None; Summary: The plugins are susceptible to DOM-based extension clickjacking, which could allow attackers to steal account credentials, 2FA codes, and credit card details. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker would create a fake site with an intrusive pop-up and embed an invisible login form that fills in the credential information when clicked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/dom-based-extension-clickjacking.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Rapper Bot” malware seized, alleged developer identified and charged</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/rapper-bot-malware-seized-alleged-developer-identified-and-charged/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has charged Ethan Foltz, the alleged developer and administrator of the "Rapper Bot" DDoS-for-hire botnet, with aiding and abetting computer intrusions. The botnet, which used Mirai-based malware, was seized as part of 'Operation PowerOff' on August 6 and had infected tens of thousands of devices globally, targeting over 18,000 entities across 80 countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/rapper-bot-malware-seized-alleged-developer-identified-and-charged/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks in Japan Surge by 1.4 Times, Signaling a Significant Increase in Cyber Threats</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-attacks-in-japan-surge-by-1-4-times/</link>
      <description>This article reports a significant increase in ransomware attacks targeting Japanese organizations, with 68 cases recorded from January to June 2025. The manufacturing sector was the most affected, and small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) were disproportionately targeted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157804</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perplexity’s Comet AI browser tricked into buying fake items online</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/perplexitys-comet-ai-browser-tricked-into-buying-fake-items-online/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Perplexity's Comet; CVE(s): None; Summary: Agentic AI browser Comet is vulnerable to phishing, prompt injection, and purchasing from fake shops due to inadequate security safeguards. The browser can autonomously interact with malicious pages and prompts, potentially leading to the theft of sensitive information such as credit card data and login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/perplexitys-comet-ai-browser-tricked-into-buying-fake-items-online/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit GenAI Platforms to Craft Sophisticated and Realistic Phishing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-genai-platforms/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting generative AI (GenAI) platforms to orchestrate advanced phishing campaigns, generating hyper-realistic phishing content and impersonating legitimate brands. This misuse amplifies social engineering threats and complicates detection. AI-powered website builders are being actively abused to deploy phishing pages with unprecedented speed, often generating fully functional sites in seconds based on simple prompts without verification requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157793</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Warns FSB-Linked Hackers Exploiting Unpatched Cisco Devices for Cyber Espionage</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fbi-warns-russian-fsb-linked-hackers.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2018-0171; Summary: A seven-year-old security flaw (CVSS score: 9.8) in the Smart Install feature of Cisco IOS Software and Cisco IOS XE software allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fbi-warns-russian-fsb-linked-hackers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers steal Microsoft logins using legitimate ADFS redirects</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-steal-microsoft-logins-using-legitimate-adfs-redirects/</link>
      <description>Hackers are using a novel technique that combines legitimate office.com links with Active Directory Federation Services (ADFS) to redirect users to a phishing page that steals Microsoft 365 logins. The method bypasses traditional URL-based detection and multi-factor authentication by leveraging a trusted domain on Microsoft's infrastructure for the initial redirect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-steal-microsoft-logins-using-legitimate-adfs-redirects/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaly Wolf Unleashing Attacks to Expose Organizations’ Hidden Secrets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scaly-wolf-unleashing-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a targeted attack by the Scaly Wolf APT group against a Russian engineering company. The attackers used phishing emails to deliver modular backdoors, including Trojan.Updatar.1, which deployed subsequent malware components and facilitated data exfiltration, system reconnaissance, and persistent access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157775</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major password managers can leak logins in clickjacking attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-password-managers-can-leak-logins-in-clickjacking-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Six major password managers (1Password, Bitwarden, Enpass, iCloud Passwords, LastPass, and LogMeOnce); CVE(s): None; Summary: The password managers are vulnerable to unpatched clickjacking flaws that could allow attackers to steal account credentials, 2FA codes, and credit card details. Threat actors can exploit the security issues by overlaying invisible HTML elements over the password manager interface, tricking users into revealing sensitive information through autofill actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-password-managers-can-leak-logins-in-clickjacking-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft investigates outage impacting Copilot, Office.com</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-outage-impacting-copilot-officecom/</link>
      <description>This article reports on an ongoing issue preventing users in North America from accessing Office.com and the Copilot AI-powered assistant. The issue is causing server connection problems and login issues for some users, with the root cause still under investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-outage-impacting-copilot-officecom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why email security needs its EDR moment to move beyond prevention</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/why-email-security-needs-its-edr-moment-to-move-beyond-prevention/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the evolution of email security, comparing it to the growth of Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). It highlights the limitations of traditional email security approaches and emphasizes the need for a layered defense that includes post-breach protections. The article does not specifically mention a vulnerability but rather explores the future of email security and its integration with other productivity tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/why-email-security-needs-its-edr-moment-to-move-beyond-prevention/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERT/CC Issues Alert on Critical Flaws in Workhorse Municipal Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cert-cc-issues-alert-on-critical-flaws-in-workhorse/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Workhorse Software Services' municipal accounting software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-9037, CVE-2025-9040; Summary: The software has two critical design flaws that allow unauthorized access to sensitive government financial data and personally identifiable information. The first vulnerability stores SQL Server connection strings in plaintext configuration files, while the second allows unauthenticated users to create complete database backups. Exploitation of these vulnerabilities could lead to data theft, tampering with financial records, and compromising audit trails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157885</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Hacker Sentenced for Defacing and Hacking Organizational Websites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/serial-hacker-sentenced/</link>
      <description>Al-Tahery Al-Mashriky, a member of extremist hacking collectives, was sentenced to 20 months in prison for illegal computer access and data exfiltration. He exploited vulnerabilities in low-security web infrastructures to gain unauthorized access and deployed hidden webpages with propagandistic content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157752</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Find AI Browsers Can Be Tricked by PromptFix Exploit to Run Malicious Hidden Prompts</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/experts-find-ai-browsers-can-be-tricked.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new prompt injection technique called PromptFix that can trick generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) models into carrying out intended actions by embedding malicious instructions inside a fake CAPTCHA check on a web page. This attack technique demonstrates how AI-driven browsers, such as Perplexity's Comet, can be deceived into interacting with phishing landing pages or fraudulent lookalike storefronts without human intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/experts-find-ai-browsers-can-be-tricked.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian state-sponsored espionage group Static Tundra compromises unpatched end-of-life network devices</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/static-tundra/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco IOS software and Cisco IOS XE software; CVE(s): CVE-2018-0171; Summary: Static Tundra, a Russian state-sponsored cyber espionage group, has been compromising unpatched and often end-of-life network devices by exploiting the seven-year-old vulnerability (CVE-2018-0171) in the Smart Install feature. The group targets organizations of strategic interest to Russia, primarily in telecommunications, higher education, and manufacturing sectors. Static Tundra uses bespoke tooling, including the historic SYNful Knock firmware implant, to maintain access for multiple years without being detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a479d3e2d85f00011b8231</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copilot Vulnerability Lets Attackers Bypass Audit Logs and Gain Hidden Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/copilot-vulnerability-lets-attackers-bypass-audit-logs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft M365 Copilot; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Microsoft's M365 Copilot allowed users to access sensitive files without leaving any trace in audit logs, creating significant security and compliance risks for organizations worldwide. The flaw exploited a fundamental issue in how Copilot handles audit logging, making it possible for malicious insiders or accidental interactions to delete audit entries, potentially causing incomplete and inaccurate audit logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157871</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legitimate Chrome VPN with 100K+ Installs Secretly Captures Screenshots and Exfiltrates Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/legitimate-chrome-vpn-with-100k-installs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: FreeVPN.One; CVE(s): None; Summary: The FreeVPN.One Chrome extension, with over 100,000 installations, has been found to be spyware that captures screenshots of users' browsing activities and exfiltrates them to remote servers without user consent or notification. The extension's malicious behavior uses a two-stage architecture for screenshot capture and demands excessive permissions, enabling the exfiltration of highly sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157717</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft reportedly fixing SSD failures caused by Windows updates</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-reportedly-fixing-ssd-failures-caused-by-windows-updates/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The recent Windows 11 24H2 updates are causing data corruption and failure issues for some SSD and HDD models on up-to-date systems, affecting drives with Phison NAND controllers, SanDisk Extreme Pro, Corsair Force MP600, Maxio SSD, KIOXIA EXCERIA PLUS G4, KIOXIA M.2 SSD, and other drives with Phison PS5012-E12 and InnoGrit controllers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-reportedly-fixing-ssd-failures-caused-by-windows-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🕵️ Webinar: Discover and Control Shadow AI Agents in Your Enterprise Before Hackers Do</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-discover-and-control-shadow-ai.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather highlights the growing concern of "shadow AI agents" that are being deployed without proper identification, ownership, or logging. These autonomous software agents can potentially be compromised and used to move through systems, grab sensitive data, or escalate privileges at machine speed. The article emphasizes the need for enterprises to bring these agents under control and implement strategies to assign accountability and enforce guardrails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-discover-and-control-shadow-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo AI Chatbot Flaw Allows Remote Script Execution on Corporate Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lenovo-ai-chatbot-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo; CVE(s): None; Summary: Lenovo's AI-powered customer support chatbot (Lena) contains multiple security flaws that enable Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks, allowing attackers to execute malicious scripts, steal sensitive session data, and potentially gain unauthorized access to corporate systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157778</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Issues Emergency Patch for Windows Reset and Recovery Bug</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-issues-emergency-patch-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports a critical issue affecting Windows reset and recovery operations across multiple versions of the operating system. A non-security out-of-band update has been released to resolve the problem, which causes some reset and recovery attempts to fail on client versions of Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157763</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Impact to Action: Turning BIA Insights Into Resilient Recovery</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/turning-bia-insights-into-resilient-recovery.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of having a robust Business Continuity and Disaster Recovery (BCDR) strategy in modern businesses. It highlights the need to conduct a business impact analysis (BIA) to identify critical functions for a business's operations and survival. The article also emphasizes the role of IT leaders in making the BIA work, ensuring that the recovery plan is executable, integrated into everyday operations, tested, and ready to scale with the business. Additionally, it provides guidance on how to conduct a BIA, including prioritizing threats, identifying critical business functions, and establishing RTOs and RPOs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/turning-bia-insights-into-resilient-recovery.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Capsule Vulnerability Enables Attackers to Inject Arbitrary Labels</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kubernetes-capsule-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kubernetes Capsule; CVE(s): CVE-2025-55205; Summary: Authenticated tenant users can inject arbitrary labels into system namespaces, bypassing multi-tenant isolation and potentially leading to cluster-wide compromise. This vulnerability enables attackers to access cross-tenant resources, circumvent quota restrictions, and exploit sensitive configurations and secrets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157753</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Apache ActiveMQ Flaw to Breach Cloud Linux Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-apache-activemq-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache ActiveMQ; CVE(s): CVE-2023-46604; Summary: Hackers are exploiting a critical remote code execution vulnerability in Apache ActiveMQ (CVE-2023-46604) to gain access to victim systems, and then patching the flaw after gaining control. This unusual behavior is used to prevent other threat actors from exploiting the same vulnerability and reduces detection by vulnerability scanners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157748</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeRabbit RCE Flaw Gives Attackers Write Access to 1M Repositories</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coderabbit-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CodeRabbit; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical remote code execution vulnerability in CodeRabbit allowed attackers to gain read and write access to over one million code repositories, including private ones. The vulnerability exploited CodeRabbit's integration with external static analysis tools, specifically targeting Rubocop, a Ruby static analyzer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157728</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea Uses GitHub in Diplomat Cyber Attacks as IT Worker Scheme Hits 320+ Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/north-korea-uses-github-in-diplomat.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on a coordinated cyber espionage campaign attributed to North Korean threat actors (Kimsuky) targeting diplomatic missions in South Korea. The campaign involved spear-phishing emails impersonating trusted contacts, which led to the delivery of Xeno RAT malware through cloud storage solutions like Dropbox and Daum Cloud.

FYSA: The campaign's infrastructure and tactics suggest a potential collaborative effort between North Korean operatives and Chinese resources for intelligence gathering efforts. The use of Korean services and infrastructure was likely intentional to blend into the South Korean network, and the attackers leveraged GitHub as a covert command-and-control channel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/north-korea-uses-github-in-diplomat.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Salty 2FA PhaaS Platform Targets Microsoft 365 Users to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-salty-2fa-phaas-platform-targets-microsoft-365-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Salty 2FA; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Salty 2FA Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) framework is a sophisticated phishing kit that targets Microsoft 365 credentials through a multi-stage execution chain. It uses evasion techniques, including rotating CAPTCHAs and fingerprinting, to bypass detection and analysis. The kit's unique characteristics include "salted" payloads, advanced obfuscation methods, and behavioral patterns such as the use of .com + .ru domain chains and specific Cloudflare resource requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157705</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Windows upgrades failing with 0x8007007F error</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-upgrades-failing-with-0x8007007f-error/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on a resolved issue that caused Windows upgrades to fail with 0x8007007F errors on some Windows 11 and Windows Server systems. The issue affected specific upgrade paths, including upgrades from Windows 10 to Windows 11, and from Windows Server 2016 to Windows Server 2022. Users experiencing the issue are advised to retry the upgrade process after the bug was fixed as of August 15, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-upgrades-failing-with-0x8007007f-error/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New GodRAT Malware Uses Screensaver and Program Files to Target Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-godrat-malware-uses-screensaver-and-program-files/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the deployment of a novel Remote Access Trojan (RAT) called GodRAT, which is distributed via Skype as malicious .scr and .pif executables. GodRAT represents an evolution of the AwesomePuppet backdoor, sharing code similarities and distribution methods, and is likely linked to the Winnti APT group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157671</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft releases emergency updates to fix Windows recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-updates-to-fix-windows-recovery/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The August 2025 Windows security updates cause issues with reset and recovery operations, impacting systems running Windows 10 and older versions of Windows 11. Installing the emergency out-of-band updates is recommended instead. The issue also affects IT professionals who want to remotely reset devices via RemoteWipe CSP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-updates-to-fix-windows-recovery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome High-Severity Vulnerability Could Let Attackers Run Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-high-severity-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-9132; Summary: The vulnerability affects the V8 JavaScript engine in Chrome, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code with the same privileges as the affected application. This out-of-bounds write issue can be exploited through specially crafted web pages or malicious JavaScript content, potentially enabling attackers to bypass sandbox security mechanisms and access sensitive user data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157664</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams “Couldn’t Connect” Issue After Sidebar Update Gets a Fix</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-couldnt-connect-gets-a-fix/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Teams; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53783; Summary: A recent interface enhancement update caused a widespread service disruption in Microsoft Teams, resulting in an error message when launching the application. The issue is not related to security risks and user data remains protected. Affected users can bypass the error by clicking on specific icons in the left-hand navigation sidebar.

FYSA: None.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157659</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 05:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McDonald’s Free Nuggets Hack Exposes Sensitive Customer Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mcdonalds-free-nuggets-hack-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: McDonald's; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports multiple critical vulnerabilities in McDonald's digital infrastructure, exposing sensitive customer data and allowing unauthorized access to internal corporate systems. The vulnerabilities include client-side password validation, plaintext passwords, API keys and secrets embedded in JavaScript code, and lack of authentication for administrative functions.

Note: No specific CVEs are mentioned in the article, so I've listed "None" as there are no publicly assigned CVEs for these vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157654</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Charges 22-Year-Old for Running RapperBot Botnet Behind 370,000 DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/doj-charges-22-year-old-for-running.html</link>
      <description>A 22-year-old man from Oregon has been charged with developing and overseeing a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS)-for-hire botnet called RapperBot. The botnet, which was used to carry out large-scale attacks targeting victims in over 80 countries since at least 2021, has been dismantled as part of an international effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/doj-charges-22-year-old-for-running.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Man Charged in ‘Rapper Bot’ DDoS Service</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/08/oregon-man-charged-in-rapper-bot-ddos-service/</link>
      <description>A 22-year-old Oregon man has been arrested for operating a massive botnet called Rapper Bot, which was used to launch distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks against targets. The botnet, which consisted of tens of thousands of hacked Internet of Things (IoT) devices, was rented out to online extortionists and caused significant disruptions to websites and networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71944</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>47,000 Individuals Affected by Data Breach, Reveals NY Business Council</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/47000-individuals-affected-by-data-breach/</link>
      <description>The Business Council of New York State has disclosed a data breach impacting approximately 47,329 individuals, likely caused by an external system intrusion exploiting weaknesses such as unpatched software vulnerabilities or phishing-enabled initial access vectors. The breach highlights the importance of real-time monitoring and vulnerability management to mitigate similar risks, as well as the need for proactive threat intelligence sharing among industry peers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157607</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPI now blocks domain resurrection attacks used for hijacking accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pypi-now-blocks-domain-resurrection-attacks-used-for-hijacking-accounts/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI (Python Package Index); CVE(s): None; Summary: The Python Package Index (PyPI) has introduced new protections against domain resurrection attacks that enable hijacking accounts through password resets. PyPI now checks whether the domains of verified email addresses on the platform have expired or are entering expiration phases, and marks those addresses as unverified. This closes the opportunity window for exploitation even if an attacker registers the domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pypi-now-blocks-domain-resurrection-attacks-used-for-hijacking-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Exposes DPRK IT Workers’ Email Addresses and Recruitment Trends</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-research-exposes-dprk-it-workers/</link>
      <description>The article reveals the tactics and techniques used by DPRK-affiliated IT professionals, known as the "Jasper Sleet" threat actor group, to gain unauthorized access to company networks. They exploit remote work opportunities in Web3, blockchain, and cryptocurrency industries, using legitimate employment to bypass traditional initial access vectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157590</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Research Reveals Security Vulnerabilities Linked to Popular VPN Apps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-research-reveals-security-vulnerabilities-linked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple VPN providers; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reveals that multiple major VPN providers have been found to be linked to three distinct "families" with shared code bases, servers, and cryptographic credentials. This lack of transparency correlates with widespread security vulnerabilities, including reused passwords, deprecated ciphers, and hard-coded symmetric keys, compromising user privacy and exposing sensitive data to interception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157577</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Okta open-sources catalog of Auth0 rules for threat detection</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/okta-open-sources-catalog-of-auth0-rules-for-threat-detection/</link>
      <description>Okta has open-sourced Sigma-based queries for Auth0 customers to detect account takeovers, misconfigurations, and suspicious behavior in event logs. The company aims to help security teams analyze Auth0 logs for suspicious activity that could indicate intrusion attempts, account takeovers, or other malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/okta-open-sources-catalog-of-auth0-rules-for-threat-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shares workaround for Teams "couldn't connect" error</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-workaround-for-teams-couldnt-connect-error/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a known issue with Microsoft Teams causing "couldn't connect" errors when launching the application. The company is working to resolve the issue and provides a temporary workaround until the fix rolls out to all impacted users. Additionally, the article highlights Microsoft's efforts to enhance security features in Teams, including protection against malicious URLs and dangerous file types, as well as an allow/block list for incoming communications from blocked domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-workaround-for-teams-couldnt-connect-error/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache ActiveMQ Flaw Exploited to Deploy DripDropper Malware on Cloud Linux Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/apache-activemq-flaw-exploited-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache ActiveMQ; CVE(s): CVE-2023-46604; Summary: A maximum-severity remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2023-46604) in Apache ActiveMQ allows threat actors to gain persistent access to cloud Linux systems, deploy malware, and patch the vulnerability to prevent further exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/apache-activemq-flaw-exploited-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Phishers Target Brokerage Customers in ‘Ramp and Dump’ Cashout Scheme</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mobile-phishers-target-brokerage-customers/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminal groups have evolved their mobile phishing kits to exploit brokerage accounts in "ramp-and-dump" schemes, leveraging compromised user credentials to manipulate foreign stock prices and circumvent traditional security controls. The kits enable attackers to preposition themselves in low-liquidity stocks by liquidating victims' existing positions and reallocating funds, exploiting vulnerabilities in brokeragemulti-factor authentication (MFA) systems, particularly those relying on phishable one-time passcodes (OTPs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157559</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic rejects claims of a zero-day RCE flaw in Defend EDR</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/elastic-rejects-claims-of-a-zero-day-rce-flaw-in-defend-edr/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Elastic Defend; CVE(s): None; Summary: AshES Cybersecurity claims to have discovered a remote code execution (RCE) flaw in Elastic Defend that would allow an attacker to bypass EDR protections, but Elastic's Security Engineering team was unable to reproduce the vulnerability and its effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/elastic-rejects-claims-of-a-zero-day-rce-flaw-in-defend-edr/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases $4 ChatGPT plan, but it's not available in the US for now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-releases-4-chatgpt-plan-but-its-not-available-in-the-us-for-now/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be an announcement from OpenAI about their new GPT Go subscription plan and its features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-releases-4-chatgpt-plan-but-its-not-available-in-the-us-for-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ClickFix Attack Deploys Fake BBC News Page and Fake Cloudflare Verification to Deceive Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-clickfix-attack-deploys-fake-bbc-news-page/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a novel ClickFix attack variant that impersonates trusted BBC news content while leveraging counterfeit Cloudflare Turnstile verification interfaces to coerce users into executing malicious PowerShell commands. The attack exploits user familiarity with legitimate web security protocols, delivering malware payloads including infostealers, ransomware, and remote access trojans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157601</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized Copyright Documents Used by Threat Actors to Target Key Employees with Noodlophile Stealer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-copyright-documents-used-by-threat-actors/</link>
      <description>The Noodlophile Stealer malware has evolved into a targeted spear-phishing operation that weaponizes copyright infringement notices to infiltrate enterprises with substantial Facebook presences. It employs multilingual content, exploits legitimate software vulnerabilities, and delivers malicious payloads disguised as evidence files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157548</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New GodRAT Trojan Targets Trading Firms Using Steganography and Gh0st RAT Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-godrat-trojan-targets-trading-firms.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a previously unreported remote access trojan called GodRAT, which delivers shellcode to download malware from a command-and-control server using steganography. The malware is based on Gh0st RAT and has been detected targeting countries in Asia, Europe, and the Middle East since September 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-godrat-trojan-targets-trading-firms.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma firm Inotiv says ransomware attack impacted operations</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pharma-firm-inotiv-says-ransomware-attack-impacted-operations/</link>
      <description>American pharmaceutical company Inotiv has been affected by a ransomware attack, which resulted in the encryption of some of its systems and data. The attack was claimed by the Qilin ransomware gang, who allegedly stole around 162,000 files amounting to 176GB and published data samples on their leak site. The incident has caused disruptions to certain business operations, with the company's IT team working to restore affected systems and migrate some operations offline to mitigate the impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pharma-firm-inotiv-says-ransomware-attack-impacted-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: Beast Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-beast-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Beast Ransomware, a multi-platform Ransomware-as-a-Service operated by affiliates. It has evolved from its origins as Monster and now targets Windows, Linux, and VMware ESXi systems. The ransomware uses various entry points to deploy, including phishing emails and compromised RDP endpoints, and can spread laterally to other systems without manual intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062749</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: August security updates break Windows recovery, reset</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-august-security-updates-break-windows-recovery-reset/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The August 2025 Windows security updates are breaking reset and recovery operations on systems running Windows 10 and older versions of Windows 11, causing issues with reinstalling the system while keeping files or remotely resetting devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-august-security-updates-break-windows-recovery-reset/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Exploit for Chained SAP Flaws Exposes Unpatched Systems to Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/public-exploit-for-chained-sap-flaws.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A new exploit combines two previously patched vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-31324 and CVE-2025-42999) to bypass authentication and achieve remote code execution. This allows attackers to upload arbitrary files, execute operating system commands with SAP administrator privileges, and conduct living-off-the-land attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/public-exploit-for-chained-sap-flaws.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in Scans From Hacked Cisco, Linksys, and Araknis Routers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surge-in-scans-from-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Small Business RV series routers, Linksys LRT series, Araknis Networks (AN-300-RT-4L2W); CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers have identified a significant increase in malicious scanning activities originating from compromised consumer and enterprise networking equipment, with a focus on Cisco, Linksys, and Araknis router models. The compromised devices are being used to conduct reconnaissance scans against internet-connected systems, potentially serving as launching points for more sophisticated attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP 0-Day Exploit Reportedly Leaked by ShinyHunters Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-0-day-exploit-reportedly-leaked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A sophisticated exploit targeting critical SAP vulnerabilities has been publicly released by ShinyHunters, which chains multiple zero-day vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary commands on target SAP systems. The exploit uses a deserialization vulnerability (CVE-2025-42999) to enable "live off the land" attacks and adjusts dynamically based on SAP NetWeaver versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157568</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Business Council discloses data breach affecting 47,000 people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/business-council-of-new-york-state-discloses-data-breach-affecting-47-000-people/</link>
      <description>The Business Council of New York State (BCNYS) has revealed a data breach that affected over 47,000 individuals, exposing personal, financial, and health information. The attackers stole files containing sensitive information, including names, Social Security numbers, dates of birth, and medical records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/business-council-of-new-york-state-discloses-data-breach-affecting-47-000-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Desigo CC Product Family and SENTRON Powermanager</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-231-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Desigo CC Product Family and SENTRON Powermanager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47809; Summary: A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Wibu CodeMeter before 8.30a, allowing a local user to gain elevated privileges after an unprivileged installation with UAC, without restarting the system. Successful exploitation could allow privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23807</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/19/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA has released four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories regarding vulnerabilities in Siemens' Desigo CC Product Family, Mendix SAML Module, Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced, and EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters. The advisories provide technical details and mitigations for the identified security issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23809</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Mendix SAML Module</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-231-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Mendix SAML Module; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40758; Summary: Improper verification of cryptographic signature in affected versions of the module allows unauthenticated remote attackers to hijack an account in specific SSO configurations, with a CVSS v3.1 base score of 8.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23808</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android Attack Targets Indian Users with Free Electricity Subsidy to Install Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-android-attack-targets-indian-users/</link>
      <description>A newly identified Android phishing campaign targets Indian users by masquerading as a government initiative offering subsidies for solar rooftop installations. The attackers leverage a fabricated mobile application to deceive victims into installing malware, promising free electricity units and stealing sensitive banking information, contacts, and SMS data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157518</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 2025: Allianz, Qantas, M&amp;S, Co-op Breaches, $140M Bank Hack &amp; SharePoint 0-Day Exploits</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/major-cyber-attacks-july-2025/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses a series of major cyberattacks that took place in July 2025. These attacks targeted various sectors, including airlines, insurers, banks, retailers, and government agencies. The breaches involved stolen credentials, zero-day exploits, and social engineering tactics. Some notable cases include the Allianz Life breach, which exposed millions of customer records; the Qantas breach, which exposed customer data; and the Abacus Market shutdown, which was likely an exit scam. Additionally, the article mentions a critical SharePoint zero-day exploit (CVE-2025-53770) that was chained with other vulnerabilities to gain persistent access. The attacks demonstrate the evolving nature of cyber threats and the importance of having visibility into these attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062735</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. Government Drops Apple Encryption Backdoor Order After U.S. Civil Liberties Pushback</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/uk-government-drops-apple-encryption.html</link>
      <description>The UK government has dropped its plan to force Apple to create a backdoor for accessing encrypted user data, following criticism from privacy advocates and Apple's appeals against the legality of the order. This development highlights the ongoing debate between governments seeking access to encrypted data and companies prioritizing user privacy and security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/uk-government-drops-apple-encryption.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Your Security Culture is Critical to Mitigating Cyber Risk</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/why-your-security-culture-is-critical.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of human risk in cybersecurity and how it often goes unaddressed despite being a significant driver of breaches. The author argues that instead of focusing on technology alone, organizations should prioritize cultivating a strong security culture that simplifies and supports secure human behavior. The article provides guidance on evaluating and strengthening an organization's security culture by examining leadership signals, security team engagement, policy design, and security training.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/why-your-security-culture-is-critical.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Kimsuky Hackers Use GitHub to Target Foreign Embassies with XenoRAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-kimsuky-hackers-use-github/</link>
      <description>The Kimsuky group (APT43) launched a DPRK-linked espionage operation targeting diplomatic missions in South Korea. The campaign involved spear-phishing emails with ZIP files hosting malware, which delivered payloads via Dropbox and Daum, allowing for data exfiltration and payload retrieval over HTTPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157503</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender AI Can Detect Plaintext Credentials in Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-defender-ai-detect-plaintext-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Active Directory systems; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability lies in the storage of plaintext credentials in free text fields within Active Directory and Microsoft Entra ID systems. This allows attackers to easily exploit the credentials, which are often stored for operational flexibility and simplicity. The AI-powered security capability from Microsoft detects exposed credentials with unprecedented precision, helping organizations eliminate this critical attack vector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157533</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware incidents in Japan during the first half of 2025</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/ransomware_incidents_in_japan_during_the_first_half_of_2025/</link>
      <description>This article reports on the increase in ransomware attacks in Japan, with a focus on small and medium-sized enterprises. The most affected industry remains manufacturing, while the ransomware group "Qilin" has been causing the most damage. The article also discusses the emergence of new groups like Kawa4096 and provides details on the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) used by these groups, including the use of the Salsa20 stream cipher for encryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689d7430e2d85f00011b7ffd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JJ Cummings: The art of controlling information</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/jj-cummings-the-art-of-controlling-information/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability or cybersecurity-relevant content. It appears to be an employee spotlight or career development story featuring JJ Cummings, leader of Cisco's Threat Intelligence and Interdiction team, discussing his role, challenges, and experiences at the company. The article does not contain any threat actor, tactics, infrastructure, scams, or impacts relevant to cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689f4691e2d85f00011b8197</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashionable Phishing Bait: GenAI on the Hook</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/genai-phishing-bait/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the growing adoption of generative AI (GenAI) and its potential to introduce new risks in cybersecurity. It highlights how GenAI can be misused by threat actors to create realistic phishing content, clone trusted brands, and automate large-scale deployment using services like low-code site builders. The article also provides indicators of these activities to support detection and response efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=152030</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPI Moves to Stop Domain Resurrection Attacks with Expired Domain Blocks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pypi-moves-to-stop-domain-resurrection-attacks/</link>
      <description>The Python Package Index (PyPI) has implemented new security measures to prevent domain resurrection attacks, a type of supply-chain threat that exploits email-based account verification systems. PyPI's solution leverages Domainr's Status API to monitor and update the status of user email addresses associated with domains entering expiration phases, automatically unverifying previously validated email addresses when a domain enters the redemption period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157527</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 09:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockbit Linux ESXi Ransomware Variant Reveals Evasion Techniques and File Encryption Process</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lockbit-linux-esxi-ransomware-variant/</link>
      <description>The article analyzes a Lockbit ransomware variant targeting Linux-based ESXi servers. It highlights the malware's evasion techniques, operational details, and encryption methods, including its use of ptrace to detect debugging environments and libsodium for key generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157493</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Packages Target Crypto Developers to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-npm-packages-target-crypto-developers/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a threat campaign dubbed "Solana-Scan" that deploys malicious npm packages to infiltrate the Solana cryptocurrency ecosystem. The packages, published by an actor operating under the handle "cryptohan", aim to lure developers in the crypto space and collect sensitive information such as cryptocurrency tokens, wallet credentials, and exchange login details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157343</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Allianz Life data breach impacts 1.1 million people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/massive-allianz-life-data-breach-impacts-11-million-people/</link>
      <description>Hackers stole the personal information of 1.1 million individuals in a Salesforce data theft attack that impacted Allianz Life, a U.S. insurance giant, and other high-profile companies worldwide. The attackers tricked employees into linking malicious OAuth apps to their company's Salesforce instance, allowing them to download and steal databases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/massive-allianz-life-data-breach-impacts-11-million-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PipeMagic Malware Imitates ChatGPT App to Exploit Windows Vulnerability and Deploy Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pipemagic-malware-imitates-chatgpt-app/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29824; Summary: PipeMagic malware is a modular backdoor that exploits the Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) elevation-of-privilege vulnerability. It poses as ChatGPT Desktop Application and enables privilege escalation, ransomware deployment, and command-and-control communication over TCP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157478</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sni5Gect Attack Targets 5G to Steal Messages and Inject Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sni5gect-attack-targets-5g/</link>
      <description>The SNI5GECT framework is a sophisticated attack framework that can intercept 5G communications, inject malicious payloads without requiring a rogue base station, and demonstrate multiple attack vectors that pose serious security risks to 5G users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157476</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Active Exploitation of Trend Micro Apex One Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-trend-micro-apex-one-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54948; Summary: The vulnerability affects the Trend Micro Apex One Management Console's on-premise deployments, allowing pre-authenticated remote attackers to upload malicious code and execute arbitrary commands, posing significant risks to organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157472</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 06:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPI Blocks 1,800 Expired-Domain Emails to Prevent Account Takeovers and Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/pypi-blocks-1800-expired-domain-emails.html</link>
      <description>The Python Package Index (PyPI) repository now checks for expired domains to prevent supply chain attacks. This change aims to tackle domain resurrection attacks that occur when attackers purchase an expired domain and use it to take control of PyPI accounts through password resets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/pypi-blocks-1800-expired-domain-emails.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 06:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Cisco Secure Links to Evade Scanners and Bypass Filters</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-cisco-secure-links/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Safe Links; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybercriminals exploit the trust in Cisco's security infrastructure by generating legitimate Cisco Safe Links for malicious purposes. They compromise accounts within Cisco-protected organizations, exploit SaaS services, or recycle active Safe Links to send phishing emails that bypass network filters and evade traditional email security scanners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157465</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Websites Compromised, Allowing Hackers Access to Employee and Confidential Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/intel-websites-compromised/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intel; CVE(s): None; Summary: Four internal Intel websites were found to have critical security flaws, exposing personal details of over 270,000 employees and potentially granting attackers access to sensitive corporate information. The vulnerabilities allowed for login bypasses, hardcoded credentials, exposed tokens, and GitHub access token manipulation, enabling unauthorized access and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157458</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 04:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Pirated Games to Bypass Microsoft Defender SmartScreen and Adblockers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-pirated-games/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated malware campaign where threat actors distribute HijackLoader, a modular malware loader, by leveraging pirated game downloads. The malware bypasses common defenses like adblockers and Microsoft Defender SmartScreen, and its modular architecture allows it to evade detection and persistence mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157423</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Locker Ransomware Launches Targeted Attacks on the Oil and Gas Sector in Pakistan</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/blue-locker-ransomware-launches-targeted-attacks/</link>
      <description>Blue Locker ransomware has compromised critical infrastructure in Pakistan, including Pakistan Petroleum Limited (PPL), using advanced tactics such as AES-RSA encryption, privilege escalation via registry modifications, and defense evasion through obfuscation and timestomping.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157363</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XenoRAT malware campaign hits multiple embassies in South Korea</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/xenorat-malware-campaign-hits-multiple-embassies-in-south-korea/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a state-sponsored espionage campaign targeting foreign embassies in South Korea, deploying XenoRAT malware from malicious GitHub repositories. The campaign has been ongoing since March and uses spearphishing attacks with contextual email lures and password-protected archives containing obfuscated PowerShell code that retrieves the XenoRAT payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/xenorat-malware-campaign-hits-multiple-embassies-in-south-korea/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noodlophile Malware Campaign Expands Global Reach with Copyright Phishing Lures</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/noodlophile-malware-campaign-expands.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors behind the Noodlophile malware are using spear-phishing emails with updated delivery mechanisms to deploy the information stealer in attacks targeting enterprises in the U.S., Europe, Baltic countries, and the Asia-Pacific region. The campaign leverages advanced spear-phishing emails posing as copyright infringement notices, tailored with reconnaissance-derived details like specific Facebook Page IDs and company ownership information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/noodlophile-malware-campaign-expands.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska man gets 1 year in prison for $3.5M cryptojacking scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nebraska-man-gets-1-year-in-prison-for-35m-cryptojacking-scheme/</link>
      <description>A Nebraska man was sentenced to one year in prison for defrauding cloud computing providers of over $3.5 million to mine cryptocurrency worth nearly $1 million. The individual, Charles O. Parks III, used various aliases and corporate entities to create accounts with multiple cloud service providers and laundered the illegal cryptocurrency proceeds using multiple crypto exchanges, online payment services, a New York City non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace, as well as bank accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nebraska-man-gets-1-year-in-prison-for-35m-cryptojacking-scheme/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Microsoft Help Index File to Deploy PipeMagic Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-microsoft-help-index-file/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29824; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to escalate privileges from a standard user account, facilitating ransomware deployment by groups like Storm-2460. The exploitation involves the use of a Microsoft Help Index File (.mshi) to deploy the PipeMagic backdoor, marking a notable evolution in malware delivery methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157326</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERMAC Android malware source code leak exposes banking trojan infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ermac-android-malware-source-code-leak-exposes-banking-trojan-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The source code for ERMAC Android banking trojan version 3.0 has been leaked online, exposing the malware's internals and infrastructure. The latest version targets over 700 banking, shopping, and cryptocurrency apps, with capabilities such as theft of sensitive user information, file access, and device control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ermac-android-malware-source-code-leak-exposes-banking-trojan-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized Python Package “termncolor” Uses Windows Run Key for Persistence</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-python-package-termncolor/</link>
      <description>A complex supply chain attack was discovered on the Python Package Index (PyPI), where a seemingly innocuous package "termncolor" imports a malicious dependency "colorinal" that triggers a multi-stage malware deployment. The attack uses DLL sideloading, AES-encrypted payloads, and disguised command-and-control communications to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157315</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK sentences “serial hacker” of 3,000 sites to 20 months in prison</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/uk-sentences-serial-hacker-of-3-000-sites-to-20-months-in-prison/</link>
      <description>A UK-based 26-year-old hacker, Al-Tahery Al-Mashriky, has been sentenced to 20 months in prison for hacking thousands of websites and stealing login details of millions of Facebook users. The investigation revealed that Al-Mashriky was linked to extremist groups and used stolen data to target and defraud individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/uk-sentences-serial-hacker-of-3-000-sites-to-20-months-in-prison/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 800 N-able servers left unpatched against critical flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-800-n-able-servers-left-unpatched-against-critical-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N-able N-central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8875, CVE-2025-8876; Summary: Over 800 N-central servers remain unpatched against two critical security vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-8875 and CVE-2025-8876) that can allow authenticated attackers to inject commands or execute commands on unpatched devices. The flaws are actively exploited, and N-able has patched them in N-central 2025.3.1, urging admins to secure their servers before further information is released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-800-n-able-servers-left-unpatched-against-critical-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Windows Vulnerability Exploited to Deploy PipeMagic RansomExx Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-windows-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29824; Summary: A privilege escalation vulnerability (CVE-2025-29824) in the Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) was exploited by threat actors to deploy the PipeMagic malware in RansomExx ransomware attacks. The vulnerability, patched by Microsoft in April 2025, allowed attackers to infiltrate victim infrastructure and deploy a full-fledged backdoor providing remote access and executing commands on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-windows-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Telegram as the Communication Channel to Exfiltrate Stolen Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-telegram-as-the-communication-channel/</link>
      <description>The article describes a phishing campaign targeting public sector clients in Kazakhstan, using Telegram's Bot API as a covert exfiltration channel. The attack employed social engineering tactics and exploited user trust through fake login pages and pre-filled email fields.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157194</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla warns Germany could soon declare ad blockers illegal</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/mozilla-warns-germany-could-soon-declare-ad-blockers-illegal/</link>
      <description>The German Federal Supreme Court's ruling on browser-based ad blockers has revived a legal battle over whether ad blockers infringe copyright, potentially leading to a ban of the tools in Germany. This could impact other browser extensions and users' choices, as well as raise concerns about a chilling effect on freedom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/mozilla-warns-germany-could-soon-declare-ad-blockers-illegal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Details of SAP 0-Day Exploitation Script for RCE Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-0-day-exploitation-script-for-rce-revealed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver's Visual Composer Metadata Uploader; CVE(s): CVE-2025–31324; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in the metadata uploader enables unauthenticated file uploads leading to remote code execution under SAP service account privileges. The exploit script automates the process, allowing attackers to upload arbitrary files and gain persistent access to affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157182</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bragg Confirms Cyberattack, Internal IT Systems Breached</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bragg-confirms-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVEs: None; Summary: The Bragg Gaming Group has disclosed a cybersecurity incident that compromised its internal computer systems. The company's preliminary investigation suggests the breach is contained within their internal environment, with no indication of personal information being compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157394</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoJ Seizes $2.8M in Crypto from Zeppelin Ransomware Group</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/doj-seizes-2-8m-in-crypto/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a law enforcement action against a Zeppelin ransomware operation, resulting in the seizure of over $2.8 million in cryptocurrency and additional assets. The investigation uncovered extensive money laundering operations designed to obscure the criminal origins of ransomware proceeds, highlighting the evolving sophistication of modern ransomware operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157383</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-20265: RCE Flaw in Cisco Secure Firewall FMC RADIUS Authentication</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-20265-rce-cisco-secure-firewall-fmc-radius/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center Software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20265; Summary: The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on targeted systems by exploiting the RADIUS subsystem's insufficient input validation during authentication. An attacker can gain shell-level access, potentially with elevated privileges, if successful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062693</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: NFC Fraud, Curly COMrades, N-able Exploits, Docker Backdoors &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-nfc-fraud-curly-comrades-n.html</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a comprehensive cybersecurity news report, covering various topics such as cryptocurrency-related fraud and money laundering, phishing attacks, malware distribution, and other cyber threats. The article does not specifically discuss a vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware. Therefore, I will not identify any vulnerable products in my response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-nfc-fraud-curly-comrades-n.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Netfilter Flaw Enables Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/linux-kernel-netfilter-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux kernel's netfilter subsystem; CVE(s): CVE-2024-53141; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Linux kernel's netfilter subsystem allows local attackers to escalate privileges through an out-of-bounds write condition. The flaw occurs in the bitmap:ip set type implementation and can be exploited by creating specially crafted ipset bitmap configurations with CIDR ranges that trigger integer underflow conditions, allowing modification of kernel memory structures and potential privilege escalation attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157268</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/18/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54948; Summary: The Trend Micro Apex One OS Command Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2025-54948) is a newly added vulnerability to CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog, indicating active exploitation. This type of vulnerability poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and requires timely remediation to protect against cyberattacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23802</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Target Nike, PayPal, and CelcomDigi in New Access and Data Sales</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/nike-paypal-and-celcomdigi-data-sales/</link>
      <description>This article highlights several significant listings on the dark web, including recruitment efforts targeting employees of top brokerage firms, a large credential dump marketed as PayPal-related, an alleged leak of over 20 million records from Malaysia's CelcomDigi, and unauthorized shell access to Nike USA. The listings demonstrate ongoing risks across sectors.

(Note: Since there are no specific vulnerabilities mentioned in the article, it does not fit into the traditional vulnerability summary format. Instead, I have provided a FYSA-style summary.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062684</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Recent Windows updates may fail to install via WUSA</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-windows-server-2025-updates-may-fail-from-network-shares/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows Update Standalone Installer (WUSA) caused Windows update failures when installing updates from a network share on Windows 11 24H2 and Windows Server 2025 systems, resulting in error ERROR_BAD_PATHNAME.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-11-windows-server-2025-updates-may-fail-from-network-shares/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ghost-Tapping Attacks Target Apple Pay and Google Pay Users’ Linked Cards</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-ghost-tapping-attacks-target-apple-pay-and-google-pay-users/</link>
      <description>Chinese-speaking cybercriminals are using ghost-tapping techniques to take advantage of Near Field Communication (NFC) relay tactics in a sophisticated evolution of payment card fraud, mainly targeting mobile payment services such as Apple Pay and Google Pay. The technique relies on open-source tools like NFCGate for capturing and modifying NFC traffic, allowing real-time emulation of tokenized card data at point-of-sale (POS) terminals or ATMs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157109</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI and npm Packages Discovered Exploiting Dependencies in Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/malicious-pypi-and-npm-packages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI (Python Package Index); CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious package named termncolor was discovered on PyPI that establishes persistence and achieves code execution through a dependency called colorinal. The package uses DLL side-loading to facilitate decryption, establish persistence, and conduct C2 communication, ending in remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/malicious-pypi-and-npm-packages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wazuh for Regulatory Compliance</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/wazuh-for-regulatory-compliance.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of adherence to regulatory compliance standards and frameworks for organizations handling sensitive data or PII. It highlights various compliance standards and frameworks, including PCI DSS, GDPR, HIPAA, NIST SP 800-53, TSC, and CMMC. The article also introduces Wazuh, an open-source security platform that provides unified XDR and SIEM protection for endpoints and cloud workloads, and explains how it can help organizations track and implement regulatory compliance standards and frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/wazuh-for-regulatory-compliance.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers’ Secret Linux Malware Surfaces Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-secret-linux-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a North Korean hacking operation's data leak, which includes a sophisticated Linux rootkit. The rootkit is a Loadable Kernel Module (LKM) that enables kernel system call interception to evade detection and conceals itself from lsmod listings, hides processes, network activity, and persistence files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157092</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI-Powered Trojan Horse Returns: How LLMs Revive Classic Cyber Threats</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/the-ai-powered-trojan-horse-returns/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new wave of trojan horses that masquerade as legitimate desktop applications. These trojans embed malicious capabilities and are undetected by VirusTotal scanners for weeks. They use Large Language Models (LLMs) to generate convincing websites, error-free content, and AI-curated databases, evading static scanners and highlighting the inadequacy of static signatures alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157078</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workday Data Breach Exposes HR Records via Third-Party CRM Hack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/workday-data-breach-exposes/</link>
      <description>Workday, an enterprise software giant, disclosed a security incident involving unauthorized access to employee information through a compromised third-party customer relationship management (CRM) platform. Threat actors successfully infiltrated the CRM system following a sophisticated social engineering campaign, gaining access to standard business contact information such as names, email addresses, and phone numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157184</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 08:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Target Back-to-School Deals, Diverting Shoppers to Fraud Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scammers-target-back-to-school-deals/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting back-to-school season by deploying sophisticated scams, targeting unsuspecting consumers with fake e-commerce sites, and phishing mechanisms. These scams aim to siphon funds and personal data, and can lead to identity theft and financial fraud. Threat actors are using AI-driven tools to create hyper-realistic advertisements, making it harder to detect anomalies in URLs or content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157070</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 08:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HR giant Workday discloses data breach after Salesforce attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hr-giant-workday-discloses-data-breach-amid-salesforce-attacks/</link>
      <description>Workday disclosed a data breach after attackers gained access to a third-party customer relationship management (CRM) platform through a social engineering attack. The incident exposed some business contact information, including names, email addresses, and phone numbers, which could be used in subsequent attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hr-giant-workday-discloses-data-breach-amid-salesforce-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of TeslaMate Servers Expose Real-Time Vehicle Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hundreds-of-teslamate-servers-expose/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeslaMate; CVE(s): None; Summary: TeslaMate servers are exposing sensitive Tesla vehicle data to the public internet without authentication, revealing real-time location tracking, charging patterns, and driving habits of unsuspecting owners. The vulnerability allows anyone with a web browser to access exact GPS coordinates of parked vehicles, track commute patterns, identify home addresses, and determine when cars aren’t present at their usual locations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157059</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical PostgreSQL Flaws Allow Code Injection During Restoration</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-postgresql-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PostgreSQL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8714, CVE-2025-8715, CVE-2025-8713; Summary: The PostgreSQL Global Development Group released emergency security updates to address three critical vulnerabilities that enable code injection attacks during database restoration processes. The flaws affect all supported versions from PostgreSQL 13 through 17 and allow attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157054</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 05:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockwell ControlLogix Ethernet Vulnerability Exposes Systems to Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rockwell-controllogix-ethernet-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation ControlLogix Ethernet modules; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7353; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the web-based debugger agent of ControlLogix communication modules allows remote attackers to execute malicious code, perform memory dumps, modify system memory, and control execution flow. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.8 out of 10 and requires no authentication or user interaction for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157049</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 05:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best Patch Management Software For IT Security 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/best-patch-management-software/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article presents a comprehensive analysis of top 10 patch management vendors in 2025, highlighting their unique features, strengths, and potential limitations. The article aims to help organizations make informed decisions when selecting a patch management solution that best suits their specific needs.

In this response, I will analyze the article's content, focusing on the various factors that influence an organization's choice of a patch management vendor. Key considerations include the size and complexity of the IT environment, operating systems and applications diversity, budget, and existing security infrastructure.

The article provides an overview of each vendor, highlighting their respective strengths in areas such as automation, scalability, ease of use, and customization. It also mentions potential limitations or areas for improvement within each solution.

In conclusion, this article presents a valuable resource for organizations seeking to evaluate patch management vendors and make informed decisions about their security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=154625</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 18:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI releases warmer GPT-5 personality, but only for non thinking model</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-releases-warmer-gpt-5-personality-but-only-for-non-thinking-model/</link>
      <description>OpenAI has rolled out a new "warmer" personality for GPT-5 and restored older models like GPT-4o. Additionally, the company has relaxed rate limits for paid users after user outrage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-releases-warmer-gpt-5-personality-but-only-for-non-thinking-model/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is adding "Projects" feature to Gemini to run research tasks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-is-adding-projects-feature-to-gemini-to-run-research-tasks/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but it contains cybersecurity-relevant content. The article discusses Google's Gemini feature called "Projects" and its upcoming API release. It also mentions previous Gemini-related vulnerabilities, such as hijacking email summaries for phishing, and a flaw in the CLI AI coding assistant that allowed stealthy code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-is-adding-projects-feature-to-gemini-to-run-research-tasks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. seizes $2.8 million in crypto from Zeppelin ransomware operator</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-seizes-28-million-in-crypto-from-zeppelin-ransomware-operator/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) seized over $2.8 million in cryptocurrency from suspected ransomware operator Ianis Aleksandrovich Antropenko, linked to the Zeppelin ransomware operation. The seizure is part of efforts to disrupt and prevent ransomware operators from using funds to rebuild infrastructure or recruit new members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-seizes-28-million-in-crypto-from-zeppelin-ransomware-operator/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic: Claude can now end conversations to prevent harmful uses</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/anthropic-claude-can-now-end-conversations-to-prevent-harmful-uses/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: This article discusses updates to the AI model "Claude" by Anthropic, including a new feature that allows it to end conversations when it feels harm or abuse. The company also reports on other developments and comparisons with OpenAI's GPT-5 and ChatGPT models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/anthropic-claude-can-now-end-conversations-to-prevent-harmful-uses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 14:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic EDR 0-Day Flaw Lets Hackers Evade Detection, Run Malware, and Trigger BSOD</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/elastic-edr-0-day-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Elastic Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) software; CVE(s): None; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the Microsoft-signed kernel driver "elastic-endpoint-driver.sys" allows attackers to bypass security measures, execute malicious code, and crash protected systems repeatedly. The flaw enables a four-step attack chain, including EDR Bypass, Remote Code Execution, Persistence, and Privileged Denial-of-Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=157022</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI prepares Chromium-based AI browser to take on Google</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-prepares-chromium-based-ai-browser-to-take-on-google/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability. It discusses OpenAI's development of an AI-powered browser using Chromium as its underlying engine and its potential features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-prepares-chromium-based-ai-browser-to-take-on-google/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak: ChatGPT cheaper plan costs $4 or £3.50, might release everywhere</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leak-chatgpt-cheaper-plan-costs-4-or-350-might-release-everywhere/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article discusses OpenAI's upcoming plan called ChatGPT Go, which will be available globally and priced at $4. Additionally, the company has added a "Voice speed" feature to the ChatGPT web app settings for voice mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leak-chatgpt-cheaper-plan-costs-4-or-350-might-release-everywhere/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is improving ChatGPT voice mode</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-is-improving-chatgpt-voice-mode/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: OpenAI has added features such as "Voice speed" and "custom instructions prefix" to the ChatGPT web app settings. Additionally, they have rolled out an upgraded model selector with access to new GPT-5 models and restored GPT-4o for paid users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-is-improving-chatgpt-voice-mode/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Released for Fortinet FortiSIEM Command Injection Flaw</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortinet-fortisiem-command-injection-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiSIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25256; Summary: A severe pre-authentication command injection vulnerability exists in Fortinet's FortiSIEM platform, allowing attackers to compromise enterprise security monitoring systems without credentials. The vulnerability affects all versions from 5.4 through 7.3.1 and requires complete migration to fixed releases for older versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156995</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher to release exploit for full auth bypass on FortiWeb</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/researcher-to-release-exploit-for-full-auth-bypass-on-fortiweb/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet, FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52970; Summary: A remote attacker can bypass FortiWeb's authentication by exploiting an out-of-bounds read in cookie parsing that sets the Era parameter to an unexpected value. This allows the server to use an all-zero secret key for session encryption and HMAC signing, making forged authentication cookies trivial to create.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/researcher-to-release-exploit-for-full-auth-bypass-on-fortiweb/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 14:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams to protect against malicious URLs, dangerous file types</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-to-protect-against-malicious-urls-dangerous-file-types/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather about various security enhancements and features being added to Microsoft Teams, including blocking malicious URLs and files, integrating with Microsoft Defender for Office 365, and preventing unauthorized screen captures. These features aim to improve protection against malware and phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-to-protect-against-malicious-urls-dangerous-file-types/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Abuse npm Developer Accounts Hijacked to Spread Malicious Packages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-abuse-npm-developer-accounts-hijacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm (multiple packages); CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated phishing campaign targeting the maintainer of eslint-config-prettier led to malicious code being distributed to thousands of developer projects worldwide, highlighting critical vulnerabilities in modern software development practices and automated dependency updating tools. The attack began with a carefully crafted phishing email that impersonated npm's official support team, leading to the publication of compromised packages containing postinstall scripts that deployed a remote access trojan specifically targeting Windows machines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156987</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERMAC V3.0 Banking Trojan Source Code Leak Exposes Full Malware Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ermac-v30-banking-trojan-source-code.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the inner workings of an Android banking trojan called ERMAC 3.0, revealing its infrastructure and capabilities, including form injection methods, data theft, and command-and-control (C2) panel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ermac-v30-banking-trojan-source-code.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit Web Hosting Infrastructure for Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-exploit-web-hosting-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The article reveals a sophisticated Chinese-speaking advanced persistent threat (APT) group, designated UAT-7237, that has been actively targeting web hosting infrastructure in Taiwan since at least 2022. The group demonstrates a refined approach to maintaining persistent access and employs distinct tactics to establish long-term presence in high-value environments, including custom shellcode loading, VPN-based persistence, cloud infrastructure, and evasion techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156979</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Group EncryptHub Exploits MSC EvilTwin Vulnerability to Deploy Fickle Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/russian-group-encrypthub-exploits-msc.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26633; Summary: The vulnerability in the Microsoft Management Console (MMC) framework was exploited by EncryptHub to deliver malicious payloads. The exploit uses social engineering techniques and a rogue MSC file to trigger the infection routine, ultimately leading to the execution of PowerShell commands that download and run additional malware.

FYSA: EncryptHub is continuing to exploit vulnerabilities and use social engineering tactics to deliver malicious payloads. They are using fake job offers, portfolio reviews, and compromised Steam games to infect targets with stealer malware. The group is also abusing trusted platforms like Brave Support to host next-stage malware and setting up phony videoconferencing lures to deceive victims into downloading malicious software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/russian-group-encrypthub-exploits-msc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best NDR Solutions (Network Detection and Response) in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/best-ndr-solutions/</link>
      <description>The article provides an analysis of various Network Detection and Response (NDR) solutions from different vendors. It highlights the key features, strengths, and capabilities of each NDR solution, including their ability to detect advanced threats, provide comprehensive visibility into network traffic, and offer automated investigation and response capabilities.

The analysis covers a range of NDR solutions from well-known vendors such as Fidelis, NetWitness, and Trend Micro. It provides insights into the unique strengths and specializations of each solution, helping readers understand which NDR might best suit their specific security needs.

The article also emphasizes the importance of NDR in modern cybersecurity, highlighting its role in detecting and responding to threats that bypass traditional security controls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149512</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Phishers Target Brokerage Accounts in ‘Ramp and Dump’ Cashout Scheme</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/08/mobile-phishers-target-brokerage-accounts-in-ramp-and-dump-cashout-scheme/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminal groups are using sophisticated phishing kits to convert stolen card data into mobile wallets, and have recently shifted their focus to targeting customers of brokerage services. They use compromised accounts in unison to manipulate stock prices, exploiting weaknesses in multi-factor authentication methods used by some financial institutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71895</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Free Data Recovery Software 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/free-data-recovery-software/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I analyzed the article and found it to be an informative piece on free data recovery tools for Windows and Mac operating systems. The article highlights 10 different software tools that can help users recover lost files from various storage devices.

The tools mentioned include Recuva, Stellar Data Recovery, Glary Undelete, MiniTool Power Data Recovery, ADRC Data Recovery Tools, PhotoRec, etc. Each tool has its unique features and capabilities, making it suitable for a wide range of users.

While the article does not discuss any specific vulnerabilities or security threats related to these data recovery tools, I would like to highlight that the best practice is to only download software from trusted sources and be cautious when using third-party downloaders or deals.

Additionally, it is essential to note that while these free data recovery tools can be helpful in recovering lost files, they may not always be effective, especially if the deleted data has been written over or if the recording medium has been physically damaged. Therefore, it's crucial for users to act quickly when realizing they have lost files and use the right tool for their specific situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=40630</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Web Servers Breached by UAT-7237 Using Customized Open-Source Hacking Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/taiwan-web-servers-breached-by-uat-7237.html</link>
      <description>A Chinese-speaking advanced persistent threat (APT) actor, tracked as UAT-7237, targets web infrastructure entities in Taiwan using customized open-sourced tools with the aim of establishing long-term access within high-value victim environments. The group relies on exploitation of known security flaws against unpatched servers and uses various tools such as Cobalt Strike, SoundBill, JuicyPotato, and Mimikatz to carry out malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/taiwan-web-servers-breached-by-uat-7237.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colt Telecom attack claimed by WarLock ransomware, data up for sale</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/colt-telecom-attack-claimed-by-warlock-ransomware-data-up-for-sale/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The article reports a cyberattack on UK-based telecommunications company Colt Technology Services, causing a multi-day outage of some operations. Initial access was likely gained by exploiting a remote code execution vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint tracked as CVE-2025-53770.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/colt-telecom-attack-claimed-by-warlock-ransomware-data-up-for-sale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS, IOS XE, and Secure Firewall Flaws Allow Remote DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-ios-xe-and-secure-firewall-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Systems; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20224, CVE-2025-20225, CVE-2025-20239, CVE-2025-20252, CVE-2025-20253, and CVE-2025-20254; Summary: Six critical vulnerabilities in the Internet Key Exchange Version 2 (IKEv2) feature across Cisco's networking and security product portfolio allow unauthenticated remote attackers to launch denial-of-service attacks, potentially causing system crashes and service disruptions. The most severe vulnerability has a CVSS base score of 8.6, indicating high severity with potential for significant impact on affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156968</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco warns of max severity flaw in Firewall Management Center</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-warns-of-max-severity-flaw-in-firewall-management-center/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20265, None for other vulnerabilities; Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the RADIUS subsystem of Cisco FMC software, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands with elevated privileges. The vulnerability affects FMC versions 7.0.7 and 7.7.0 when RADIUS authentication is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-warns-of-max-severity-flaw-in-firewall-management-center/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft reminds of Windows 10 support ending in two months</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-reminds-users-of-windows-10-retirement-in-october/</link>
      <description>None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-reminds-users-of-windows-10-retirement-in-october/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MadeYouReset: New HTTP/2 DoS Vulnerability Explained</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/madeyoureset-new-http-2-dos-vulnerability-explained/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various HTTP/2 servers; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8671, CVE-2025-48989, CVE-2025-55163, CVE-2025-54500, CVE-2025-36047; Summary: A newly discovered technique called "MadeYouReset" allows attackers to coax HTTP/2 servers into resetting their own streams, bypassing many Rapid Reset defenses. The attack works by sending normal-looking HTTP/2 frames that cause subtle protocol violations, forcing the server to issue its own resets and increasing resource pressure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062675</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F5 Fixes HTTP/2 Flaw Affecting Multiple Products in Massive DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/f5-fixes-http-2-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: F5 Networks BIG-IP products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54500; Summary: The vulnerability, known as the "HTTP/2 MadeYouReset Attack", exploits a flaw in HTTP/2 implementation that enables attackers to overwhelm systems using specially crafted control frames, potentially causing denial-of-service conditions. Malformed HTTP/2 control frames bypass the maximum concurrent streams limit, leading to CPU resource exhaustion and denial-of-service conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156934</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: Void Blizzard</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-void-blizzard/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

Void Blizzard is a newly identified Russian state-sponsored cyber threat group that targets governments, defense sectors, critical infrastructure, and high-tech companies in NATO and EU countries. The group uses simple but effective techniques, including "living off the land" methods, stolen credentials, and phishing attacks. Void Blizzard has achieved high success rates by exploiting cloud APIs like Microsoft Graph and Exchange Online, as well as using automation and rapid access to compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062664</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageMagick Vulnerabilities Cause Memory Corruption and Integer Overflows</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/imagemagick-vulnerabilities-cause-memory-corruption/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ImageMagick; CVE(s): CVE-2025-55154, CVE-2025-55004, CVE-2025-55005, and CVE-2025-55160; Summary: Four critical security vulnerabilities affecting millions of applications that rely on ImageMagick for image processing have been patched. The flaws include integer overflows in MNG magnification calculations, heap-buffer overflows during image magnification, and undefined behavior in CloneSplayTree operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156928</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishing Campaign Exploits Japanese Character “ん” to Imitate Forward Slash</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/phishing-campaign-exploits-japanese-character/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated phishing campaign that exploits the Japanese hiragana character "ん" to create deceptively authentic-looking URLs. The campaign targets Booking.com customers, using URLs that appear legitimate but actually redirect victims to malicious domains. The attacks are challenging to identify due to their refinement and rely on social engineering techniques rather than technical vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156958</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plex warns users to patch security vulnerability immediately</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/plex-warns-users-to-patch-security-vulnerability-immediately/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Plex Media Server; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports a recently patched security vulnerability in Plex Media Server versions 1.41.7.x to 1.42.0.x, with no additional details provided about the patch or the vulnerability itself. Users are advised to update their software as soon as possible to prevent exploitation by threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/plex-warns-users-to-patch-security-vulnerability-immediately/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Sanctions Garantex and Grinex Over $100M in Ransomware-Linked Illicit Crypto Transactions</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/us-sanctions-garantex-and-grinex-over.html</link>
      <description>The US Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) has renewed sanctions against Russian cryptocurrency exchange platform Garantex for facilitating ransomware actors and other cybercriminals. Garantex is accused of processing over $100 million in transactions linked to illicit activities since 2019, with its successor Grinex allegedly continuing these activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/us-sanctions-garantex-and-grinex-over.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust + AI: Privacy in the Age of Agentic AI</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/zero-trust-ai-privacy-in-age-of-agentic.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the concept of agentic AI, which is becoming increasingly autonomous in its decision-making processes. It highlights how this type of AI can infer and interpret data, making assumptions and acting on partial signals. The article emphasizes that privacy in a world of minds (both biological and synthetic) is no longer just about secrecy but rather reciprocity, alignment, and governance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/zero-trust-ai-privacy-in-age-of-agentic.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAT-7237 targets Taiwanese web hosting infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/uat-7237-targets-web-hosting-infra/</link>
      <description>UAT-7237 is a Chinese-speaking advanced persistent threat (APT) group that has been active since at least 2022, targeting web infrastructure entities in Taiwan. They use open-sourced tooling, customized to evade detection, and employ tactics such as using Cobalt Strike, Mimikatz, and JuicyPotato for credential extraction and privilege escalation. The group also uses SoftEther VPN clients and exploits known vulnerabilities on unpatched servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689caff6e2d85f00011b7f54</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VirtualBox 7.2 Adds Windows 11/Arm VM Support and Key Bug Fixes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/virtualbox-7-2-adds-windows-11-arm-vm-support/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of VirtualBox 7.2.0, a major update that enhances ARM virtualization capabilities and introduces comprehensive Windows 11/ARM support. The update also includes performance enhancements, interface redesigns, and addresses critical issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156953</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HexStrike AI Links ChatGPT, Claude, and Copilot to 150+ Security Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hexstrike-ai-links-security-tools/</link>
      <description>This article is about the integration of ChatGPT, Claude, and GitHub Copilot with HexStrike AI's autonomous cybersecurity framework. It enables these AI agents to orchestrate over 150 professional security tools for comprehensive penetration testing and vulnerability intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156948</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palo Alto GlobalProtect Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation via Certificate Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/palo-alto-globalprotect-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect App; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2183; Summary: A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect app allows attackers to escalate privileges, install malicious software, and bypass security controls by exploiting improper certificate validation. The flaw affects multiple versions of the VPN client across Windows and Linux platforms, with Windows and Linux systems bearing the primary risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156944</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US sanctions Grinex crypto-exchange, successor to Garantex</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-grinex-crypto-exchange-garantexs-successor/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury has announced sanctions against Grinex, a cryptocurrency exchange suspected to be a rebrand of previously sanctioned Garantex, which was linked to ransomware gangs and laundered money for cybercriminals. The sanctions also target three co-founders and six partner companies allegedly involved with Garantex.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-sanctions-grinex-crypto-exchange-garantexs-successor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Code of ERMAC V3.0 Malware Exposed by ‘changemeplease’ Password</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/source-code-of-ermac-v3-0-malware-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ERMAC V3.0; CVE(s): None; Summary: The complete source code of ERMAC V3.0, a sophisticated banking trojan, was exposed due to a weak default password "changemeplease". The leak reveals multiple critical security flaws, including hardcoded JWT secret token, static admin bearer token, and default root credentials, which can be exploited to disrupt ERMAC operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156918</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Managed Detection And Response (MDR) Companies in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/managed-detection-and-response-mdr-companies/</link>
      <description>I have analyzed the article and it does not appear to be discussing a specific software, hardware, or firmware vulnerability. Instead, it appears to be an overview of different Managed Detection and Response (MDR) services offered by various cybersecurity companies. The article provides information about each company's MDR offerings, highlighting their unique features, strengths, and approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149736</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall Snort 3 Vulnerability Enable DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-secure-firewall-snort-3-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20217; Summary: The vulnerability in the Snort 3 Detection Engine allows unauthenticated remote attackers to launch denial of service (DoS) attacks, potentially disrupting critical network operations. Exploitation involves sending specially crafted traffic through the affected device, causing an infinite loop during packet inspection, and can be mitigated only by applying available security updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156910</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Warns of CVSS 10.0 FMC RADIUS Flaw Allowing Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cisco-warns-of-cvss-100-fmc-radius-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20265; Summary: The vulnerability affects the RADIUS subsystem implementation and could permit an unauthenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary shell commands that are executed by the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands at a high privilege level, requiring Cisco Secure FMC Software to be configured for RADIUS authentication for the web-based management interface, SSH management, or both.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cisco-warns-of-cvss-100-fmc-radius-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP/2 MadeYouReset Vulnerability Enables Massive DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/http-2-madeyoureset-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HTTP/2 protocol; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8671; Summary: The "MadeYouReset" vulnerability allows attackers to bypass HTTP/2's concurrency limits, enabling unbounded concurrent work on target servers with minimal resources, potentially leading to massive DDoS attacks and overwhelming servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156904</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall Vulnerability Lets Attackers Execute Remote Shell Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-secure-firewall-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20265; Summary: The vulnerability in Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center's RADIUS subsystem allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely execute shell commands with elevated privileges, potentially gaining high-level system access without prior authentication. This can lead to complete control over the firewall management system and potential further network attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156899</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Actors Combine Legitimate Tools with Custom Malware to Evade Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-actors-combine-legitimate-tools/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Crypto24 strain's multi-stage attacks, which employ legitimate system tools and bespoke malware to infiltrate networks, maintain persistence, and evade EDR systems. The attacks target high-profile organizations across various sectors, using tools like PSExec, AnyDesk, and keyloggers to exfiltrate data via Google Drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156834</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over $300 million in cybercrime crypto seized in anti-fraud effort</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-300-million-in-cybercrime-crypto-seized-in-anti-fraud-effort/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses two initiatives involving law enforcement and private companies that have resulted in the freezing of over $300 million worth of cryptocurrency linked to cybercrime and fraud schemes. The initiatives, led by the T3 Financial Crime Unit and Chainalysis, involved coordinated investigations and global collaboration to detect and intervene at the blockchain level, significantly hindering cybercriminals from moving or spending scam proceeds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-300-million-in-cybercrime-crypto-seized-in-anti-fraud-effort/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-846: Apple macOS USD importMeshJointWeights Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-846/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31281; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27058</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage CrossC2 to Extend Cobalt Strike to Linux and macOS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-crossc2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrossC2; CVE(s): None; Summary: CrossC2 is an unofficial extension tool that creates Cobalt Strike Beacons that work with Linux and macOS. It was used by threat actors to target Active Directory infrastructures, exploiting Linux servers as potential entry points and capitalizing on the frequent absence of endpoint detection and response (EDR) systems in such environments. The tool integrates custom loaders, including ReadNimeLoader, and employs anti-analysis measures and sophisticated anti-debugging techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156814</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS1Bot: Multi-Stage Malware Framework Targeting Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ps1bot-multi-stage-malware-framework/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a malware campaign, dubbed PS1Bot, which has been active since early 2025. The malware uses malvertising and SEO poisoning to distribute compressed archives with file names mimicking legitimate search queries. Upon extraction, the archives contain a JavaScript file that downloads PowerShell scripts from an attacker-controlled server, which poll a command-and-control (C2) server and execute in-memory to minimize disk artifacts and enhance stealth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156797</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened in Vegas (that you actually want to know about)</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/what-happened-in-vegas-that-you-actually-want-to-know-about/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various cybersecurity-related topics, including threat actors, tactics, infrastructure, and impacts. It mentions Russian government hackers allegedly being behind a data breach affecting the US federal court filing system, as well as North Korean state-sponsored hacking group Kimsuky suffering a data breach. Additionally, it warns about a widespread malvertising campaign distributing malware that steals sensitive information and maintains persistent access on infected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689cebb2e2d85f00011b7fd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto24 ransomware hits large orgs with custom EDR evasion tool</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/crypto24-ransomware-hits-large-orgs-with-custom-edr-evasion-tool/</link>
      <description>Crypto24 ransomware group uses custom utilities to evade security solutions, exfiltrate data, and encrypt files. The group has been identified using default administrative accounts on Windows systems, creating malicious services and tasks, and disabling security agents from multiple vendors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/crypto24-ransomware-hits-large-orgs-with-custom-edr-evasion-tool/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NFC-Based PhantomCard Malware Targets Android Banking Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-nfc-based-phantomcard-malware/</link>
      <description>PhantomCard is a sophisticated NFC-based Trojan designed to relay sensitive card data from victims' devices to cybercriminals. It operates by masquerading as a legitimate "card protection" app and exploits the NFC reader in modern Android devices, focusing on the ISO-DEP protocol standard used in EMV contactless cards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156786</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Advanced Tactics to Personalize Phishing for Malware Delivery</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-advanced-tactics/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using topic customization as a more advanced strategy in targeted malware-delivery phishing campaigns. The approach involves crafting personalized subject lines, attachment names, and embedded links to mimic authentic communications, evading detection and facilitating successful compromises. Key insights reveal that when combined with Remote Access Trojans (RATs) or Information Stealers, these campaigns can grant attackers remote access or harvest credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156775</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Mandates License or Certification for Crypto App Developers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-mandates-license-or-certification/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article highlights the cryptocurrency ecosystem's ongoing challenges in balancing accessibility with security, as regulatory frameworks evolve. The Google Play requires developers to meet stringent publishing requirements, and the FBI warns of sophisticated recovery scams targeting previous fraud victims. The article emphasizes the importance of vigilance against compliance failures and criminal exploitation, as the industry seeks legitimacy and sustainable growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156877</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Microsoft Flaw to Breach Canadian House of Commons to Gain Unauthorized Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-microsoft-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49704, and CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint was exploited by an unidentified threat actor to access sensitive government employee data at the Canadian House of Commons. The attack allowed unauthorized remote code execution through advanced deserialization techniques and ViewState abuse, bypassing authentication controls including multi-factor authentication and single sign-on systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156876</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Russian hackers blamed for water dam sabotage in Norway</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-russian-hackers-blamed-for-water-dam-sabotage-in-norway/</link>
      <description>Pro-Russian hackers took control of critical operation systems at a dam in Norway, opening outflow valves and demonstrating their ability to remotely hack critical infrastructure. The attack was seen as a display of capabilities rather than an attempt to cause damage, with the goal of exerting influence and creating fear or unrest in the population. This is the second time Russia has been associated with attacks against Norwegian entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-russian-hackers-blamed-for-water-dam-sabotage-in-norway/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Dominates July with Over 70 Claimed Victims</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-ransomware-dominates-july/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2023-48788, CVE-2019-18935, CVE-2025-5777, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771, CVE-2025-49704, and CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A variety of vulnerabilities were weaponized in ransomware campaigns, including SQL injection flaws in Fortinet FortiClientEMS (CVE-2023-48788) and deserialization vulnerability in Progress Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX (CVE-2019-18935), as well as out-of-bounds read issue in Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway (CVE-2025-5777) and Microsoft SharePoint flaws (CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771, CVE-2025-49704, and CVE-2025-49706). These exploits facilitated initial access and lateral movement, enabling attackers to deploy payloads efficiently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156612</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HTTP/2 'MadeYouReset' Vulnerability Enables Large-Scale DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-http2-madeyoureset-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48989, None (for other impacted products); Summary: MadeYouReset is an attack technique that bypasses server-imposed limits on HTTP/2 requests, allowing thousands of concurrent requests and inducing denial-of-service (DoS) attacks. The vulnerability takes advantage of stream errors and the use of RST_STREAM frames to trigger protocol violations in unexpected ways, prompting the server to reset streams and exhaust resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-http2-madeyoureset-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-838: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows 11 vhdmp Use-After-Free Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-838/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50167; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the Virtual Hard Disk Miniport driver due to lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27158</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Windows Server bug causing cluster, VM issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-server-bug-causing-cluster-vm-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2019; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Cluster service on Windows Server 2019 may fail to function correctly after installing the July Windows security update, causing nodes to fail to rejoin the cluster or enter quarantine states, virtual machines to experience multiple restarts, and frequent errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-windows-server-bug-causing-cluster-vm-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-839: Microsoft Teams Real Time Media Manager Integer Underflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-839/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Teams; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53783; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Teams without authentication. The issue results from an integer underflow before writing to memory, which can be leveraged by attackers to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26363</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-840: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows 11 vhdmp Improper Validation of Array Index Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-840/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11 vhdmp; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53155; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting an improper validation of array index in the Virtual Hard Disk Miniport driver, which can result in a write past the end of an array.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27256</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-841: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows 11 vhdmp Integer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-841/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53723; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting an integer overflow in the Virtual Hard Disk Miniport driver, resulting in an elevated SYSTEM context. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27235</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-842: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows Exposed Dangerous Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-842/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53156; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must execute low-privileged code to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the Windows Storage Port Driver due to an exposed dangerous function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27171</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-843: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows win32kbase Type Confusion Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-843/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50168; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting a type confusion condition in the win32kbase driver. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can result in arbitrary code execution in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27188</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-844: Microsoft Windows Subsystem for Linux WslCoreVm::Initialize Incorrect Privilege Management Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-844/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53788; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to read arbitrary files on affected installations of Microsoft Windows, requiring low-privileged code execution. The issue exists within WslCoreVm::Initialize method due to incorrect privilege management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27541</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-845: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft Windows win32kfull Race Condition Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-845/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53132; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the win32kfull driver due to a lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27174</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booking.com phishing campaign uses sneaky 'ん' character to trick you</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bookingcom-phishing-campaign-uses-sneaky-character-to-trick-you/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting the Japanese hiragana character "ん" (Unicode U+3093) in a new phishing campaign, making URLs appear realistic to a casual glance. The attack creates fake Booking.com links that direct users to malicious sites, delivering malware and potentially leading to infostealers or remote access trojans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bookingcom-phishing-campaign-uses-sneaky-character-to-trick-you/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Theft Replaces Encryption: Blue Report 2025 on Ransomware &amp; Infostealers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/when-theft-replaces-encryption-blue-report-2025-on-ransomware-and-infostealers/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolving threat landscape, revealing that ransomware operators and infostealer campaigns focus on credential theft, data exfiltration, and lateral movement. It highlights the failure of organizations to detect these tactics, with a 3% prevention rate for data exfiltration, and a 46% success rate for password cracking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/when-theft-replaces-encryption-blue-report-2025-on-ransomware-and-infostealers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Found Using CrossC2 to Expand Cobalt Strike Beacon’s Reach to Linux and macOS</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-warn-crossc2-expands-cobalt.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a command-and-control (C2) framework called CrossC2 being used in attacks to extend Cobalt Strike's functionality to Linux and Apple macOS. The attacks targeted multiple countries, including Japan, and involved the use of custom malware as a loader for Cobalt Strike, as well as various tools such as PsExec, Plink, and Cobalt Strike itself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-warn-crossc2-expands-cobalt.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada’s House of Commons investigating data breach after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canadas-house-of-commons-investigating-data-breach-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53786; Summary: A threat actor exploited a recent Microsoft vulnerability to gain access to a database containing sensitive information used to manage House of Commons computers and mobile devices. The attack also resulted in the theft of some employee data, including names, job titles, office locations, and email addresses.

FYSA: The article reports on a data breach affecting the House of Commons of Canada, where a threat actor exploited a Microsoft vulnerability to gain access to sensitive information. The stolen data could be used to target and impersonate parliamentarians or exploited in scams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canadas-house-of-commons-investigating-data-breach-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-25256: FortiSIEM Flaw Enables Unauthenticated RCE</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-25256-fortisiem-flaw-enables-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiSIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25256; Summary: The vulnerability is an OS command injection flaw (CWE-78) that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands on affected systems. The exploit code has been identified in the wild, making it critical for organizations using vulnerable versions to act fast and upgrade or migrate to supported releases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062655</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes Operational Technology Guide for Critical Infrastructure Stakeholders</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-operational-technology-guide/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has released a comprehensive guide, "Foundations for OT Cybersecurity: Asset Inventory Guidance for Owners and Operators," to help critical infrastructure stakeholders develop and maintain operational technology (OT) asset inventories and taxonomies. The guide provides best practices for creating an OT taxonomy and highlights the importance of integrating the inventory into broader cybersecurity and risk management efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156799</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft IIS Web Deploy Vulnerability Allows Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-iis-web-deploy-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft IIS Web Deploy; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53772; Summary: The vulnerability allows authenticated attackers with low-level privileges to potentially gain complete control over vulnerable systems by exploiting the deserialization process, allowing remote code execution. This flaw stems from improper deserialization of untrusted data within the Web Deploy framework and affects the core functionality of Web Deploy, making it a significant security concern for organizations using IIS Web Deploy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156761</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-09</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13089, CVE-2024-13090; Summary: An authenticated administrator can execute unauthorized arbitrary OS commands due to an OS command injection vulnerability and a privilege escalation vulnerability. Successful exploitation could impact confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23777</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Opcenter Quality</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Opcenter Quality; CVE(s): CVE-2024-41979, CVE-2024-41980, CVE-2024-41982, CVE-2024-41983, CVE-2024-41984, CVE-2024-41985, CVE-2024-41986; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Siemens Opcenter Quality allow an attacker to gain complete access of the application, access sensitive information, execute a Machine-In-The-Middle attack, and compromise confidentiality and integrity of data. Successful exploitation could also lead to unauthorized access if sessions are left idle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23774</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Viewpoint</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-23</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Viewpoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7973; Summary: The vulnerability in FactoryTalk Viewpoint version 14.00 and prior allows attackers to hijack the cscript.exe console window, which runs with SYSTEM privileges, enabling full privilege escalation. Successful exploitation could result in full privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23791</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Simcenter Femap</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Simcenter Femap V2406 and V2412; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40762, CVE-2025-40764; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Siemens Simcenter Femap allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process by exploiting out-of-bounds write and read vulnerabilities while parsing specially crafted STP and BMP files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23772</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-11</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SIMATIC S7-PLCSIM, SIMOCODE ES, SIMOTION SCOUT TIA, SINAMICS Startdrive, SIMATIC STEP 7, SIMATIC WinCC, SIRIUS Safety ES, SIRIUS Soft Starter ES, and TIA Portal Cloud; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40759; Summary: A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists in the affected Siemens products, which could allow an attacker to cause a type confusion and execute arbitrary code. Successful exploitation requires low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23779</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Engineering Platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens; CVE(s): CVE-2024-54678; Summary: A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in Siemens' products allows a local authenticated attacker to cause a type confusion and execute arbitrary code within the affected application. The vulnerability affects various products including SIMATIC PCS neo, SIMATIC WinCC, SIMOCODE ES, SIMOTION SCOUT TIA, SINAMICS Startdrive, SIRIUS Safety ES, SIRIUS Soft Starter ES, TIA Portal Cloud, and TIA Portal Test Suite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23771</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Thirty-Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/14/cisa-releases-thirty-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released 32 Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 14, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories cover various products from Siemens and Rockwell Automation, including SIMATIC RTLS Locating Manager, COMOS, and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23800</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM ROX II</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-226-14</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM ROX II Family; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33023; Summary: The vulnerability allows an authenticated remote attacker with high privileges in the web interface to upload arbitrary files, which could lead to a higher level of attack complexity. Exploitation could allow an attacker to upload files onto the filesystem of devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23782</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
