<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 10:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Fake VPN and Browser NSIS Installers to Deliver Winos 4.0 Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-use-fake-vpn-and-browser-nsis.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a malware campaign that uses fake software installers to deliver the Winos 4.0 framework, a remote access trojan written in C++. The campaign uses a multi-stage loader called Catena, which evades traditional antivirus tools and allows the malware to maintain persistence on infected hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-use-fake-vpn-and-browser-nsis.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI confirms Operator Agent is now more accurate with o3</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-operator-agent-is-now-more-accurate-with-o3/</link>
      <description>OpenAI has updated its Operator Agent, a tool that allows users to delegate web tasks to AI, using the o3 model. This improvement enables more persistent and accurate interactions with the browser, increasing overall task success rate. The feature is currently exclusive to the $200 Pro subscription but may be available for lower-tier subscribers in the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-operator-agent-is-now-more-accurate-with-o3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 23:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds charge 16 Russians allegedly tied to botnets used in cyberattacks and spying</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/feds-charge-16-russians-allegedly-tied-to-botnets-used-in-cyberattacks-and-spying/</link>
      <description>A significant milestone was achieved in disrupting a large-scale Russian-origin hacking operation, DanaBot, which was involved in both state-sponsored and criminal activities. The takedown of DanaBot's infrastructure may have created a vacuum, allowing another group to take its place, but repeated disruptions can keep the threat actors on their heels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/feds-charge-16-russians-allegedly-tied-to-botnets-used-in-cyberattacks-and-spying/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers cause GitLab AI developer assistant to turn safe code malicious</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/researchers-cause-gitlab-ai-developer-assistant-to-turn-safe-code-malicious/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: An attacker can embed an instruction into source code or a merge request to leak confidential resources available to the targeted user by exploiting Duo's chatbot feature. The exploit uses base64 encoding and appending the stolen data inside a GET request sent to a user-controlled website, allowing exfiltration of sensitive information such as source code or vulnerability reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/researchers-cause-gitlab-ai-developer-assistant-to-turn-safe-code-malicious/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of malicious packages on NPM collect host and network data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dozens-of-malicious-packages-on-npm-collect-host-and-network-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NPM packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A threat actor uploaded 60 malicious packages to the NPM repository, which collect sensitive host and network data and send it to a Discord webhook controlled by the attacker. The packages were designed to appear legitimate and target developers who use CI/CD pipelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dozens-of-malicious-packages-on-npm-collect-host-and-network-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Trust Policy Bypass Enables Exploitation of Vulnerabilities and Manipulation of NHI Secrets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zero-trust-policy-bypass-enables-exploitation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ISC BIND; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40775; Summary: A critical attack vector exploits protocol vulnerabilities to disrupt DNS infrastructure and manipulate Non-Human Identity (NHI) secrets, ultimately bypassing zero-trust security frameworks. Attackers craft a malformed TSIG DNS packet with an invalid algorithm field to trigger an assertion failure in BIND versions 9.20.0-9.20.8, crashing the server and disrupting DNS resolution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138300</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actor Sells Burger King Backup System RCE Vulnerability for $4,000</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actor-sells-burger-king-backup-system/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AhsayCBS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The threat actor #LongNight has reportedly put up for sale remote code execution (RCE) access to Burger King Spain's backup system, leveraging vulnerabilities in the AhsayCBS platform. This exploit offers malicious actors a potential gateway to compromise critical infrastructural components of Burger King Spain's operations in Spain, posing a catastrophic risk of data breaches or ransomware attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138275</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Nexus Hackers Exploit Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-nexus-hackers-exploit-ivanti/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in EPMM version 12.5.0.0 and earlier allow unauthenticated remote code execution on internet-facing systems, posing a severe risk to enterprise security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138285</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target macOS Users with Fake Ledger Apps to Deploy Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-macos-users/</link>
      <description>Hackers are targeting macOS users with malicious clones of Ledger Live, stealing passwords, wallet details, and seed phrases. The malware campaign uses social engineering tactics to bypass security defenses and exfiltrate sensitive data. The attacks involve fake apps, phishing pages, and command-and-control servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138255</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use TikTok Videos to Distribute Vidar and StealC Malware via ClickFix Technique</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-use-tiktok-videos-to-distribute.html</link>
      <description>Latrodectus malware uses ClickFix as a distribution vector, allowing it to execute in memory and bypass detection by browsers or security tools. The malware is a downloader for other payloads, such as ransomware, and has been observed using PowerShell commands to trick users into executing malicious files.

FYSA: A new social engineering campaign is spreading on TikTok, using AI-generated videos to deliver Vidar and StealC information stealers. The videos instruct users to run malicious commands to activate Windows, Microsoft Office, CapCut, and Spotify, compromising their own systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hackers-use-tiktok-videos-to-distribute.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker steals $223 million in Cetus Protocol cryptocurrency heist</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-223-million-in-cetus-protocol-cryptocurrency-heist/</link>
      <description>The Cetus Protocol decentralized exchange (DEX) suffered a theft of $223 million in cryptocurrency, with the attacker exploiting a vulnerable package. The incident occurred after an emergency vote by validators paused $162 million on the Sui blockchain. The platform offered a time-sensitive whitehat settlement to return the stolen funds and announced a $5 million bounty for information leading to the identification and arrest of the hacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-223-million-in-cetus-protocol-cryptocurrency-heist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI warns of Luna Moth extortion attacks targeting law firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-luna-moth-extortion-attacks-targeting-law-firms/</link>
      <description>The Silent Ransom Group (SRG), also known as Luna Moth, has been targeting US law firms and financial institutions with callback phishing and social engineering attacks. They impersonate IT support to gain access to networks and extort victims by threatening to leak sensitive information online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-of-luna-moth-extortion-attacks-targeting-law-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Targets Stark Industries in Cyberattack Sanctions Crackdown</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eu-targets-stark-industries/</link>
      <description>The European Union has expanded its sanctions against 21 individuals and 6 entities in response to Russia's campaign of hybrid threats. The new measures target a wider range of assets, including digital and communication networks, credit institutions, financial entities, and crypto-asset service providers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138257</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice.ai’s Unrestricted Access Sparks Concerns Over AI-Driven Cyber Threats</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/venice-ais-unrestricted-access/</link>
      <description>Venice.ai, an AI platform that integrates open-source models without content moderation or ethical guardrails, has emerged as a hub for both legitimate users seeking creative freedom and malicious actors seeking to automate and scale cyberattacks. The platform's unrestricted nature has sparked debate among cybersecurity professionals, policymakers, and AI developers about the need for regulations and ethics in AI development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138241</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenAI Assistant DIANNA Uncovers New Obfuscated Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/genai-assistant-dianna/</link>
      <description>BypassERWDirectSyscallShellcodeLoader is a sophisticated new malware strain generated with the assistance of large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT and DeepSeek. It is engineered with unprecedented speed, complexity, and obfuscation, rendering legacy antivirus (AV) solutions and signature-based defenses obsolete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138230</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViciousTrap Uses Cisco Flaw to Build Global Honeypot from 5,300 Compromised Devices</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/vicioustrap-uses-cisco-flaw-to-build.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Small Business RV016, RV042, RV042G, RV082, RV320, RV325 Routers; CVE(s): CVE-2023-20118; Summary: The vulnerability (CVE-2023-2018) is a critical security flaw that allows threat actors to compromise nearly 5,300 unique network edge devices and turn them into honeypot-like networks. Exploitation involves the execution of a shell script (NetGhost), which redirects incoming traffic to a honeypot infrastructure under attacker control, allowing interception of network flows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/vicioustrap-uses-cisco-flaw-to-build.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Expose 184 Million User Passwords via Open Directory</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/expose-184-million-user-passwords/</link>
      <description>A publicly accessible database containing 184,162,718 unique logins and passwords has been discovered, exposing sensitive information such as emails, usernames, passwords, and direct URLs to login pages for various services. The database was not password-protected or encrypted, leaving it vulnerable to anyone who found it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138222</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Formjacking Malware Targets E-Commerce Sites to Steal Credit Card Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-formjacking-malware-targets-e-commerce-sites/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WooCommerce; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new formjacking malware targets WooCommerce-based e-commerce sites to steal sensitive credit card information. The malware seamlessly integrates into the legitimate payment workflow, mimicking design and functionality with precision, making it difficult for site owners and customers to detect. It captures input in real-time, ensuring data is harvested even if a transaction isn’t completed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138207</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Duo Vulnerability Exploited to Inject Malicious Links and Steal Source Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gitlab-duo-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab Duo; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers could exploit an indirect prompt injection flaw to exfiltrate private source code, manipulate AI-generated code suggestions, and leak confidential zero-day vulnerabilities by embedding malicious instructions in project content. The vulnerability leveraged GitLab Duo's real-time Markdown rendering and insufficient input sanitization, allowing attackers to inject raw HTML tags into the AI's responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138145</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Infrastructure and TTPs Behind ALCATRAZ Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-uncover-infrastructure-and-ttps/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new malware family called DOUBLELOADER, which is protected by the open-source obfuscator ALCATRAZ. The malware uses various techniques such as control flow flattening, instruction mutation, and anti-disassembly tricks to hinder analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138185</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAG-110 Hackers Deploy Malicious Word Templates in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tag-110-hackers-deploy-malicious-word-templates/</link>
      <description>TAG-110, a Russia-aligned threat actor, has shifted tactics to target government, educational, and research entities in Tajikistan by leveraging macro-enabled Microsoft Word template files (.dotm) for initial access and persistence. The campaign involves the use of VBA macros to collect system information and transmit it to a command-and-control (C2) server, potentially deploying known TAG-110 malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138135</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300 Servers and €3.5M Seized as Europol Strikes Ransomware Networks Worldwide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/300-servers-and-35m-seized-as-europol.html</link>
      <description>As part of Operation Endgame, law enforcement agencies took down 300 servers, neutralized 650 domains, and issued arrest warrants against 20 targets. Additionally, €3.5 million in cryptocurrency was seized, bringing the total amount seized during the operation to over €21.2 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/300-servers-and-35m-seized-as-europol.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winos 4.0 Malware Masquerades as VPN and QQBrowser to Target Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/winos-4-0-malware-masquerades-as-vpn-and-qqbrowser/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign using Winos 4.0, a memory-resident stager, has been uncovered by Rapid7, targeting users through fake installers of popular software like LetsVPN and QQBrowser. The campaign employs a multi-layered infection chain dubbed the Catena loader, which uses trojanized NSIS installers to deliver payloads entirely in memory, evading traditional antivirus tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138123</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeLine WAF: Open Source Web Application Firewall with Zero-Day Detection and Bot Protection</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/safeline-waf-open-source-web.html</link>
      <description>None (This article is not about a vulnerability but provides information on the features and benefits of an open-source Web Application Firewall called SafeLine.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/safeline-waf-open-source-web.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETGEAR Router Flaw Allows Full Admin Access by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/netgear-router-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NETGEAR DGND3700v2 wireless routers; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4978; Summary: A severe authentication bypass vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to gain full administrative control over affected devices, enabling complete network compromise, credential theft, malware deployment, and traffic interception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138115</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarcity signals: Are rare activities red flags?</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/scarcity-signals-are-rare-activities-red-flags/</link>
      <description>The article presents a study by Cisco Talos analyzing PowerShell network connection logs from June 1, 2024 to December 31, 2024. The researchers found that domains that PowerShell rarely connects to are more likely to be malicious than frequently contacted domains, regardless of the PowerShell module used. The study highlights the importance of considering subdomains when looking for malicious network traffic and suggests focusing investigations on rare domains due to their higher likelihood of being malicious.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682f3d9733f1ee0001266aae</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Market: Torzon Market</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-market-torzon-market/</link>
      <description>No vulnerability is discussed in this article. The article provides an overview of a Dark Web marketplace called Torzon Market, which hosts illegal products and services and facilitates transactions through cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Monero. The article highlights the market's features, product categories, security measures, and threat implications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060183</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok videos now push infostealer malware in ClickFix attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tiktok-videos-now-push-infostealer-malware-in-clickfix-attacks/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are using TikTok videos, possibly generated using AI, to trick users into infecting themselves with Vidar and StealC information-stealing malware through ClickFix attacks. The videos instruct viewers to run PowerShell commands, which download and execute remote scripts that install the malware, allowing it to steal sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tiktok-videos-now-push-infostealer-malware-in-clickfix-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Endgame Crushes DanaBot Malware, Shuts Down 150 C2 Servers and Halts 1,000 Daily Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/operation-endgame-crushes-danabot-malware/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather an operation to disrupt a notorious malware called DanaBot. The operation, known as Operation Endgame II, successfully dismantled a significant portion of DanaBot's infrastructure and exposed its sophisticated tactics behind its resilience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138098</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple XNU Kernel Flaw Enables Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apple-xnu-kernel-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31219; Summary: The vulnerability in Apple's XNU kernel (CVE-2025-31219) allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code with kernel-level access. The flaw arises from improper memory handling and a race condition, which can be exploited by an attacker with low privileges on the target system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138079</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LockBit: Data Leak Reveals Leading Affiliates and How They Operate</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lockbit-data-leak-reveals-leading-affiliates/</link>
      <description>The article provides a unique glimpse into the inner workings of the LockBit ransomware group's "LockBit Lite" panel, which offers an accessible entry point for novice threat actors. The leaked data reveals the group's focus on Chinese organizations and Russian targets, as well as its attempts to recruit new members. The article also highlights the operational inefficiencies within the Lite program, including decryptor failures and instances where affiliates provided basic security advice to victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138082</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViciousTrap Hackers Breaches 5,500+ Edge Devices from 50+ Brands, Turns Them into Honeypots</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vicioustrap-hackers-breaches-5500-edge-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVEs: CVE-2023-20118, CVE-2021-32030; Summary: A sophisticated threat actor, dubbed ViciousTrap, has compromised over 5,500 edge devices from multiple brands, transforming them into a massive honeypot-like network. The attack chain begins with the exploitation of known vulnerabilities and deploys a shell script to redirect inbound traffic to attacker-controlled interception servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138035</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Notepad gets AI-powered text writing capabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-notepad-gets-ai-powered-text-writing-capabilities/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the development of AI-powered features in Microsoft's Notepad application, including a new "Write" feature that generates text based on custom prompts. It also mentions updates to Paint and Snipping Tool, as well as other related news and announcements from Microsoft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-notepad-gets-ai-powered-text-writing-capabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hacker Indicted Over $24 Million Qakbot Ransomware Operation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/24-million-qakbot-operation/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice has indicted Rustam Rafailevich Gallyamov for leading the development and deployment of the Qakbot malware, which infected over 700,000 computers globally and enabled ransomware attacks, credential theft, and botnet activity. The malware's capabilities included credential harvesting, lateral movement, payload delivery, persistence, and evasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138073</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Zero-Day Under Attack: PoC Now Publicly Available</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortinet-zero-day-poc/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: The vulnerability allows for unauthenticated remote code execution due to a stack-based buffer overflow in the handling of session cookies within the administrative API. Attackers can supply a base64-encoded string that exceeds the allocated buffer size, resulting in an overflow and potential arbitrary code execution with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138030</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Dismantles DanaBot Malware Network, Charges 16 in $50M Global Cybercrime Operation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-dismantles-danabot-malware-network.html</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the disruption of an online infrastructure associated with DanaBot malware and unsealed charges against 16 individuals for their alleged involvement in its development and deployment. The article highlights the impact of DanaBot on hundreds of thousands of victims worldwide, causing millions of dollars in losses, and its capabilities to steal data, hijack banking sessions, and provide remote access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/us-dismantles-danabot-malware-network.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police takes down 300 servers in ransomware supply-chain crackdown</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-takes-down-300-servers-in-ransomware-supply-chain-crackdown/</link>
      <description>Operation Endgame, an international law enforcement operation, seized 300 servers and 650 domains used for launching ransomware attacks. The operation targeted various cybercrime operations, including Bumblebee, Lactrodectus, Qakbot, DanaBot, Trickbot, and Warmcookie, disrupting the services criminals rely on to deploy ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-takes-down-300-servers-in-ransomware-supply-chain-crackdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Crackdown Nets 270 Dark Web Vendors in Major Arrests</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/global-crackdown-nets-270-dark-web-vendors-in-major-arrests/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

Operation RapTor was a coordinated international crackdown on cyber-enabled crime on the dark web, resulting in the arrest of 270 individuals involved in trafficking drugs, weapons, counterfeit goods, and illicit services. The operation used sophisticated intelligence gathering and technical forensics to identify vendors and buyers who had conducted thousands of illicit trades, despite relying on end-to-end encryption and anonymizing networks like Tor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138029</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Threat Actors Targeting Commvault Azure App to Steal Secrets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-commvault-azure-app/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Commvault Metallic software-as-a-service (SaaS); CVE(s): CVE-2025-3928, CVE-2025-34028; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-3928) in Commvault's web server was exploited by threat actors to access client secrets for the MetallicMicrosoft 365 (M365)backup solution. The compromise allowed attackers to potentially access customers' M365 environments and pose a risk to sensitive enterprise data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138028</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Warns of Suspected Broader SaaS Attacks Exploiting App Secrets and Cloud Misconfigs</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cisa-warns-of-suspected-broader-saas.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Commvault Web Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3928; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the Commvault Web Server (CVE-2025-3928) allows remote, authenticated attackers to create and execute web shells, enabling unauthorized access to customer M365 environments. The vulnerability was exploited by a nation-state threat actor, which may have accessed client secrets and app credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/cisa-warns-of-suspected-broader-saas.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 05:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Duo Vulnerability Enabled Attackers to Hijack AI Responses with Hidden Prompts</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/gitlab-duo-vulnerability-enabled.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab Duo; CVE(s): None; Summary: An indirect prompt injection flaw in GitLab's AI-powered coding assistant Duo allows attackers to steal source code, manipulate code suggestions, and exfiltrate confidential information. The vulnerability enables threat actors to inject hidden prompts within merge requests, commit messages, or comments, which can then be used to execute malicious JavaScript packages or redirect users to fake login pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/gitlab-duo-vulnerability-enabled.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langflow: CVE-2025-3248: Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/blog/langflow-cve-2025-3248</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: A critical missing authentication vulnerability allows remote, unauthenticated attackers to send crafted HTTP requests and execute arbitrary code by abusing Python decorators and default arguments. Exploiting the vulnerability can lead to remote code execution (RCE) without authentication or adequate restriction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/blog/langflow-cve-2025-3248</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude 4 benchmarks show improvements, but context is still 200K</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-4-benchmarks-show-improvements-but-context-is-still-200k/</link>
      <description>Anthropic announced Claude 4 models, which outperform previous models and competitors in coding benchmarks. However, the model still has a limited context window of 200,000 tokens, lagging behind competitors like Google's Gemini 2.5 Pro and ChatGPT's 4.1 models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-4-benchmarks-show-improvements-but-context-is-still-200k/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oops: DanaBot Malware Devs Infected Their Own PCs</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/oops-danabot-malware-devs-infected-their-own-pcs/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a malware-as-a-service platform called DanaBot, which was used for credential theft and banking fraud. The FBI unsealed criminal charges against 16 individuals accused of operating and selling the malware, which infected over 300,000 systems globally and caused estimated losses of more than $50 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71351</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US indicts leader of Qakbot botnet linked to ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-indicts-leader-of-qakbot-botnet-linked-to-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article reports on the indictment of Russian national Rustam Rafailevich Gallyamov for leading the Qakbot botnet malware operation that compromised over 700,000 computers and enabled ransomware attacks. The operation was used to provide initial access for various ransomware gangs, resulting in hundreds of millions of dollars in damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-indicts-leader-of-qakbot-botnet-linked-to-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destructive malware available in NPM repo went unnoticed for 2 years</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/05/destructive-malware-available-in-npm-repo-went-unnoticed-for-2-years/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NPM (Node Package Manager); CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on malicious NPM packages that were designed to detonate on specific dates in 2023 and beyond. The packages, masquerading as legitimate development tools, targeted users of popular JavaScript ecosystems such as React, Vue, and Vite. The impact includes system shutdowns, file deletion, and JavaScript prototype corruption if installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/05/destructive-malware-available-in-npm-repo-went-unnoticed-for-2-years/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CefSharp Enumeration Tool Identifies Critical Security Issues in .NET Desktop Applications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cefsharp-enumeration-tool-identifies-critical-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CefSharp; CVE(s): None; Summary: CefSharp, a lightweight wrapper around the Chromium Embedded Framework (CEF), allows developers to embed Chromium browsers within .NET applications. However, this powerful framework often lacks proper security hardening, exposing applications to severe risks such as stealthy exploitation, persistence mechanisms, and even Remote Code Execution (RCE) when misconfigurations are present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137943</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghosted by a cybercriminal</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/ghosted-by-a-cybercriminal/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses the trend of threat actors forming partnerships or "partnerships" across the attack chain, with each group handling a slice of the operation. The author notes that this compartmentalized approach can lead to fragile supply chains and potential issues if one actor drops out. The article also mentions recent examples of cybercriminal groups imploding due to poor communication, infighting, or other issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682e27f35a640a000109c19a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Exploit Oracle Cloud Infrastructure to Target Scaleway Object Storage</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-hackers-exploit-oracle-cloud-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Russian-speaking attackers are using trusted cloud infrastructure platforms like Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) Object Storage and Scaleway Object Storage to propagate Lumma Stealer malware. The attacks target Windows systems, stealing credentials, system data, and cryptocurrency wallets, and exploit fake reCAPTCHA pages hosted on legitimate cloud services to trick users into executing malicious commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137929</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Netwrix Password Manager Enables Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-netwrix-password-manager/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Netwrix Password Secure; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical security vulnerability was discovered in Netwrix Password Secure, allowing authenticated attackers to execute remote code on other users' systems by exploiting a flaw in the document-sharing functionality. The issue stems from the application's failure to verify the file path and document type attributes when updating document links, which can be used to bypass whitelisting of allowed file types and execute malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137917</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers use fake Ledger apps to steal Mac users’ seed phrases</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-use-fake-ledger-apps-to-steal-mac-users-seed-phrases/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ledger; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybercriminals are using fake Ledger apps to target macOS users and steal seed phrases that protect access to digital cryptocurrency wallets. The malicious apps impersonate the legitimate Ledger app, tricking users into entering their seed phrase on a phishing page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-use-fake-ledger-apps-to-steal-mac-users-seed-phrases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cityworks Zero-Day Vulnerability Used by UAT-638 Hackers to Infect IIS Servers with Shell Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cityworks-zero-day-vulnerability-used-by-uat-638-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cityworks; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0994; Summary: A zero-day remote-code-execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-0994) in Cityworks, a widely used asset management system, has been actively exploited by Chinese-speaking threat actors (UAT-6382). The attackers target enterprise networks of local governing bodies in the United States, deploying web shells and custom malware on IIS web servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137905</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Warn of ‘Smiao Network’ Cyber Threat Against Taiwan’s Federal Staff</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-warn-of-smiao-network-cyber-threat/</link>
      <description>The Smiao Network is a Chinese intelligence operation targeting federal workers in the US and Taiwan. It uses deceptive online recruitment schemes to extract sensitive information from high-value professionals. The operation employs fake consulting firms and social engineering tactics to recruit insiders, with some success in the US and potential threats in Taiwan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137891</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vidar and StealC Malware Delivered Through Viral TikTok Videos by Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vidar-and-stealc-malware-delivered/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated social engineering campaign is using TikTok to distribute information-stealing malware Vidar and StealC. The campaign leverages AI-generated video content, fake voices, and step-by-step instructions to deceive users into executing harmful PowerShell commands, posing significant risks to individual users and businesses through data exfiltration and credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137875</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities carry out global takedown of infostealer used by cybercriminals</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/authorities-carry-out-global-takedown-of-infostealer-used-by-cybercriminals/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: Lumma is an info stealer malware used by various cybercriminal groups, including Scattered Spider and nation-state actors, to steal sensitive information such as credit card numbers, cryptocurrency data, and more. The malware's prevalence has made it easier for attackers to hide their tracks, and its usage has exploded in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/authorities-carry-out-global-takedown-of-infostealer-used-by-cybercriminals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Security Achieves SOC 2 Type 1 Compliance, Validating Security Controls for Its Attack Surface Management Platform</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/halo-security-achieves-soc-2-type-1-compliance/</link>
      <description>Halo Security, a provider of attack surface management and penetration testing services, has achieved SOC 2 Type 1 compliance following an audit by Insight Assurance. This certification demonstrates the company's commitment to protecting customer data with robust security measures, implemented policies, and defined access controls. The achievement is seen as essential for a company that helps organizations identify and remediate security vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=138008</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Weaponized npm Packages to Target React and Node.js JavaScript Frameworks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-weaponized-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A series of malicious npm packages have been found targeting popular frameworks like React, Vue.js, Vite, Node.js, and the Quill Editor. The packages were crafted by a threat actor under the npm alias “xuxingfeng” and carry destructive payloads aimed at corrupting data, deleting critical files, and triggering system shutdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137855</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrests 270 dark web vendors, buyers in global crackdown</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-arrests-270-dark-web-vendors-buyers-in-global-crackdown/</link>
      <description>The article reports on an international law enforcement operation called "Operation RapTor" that targeted dark web vendors and customers from ten countries. The operation resulted in 270 arrests, the seizure of €184 million in cash and cryptocurrency, over 2 tonnes of drugs, and over 180 firearms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-arrests-270-dark-web-vendors-buyers-in-global-crackdown/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious VS Code Extensions Target Windows Solidity Developers to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-vs-code-extensions-target-windows-solidity-developers/</link>
      <description>A targeted malware campaign targeting Solidity developers on Windows systems uses malicious Visual Studio Code (VS Code) extensions as the initial attack vector. The campaign delivers a complex multi-stage infection chain to steal cryptocurrency wallet credentials and establish persistence on victim systems, highlighting the risk of supply chain attacks in development environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137794</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma Stealer Infrastructure Behind Global Attacks on Millions of Users Dismantled</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lumma-stealer-infrastructure-behind-global-attacks/</link>
      <description>The US Justice Department, in collaboration with the FBI and private sector partners like Microsoft, has disrupted the Lumma Stealer malware infrastructure, a notorious Malware-as-a-Service platform linked to over 1.7 million instances of data theft worldwide. The operation involved seizing five critical internet domains used as user panels for deploying the malware and marks a decisive step in curbing one of the most active cyber threats in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137953</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Using Trusted Google Domains to Spread Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-using-trusted-google-domains/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google APIs; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybercriminals are exploiting integrations with Google APIs, specifically through JSONP calls, to inject malicious scripts into legitimate online stores, redirecting unsuspecting shoppers to fraudulent payment pages and tricking them into disclosing sensitive credit card information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137756</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Kernel Zero-Day SMB Vulnerability Discovered via ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/linux-kernel-zero-day-smb-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: The Linux kernel's SMB server implementation using OpenAI's o3 language model; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37899; Summary: A zero-day use-after-free bug in the Linux kernel's SMB server implementation allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges by exploiting a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137893</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit Trimble Cityworks Flaw to Infiltrate U.S. Government Networks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-trimble.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trimble Cityworks; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0944; Summary: A remote-code-execution vulnerability in Trimble Cityworks, tracked as CVE-2025-0944 (CVSS score: 8.6), allows attackers to deliver Cobalt Strike and VShell. The vulnerability has been exploited by the Chinese-speaking threat actor UAT-6382 to conduct reconnaissance, deploy web shells, and maintain long-term access to infected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-trimble.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gujarat Teen Arrested for Orchestrating Over 50 Cyberattacks in ‘Operation Sindoor’</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gujarat-teen-arrested-for-orchestrating-over-50-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>The Gujarat Anti-Terrorism Squad (ATS) apprehended two individuals, including a minor, for orchestrating sophisticated cyber attacks against Indian websites and disseminating anti-national content online. The suspects demonstrated advanced technical proficiency despite limited formal education, having established multiple communication channels to document and share their exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137879</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANS 2025 Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) Survey: Navigating Uncertainty in Today’s Threat Landscape</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/sans-2025-cyber-threat-intelligence-cti-survey/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability but provides insights into the Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) landscape, highlighting trends and best practices in 2025. It discusses the use of MITRE ATT&amp;CK framework, leveraging Artificial Intelligence (AI) in CTI workflows, and challenges faced by CTI teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060170</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Webex Meetings Vulnerability Enables HTTP Response Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-webex-meetings-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Webex Meetings; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability in Cisco Webex Meetings allows remote attackers to manipulate HTTP responses without authentication using HTTP cache poisoning techniques. This could potentially disrupt how the service delivers responses to client applications, allowing attackers to compromise the integrity of HTTP responses and return incorrect information to legitimate clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137838</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Expert Reveals the Hidden Dangers of Bad Code on Your PC’s Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-expert-reveals-the-hidden-dangers-of-bad-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft .NET; CVE(s): None; Summary: The .NET framework has a memory leak when using the "reloadOnChange: true" parameter in configuration files. This can cause gradual system resource consumption, leading to slow performance or crashes. The issue is more prominent in .NET 7 and higher due to changes in memory management architecture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137866</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti EPMM flaw exploited by Chinese hackers to breach govt agencies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-epmm-flaw-exploited-by-chinese-hackers-to-breach-govt-agencies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4428; Summary: A remote code execution flaw (CVE-2025-4428) allows attackers to execute code remotely on Ivanti EPMM version 12.5.0.0 and earlier via specially crafted API requests, which has been exploited by the UNC5221 activity cluster since May 15, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-epmm-flaw-exploited-by-chinese-hackers-to-breach-govt-agencies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-unified-intelligence-center-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Intelligence Center; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20113, CVE-2025-20114; Summary: The Unified Intelligence Center contains two security vulnerabilities that allow authenticated remote attackers to escalate privileges. The more severe flaw (CVE-2025-20113) has a CVSS score of 7.1 and enables attackers to elevate their privileges to Administrator level for a limited set of functions, while the secondary vulnerability (CVE-2025-20114) allows horizontal privilege escalation attacks through insecure direct object references.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137830</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-47949: Samlify Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-47949-samlify-authentication-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samlify; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47949; Summary: A critical Signature Wrapping vulnerability (CVE-2025-47949) in Samlify versions prior to v2.10.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication mechanisms, granting unauthorized access. The flaw enables manipulation of signed SAML responses, posing a significant risk to systems relying on SAML-based Single Sign-On (SSO).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060162</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers breach US local governments using Cityworks zero-day</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-breach-us-local-governments-using-cityworks-zero-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trimble Cityworks; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0994; Summary: The Trimble Cityworks GIS-based asset management software contains a high-severity deserialization vulnerability (CVE-2025-0994) that allows authenticated threat actors to execute code remotely on Microsoft IIS servers. The vulnerability was exploited by Chinese-speaking hackers, known as UAT-6382, to breach multiple local governing bodies across the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-breach-us-local-governments-using-cityworks-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NIST Security Metric Aims to Pinpoint Exploited Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nist-security-metric-aims-to-pinpoint/</link>
      <description>The National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) have introduced a new security metric called Likely Exploited Vulnerabilities (LEV) to improve vulnerability management. The LEV metric aims to predict which vulnerabilities are most likely to be exploited, enabling organizations to prioritize remediation efforts more efficiently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137799</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting Lumma Stealer Malware – Microsoft Leads Global Action</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/disrupting-lumma-stealer-malware-microsoft-leads-global-action/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the takedown of LummaC2, an infostealer malware strain used by threat actors worldwide. The malware was distributed via spear phishing emails, malicious links, and spoofed software downloads, and had features such as browser data theft, credential harvesting, and crypto wallet extraction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060152</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Windows Server 2025 dMSA Vulnerability Enables Active Directory Compromise</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/critical-windows-server-2025-dmsa.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): None; Summary: A privilege escalation flaw has been demonstrated in Windows Server 2025 that makes it possible for attackers to compromise any user in Active Directory (AD) by exploiting the delegated Managed Service Account (dMSA) feature. The attack simulates the dMSA migration process, allowing an attacker to gain similar privileges and breach the entire domain even if the organization's Windows Server 2025 domain isn't using dMSAs at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/critical-windows-server-2025-dmsa.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC finalizes order requiring GoDaddy to secure hosting services</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ftc-finalizes-order-requiring-godaddy-to-secure-hosting-services/</link>
      <description>GoDaddy has finalized an order with the FTC to secure its services after allegations of data security failures led to several breaches since 2018. The order requires GoDaddy to establish a robust information security program, secure APIs, and implement multi-factor authentication (MFA) among other measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ftc-finalizes-order-requiring-godaddy-to-secure-hosting-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit Ivanti EPMM Bugs in Global Enterprise Network Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-ivanti-epmm.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The pair of security flaws allows execution of arbitrary code on a vulnerable device without authentication. They were exploited by UNC5221, a Chinese cyber espionage group, to target various sectors across Europe, North America, and Asia-Pacific. The attack chain involves targeting the "/mifs/rs/api/v2/" endpoint to obtain an interactive reverse shell and remotely execute commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-ivanti-epmm.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advisory Update on Cyber Threat Activity Targeting Commvault’s SaaS Cloud Application (Metallic)</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/22/advisory-update-cyber-threat-activity-targeting-commvaults-saas-cloud-application-metallic</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Commvault Metallic Microsoft 365 backup software-as-a-service (SaaS); CVE(s): CVE-2025-3928; Summary: Threat actors may have accessed client secrets for Commvault's Metallic M365 backup SaaS solution, hosted in Azure, providing unauthorized access to customers' M365 environments. This vulnerability is part of a larger campaign targeting various SaaS companies' cloud applications with default configurations and elevated permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23430</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/22/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4632; Summary: The vulnerability allows for path traversal, posing a significant risk to the federal enterprise and other organizations. It has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23428</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/22/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on May 22, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories are related to Lantronix Device Installer and Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Historian ThingWorx products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23426</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Historian ThingWorx</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-142-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Historian ThingWorx, 95057C-FTHTWXCT11; CVE(s): CVE-2018-1285; Summary: Successful exploitation of this XXE-based vulnerability could allow an attacker to launch attacks on applications that accept malicious log4net configuration files. The vulnerability affects versions v4.02.00 and prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23425</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lantronix Device Installer</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-142-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lantronix Device Installer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4338; Summary: Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in the Device Installer software, allowing an attacker to gain access to the host machine or obtain credentials to access network devices. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to modify configurations and gain access to the password hash of the user running the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23424</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Best Practices Guide for Securing AI Data Released</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/22/new-best-practices-guide-securing-ai-data-released</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the National Security Agency, the Federal Bureau of Investigation, and international partners released a joint information sheet on AI data security best practices. The document highlights the importance of securing data used to train and operate AI systems to ensure their accuracy, integrity, and trustworthiness. It provides recommendations for organizations to adopt robust data protection measures, proactively manage risks, and strengthen monitoring and threat detection capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23419</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Learn How to Build a Reasonable and Legally Defensible Cybersecurity Program</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/webinar-learn-how-to-build-reasonable.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of having a structured cybersecurity program to meet legal and industry standards, citing new privacy laws, ransomware lawsuits, and regulatory investigations as examples of the increasing expectations on organizations. It promotes a free webinar hosted with the Center for Internet Security (CIS) that provides a practical approach to building a cybersecurity program that meets these standards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/webinar-learn-how-to-build-reasonable.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatched Versa Concerto Flaws Let Attackers Escape Docker and Compromise Host</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/unpatched-versa-concerto-flaws-let.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Concerto; CVE(s): CVE-2025-34025, CVE-2025-34026, CVE-2025-34027; Summary: The Versa Concerto network security and SD-WAN orchestration platform has multiple critical vulnerabilities that can be exploited to take control of susceptible instances. These vulnerabilities include a privilege escalation and Docker container escape vulnerability (CVE-2025-34025), an authentication bypass vulnerability in the Traefik reverse proxy configuration (CVE-2025-34026 and CVE-2025-34027), which could allow remote code execution using LD_PRELOAD and a reverse shell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/unpatched-versa-concerto-flaws-let.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Cyber Attacks in Review: April 2025</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/major-cyber-attacks-in-review-april-2025/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article provides a roundup of 10 notable cybersecurity incidents that occurred in April 2025. The incidents include data breaches at healthcare providers, telecom giants, and open-source ecosystems, as well as ransomware attacks and hacktivist activity. The article highlights the patterns behind these incidents, including credential theft, misconfigurations, and vulnerable third parties. It also provides an overview of the impact of these incidents and the measures taken to contain them.

Additionally, the article touches on various cybersecurity-relevant topics, such as SIM swapping, phishing-resistant MFA, and the importance of connected visibility across digital footprints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060131</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal now blocks Microsoft Recall screenshots on Windows 11</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/signal-now-blocks-microsoft-recall-screenshots-on-windows-11/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Microsoft Recall feature, introduced in May 2024, continuously takes screenshots of all active windows every few seconds and analyzes them to build a database that can be searched using natural language. This has been criticized by security experts as a privacy nightmare and significant security risk due to the potential for attackers to steal user data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/signal-now-blocks-microsoft-recall-screenshots-on-windows-11/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity Security Has an Automation Problem—And It's Bigger Than You Think</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/identity-security-has-automation.html</link>
      <description>New research from Cerby reveals that human error remains a significant threat to enterprise security, with few organizations having fully automated their core identity workflows. Manual processes and reliance on humans for tasks like password management, MFA enablement, and user provisioning leave organizations exposed to breaches and compliance failures. The study highlights the need for automation in identity security, citing a 41% manual sharing of passwords and an 89% reliance on users for MFA enablement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/identity-security-has-automation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAT-6382 exploits Cityworks zero-day vulnerability to deliver malware</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/uat-6382-exploits-cityworks-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a technical analysis of a malicious software campaign, specifically focusing on the VShell stager and its components. The article details the tactics used by threat actors to deliver malware through TetraLoader and VShell, as well as the characteristics of the CobaltStrike beacons used in this campaign.

Based on the provided information, I did not identify any specific vulnerabilities discussed in the article. Instead, the analysis highlights the techniques employed by malicious actors to evade detection and compromise target systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682c99a99e517d0001f3c25e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versa Concerto 0-Day Flaw Enables Remote Code Execution by Bypassing Authentication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/versa-concerto-0-day-flaw-enables-remote-code-execution/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Concerto; CVE(s): CVE-2025-34025, CVE-2025-34026, CVE-2025-34027; Summary: Multiple critical vulnerabilities were discovered in Versa Concerto's network security and SD-WAN orchestration platform, including authentication bypass flaws, arbitrary file write vulnerabilities, and container escape techniques that allow attackers to fully compromise both the application and underlying host system. The issues stem from inconsistent URL processing and a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability in the AuthenticationFilter class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137765</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatched critical bugs in Versa Concerto lead to auth bypass, RCE</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/unpatched-critical-bugs-in-versa-concerto-lead-to-auth-bypass-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Concerto; CVE(s): CVE-2025-34027, CVE-2025-34026, CVE-2025-34025; Summary: Critical vulnerabilities in Versa Concerto allow remote attackers to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary code. Two critical issues (CVE-2025-34027 and CVE-2025-34026) allow for authentication bypass and remote code execution, while a high-severity issue (CVE-2025-34025) exposes host binaries to container writes, enabling full host compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/unpatched-critical-bugs-in-versa-concerto-lead-to-auth-bypass-rce/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Targets Coinbase Users Targeted in Advanced Social Engineering Hack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-targets-coinbase-users/</link>
      <description>Coinbase users are being targeted by a social engineering campaign that manipulates human psychology and leverages stolen insider data to execute highly personalized fraud. The attackers use a four-stage methodology that bypasses Coinbase's technical infrastructure, impersonating official support and using phishing emails and texts to guide victims into transferring assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137747</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit PyBitmessage Library to Evade Antivirus and Network Security Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-pybitmessage-library/</link>
      <description>A new strain of backdoor malware is distributed alongside a Monero coin miner, utilizing the PyBitmessage library for covert peer-to-peer communications. The malware encrypts data exchanges and anonymizes identities, making it challenging to detect by antivirus software and network security solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137699</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several GitLab Vulnerabilities Enable Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/several-gitlab-vulnerabilities-enable-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0993, CVE-2024-7803, CVE-2024-12093, CVE-2025-4979, CVE-2025-0679, CVE-2024-9163, CVE-2025-1110; Summary: GitLab issued critical security patches addressing 11 vulnerabilities across its Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE) platforms. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2025-0993) enables authenticated attackers to trigger server resource exhaustion through an unprotected large blob endpoint, scoring 7.5 on the CVSS v3.1 scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137744</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Identity Services RADIUS Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Trigger Denial of Service Condition</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-identity-services-radius-vulnerability-allows-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause a denial of service condition by exploiting flaws in the RADIUS message processing feature, causing affected devices to reload and disrupt network authentication services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137737</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grafana Zero-Day Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Redirect Users to Malicious Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/grafana-zero-day-vulnerability-allows-attackers-to-redirect-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grafana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4123; Summary: The Grafana XSS vulnerability (CVE-2025-4123) allows attackers to redirect users to malicious websites, enabling execution of arbitrary JavaScript code. The vulnerability can be exploited without editor permissions and has a CVSS score of 7.6 (HIGH). It impacts all supported versions of Grafana OSS and Enterprise, including versions 11.2 through 12.0, as well as unsupported versions dating back to at least Grafana 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137731</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI and Europol Disrupt Lumma Stealer Malware Network Linked to 10 Million Infections</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fbi-and-europol-disrupt-lumma-stealer.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the takedown of 2,300 domains associated with the LummaC2 infostealer malware by global law enforcement agencies and private sector firms. The malware is used to steal sensitive information from millions of victims for fraudulent purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fbi-and-europol-disrupt-lumma-stealer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Exploit BIND DNS Server Vulnerability to Crash Servers Using Malicious Packets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-exploit-bind-dns-server-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Internet Systems Consortium (ISC) BIND; CVE(s): CVE-2023-5517, CVE-2023-5679, CVE-2024-0760, CVE-2024-12705; Summary: The vulnerability in BIND DNS server software allowed attackers to crash DNS servers by sending specifically crafted malicious packets. This flaw could cause named (the BIND DNS server process) to terminate unexpectedly with an assertion failure when specific queries were processed with certain features enabled, posing a significant risk to DNS infrastructure and potentially affecting thousands of users and dependent systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137701</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Process Injection Technique Evades EDR by Injecting Malicious Code into Windows Processes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-process-injection-technique-evades-edr/</link>
      <description>Researchers discovered a novel process injection technique that exploits shared memory regions and thread context manipulation to execute malicious payloads without triggering standard detection heuristics. This method bypasses leading Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) systems by avoiding traditional memory allocation and modification patterns, evading detection in multiple commercial EDR products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137682</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Deep Web and Dark Web Forums</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/top-10-deep-web-and-dark-web-forums/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the top Dark Web hacker forums, which serve as key platforms for threat actors to share tools, trade stolen data, and coordinate illicit activities. These forums are not static and can evolve, vanish, or reappear under new names and leadership. The article highlights the importance of tracking these forums for security researchers and professionals engaged in Dark Web threat intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100043222</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThreatBook Recognized as a Notable Vendor in Global Network Analysis and Visibility (NAV) Report</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threatbook-recognized-as-a-notable-vendor-in-global-network-analysis-and-visibility/</link>
      <description>ThreatBook, a global leader in cyber threat and response solutions, has been recognized as a notable vendor in Forrester's Network Analysis And Visibility Solutions Landscape, Q2 2025 report. This recognition highlights ThreatBook's technical excellence and strong market performance in delivering real-time security insights across cloud, hybrid, and on-premises environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137688</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Aligned TAG-110 Targets Tajikistan with Macro-Enabled</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/russia-aligned-tag-110-targets-tajikistan-with-macro-enabled</link>
      <description>This article reports on a phishing campaign attributed to TAG-110, a Russia-aligned threat actor. The campaign targets Tajikistan government institutions and educational/research bodies, using macro-enabled Word template files (.dotm) as lure material. The documents share VBA code with previous campaigns, indicating the group's persistence in targeting Central Asia. Insikt Group warns of potential further attacks and provides recommendations for detection and prevention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/russia-aligned-tag-110-targets-tajikistan-with-macro-enabled</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic web config hints at Claude Sonnet 4 and Opus 4</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/anthropic-web-config-hints-at-claude-sonnet-4-and-opus-4/</link>
      <description>Anthropic, the AI company, is reportedly working on new advanced AI models called Claude Sonnet 4 and Opus 4. These models are believed to be part of the Claude 4 series and are being tested or promoted internally with features like "show_raw_thinking" pointing to reasoning capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/anthropic-web-config-hints-at-claude-sonnet-4-and-opus-4/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 23:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI hints at a big upgrade for ChatGPT Operator Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-hints-at-a-big-upgrade-for-chatgpt-operator-agent/</link>
      <description>OpenAI's Operator AI agent, currently in research preview, will soon become a useful tool according to Jerry Tworek, VP of Research at OpenAI. The AI agent allows users to delegate web tasks and automate repetitive browser tasks, with plans for significant improvements soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-hints-at-a-big-upgrade-for-chatgpt-operator-agent/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Samlify SSO flaw lets attackers log in as admin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-samlify-sso-flaw-lets-attackers-log-in-as-admin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samlify; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47949; Summary: A critical authentication bypass vulnerability allows attackers to impersonate admin users by injecting unsigned malicious assertions into legitimately signed SAML responses, impacting all versions of Samlify before 2.10.0. The flaw can be exploited with access to a valid signed XML blob, allowing unauthorized remote attackers to perform privilege escalation and log in as administrators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-samlify-sso-flaw-lets-attackers-log-in-as-admin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian hackers breach orgs to track aid routes to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-breach-orgs-to-track-aid-routes-to-ukraine/</link>
      <description>APT28 (Fancy Bear/Forest Blizzard) hackers, sponsored by the Russian government, have been conducting a cyberespionage campaign targeting international organizations since 2022, compromising entities in defense, transportation, IT services, air traffic, and maritime sectors in 12 European countries and the United States. The hackers used various tactics, including password spraying, spear-phishing, and exploiting Microsoft Exchange vulnerabilities, to gain initial access and then move laterally within victim networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-breach-orgs-to-track-aid-routes-to-ukraine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Microsoft has simply given us no other option,” Signal says as it blocks Windows Recall</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/signal-resorts-to-weird-trick-to-block-windows-recall-in-desktop-app/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Recall; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Recall feature indexes Zoom meetings, emails, photos, medical conditions, and Signal conversations without user consent. It still takes screenshots of payment card details, decrypts database contents with a simple fingerprint scan or PIN, and lacks granular control for developers to prevent content indexing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/signal-resorts-to-weird-trick-to-block-windows-recall-in-desktop-app/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-306: Docker Desktop Helper Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-306/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Docker Desktop; CVE(s): CVE-2024-5652; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Docker Desktop, requiring low-privileged code execution and exploiting the WindowsContainersController class by creating a junction to delete a folder. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23513</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-307: Linux Kernel OpenvSwitch Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-307/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux Kernel OpenvSwitch; CVE(s): ZDI-25-307, ZDI-CAN-26711; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Linux Kernel. An attacker must obtain high-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which exists in the handling of userspace attributes due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26711</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-308: Adobe Dreamweaver V8 Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-308/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Dreamweaver V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30310; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Dreamweaver. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the JavaScript engine due to a vulnerable version of V8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25684</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to enforce location tracking app on all foreigners in Moscow</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/government/russia-to-enforce-location-tracking-app-on-all-foreigners-in-moscow/</link>
      <description>The Russian government has introduced a mandatory tracking app for all foreign nationals in the Moscow region, aiming to tackle migrant crimes and strengthen control over migration. The app will monitor residence location, fingerprint, face photograph, and real-time geo-location. Critics argue that this proposal violates privacy rights and raises concerns about its feasibility and potential to deter labor migrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/government/russia-to-enforce-location-tracking-app-on-all-foreigners-in-moscow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-291: (Pwn2Own) Mozilla Firefox IonMonkey JIT Compiler Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-291/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4919; Summary: The IonMonkey JIT compiler in Mozilla Firefox contains an integer overflow remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27172</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-292: (Pwn2Own) Mozilla Firefox SpiderMonkey Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-292/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4919; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Mozilla Firefox. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists within the SpiderMonkey engine due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27202</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-293: Microsoft Windows Installer Service Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-293/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29837; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by creating a symbolic link within the Windows Installer service, granting read access to arbitrary files and potentially disclosing stored credentials. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26153</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-294: Microsoft PC Manager MSPCManagerService Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-294/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft PC Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29975; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft PC Manager by creating a symbolic link and abusing the MSPCManagerService, allowing deletion of arbitrary files. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be leveraged to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26137</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-295: Trend Micro Apex Central widget getObjWGFServiceApiByApiName Local File Inclusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-295/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47865; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central by leveraging a local file inclusion remote code execution flaw in the getObjWGFServiceApiByApiName function, requiring authentication to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24938</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Exploit Email and VPN Vulnerabilities to Spy on Ukraine Aid Logistics</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-exploit-email-and-vpn.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2020-12641, CVE-2020-35730, CVE-2021-44026, CVE-2023-23397, CVE-2023-38831; Summary: APT28 (aka BlueDelta, Fancy Bear, or Forest Blizzard) has been attributed to a state-sponsored campaign targeting Western logistics entities and technology companies since 2022. The campaign uses a mix of previously disclosed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including password spraying, spear-phishing, modifying Microsoft Exchange mailbox permissions for espionage purposes, and exploiting vulnerabilities in various webmail services like Roundcube, Horde, MDaemon, and Zimbra.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russian-hackers-exploit-email-and-vpn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-296: Trend Micro Apex Central modTMCM Unrestricted File Upload Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-296/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47866; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to upload arbitrary files on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central, requiring authentication to exploit. The issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, enabling the upload of arbitrary files and potentially allowing code execution in the context of IUSR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25331</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-297: Trend Micro Apex Central widget getBlock Local File Inclusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-297/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47867; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central, requiring authentication. The issue stems from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to passing it to a PHP include function, which can be exploited to execute code in the context of IUSR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24936</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-298: Apple macOS MP4 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-298/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31233; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS, requiring user interaction. It exists within the parsing of MP4 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26826</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-299: Apple macOS acv2 Codec Converter Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-299/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31208; Summary: The acv2 codec converter in Apple macOS allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information through an out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability. User interaction is required, and the issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26783</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-300: Apple macOS PDF Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-300/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31209; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. The flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26714</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-301: Apple Safari Scrollbar Animation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-301/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31238; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple Safari, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the handling of scrollbar animation due to a lack of validating an object's existence before performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26150</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-302: Apple macOS CoreMedia Framework Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-302/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS CoreMedia Framework; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31239; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the CoreMedia framework due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26650</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-303: Apple Safari SandboxBroker ZIP File Processing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-303/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24222; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple Safari by reading past the end of an allocated buffer when processing ZIP files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26148</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-304: Apple macOS JPEG Image Decoding Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-304/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31251; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the JPEG image decoding functionality. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26603</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-305: Apple XNU kernel vm_map Race Condition Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-305/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple XNU kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31219; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Apple macOS. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the handling of virtual memory allocations in the macOS kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24156</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target Mobile Users Using PWA JavaScript to Bypass Browser Security</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-mobile-users-using-pwa-javascript/</link>
      <description>A new injection campaign targets mobile users through malicious third-party JavaScript, delivering a Chinese adult-content Progressive Web App (PWA) scam. The attack injects scripts into compromised websites, filtering out desktop users and exclusively targeting mobile devices to deliver fake adult content zones and push malware downloads for Android and iOS devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137642</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3AM ransomware uses spoofed IT calls, email bombing to breach networks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/3am-ransomware-uses-spoofed-it-calls-email-bombing-to-breach-networks/</link>
      <description>The article describes a targeted ransomware attack campaign conducted by a 3AM ransomware affiliate using email bombing and spoofed IT support calls to socially engineer employees into giving credentials for remote access. The attackers used tactics such as vishing via Microsoft Teams, Quick Assist abuse, and real phone phishing to gain access to corporate systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/3am-ransomware-uses-spoofed-it-calls-email-bombing-to-breach-networks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Zombie Malware Infects Containers for Crypto Mining and Self-Replication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/docker-zombie-malware-infects-containers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Docker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a novel malware campaign that targets containerized infrastructures by exploiting insecurely exposed Docker APIs. The attack spreads malicious containers and mines Dero cryptocurrency using self-replicating propagation mechanism, transforming compromised containers into "zombies" that mine cryptocurrency and infect new victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137633</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Masquerade as Organizations to Steal Payroll Logins and Redirect Payments from Employees</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-masquerade-as-organizations-to-steal-payroll-logins/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated search engine optimization (SEO) poisoning scheme has been deployed to orchestrate payroll fraud against a manufacturing sector customer. The attack involves creating fake authentication portals that mirror legitimate organizational login pages, manipulating search engine results to rank malicious sites at the top, and exploiting mobile-specific SEO manipulation to redirect users to phishing pages mimicking Microsoft login portals.

Note: There is no specific product or software mentioned in the article, but rather a technique used by attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137623</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PupkinStealer Exploits Web Browser Passwords and App Tokens to Exfiltrate Data Through Telegram</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pupkinstealer-exploits-web-browser-passwords/</link>
      <description>PupkinStealer (also known as PumpkinStealer) is a .NET-based information-stealing malware that targets sensitive data such as web browser passwords and application session tokens. It uses Telegram's Bot API to exfiltrate stolen data, and employs tactics mapped to the MITRE ATT&amp;CK framework for initial access through phishing and social engineering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137617</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>71 Fake Websites Impersonating German Retailer to Steal Payment Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/71-fake-websites-impersonating-german-retailer/</link>
      <description>A sprawling network of 71 fraudulent e-commerce domains impersonating a German retailer has been detected, employing advanced brand impersonation tactics and designed to harvest personal and financial data. The primary goal is to facilitate downstream fraud and card compromise, posing significant financial risks to card issuers and merchant acquirers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137608</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma infostealer malware operation disrupted, 2,300 domains seized</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-operation-disrupted-2-300-domains-seized/</link>
      <description>A coordinated disruption action targeted the Lumma malware-as-a-service information stealer operation, resulting in Microsoft's seizure of approximately 2,300 domains and multiple law enforcement authorities and tech companies disrupting its infrastructure. The effort denied access to the control panel, marketplace, and Internet infrastructure used by the malware, imposing operational and financial costs on both the operators and customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-operation-disrupted-2-300-domains-seized/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Scan Uncovers 150K Industrial Systems Worldwide Vulnerable to Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-scan-uncovers-150k-industrial-systems/</link>
      <description>The article reports that approximately 150,000 industrial control systems (ICS) worldwide are directly accessible on the public internet, posing severe risks of catastrophic cyberattacks. The study utilized advanced application-layer scanning to identify ICS devices, revealing a large number of exposed systems globally, with many not designed with robust security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137582</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Introduces Enhanced Administrator Protection to Strengthen Security Against Elevated Privilege Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-introduces-enhanced-administrator-protection/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the introduction of Administrator Protection, a security feature designed to safeguard systems against privilege escalation attacks. This feature creates a security boundary around administrative operations by implementing a hidden system-managed profile-separated local user account that generates isolated admin tokens, preventing user-level malware from compromising code running in elevated contexts and eliminating auto-elevation functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137592</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-stealing Chrome extensions impersonate Fortinet, YouTube, VPNs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-stealing-chrome-extensions-impersonate-fortinet-youtube-vpns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome Web Store; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious campaign has been discovered on the Google Chrome Web Store, featuring over 100 fake browser extensions that mimic legitimate tools to steal browser cookies and execute remote scripts. The extensions offer some functionality but also connect to threat actor infrastructure to steal user information or receive commands to execute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-stealing-chrome-extensions-impersonate-fortinet-youtube-vpns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThreatLocker Patch Management: A Security-First Approach to Closing Vulnerability Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threatlocker-patch-management-a-security-first-approach-to-closing-vulnerability-windows/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of patch management in cybersecurity, highlighting the challenges organizations face in executing consistent and secure patching at scale. It introduces ThreatLocker's Patch Management solution as a way to provide security teams with greater control, visibility, and confidence over patching workflows while minimizing risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threatlocker-patch-management-a-security-first-approach-to-closing-vulnerability-windows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Union sanctions Stark Industries for enabling cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/european-union-sanctions-stark-industries-for-enabling-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a specific vulnerability, but rather the imposition of sanctions by the European Union against web-hosting provider Stark Industries and its owners for enabling "destabilising activities" against the EU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/european-union-sanctions-stark-industries-for-enabling-cyberattacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PureRAT Malware Spikes 4x in 2025, Deploying PureLogs to Target Russian Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/purerat-malware-spikes-4x-in-2025.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a phishing campaign targeting Russian organizations, distributing malware called PureRAT. The attack chain begins with a phishing email containing a RAR file attachment or link, which extracts an executable that unpacks and runs the main payload, PureRAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/purerat-malware-spikes-4x-in-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerDNS Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Trigger DoS Attacks Through Malicious TCP Connections</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/powerdns-vulnerability-let-attacker-trigger-dos-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PowerDNS DNSdist; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30193; Summary: The DNSdist load balancer has a vulnerability (CVE-2025-30193) that allows remote attackers to trigger denial of service attacks without authentication, affecting all versions prior to 1.9.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137557</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanHelsing Ransomware Builder Exposed on Hacker Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VanHelsing Ransomware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The source code for the VanHelsing ransomware operation has been leaked publicly due to an internal dispute with a former developer. The leak includes critical components of the ransomware infrastructure, but some elements remain missing, limiting immediate exploitation by opportunistic threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137537</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Warns: One-Third of Cyber Attacks Use Advanced Tactics to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-warns-one-third-of-cyber-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a trend in cyber intrusions that rely on identity-based attacks, exploiting valid login credentials to breach systems. This trend is driven by the use of generative AI (gen AI) and other sophisticated tools to scale phishing campaigns and harvest credentials through infostealer malware and credential phishing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137563</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-Year-Old Hacker Admits Guilt in Major Cyberattack on PowerSchool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacker-admits-guilt-in-major-cyberattack-on-powerschool/</link>
      <description>Matthew D. Lane, a 19-year-old Massachusetts college student, has been accused of orchestrating a cyberattack on PowerSchool, a widely used educational software provider, resulting in the theft of confidential data from millions of students and teachers. The attack involved unauthorized access to cloud storage providers and the threat of publishing sensitive information unless a ransom was paid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137511</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Kling AI Facebook Ads Deliver RAT Malware to Over 22 Million Potential Victims</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-kling-ai-facebook-ads-deliver-rat.html</link>
      <description>Counterfeit Facebook pages and sponsored ads are being used to trick users into downloading malware. The fake websites offer AI-powered image and video generation, but actually download a malicious Windows executable that installs a remote access trojan (RAT) and stealer, which steals sensitive data and exfiltrates it to a command-and-control server.

FYSA: Vietnamese threat actors are using Facebook malvertising techniques to distribute stealer malware, leveraging the popularity of generative AI tools as lures. The campaign impersonated Kling AI through fake ads and deceptive websites, demonstrating social engineering tactics combined with advanced malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-kling-ai-facebook-ads-deliver-rat.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Target U.S. Critical Infrastructure with LummaC2 Malware</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/21/threat-actors-target-us-critical-infrastructure-lummac2-malware</link>
      <description>The joint Cybersecurity Advisory by CISA and the FBI details the tactics, techniques, and procedures, as well as indicators of compromise (IOCs), linked to threat actors deploying LummaC2 malware. This malware poses a serious threat capable of infiltrating networks and exfiltrating sensitive information across U.S. critical infrastructure sectors. The advisory urges organizations to review it and implement recommended mitigations to reduce exposure and impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23422</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy LummaC2 Malware to Exfiltrate Sensitive Data from Organizations</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-141b</link>
      <description>The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) have issued a joint advisory on LummaC2 malware, highlighting its tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The advisory provides guidance on mitigations to reduce the risk of compromise by LummaC2 malware, including implementing application controls, protecting against phishing campaigns, and exercising, testing, and validating security programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23420</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian GRU Cyber Actors Targeting Western Logistics Entities and Tech Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/21/russian-gru-cyber-actors-targeting-western-logistics-entities-and-tech-companies</link>
      <description>A joint cybersecurity advisory was released by CISA, NSA, FBI, and other U.S. and international partners regarding a Russian state-sponsored cyber espionage campaign targeting Western logistics entities and technology companies, including those involved in delivering foreign assistance to Ukraine. The campaign is attributed to the Russian General Staff Main Intelligence Directorate (GRU) 85th Main Special Service Center, military unit 26165, which has been previously linked to IP camera attacks in Ukraine and bordering NATO nations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian GRU Targeting Western Logistics Entities and Technology Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-141a</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I analyzed the article provided, which appears to be a threat report on GRU unit 26165's tactics and techniques used in malicious activities. The article highlights various indicators of compromise (IoCs), tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) employed by this actor group.

The report discusses multiple aspects of cybersecurity, including:

1. Identity and Access Management: It emphasizes the importance of strong access controls, multi-factor authentication, and account throttling or lockout to prevent credential theft.
2. Network Security: The article suggests disabling NTLM entirely and migrating to more robust authentication processes like PKI certificate authentication.
3. IP Camera Security: It provides guidelines for securing IP cameras by ensuring they are currently supported, applying security patches and firmware updates, disabling remote access if unnecessary, and using a VPN for remote connections.

The report also includes several mitigation techniques, such as:

1. Disable Universal Plug and Play (UPnP), Peer-to-Peer (P2P), and Anonymous Visit features on IP cameras and routers.
2. Turn off other ports/services not in use (e.g., FTP, web interface, etc.).
3. Configure, tune, and monitor logging if available on the IP camera.

In conclusion, this report is a valuable resource for cybersecurity professionals seeking to understand and mitigate GRU unit 26165's tactics and techniques. It provides actionable guidance on various aspects of network security, identity and access management, and IP camera security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23341</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SideWinder APT Hackers Exploits Legacy Office Vulnerabilities to Deploy Malware Undetected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sidewinder-apt-hackers-exploits-legacy-office-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2017-0199, CVE-2017-11882; Summary: The SideWinder APT group exploits unpatched legacy Microsoft Office vulnerabilities to deploy credential-stealing malware, using spear-phishing emails with malicious Word or RTF attachments. The exploit chain begins with remote code execution and memory corruption bugs, and ultimately leads to the exfiltration of sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137533</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health hit by system-wide outage after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-hit-by-system-wide-outage-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>A healthcare network, Kettering Health, experienced a system-wide technology outage due to a cyberattack, which forced the cancellation of inpatient and outpatient procedures. The attack may have involved ransomware, as Interlock ransomware gang is suspected to be behind the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-hit-by-system-wide-outage-after-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing CI/CD workflows with Wazuh</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/securing-cicd-workflows-with-wazuh.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery/Deployment (CI/CD) workflows, including supply chain attacks, insecure dependencies, insider threats, lack of visibility, compliance requirements, code and dependency vulnerabilities, container vulnerabilities, and misconfiguration of CI/CD tools. It highlights the importance of integrating security measures into CI/CD pipelines to maintain confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/securing-cicd-workflows-with-wazuh.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellcom Confirms Cybersecurity Breach After Network Failure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cellcom-confirms-cybersecurity-breach/</link>
      <description>The article reports a cyberattack on Cellcom/Nsight's network infrastructure, causing a five-day service disruption. The company confirmed the incident and assured customers that sensitive personal information remains secure. The attack did not compromise customer data repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137500</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LockBit Internal Data Leak Reveals Payload Creation Methods and Ransom Demands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lockbit-internal-data-leak-reveals-payload/</link>
      <description>This article reveals a major data breach of the LockBit ransomware group's operations, exposing internal processes and sensitive data. The leak includes details on ransomware payload creation, negotiation tactics with victims, and configuration data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137506</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Detect Phishing Attacks Faster: Tycoon2FA Example</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-to-detect-phishing-attacks-faster.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of phishing detection in corporate environments and highlights the capabilities of ANY.RUN's Interactive Sandbox in detecting and analyzing evasive phishing attacks. It provides a real-world example of a suspicious email and walks through how the sandbox can be used to detonate every stage of an attack, from the first click to the final payload. The article emphasizes the benefits of using sandboxes like ANY.RUN in detecting and responding to phishing threats quickly and efficiently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-to-detect-phishing-attacks-faster.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks &amp; Spencer faces $402 million profit hit after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marks-and-spencer-faces-402-million-profit-hit-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Marks &amp; Spencer, a British retailer, is bracing for a potential profit hit of up to £300 million ($402 million) following a recent cyberattack that led to widespread operational and sales disruptions. The company's online retail systems are still disabled, and the disruptions are expected to last at least until July. The attack was linked to the Scattered Spider, a collective of cybercriminals known for breaching high-profile organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marks-and-spencer-faces-402-million-profit-hit-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100 Malicious Chrome Extensions Exploiting Users to Steal Login Credentials and Execute Remote Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-100-malicious-chrome-extensions-exploiting-users/</link>
      <description>A network of over 100 malicious Chrome extensions has been discovered, stealing login credentials and executing unauthorized remote code. The extensions inject harmful scripts into the browser environment, harvesting critical data and exploiting vulnerabilities to establish backdoor access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137460</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti EPMM 0-Day RCE Vulnerability Under Active Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-epmm-0-day-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The EPMM contains a critical vulnerability chain that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems. The vulnerability combines an authentication bypass (CVE-2025-4427) and a remote code execution flaw (CVE-2025-4428) to create a critical attack vector. Exploitation has been observed since May 16th following the publication of proof-of-concept exploits by multiple security firms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137448</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase says recent data breach impacts 69,461 customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-says-recent-data-breach-impacts-69-461-customers/</link>
      <description>A data breach at Coinbase affected 69,461 individuals, exposing customer and corporate data. The breached information included personal identifiers such as name, date of birth, social security numbers, and account information, which could be used in social engineering attacks to convince victims to move their funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-says-recent-data-breach-impacts-69-461-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Alerts Users to Multiple Critical Vulnerabilities Affecting Data Center Server</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/atlassian-alerts-users-to-multiple-critical-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31650, CVE-2024-47072, CVE-2024-57699, CVE-2025-24970, CVE-2025-22157; Summary: Eight high-severity vulnerabilities affecting multiple enterprise products in Atlassian's Data Center and Server offerings, including denial-of-service attacks and privilege escalation. The vulnerabilities were discovered through various means, including the Bug Bounty program, penetration testing, and third-party library scans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137415</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Could Leverage Google Cloud Platform for Malicious Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-could-leverage-google-cloud-platform/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Cloud Platform's (GCP) Cloud Functions and Cloud Build services; CVE(s): None; Summary: The default Cloud Build Service Account (SA) previously granted excessive permissions during the deployment of Cloud Functions, allowing attackers to escalate privileges by exploiting the deployment process. This could have enabled malicious activities, including environment enumeration, across multiple cloud platforms, despite Google's partial remediation patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137427</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Hackers Create Fake AI Tool to Exploit Millions of Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-hackers-create-fake-ai-tool/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a sophisticated campaign by hostile actors posing as Kling AI, an AI-powered picture and video synthesis platform. The attackers use counterfeit Facebook pages and paid advertisements to lure users into downloading malicious Windows executables disguised with double extensions and Hangul Filler characters, which execute anti-analysis tricks and deploy a PureHVNC Remote Access Trojan (RAT) that steals credentials and session tokens from various browser extensions and standalone applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137358</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Expose PWA JavaScript Attack That Redirects Users to Adult Scam Apps</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-pwa-javascript.html</link>
      <description>A new campaign has been discovered that employs malicious JavaScript injections on mobile devices to redirect site visitors to a Chinese adult-content Progressive Web App (PWA) scam, aiming to bypass basic browser protections and retain users longer. The attack only triggers on mobile devices and is designed to evade detection mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-pwa-javascript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Phishing Attack Uses AES &amp; Malicious npm Packages to Office 365 Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-phishing-attack-uses-aes-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>A highly sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Microsoft Office 365 (O365) credentials was uncovered by Fortra's Suspicious Email Analysis team. The attack employed modern technologies and developer infrastructure, including AES encryption, malicious npm packages, and content delivery networks (CDNs), to deliver a counterfeit O365 login page designed to steal credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137312</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health Experiences System-Wide Outage Due to Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kettering-health-experiences-system-wide-outage/</link>
      <description>A ransomware attack has hit Kettering Health, a major healthcare provider, causing a system-wide technology outage that has severely limited access to critical patient care systems. The attack is part of a troubling trend of cyber attacks targeting healthcare institutions, which are particularly vulnerable due to their critical need for immediate access to patient information and the life-or-death nature of their services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137342</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Lexmark Printers Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-lexmark-printers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lexmark; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1127; Summary: The vulnerability is a critical security flaw affecting over 150 Lexmark printer and multifunction device models. It enables remote attackers to execute malicious code on unpatched systems through a combination of path traversal and concurrent execution flaws, with the potential for full system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137322</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attaxion Leads the Way as First EASM Platform to Integrate ENISA’s EU Vulnerability Database (EUVD)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attaxion-becomes-the-first-easm-platform-to-integrate-enisas-eu-vulnerability-database-euvd/</link>
      <description>The article announces the integration of the European Vulnerability Database (EUVD) into Attaxion's external attack surface management platform. This integration provides broader coverage and context for vulnerability prioritization, including EUVD IDs, exploitation confirmation, affected products, and references.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137374</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Can Now Auto-Change Compromised Passwords Using Its Built-In Manager</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-chrome-can-now-auto-change.html</link>
      <description>Google has announced a new feature in its Chrome browser that enables automated password changes when compromised credentials are detected during sign-in. The feature aims to reduce friction and help users keep their accounts secure without requiring manual intervention. Website owners can support this feature by adopting specific methods, such as using well-known URLs for password change forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-chrome-can-now-auto-change.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Palo Alto GlobalProtect Gateway &amp; Portal Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-palo-alto-globalprotect-gateway-portal/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0133; Summary: A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks' GlobalProtect gateway and portal features allows attackers to execute malicious JavaScript code in authenticated users' browsers, posing risks of phishing and credential theft, particularly for organizations using Clientless VPN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137308</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk Targets DNS Vulnerabilities to Hijack Cloud Resources and Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hazy-hawk-targets-dns-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Sophisticated threat actor "Hazy Hawk" has been exploiting DNS misconfigurations since at least December 2023 to hijack abandoned cloud resources from high-profile organizations. The actor utilizes these hijacked subdomains to distribute scams and malware, leveraging the inherent trustworthiness of the compromised domains to evade security controls and achieve higher rankings in search results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerSchool hacker pleads guilty to student data extortion scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/powerschool-hacker-pleads-guilty-to-student-data-extortion-scheme/</link>
      <description>This article is about a cyberattack on PowerSchool that resulted in the theft of personal data for millions of students and teachers. The attacker, Matthew D. Lane, 19, has agreed to plead guilty to four federal charges related to the attack, including cyber extortion conspiracy, unauthorized access to protected computers, and aggravated identity theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/powerschool-hacker-pleads-guilty-to-student-data-extortion-scheme/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KrebsOnSecurity Hit With Near-Record 6.3 Tbps DDoS</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/krebsonsecurity-hit-with-near-record-6-3-tbps-ddos/</link>
      <description>A massive distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack of over 6.3 terabits per second was launched against KrebsOnSecurity, with the attacker believed to be testing a new Internet of Things (IoT) botnet capable of launching crippling digital assaults. The botnet, known as Aisuru, is reportedly controlled by a 21-year-old individual claiming to reside in Brazil who has been peddling access to their DDoS machine on public Telegram chat channels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71303</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile carrier Cellcom confirms cyberattack behind extended outages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-carrier-cellcom-confirms-cyberattack-behind-extended-outages/</link>
      <description>Cellcom, a Wisconsin wireless provider, has confirmed that a cyberattack is responsible for the widespread service outage and disruptions that began on May 14, 2025. The attack affected voice and SMS services, leaving customers unable to make phone calls or send text messages. Cellcom's CEO has assured that the company has protocols in place for such incidents and is working to restore full service by the end of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-carrier-cellcom-confirms-cyberattack-behind-extended-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premium WordPress 'Motors' theme vulnerable to admin takeover attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/premium-wordpress-motors-theme-vulnerable-to-admin-takeover-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The Motors WordPress theme contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to hijack administrator accounts and take complete control of websites. This flaw affects all versions up to 5.6.67, and exploitation enables attackers to implant malware, exfiltrate sensitive data, or redirect visitors to dangerous sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/premium-wordpress-motors-theme-vulnerable-to-admin-takeover-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanHelsing ransomware builder leaked on hacking forum</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-leaked-on-hacking-forum/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VanHelsing RaaS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The source code for the VanHelsing ransomware-as-a-service operation's affiliate panel, data leak blog, and Windows encryptor builder was leaked after an old developer tried to sell it on the RAMP cybercrime forum. The leaked code includes the legitimate builder for the Windows encryptor and the source code for the affiliate panel and data leak site, but is incomplete as it does not include the Linux builder or any databases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-leaked-on-hacking-forum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s how Windows 11 aims to make the world safe in the post-quantum era</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/heres-how-windows-11-aims-to-make-the-world-safe-in-the-post-quantum-era/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the security concerns surrounding Post-Quantum Cryptography (PQC) algorithms, specifically the increased key sizes and potential errors introduced into software during the transition away from RSA and Elliptic Curve cryptography.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/heres-how-windows-11-aims-to-make-the-world-safe-in-the-post-quantum-era/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SK Telecom says malware breach lasted 3 years, impacted 27 million numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sk-telecom-says-malware-breach-lasted-3-years-impacted-27-million-numbers/</link>
      <description>SK Telecom suffered a malware attack that exposed USIM data of 27 million subscribers, including IMSI, USIM authentication keys, network usage data, and SMS/contacts stored in the SIM. The company detected the malware on April 19, 2025, and isolated equipment suspected of being hacked, but initially undetected for nearly three years from June 15, 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sk-telecom-says-malware-breach-lasted-3-years-impacted-27-million-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk gang exploits DNS misconfigs to hijack trusted domains</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hazy-hawk-gang-exploits-dns-misconfigs-to-hijack-trusted-domains/</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as "Hazy Hawk" is hijacking forgotten DNS CNAME records pointing to abandoned cloud services, using the compromised domains to distribute scams, fake apps, and malicious ads. The attacker's technique involves registering a new cloud resource with the same name as the original one, causing the subdomain to resolve to their new site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hazy-hawk-gang-exploits-dns-misconfigs-to-hijack-trusted-domains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk Exploits DNS Records to Hijack CDC, Corporate Domains for Malware Delivery</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hazy-hawk-exploits-dns-records-to.html</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as Hazy Hawk has been observed hijacking abandoned cloud resources, including Amazon S3 buckets and Microsoft Azure endpoints, by leveraging misconfigurations in DNS records. The hijacked domains are used to host URLs that direct users to scams and malware via traffic distribution systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hazy-hawk-exploits-dns-records-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky APT Group Deploys PowerShell Payloads to Deliver XWorm RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-apt-group-deploys-powershell-payloads/</link>
      <description>This article describes a malware campaign orchestrated by the Kimsuky APT group, using PowerShell payloads to deliver the XWorm Remote Access Trojan (RAT). The campaign involves multi-stage attacks, fileless execution, and Living-off-the-Land Binaries and Scripts (LOLBAS) techniques to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137257</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100+ Fake Chrome Extensions Found Hijacking Sessions, Stealing Credentials, Injecting Ads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/100-fake-chrome-extensions-found.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unknown threat actor; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes malicious Chrome Browser extensions created by an unknown threat actor since February 2024. These extensions masquerade as seemingly benign utilities but can exfiltrate data, receive commands, and execute arbitrary code. They also enable credential and cookie theft, session hijacking, ad injection, and phishing via DOM manipulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/100-fake-chrome-extensions-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Role of Multi-Factor Authentication in Mobile Banking Security</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/multi-factor-authentication-in-mobile-banking-security/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) in securing mobile banking transactions. It highlights the effectiveness of MFA in reducing financial fraud incidents, with biometric authentication emerging as the most secure method. The article also touches on encryption, tokenization, and user education as additional measures to ensure secure transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060102</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More_Eggs Malware Uses Job Application Emails to Distribute Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/more_eggs-malware-uses-job-application-emails/</link>
      <description>The article describes the More_Eggs malware, a JavaScript backdoor that exploits human trust through social engineering. It targets HR departments by masquerading as job application emails and uses obfuscated scripts and legitimate system binaries to establish a foothold in targeted environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137245</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trojanized RVTools push Bumblebee malware in SEO poisoning campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trojanized-rvtools-push-bumblebee-malware-in-seo-poisoning-campaign/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RVTools; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official website for the RVTools VMware management tool was taken offline due to a supply chain attack that distributed trojanized installers disguising as Bumblebee malware loaders. The attackers used fake typo-squatted domains and SEO poisoning to promote the malicious installers, which attempted to execute a malicious version.dll that was detected as the Bumblebee malware loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trojanized-rvtools-push-bumblebee-malware-in-seo-poisoning-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RVTools hit in supply chain attack to deliver Bumblebee malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rvtools-hit-in-supply-chain-attack-to-deliver-bumblebee-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Robware RVTools; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official website for the RVTools VMware management tool was taken offline due to a supply chain attack that distributed a trojanized installer, dropping the Bumblebee malware loader on users' machines. The malware is designed to download and execute additional payloads, including Cobalt Strike beacons, information stealers, and ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rvtools-hit-in-supply-chain-attack-to-deliver-bumblebee-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedisRaider Campaign Targets Linux Servers by Exploiting Misconfigured Redis Instances</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/redisraider-campaign-targets-linux-servers/</link>
      <description>The RedisRaider campaign is a sophisticated Linux worm that targets publicly accessible Redis instances with misconfigured servers. It exploits vulnerabilities to deploy a customized XMRig miner and employs advanced obfuscation, anti-forensics measures, and manipulation of Redis configurations to evade detection. The malware also has a web-based mining component, revealing a broader monetization strategy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137230</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service desks are under attack: What can you do about it?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/service-desks-are-under-attack-what-can-you-do-about-it/</link>
      <description>The article discusses social engineering attacks on service desk agents, where attackers use tactics such as pretexting, vishing, and building urgency and trust to gain initial access. This is often followed by privilege escalation or deploying ransomware. The article highlights the importance of verifying identities and implementing rigorous identity checks to prevent these attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/service-desks-are-under-attack-what-can-you-do-about-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Abuse TikTok and Instagram APIs to Verify Stolen Account Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-abuse-tiktok-and-instagram-apis/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI (Python Package Index); CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybercriminals are leveraging the PyPI to distribute malicious tools designed to exploit TikTok and Instagram APIs for verifying stolen account credentials. These packages, including checker-SaGaF, steinlurks, and sinnercore, automate the process of validating emails and usernames against social media platforms, posing significant supply chain security risks due to their unauthorized network access and malicious behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137204</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regeneron to Buy 23andMe for $256M Amid Growing Data Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/regeneron-to-buy-23andme-for-256m-amid/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the acquisition of 23andMe by Regeneron Pharmaceuticals, with concerns about the fate of sensitive genetic information collected from millions of customers. Regeneron has emphasized its commitment to protecting customer data and pledged to comply with existing privacy policies and applicable laws. The acquisition is seen as a significant consolidation in the genetics industry, highlighting the value of large-scale genetic databases in modern drug development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137206</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: Aquatic Panda</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-aquatic-panda/</link>
      <description>Aquatic Panda is a suspected China-based threat group focused on intelligence gathering and industrial espionage. The group operates within a wider network of government-linked teams and private contractors, reflecting China's modern cyber strategy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060086</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Includes MDaemon Email Server XSS Flaw in KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-includes-mdaemon-email-server-xss-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MDaemon Email Server; CVE(s): CVE-2024-11182; Summary: The MDaemon Email Server prior to version 24.5.1c contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that allows attackers to inject malicious JavaScript code via crafted HTML emails, enabling them to execute arbitrary code within the user's browser window and potentially access sensitive data and functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137183</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Weaponized RAR Archives to Deliver Pure Malware in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-weaponized-rar-archives/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated malware campaign targeting Russian organizations with the Pure malware family. The malware is distributed via spam emails containing malicious RAR archives or links to such archives, and once executed, allows attackers to gain persistent access to compromised systems, steal credentials, and exfiltrate data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137190</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Asian Ministries Hit by SideWinder APT Using Old Office Flaws and Custom Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/south-asian-ministries-hit-by.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2017-0199, CVE-2017-11882; Summary: SideWinder threat actors used spear phishing emails with geofenced payloads to target high-level government institutions in Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, and Pakistan. The attack chain leveraged remote code execution flaws in Microsoft Office (CVE-2017-0199 and CVE-2017-11882) to deploy StealerBot malware, which maintains persistent access and collects sensitive data from compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/south-asian-ministries-hit-by.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Default IAM Roles Found to Enable Lateral Movement and Cross-Service Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/aws-default-iam-roles-found-to-enable.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Web Services; CVE(s): None; Summary: Default IAM roles in AWS services like SageMaker, Glue, EMR, and Lightsail grant overly broad permissions, allowing attackers to escalate privileges, manipulate other AWS services, and compromise entire AWS accounts. These roles can be exploited to perform administrative actions, break isolation boundaries between services, and move laterally across services within the same account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/aws-default-iam-roles-found-to-enable.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack on Serviceaide Compromises Data of 480,000 Catholic Health Patients</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattack-on-serviceaide-compromises-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Serviceaide; CVE(s): None; Summary: An improperly secured Elasticsearch database left sensitive information of approximately 480,000 patients exposed for nearly seven weeks. The incident was caused by a misconfigured database managed by Serviceaide, which became publicly accessible on September 19, 2024, and was only discovered on November 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137162</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy Bumblebee Malware via Poisoned Bing SEO Results</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-bumblebee-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a cyberattack campaign that uses SEO poisoning to distribute the Bumblebee malware. The attackers create fake download websites mimicking legitimate software packages and optimize their malicious sites to rank at the top of Bing search results. The malware is used as a downloader for additional payloads, making it particularly dangerous in developer environments where privileged access could be leveraged for broader attacks or data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137150</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Flaw in WordPress Plugin Puts 22,000 Websites at Risk of Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/security-flaw-in-wordpress-plugin-puts-22000-websites/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The Motors WordPress theme has an unauthenticated privilege escalation vulnerability that allows attackers to change passwords of any user, including administrators, without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability, with a critical CVSS rating of 9.8, can be exploited by unauthenticated threat actors to gain complete control over compromised websites, enabling attacks such as uploading malicious files, injecting malware, or redirecting users to phishing sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137137</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical VMware Cloud Foundation Vulnerability Exposes Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vmware-cloud-foundation-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Broadcom VMware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41229, CVE-2025-41230, CVE-2025-41231; Summary: Three significant security vulnerabilities in VMware Cloud Foundation platform allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information and internal services. The flaws affect versions 4.5.x and 5.x and require immediate patching as no workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137120</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danfoss AK-SM 8xxA Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-140-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Danfoss AK-SM 8xxA Series; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41450; Summary: The AK-SM 800A system manager has an improper authentication vulnerability due to datetime-based password generation, which could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication and execute arbitrary code. The affected versions are prior to R4.2, and Danfoss has released version R4.2 to address the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23408</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vertiv Liebert RDU101 and UNITY</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-140-10</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vertiv Liebert RDU101 and Liebert UNITY; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46412, CVE-2025-41426; Summary: The Liebert RDU101 and Liebert UNITY products contain vulnerabilities that could allow an attacker to bypass authentication, cause a denial-of-service condition, or achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23415</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions and Mitsubishi Electric Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-140-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions, ICONICS Product Suite and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0921; Summary: An execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability in the AlarmWorX64 MMX Pager agent can allow an attacker to make unauthorized writes to arbitrary files, potentially leading to information tampering or denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on affected PCs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23409</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
