<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:06:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Spike in Fortinet VPN brute-force attacks raises zero-day concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spike-in-fortinet-vpn-brute-force-attacks-raises-zero-day-concerns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports a massive spike in brute-force attacks targeting Fortinet SSL VPNs and FortiManager, which is often seen as a precursor to new vulnerability disclosures. The campaign started with FortiOS SSL VPN endpoints and later shifted to FortiManager's FGFM profile, suggesting the same attackers or toolset/infrastructure were used.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spike-in-fortinet-vpn-brute-force-attacks-raises-zero-day-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania attorney general's email, site down after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pennsylvania-attorney-generals-email-site-down-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: Multiple public-facing Citrix NetScaler appliances on the Pennsylvania Attorney General's network were found to be vulnerable to attacks exploiting a critical vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-5777 (Citrix Bleed 2).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pennsylvania-attorney-generals-email-site-down-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Purple Teaming Companies in 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/purple-teaming-companies/</link>
      <description>The provided article highlights eight companies that specialize in Purple Teaming, a collaborative approach to cybersecurity that simulates real-world cyber attacks on an organization's digital assets to identify and address vulnerabilities. These companies are Deloitte, QualySec, Redscan, SCYTHE, and others, offering comprehensive services including penetration testing, red teaming, and incident response.

While the article does not specifically discuss a vulnerability (software, hardware, or firmware), it provides valuable insights into the importance of aligning defense and offense in cybersecurity. The highlighted companies demonstrate unique strengths in providing tailored Purple Teaming services that can help organizations achieve robust cybersecurity resilience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149462</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartLoader Malware Masquerades as Legitimate GitHub Repository to Infect Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/smartloader-malware-masquerades-as-legitimate-github-repository/</link>
      <description>This article describes a sophisticated campaign involving the dissemination of SmartLoader malware through GitHub repositories designed to mimic legitimate software projects. The malware targets users searching for illicit content and exploits trust in GitHub's ecosystem, ultimately leading to the installation of payloads such as infostealers like Rhadamanthys, Redline, and Lumma Stealer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156388</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-744: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 reset_password.cgi Improper Certificate Validation Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-744/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-744, ZDI-CAN-25483; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the reset_password.cgi endpoint due to improper certificate validation, allowing attackers to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25483</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Dedicated Phishlet for FIDO Authentication Downgrade Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-dedicated-phishlet/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel technique allows threat actors to bypass FIDO-based authentication through downgrade attacks, leveraging a custom phishlet within adversary-in-the-middle (AiTM) frameworks. The attack exploits gaps in browser compatibility and user agent handling, forcing victims to revert to less secure MFA mechanisms, enabling credential theft and session hijacking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156376</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-652: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft SharePoint ToolPane Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-652/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53771; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint, allowing unauthorized access. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the ToolPane endpoint due to inadequate restrictions on a protected API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27790</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-653: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft SharePoint Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-653/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint Server, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The issue stems from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to deserialization of untrusted data and potential code execution in the context of the SharePoint web server process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27791</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-654: SolarWinds TFTP Server Deserialization of Untrusted Data Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-654/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds TFTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26397; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of SolarWinds TFTP Server by deserializing untrusted data. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system and can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26280</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-655: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server downloadChangedFiles Directory Traversal Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-655/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54438; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server, without requiring authentication. The flaw exists in the downloadChangedFiles function due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26520</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-656: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server getZipFileListForImport Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-656/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54439; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server by uploading arbitrary files without proper validation. Although authentication is required, the existing mechanism can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25809</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-657: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server MagicInfoWebAuthorClient Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-657/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54440; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The flaw exists within the MagicInfoWebAuthorClient app due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing the upload of arbitrary files and execution in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26519</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShinyHunters May Have Teamed Up With Scattered Spider in Salesforce Attack Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/shinyhunters-may-have-teamed-up-with-scattered-spider/</link>
      <description>ShinyHunters, a financially motivated threat group, has launched sophisticated attacks targeting Salesforce instances across high-profile enterprises in various industries. The attacks involve ticket-themed phishing domains and credential-harvesting pages, as well as vishing campaigns and data exfiltration via Mullvad VPN obfuscation. Circumstantial evidence suggests a potential alliance between ShinyHunters and Scattered Spider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156365</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-658: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server getFontFileFromMagicInfoServer Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-658/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54441; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server, with authentication bypassable. The flaw exists within the getFontFileFromMagicInfoServer method due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing upload of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25807</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-659: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server SWUpdateFileUploadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-659/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54443; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The flaw exists in the SWUpdateFileUploadServlet class due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25772</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-660: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server filenameHasExecutableType Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-660/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung, MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54444; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. It exists in the implementation of the filenameHasExecutableType method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25804</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-661: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server parseXMLString XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-661/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54445; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. It exists in the implementation of the parseXMLString method due to improper XML External Entity (XXE) reference restrictions, allowing an attacker to embed contents back into the XML document for further processing and disclosing SYSTEM-level information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25860</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-662: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server ResponseUploadActivity Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-662/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54446; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of the Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The issue is caused by a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations, which can be exploited to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25955</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-663: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server OpenApiController Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-663/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54447; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the OpenApiController class due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing upload of arbitrary files and execution of code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25885</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-664: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server copyResourceToFile Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-664/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54448; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The flaw exists in the copyResourceToFile method due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing uploads of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25874</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-665: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server fillLftOrLfdInfo Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-665/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54449, ZDI-CAN-25873, ZDI-25-665; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25873</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-666: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server DeviceLogUploadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-666/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54450; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26057</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-667: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server MagicInfoCache Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-667/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54451; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The issue exists within the RMI service due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26058</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-668: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server ServletAuthenticationProcessingFilter Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-668/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54452; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to partially bypass authentication on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server, without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the ServletAuthenticationProcessingFilter class due to an improper implementation of the authentication algorithm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25800</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-669: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server FtpMetaUploadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-669/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54453; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server by bypassing authentication and exploiting a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths in the FtpMetaUploadServlet class.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25802</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-670: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server PremiumClientService Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-670/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung, MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54454; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the PremiumClientService class due to a hard-coded cryptographic key, which can be leveraged to bypass system authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25839</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-671: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server PremiumClientService Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-671/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54455; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server, with no authentication required to exploit it. The flaw exists within the PremiumClientService class due to a hard-coded cryptographic key, which can be leveraged by an attacker to bypass system authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25978</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-672: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server filenameHasExecutableType Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-672/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54442; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server without authentication. The issue exists within the implementation of the filenameHasExecutableType method and can be exploited by uploading arbitrary files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25806</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-673: Apple Safari getHourCycles Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-673/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43209; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple Safari. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26616</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-674: Apple macOS AppleIntelKBLGraphics Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-674/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43255; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. An attacker must obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the AppleIntelKBLGraphics kext due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26636</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-675: Apple macOS USD readAccessorInts Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-675/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31280; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. The flaw exists within the USD library due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26847</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-676: Apple macOS USD importSkeletons Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-676/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43219; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26978</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-677: Apple macOS USD CustomLoadImageData Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-677/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43218; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. It is an out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability in the USD CustomLoadImageData library, which can be exploited by reading past the end of an allocated buffer due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27036</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-678: Apple macOS ICC Profile Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-678/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43239; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS by exploiting an out-of-bounds write flaw in ICC profile parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27041</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-679: Apple macOS USD readColor Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-679/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43215; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27106</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-680: Apple macOS AudioToolbox MP4 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-680/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS AudioToolbox MP4 File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43186; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the AudioToolbox framework due to improper validation of user-supplied data. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27274</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-681: Apple macOS MediaToolbox Framework Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-681/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS MediaToolbox Framework; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43210; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the MediaToolbox framework due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27287</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-682: Apple macOS USD importMeshes Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-682/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43264; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, but attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26829</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-683: Apple macOS USD importMeshJointWeights Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-683/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43264; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer, which can be exploited by interaction with the USD library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27105</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-684: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-684/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43224; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26830</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-685: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-685/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43224; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. It is caused by a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in an out-of-bounds read information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26853</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-686: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-686/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43224; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. The specific flaw exists within the USD library due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26914</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-687: Apple macOS USD readAccessorDataToFloat Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-687/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31281; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS by reading past the end of an allocated buffer due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. Interaction with the USD library is required to exploit this vulnerability, and attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26846</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-688: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-688/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31281; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. It exists within the USD library due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26966</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-689: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-689/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31281; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. It is a heap-based buffer overflow in the USD library, caused by lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length before copying it to a buffer. An attacker can exploit this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27107</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-690: Apple macOS USD importNodeAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-690/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43221; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26909</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-691: Apple macOS USD importAnimations Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-691/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43221; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS, resulting from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26915</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-692: Oracle VirtualBox VirtIO-SCSI Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-692/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2024-21273; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting uninitialized memory in the VirtIO-SCSI module. An attacker must first obtain high-privileged code execution on the target guest system to exploit this issue, which can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25015</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-693: Norton Utilities Ultimate NortonUtilitiesSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-693/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Norton Utilities Ultimate; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13944; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Norton Utilities Ultimate by creating a symbolic link and abusing the Norton Utilities Service. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete arbitrary files or execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25570</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-694: Delta Electronics DTN Soft Project File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-694/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics DTN Soft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53416; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics DTN Soft by deserializing untrusted data. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists in the processing of project files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25406</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-695: AVG TuneUp for PC TuneupSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-695/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVG TuneUp for PC; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13944; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of AVG TuneUp for PC. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and can leverage it to delete a directory and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25509</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-696: Avast Cleanup Premium TuneupSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-696/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Avast Cleanup Premium; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13961; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Avast Cleanup Premium by creating a symbolic link within the Avast Cleanup Service. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25549</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-697: AVG TuneUp for PC TuneupSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-697/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVG TuneUp for PC; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13959; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of AVG TuneUp for PC by creating a symbolic link. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete directories and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25498</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-698: Avast Cleanup Premium TuneupSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-698/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Avast Cleanup Premium; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13962; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Avast Cleanup Premium by creating a symbolic link, which can be used to delete directories and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25548</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-699: Autodesk AutoCAD 3DM File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-699/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5043; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DM files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26848</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-700: Autodesk AutoCAD X_T File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-700/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5038; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of X_T files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26927</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-701: Autodesk AutoCAD PRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-701/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6631; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD, requiring user interaction. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in PRT file parsing, leading to a write past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27221</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-702: Autodesk AutoCAD PRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-702/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6635; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27253</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-703: Autodesk AutoCAD PRT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-703/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6636; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it exists within the parsing of PRT files due to a lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27222</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-704: Autodesk AutoCAD PRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-704/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6637; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required, and the issue exists within the parsing of PRT files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27223</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-705: Autodesk AutoCAD PRT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-705/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7497; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRT files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27225</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-706: Autodesk AutoCAD 3DM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-706/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk AutoCAD; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7675; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk AutoCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of 3DM files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27226</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-707: AVG TuneUp for PC TuneUp Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-707/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVG TuneUp for PC; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13960; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of AVG TuneUp for PC. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete a file and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23383</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-708: Mozilla Firefox Web Page Download Mark-Of-The-Web Protection Mechanism Failure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-708/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3863; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-Of-The-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Mozilla Firefox, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists within the web page download functionality, allowing an attacker to create files without the Mark-Of-The-Web and potentially execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-22536</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-709: Apple Safari JavascriptCore WasmToJSException Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-709/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple Safari; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43214; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple Safari, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the WasmToJSException operation, allowing an attacker to trigger a type confusion condition and execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27217</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-710: SolarWinds Platform SolarWindsAgent64 Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-710/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds Platform; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45710; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of SolarWinds Platform. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which can then be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24672</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-711: (Pwn2Own) Tesla Wall Connector Content-Length Header Improper Input Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-711/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tesla Wall Connector; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8320; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices without authentication. The issue is caused by improper input validation in the parsing of the HTTP Content-Length header, resulting in memory access past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26300</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-712: (Pwn2Own) Tesla Wall Connector Firmware Downgrade Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-712/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tesla Wall Connector; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8321; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue exists within the firmware upgrade feature due to a lack of an anti-downgrade mechanism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26299</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-713: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-713/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7999; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs when parsing AR files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker can leverage this type confusion condition to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26049</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-714: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-714/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7994; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by reading past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of AR files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25976</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-715: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-715/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7998; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of CO files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26046</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-716: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-716/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7996; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of AR files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25982</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-717: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-717/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7995; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting a type confusion condition in the parsing of CO files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25981</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-718: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-718/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8000; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of LI files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a type confusion condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26051</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-719: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-719/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7997; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by parsing XE files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read before the start of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26045</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-720: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-720/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8003; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26235</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-721: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-721/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8001; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26053</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-722: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-722/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8005; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26237</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-723: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-723/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8004; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26236</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-724: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-724/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8002; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting a type confusion condition in the parsing of CO files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26233</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-725: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-725/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8006; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it exists within the parsing of XE files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26238</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-726: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-726/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7993; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting a use-after-free remote code execution flaw in the parsing of LI files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25355</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-727: Apple macOS libFontValidation kern Table Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-727/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): ZDI-25-727, ZDI-CAN-25365; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. It exists within the parsing of kern tables in the libFontValidation library and can be exploited by interaction with the library. The issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25365</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-728: Apple macOS MediaToolbox Framework Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-728/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS MediaToolbox Framework; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31239; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Apple macOS. Interaction with the MediaToolbox framework is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the implementation of audio decoding due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26782</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-729: (Pwn2Own) Canonical Ubuntu Kernel taprio Scheduler Race Condition Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-729/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Canonical Ubuntu Kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2024-50126; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Canonical Ubuntu by exploiting a race condition in the taprio scheduler. The attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23656</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-730: (Pwn2Own) Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-730/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lorex; 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3132; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Cameras without authentication. The flaw exists within the sonia module due to improper validation of user-supplied data before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25647</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-731: (Pwn2Own) Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-731/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lorex; 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera; CVE(s): CVE-2024-52544; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Cameras. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the sonia module due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25537</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-732: (Pwn2Own) Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera Improper Validation of Array Index Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-732/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lorex; 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Camera; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8389; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Lorex 2K Indoor Wi-Fi Security Cameras without authentication. The issue results from improper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to a read past the end of an array, allowing for remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25639</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-733: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole compressConfigFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-733/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8426; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information or create a denial-of-service condition. Authentication is not required, and the issue occurs due to improper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24915</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-734: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 IPMI Use of Weak Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-734/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-734, ZDI-CAN-25633; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers by using the WAN MAC address as a default password. The issue exists within the IPMI interface and can be exploited without requiring authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25633</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft removes PowerShell 2.0 from Windows 11, Windows Server</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-removes-powershell-20-from-windows-11-windows-server/</link>
      <description>Microsoft will permanently remove PowerShell 2.0 from Windows 11 version 24H2, starting in August, and from Windows Server 2025 in September. The move aims to reduce system complexity and improve security by removing legacy code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-removes-powershell-20-from-windows-11-windows-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-735: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 local_pwd_reset HTTP Request Smuggling Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-735/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-735, ZDI-CAN-25631; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests on affected routers, bypassing authentication. The issue is due to inconsistent parsing of HTTP header terminators in the local_pwd_reset endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25631</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-736: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 access_setting HTTP Request Smuggling Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-736/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25632, None; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers. The flaw exists within the access_setting endpoint due to inconsistent parsing of terminators of HTTP headers, which can be bypassed and leveraged for code execution in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25632</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-737: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 do_fetch Improper Certificate Validation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-737/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-737, ZDI-CAN-25530; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise transport security on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without requiring authentication. The issue is due to improper validation of the certificate presented by the server in the do_fetch method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25530</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-738: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 SSH Use of Weak Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-738/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-738, ZDI-CAN-25635; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers by using the default SSH credentials, which use the WAN MAC address as a password. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25635</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-739: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-739/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-739, ZDI-CAN-25634; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers by exploiting an improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints in the SSH daemon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, but it can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25634</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-740: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 backup Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-740/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-740, ZDI-CAN-25641; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers by exploiting a hardcoded cryptographic key in the Backup and Restore functionality. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25641</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-741: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 openvpn_cli user_name SQL Injection Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-741/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): CVE-2024-50389; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries, allowing an attacker to exploit this vulnerability and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25580</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-742: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 Active Directory Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-742/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-742, ZDI-CAN-25587; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to bypass authentication on the system by leveraging a flaw in the Active Directory integration's improper implementation of an authentication algorithm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25587</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-743: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 qnap_exec Command Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-743/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-743, ZDI-CAN-25585; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25585</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-745: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 reset_password.cgi Improper Certificate Validation Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-745/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-745, ZDI-CAN-25644; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the reset_password.cgi endpoint due to improper certificate validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25644</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-746: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 reset_password.cgi Improper Certificate Validation Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-746/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-746, ZDI-CAN-25645; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without requiring authentication. The issue occurs due to improper certificate validation in the reset_password.cgi endpoint. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information related to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25645</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-747: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 reset_password.cgi Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-747/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-747, ZDI-CAN-25646; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of the QNAP TS-464. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the reset_password.cgi endpoint due to a hard-coded cryptographic key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25646</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-748: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 system.db Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-748/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-748, ZDI-CAN-25657; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without requiring authentication. The issue results from the use of a hard-coded cryptographic key, which can be exploited in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to bypass system authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25657</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-749: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 qfirewall Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints Firewall Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-749/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-749, ZDI-CAN-25596; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass firewall rules on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without authentication. The flaw exists within the implementation of firewall rules, resulting from failing to bind LAN IP ranges to the LAN interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25596</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-750: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 lionic_dpi parseMIME Out-of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-750/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-750, ZDI-CAN-25624; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without authentication. The flaw exists within the parseMIME method due to improper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25624</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-751: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 IPv6 Incorrectly Specified Destination in a Communication Channel Network Spoofing Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-751/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-751, ZDI-CAN-25625; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to redirect localhost traffic on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without authentication. The issue exists within the /etc/hosts file and can be exploited in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25625</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-752: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 gRPC WAN_ADDR6 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-752/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-752, ZDI-CAN-25667; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without authentication. The issue exists within the handling of gRPC messages and can be exploited by leveraging a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call, allowing for root-level code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25667</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-753: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 Improper Handling of URL Encoding Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-753/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-753, ZDI-CAN-25482; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without requiring authentication. The issue is caused by an improper implementation of the URL decoding algorithm within the device's function responsible for handling URL encoding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25482</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-754: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 privWizard.cgi Authentication CRLF Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-754/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-754, ZDI-CAN-25653; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices by injecting CRLF sequences into the privWizard.cgi endpoint, bypassing authentication and gaining access to protected resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25653</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-755: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 qsyslog-cli username Format String Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-755/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-755, ZDI-CAN-25672; Summary: The qsyslog-cli executable on affected QNAP QHora-322 routers has a format string remote code execution vulnerability. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25672</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-756: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-756/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-756, ZDI-CAN-25488; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to access the management interface of affected QNAP QHora-322 router installations without authentication. The issue is due to exposing the management interface on the WAN side of the router over IPv6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25488</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-757: (Pwn2Own) QNAP QHora-322 tar Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-757/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP QHora-322; CVE(s): ZDI-25-757, ZDI-CAN-25673; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP QHora-322 routers without authentication. The flaw exists within the handling of parameters provided to the tar executable, resulting from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25673</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-758: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 Samba Command Argument Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-758/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): ZDI-25-758, ZDI-CAN-25612; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the provided username during authentication, leading to a command injection issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25612</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-759: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 Log Tool SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-759/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): CVE-2024-50387; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the handling of command line arguments and results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25656</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-760: (Pwn2Own) QNAP TS-464 rsync Daemon Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-760/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP TS-464; CVE(s): CVE-2024-50388; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of QNAP TS-464 devices without authentication. The flaw exists in the handling of provided usernames and passwords during authentication, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25536</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-761: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-761/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8472; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must connect to a malicious Bluetooth device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26316</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-762: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 UPDM_wstpCBCUpdStart Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-762/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8473; Summary: The Alpine iLX-507 UPDM_wstpCBCUpdStart command injection vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected devices without authentication. The flaw occurs due to improper validation of user-supplied data before executing a system call, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26317</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-763: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 CarPlay Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-763/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8474; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the implementation of the Apple CarPlay protocol due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26318</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-764: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 AVRCP Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-764/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8475; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the implementation of the AVRCP protocol due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26321</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-765: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 TIDAL Improper Certificate Validation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-765/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8476, ZDI-CAN-26322, ZDI-25-765; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices without authentication. The issue exists within the TIDAL music streaming application due to improper certificate validation, which can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26322</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-766: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 Command Injection Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-766/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8480; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call, which can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26357</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-767: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-767/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Alpine iLX-507; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8477; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Alpine iLX-507 devices, requiring user interaction to connect to a malicious Bluetooth device. The issue is due to improper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26324</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-768: NI LabVIEW VI File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-768/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NI LabVIEW; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7848; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NI LabVIEW. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists in the parsing of VI files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27081</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-769: NI LabVIEW VI File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-769/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NI LabVIEW; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7849; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NI LabVIEW, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of VI files due to insufficient validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition that can be exploited to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27088</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-770: Microsoft Skype Chromium Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Skype; CVE(s): ZDI-25-770, ZDI-CAN-25335; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Skype by exploiting a vulnerable version of Google Chromium. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25335</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-771: Trend Micro Apex One Console Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-771/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54948; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of IUSR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27834</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-772: Trend Micro Apex One Console Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-772/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54987; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex One without authentication. The issue occurs due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of IUSR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27855</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-773: (0Day) Google Drive File Sharing Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-773/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Drive; CVE(s): ZDI-25-773, ZDI-CAN-24742; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Google Drive. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the Google Drive desktop application for Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24742</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-774: (0Day) Google Drive ZIP File Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-774/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Drive; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-24741, ZDI-25-774; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Google Drive. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the handling of ZIP archives and can lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-775: (0Day) Google Chrome SwiftShader Out-Of-Bound Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-775/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25494, None; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Google Chrome. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the WebGPU API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25494</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-776: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-776/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8628; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings, allowing attackers to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26064</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-777: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-777/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood; DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8629; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists in the firmware update process due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, enabling root-level code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26252</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-778: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-778/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8630; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication, exploiting the firmware update process by not properly validating a user-supplied string before executing a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26253</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-779: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-779/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood; DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8631; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The issue exists in the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, enabling attackers to execute code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26254</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-780: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-780/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8632; Summary: The vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations, with no authentication required. It exists within the firmware update process due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before executing a system call. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26255</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-781: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-781/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8633; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists in the firmware update process and results from a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before executing a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26256</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-782: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-782/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8634; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26257</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-783: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-783/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8635; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before executing a system call, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26258</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-784: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-784/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8636; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication, leveraging a command injection flaw in the firmware update process due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26259</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-785: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-785/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8637; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26260</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-786: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-786/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8638; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26261</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-787: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-787/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood; DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8639; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process, resulting from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26262</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-788: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-788/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE-2025-8640; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing attackers to run code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26263</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom and Xerox Release Critical Security Updates Fixing Privilege Escalation and RCE Flaws</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/zoom-and-xerox-release-critical.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zoom; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49457; Summary: The vulnerability in Zoom Clients for Windows allows an unauthenticated user to conduct privilege escalation via network access, with a CVSS score of 9.6. Affected products include Zoom Workplace, Zoom Workplace VDI, Zoom Rooms, and Zoom Meeting SDK, all before version 6.3.10.

Vulnerable Product: Xerox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8355, CVE-2025-8356; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Xerox FreeFlow Core include an XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability leading to server-side request forgery (SSRF), and a path traversal vulnerability leading to remote code execution. Both issues have been addressed in version 8.0.4, with CVSS scores of 7.5 and 9.8, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/zoom-and-xerox-release-critical.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-789: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-789/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8641; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices, with no authentication required. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26264</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-790: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-790/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8642; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices, without requiring authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26265</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-791: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-791/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8643; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26266</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-792: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-792/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8644; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists in the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing attackers to execute code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26267</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-793: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-793/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8645; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and it exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26268</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-794: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-794/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8646; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The flaw exists within the firmware update process due to improper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26269</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-795: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-795/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8647; Summary: The Kenwood DMX958XR firmware update process contains a command injection vulnerability that allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected devices without authentication. The vulnerability arises from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, enabling attackers to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26270</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-796: (0Day) Kenwood DMX958XR Firmware Update Command Injection Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-796/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8648; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The issue exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing attackers to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26271</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-797: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-797/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8649; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The issue exists within the JKWifiService due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing attackers to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26305</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-798: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-798/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8650; Summary: The vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. It exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing attackers to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26306</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-799: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-799/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8651; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The issue exists within the JKWifiService due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, enabling code execution in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26307</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-800: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR JKWifiService Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-800/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8652; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before using them to execute system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26311</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-801: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR JKRadioService Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-801/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8653; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR, without requiring authentication. The issue is a stack-based buffer overflow in the JKRadioService, resulting from improper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26312</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-802: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR ReadMVGImage Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-802/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8654; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. It occurs in the ReadMVGImage function due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26313</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-803: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR libSystemLib Command injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-803/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8655, ZDI-CAN-26314; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices without authentication. The issue exists within the firmware update process due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26314</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-804: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) Kenwood DMX958XR Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-804/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kenwood DMX958XR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8656; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to downgrade software on affected installations of Kenwood DMX958XR devices, without requiring authentication. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26355</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-805: (0Day) Vacron Camera ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-805/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vacron Camera; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8613; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Vacron Camera devices. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the webs.cgi endpoint due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before executing system calls. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25892</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-806: (0Day) AOMEI Backupper Workstation Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-806/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AOMEI; Backupper Workstation; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8612; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of AOMEI Backupper Workstation by creating a junction and abusing the restore functionality. An attacker must obtain low-privileged code execution and user interaction from an administrator to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27059</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-807: (0Day) AOMEI Cyber Backup Missing Authentication for Critical Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-807/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AOMEI Cyber Backup; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8611; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of AOMEI Cyber Backup without authentication. The issue exists within the DaoService service, which listens on TCP port 9074 by default, and can be exploited to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26158</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-808: (0Day) AOMEI Cyber Backup Missing Authentication for Critical Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-808/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AOMEI Cyber Backup; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8610; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of AOMEI Cyber Backup without authentication, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. The flaw exists within the StorageNode service, which listens on TCP port 9075 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26156</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-809: (0Day) Microsoft Exchange PowerShell Exposed Dangerous Method NTLM Relay Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-809/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Exchange; CVE(s): ZDI-25-809, ZDI-CAN-23450; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of Microsoft Exchange. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the PowerShell backend due to an exposed dangerous method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23450</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-810: (0Day) Microsoft Windows ZIP File Insufficient UI Warning Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-810/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-25-810, ZDI-CAN-23945; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the SmartScreen security feature on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting a ZIP file handling issue. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23945</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-811: (0Day) Microsoft Office OfficeApps Unintended Proxy Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-811/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office OfficeApps; CVE(s): ZDI-25-811, ZDI-CAN-23946; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to host arbitrary documents on a trusted domain used by Microsoft Office. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23946</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-812: (0Day) Microsoft Windows SmartScreen Bypass Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-812/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-25-812, ZDI-CAN-23938; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the SmartScreen security feature on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23938</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-813: (0Day) Microsoft PowerShell TryModuleAutoLoading Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-813/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft PowerShell; CVE(s): ZDI-25-813, ZDI-CAN-23444; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft PowerShell. The specific flaw exists within the TryModuleAutoLoading method due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23444</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-814: (0Day) Microsoft Windows MonikerLink Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-814/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-23548, ZDI-25-814; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the handling of redirections. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to relay NTLM credentials in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23548</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-815: (0Day) Microsoft Windows CAB File SmartScreen Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-815/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows CAB File; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-23990, None; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting a flaw in the handling of CAB files. User interaction is required for exploitation, and an attacker can execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23990</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-816: (0Day) Microsoft Azure AP5GC gNB-ID Use of Multiple Resources with Duplicate Identifier Denial-Of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-816/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): ZDI-25-816, ZDI-CAN-23960; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Microsoft Azure by exploiting the handling of gNB-ID provided to the AP5GC endpoint. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23960</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-817: (0Day) Microsoft Edge PDF NTLM Response Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-817/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Edge; CVE(s): ZDI-25-817, ZDI-CAN-23584; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of Microsoft Edge by not respecting the Mark-of-the-Web on PDF documents saved from untrusted locations. User interaction is required for exploitation, which involves visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23584</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-818: (0Day) Microsoft Windows OneDrive SmartScreen Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-818/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows OneDrive; CVE(s): ZDI-25-818, ZDI-CAN-24078; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting a flaw in the implementation of OneDrive file syncing. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this to bypass SmartScreen protection and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24078</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-819: (0Day) Microsoft Windows NetBIOS Hostname SmartScreen Bypass Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-819/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-25-819, ZDI-CAN-24425; Summary: This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the SmartScreen security feature on affected Microsoft Windows installations by advertising a NetBIOS name. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24425</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-820: (0Day) Microsoft SharePoint IsAuthorizedType Deserialization of Untrusted Data Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-820/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): ZDI-25-820, ZDI-CAN-24831; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information or create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the SPNoCodeXomlCompiler.IsAuthorizedType method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24831</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-821: (0Day) Microsoft Windows Internet Explorer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-821/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Internet Explorer; CVE(s): ZDI-25-821, ZDI-CAN-24974; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can launch it via COM from an Internet Shortcut file or other vector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24974</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-822: (0Day) Microsoft SharePoint GetTransformer Unsafe Reflection Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-822/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): ZDI-25-822, ZDI-CAN-25207; Summary: The GetTransformer method in affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition requiring authentication. The vulnerability exists due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data leading to unsafe reflection. An attacker can exploit this to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25207</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-823: (0Day) Microsoft Windows Theme File Parsing Improper Input Validation NTLM Relay Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-823/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-26372, ZDI-25-823; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of theme files due to improper input validation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26372</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-824: (0Day) Microsoft Windows Theme File Parsing Improper Input Validation NTLM Relay Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-824/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-26364, None; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of theme files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26364</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-825: Apple macOS AudioToolboxCore Audio Conversion Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-825/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS AudioToolboxCore; CVE(s): ZDI-25-825, ZDI-CAN-26281; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS. The issue exists in the handling of audio conversion and results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to reading past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26281</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-826: (0Day) Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert ExportDataAsXML Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-826/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54925; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert without requiring authentication. The flaw exists within the implementation of the ExportDataAsXML method, due to a lack of proper validation of a URI prior to accessing resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26464</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-827: (0Day) Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert GetTgmlContent Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-827/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54926; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations, requiring authentication to exploit. The issue is due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to file operations, allowing an attacker to disclose information in the context of LOCAL SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26273</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-828: (0Day) Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert HttpPostedFile Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-828/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54927; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the HttpPostedFile module due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26274</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-829: (0Day) Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert GetFilteredSinkProvider Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-829/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54923; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data leading to deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26275</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-830: (0Day) Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert GetPagesAsImages Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-830/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54924; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert without requiring authentication. The flaw exists in the GetPagesAsImages method due to a lack of proper URI validation, which can be exploited to obtain information in the context of LOCAL SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26463</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web DDoS and App Exploitation Attacks Surge in First Half of 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/web-ddos-and-app-exploitation-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article reports a significant increase in Web DDoS attacks, with a 39% rise compared to the second half of 2024. Threat actors are using automated tools and generative AI to launch sustained attacks below 100,000 requests per second (RPS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156355</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft asks users to ignore certificate enrollment errors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-asks-users-to-ignore-certificate-enrollment-errors/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has asked customers to disregard CertificateServicesClient (CertEnroll) errors that appear after installing the July 2025 preview update and subsequent Windows 11 24H2 updates. The error is caused by a feature still under development and does not impact Windows processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-asks-users-to-ignore-certificate-enrollment-errors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and Partners Release Asset Inventory Guidance for Operational Technology Owners and Operators</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/13/cisa-and-partners-release-asset-inventory-guidance-operational-technology-owners-and-operators</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and its partners released guidance on creating and maintaining operational technology (OT) asset inventories and taxonomies, aiming to help OT owners and operators identify and safeguard critical assets. This guidance can help organizations gain insights into their architecture, optimize defenses, and reduce cybersecurity risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23750</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VexTrio Hackers Use Fake CAPTCHAs and Malicious Apps on Google Play &amp; App Store to Target Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vextrio-hackers-use-fake-captchas-and-malicious-apps/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a highly skilled cybercriminal network, VexTrio Viper, which has been active since at least 2017. The group uses advanced tactics such as lookalike domains, registered domain generation algorithms (RDGAs), and traffic distribution systems (TDSs) to deliver malware, scams, and illicit content to users worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156315</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple GitLab Vulnerabilities Allow Account Takeover and Stored XSS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-gitlab-vulnerabilities-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab (Community Edition and Enterprise Edition); CVE(s): CVE-2025-6186, CVE-2025-7734, CVE-2025-7739, CVE-2025-8094; Summary: GitLab has released critical security patches addressing multiple high-severity vulnerabilities that could enable account takeovers, stored cross-site scripting attacks, and privilege escalation. The most concerning vulnerabilities involve multiple cross-site scripting flaws that allow authenticated attackers to execute malicious actions on behalf of other users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156445</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Warns About FortiSIEM Vulnerability (CVE-2025-25256) With In-the-Wild Exploit Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fortinet-warns-about-fortisiem.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiSIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25256; Summary: An OS Command Injection vulnerability in FortiSIEM allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted CLI requests, with a CVSS score of 9.8 out of 10.0. The vulnerability exists in multiple versions and has been exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fortinet-warns-about-fortisiem.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Office Vulnerabilities Allow Attackers to Execute Remote Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-office-vulnerabilities-3/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53731, CVE-2025-53740, CVE-2025-53730; Summary: Three critical security vulnerabilities in Microsoft Office allow attackers to execute malicious code remotely on affected systems. The vulnerabilities, caused by use-after-free memory corruption issues, can be exploited to manipulate system memory and execute arbitrary code, with high levels of confidentiality, integrity, and availability impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156436</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI SOC 101: Key Capabilities Security Leaders Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-soc-101-key-capabilities-security.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the benefits of incorporating AI-powered Security Operations Center (SOC) capabilities to improve efficiency, reduce risk, and enhance security outcomes. It highlights the challenges faced by traditional SOCs, such as repetitive and time-consuming investigations, and how AI-driven triage, investigation, and detection coverage analysis can address these issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-soc-101-key-capabilities-security.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI adds new GPT-5 models, restores o3, o4-mini and it's a mess all over again</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-adds-new-gpt-5-models-restores-o3-o4-mini-and-its-a-mess-all-over-again/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware. It appears to be an update announcement for ChatGPT with new model options and legacy models available.

FYSA: The article mentions that 46% of environments had passwords cracked, nearly doubling from 25% last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-adds-new-gpt-5-models-restores-o3-o4-mini-and-its-a-mess-all-over-again/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Exchange Server Flaws Allow Network-Based Spoofing and Data Tampering</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-exchange-server-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25007, CVE-2025-25005, CVE-2025-49743; Summary: Microsoft Exchange Server has been affected by critical security vulnerabilities that could enable attackers to conduct network-based spoofing attacks and tamper with sensitive data. The flaws, identified as CVE-2025-25007 and CVE-2025-25005, pose significant risks to organizations running Microsoft's email and collaboration platform, allowing malicious actors to impersonate legitimate users or systems, potentially leading to sophisticated social engineering attacks or unauthorized access attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156425</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Remote Desktop Services Flaw Allows Network-Based Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-remote-desktop-services-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Services; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53722; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to launch denial-of-service attacks remotely without requiring authentication or user interaction, consuming system resources and rendering the service unavailable. Attack complexity is low, making it accessible to a broader range of threat actors, with potential impact on system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156411</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curly COMrades APT Hackers Target Critical Organizations Across Multiple Countries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/curly-comrades-apt-hackers-target-critical-organizations/</link>
      <description>Bitdefender Labs has identified a sophisticated APT group dubbed Curly COMrades, targeting critical infrastructure in geopolitically sensitive regions, employing stealthy tactics to secure long-term network access and exfiltrate sensitive data. The group uses credential theft, custom malware, and blended tactics to evade detection, highlighting the evolving threat landscape where trust in legitimate infrastructure is exploited for sustained espionage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156292</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot RCE Vulnerability via Prompt Injection Enables Full System Compromise</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/github-copilot-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub Copilot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53773; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in GitHub Copilot allows attackers to achieve remote code execution and complete system compromise through prompt injection techniques. The vulnerability exploits the AI assistant's ability to modify project files without user approval, enabling attackers to manipulate Copilot into adding malicious lines to configuration files, ultimately leading to unrestricted command execution with full system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156403</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
