<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 11:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Apache CloudStack Flaw Allows Attackers to Execute Privileged Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-cloudstack-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache CloudStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26521, CVE-2025-47713, CVE-2025-30675, CVE-2025-47849, CVE-2025-22829; Summary: Five critical security vulnerabilities were found in Apache CloudStack, including a privilege escalation flaw allowing Domain Admins to reset admin passwords and a vulnerability that enables attackers to impersonate the cluster creator. Upgrading to version 4.19.3.0 or 4.20.1.0 is recommended to remediate these issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141655</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinoTrack GPS Devices Vulnerable to Remote Vehicle Control via Default Passwords</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sinotrack-gps-devices-vulnerable-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SinoTrack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5484, CVE-2025-5485; Summary: Two vulnerabilities in SinoTrack GPS devices allow an attacker to access device profiles without authorization, enabling remote functions on connected vehicles such as tracking locations and disconnecting power to the fuel pump. The flaws stem from weak authentication using a default password and a numerical identifier printed on the receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sinotrack-gps-devices-vulnerable-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Lean Security Model: 5 Lessons from River Island</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-build-lean-security-model-5.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses how River Island, a UK fashion retailer, implemented a lean security model using Intruder's exposure management platform. This allowed their small team of three to improve visibility, respond faster to threats, and empower others across the business to fix vulnerabilities. The approach involves adopting continuous network monitoring, consolidating security tools, and automating vulnerability scanning and remediation processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-build-lean-security-model-5.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPE Aruba Network Flaw Exposes Sensitive Data to Potential Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hpe-aruba-network-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Networking Private 5G Core Platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37100; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in the API implementation of the Private 5G Core Platform allows unauthorized access to sensitive system files, posing a risk to enterprise confidentiality and infrastructure integrity. Exploitation can occur remotely with valid credentials or authentication to the system, enabling attackers to download protected system files containing sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141640</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patches 67 Vulnerabilities Including WEBDAV Zero-Day Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-patches-67-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WEBDAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A remote code execution flaw in Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WEBDAV) has been weaponized in real-world attacks, allowing an attacker to execute malware by deceiving users into clicking on a specially crafted URL. The vulnerability, rated Critical, can be triggered by manipulating the working directory and is exploited through a .url file that launches iediagcmd.exe, which then executes another payload called Horus Loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-patches-67-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insyde UEFI Flaw Enables Digital Certificate Injection via NVRAM Variable</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/insyde-uefi-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Insyde H2O UEFI firmware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4275; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the SecureFlashCertData NVRAM variable allows attackers to inject malicious digital certificates and bypass Secure Boot protections, enabling pre-boot execution of unsigned code. This flaw enables severe risks to enterprise and consumer devices, allowing for persistence across reboots and OS reinstalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141634</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Chrome Flaws Enable Remote Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-chrome-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5958, CVE-2025-5959; Summary: The Stable channel of Google Chrome has been updated to version 137.0.7151.103 for Windows and Mac, and 137.0.7151.103 for Linux. Two high-severity security vulnerabilities have been addressed: a use-after-free condition in the Chrome Media component (CVE-2025-5958) that can lead to arbitrary code execution or denial-of-service attacks, and a type confusion vulnerability in the V8 JavaScript engine (CVE-2025-5959) that can be leveraged for remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141625</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 06:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Tuesday, June 2025 Edition</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/patch-tuesday-june-2025-edition/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: The article reports on multiple vulnerabilities in Microsoft Windows operating systems and software. One vulnerability, CVE-2025-33053, is a remote code execution flaw in the Windows implementation of WebDAV, which has already been exploited. Another vulnerability, CVE-2025-33073, is an elevation of privilege flaw in the SMB client, which can grant attackers SYSTEM-level control over a vulnerable PC.

FYSA: Several cybersecurity-relevant details are highlighted in the article, including the exploitation of a zero-day flaw and public proof-of-concept code for another flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71465</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-332: Microsoft Windows Installer Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-332/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33075; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by abusing the Windows Installer service. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this flaw, which can be used to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26710</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-333: Microsoft Windows Installer Service Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-333/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32714; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the Windows Installer service that uses an unsecured location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26487</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-334: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Gateway Service Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-334/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Gateway Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30394; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Microsoft Windows, without requiring authentication. The issue exists within the Remote Desktop Gateway service due to a null pointer dereference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26776</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-335: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-335/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43575; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC by writing past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26342</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-336: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Collab Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-336/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43573; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the handling of Collab objects due to lack of validating object existence prior to operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26590</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-337: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Font Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-337/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47112; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data that can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26777</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-338: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC Collab Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-338/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43574; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Adobe Acrobat Reader DC. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Collab objects and can be exploited by not validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26593</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-339: JupyterLab Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-339/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jupyter; JupyterLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30167; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of JupyterLab. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and it is triggered only when a target user makes use of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25932</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DanaBot malware operators exposed via C2 bug added in 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/danabot-malware-operators-exposed-via-c2-bug-added-in-2022/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: DanaBot Malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in the DanaBot malware operation introduced in June 2022 allowed security researchers to gain insight into the malware's internal operations and the people behind it, leading to the identification, indictment, and dismantling of their operations. The "DanaBleed" flaw was a memory leak that exposed private data, including threat actor details, backend infrastructure, and victim data, for over three years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/danabot-malware-operators-exposed-via-c2-bug-added-in-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday for June 2025 — Snort rules and prominent vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-june-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32710, CVE-2025-29828, CVE-2025-33071, CVE-2025-47172, CVE-2025-47162, CVE-2025-47164, CVE-2025-47167, CVE-2025-47953; Summary: The vulnerabilities affect various Microsoft Windows services and applications, including Remote Desktop Services, Schannel (Secure Channel), KDC Proxy service, Microsoft Office, and SharePoint server. They are remote code execution (RCE) or elevation of privilege vulnerabilities with varying attack complexities and exploitation likelihoods.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6848785af23a7100010e4c1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConnectWise rotating code signing certificates over security concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-rotating-code-signing-certificates-over-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise (various products); CVE(s): None; Summary: ConnectWise is rotating the digital code signing certificates used to sign ScreenConnect, Automate, and RMM executables due to concerns raised by a third-party security researcher about how certain configuration data can be abused by threat actors. The action is unrelated to any security incidents, including a nation-state cyberattack suffered last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/connectwise-rotating-code-signing-certificates-over-security-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Secure Boot flaw lets attackers install bootkit malware, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-secure-boot-flaw-lets-attackers-install-bootkit-malware-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3052; Summary: A Secure Boot bypass vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-3052, allows attackers with admin rights to modify a user-writable NVRAM variable and disable Secure Boot, enabling the installation of bootkit malware. The flaw affects nearly every system that trusts Microsoft's "UEFI CA 2011" certificate, which is widely used in modern systems utilizing UEFI firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-secure-boot-flaw-lets-attackers-install-bootkit-malware-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Windows WebDAV 0-Day RCE Vulnerability Actively Exploited in The Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-windows-webdav-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft Windows allows remote code execution through manipulation of a system's working directory. The flaw was actively exploited by the advanced persistent threat (APT) group Stealth Falcon, who used it to deliver malicious files and inject shellcode into legitimate system processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141611</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found in the wild: 2 Secure Boot exploits. Microsoft is patching only 1 of them.</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/unearthed-in-the-wild-2-secure-boot-exploits-microsoft-patches-only-1-of-them/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers with brief physical access to a device can boot it up in IGEL and modify the boot loader to install malware. This vulnerability allows bypassing Secure Boot protections, potentially loading an untrusted OS on systems that trust the Microsoft 3rd Party UEFI CA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/unearthed-in-the-wild-2-secure-boot-exploits-microsoft-patches-only-1-of-them/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 19:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday June 2025 – 66 Vulnerabilities Patched Including 2 Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-june-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the WebDAV component of Windows was actively exploited and a publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerability in the SMB client allowed for elevation of privilege. The vulnerabilities could be exploited to execute arbitrary code or gain SYSTEM-level privileges, making timely patching essential.

Note: There are 66 vulnerabilities patched in total, but only these two specific vulnerabilities are mentioned as zero-days with exploitation details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141601</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Highlights the Internet as the Primary Threat to Industrial Automation Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-highlights-the-internet-as-the-primary-threat/</link>
      <description>According to Kaspersky ICS CERT, the internet is the primary source of threats to operational technology (OT) infrastructure worldwide, with 21.9% of Industrial Control System (ICS) computers encountering malicious objects in the first quarter of 2025. The report highlights regional disparities in cybersecurity maturity, with Africa and South-East Asia facing heightened exposure to internet-based threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141568</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Releases Patch Fixing 254 Vulnerabilities, Closing High-Severity Security Gaps</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/adobe-releases-patch-fixing-254.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe; CVEs: CVE-2025-47110, CVE-2025-43585, None (for others); Summary: Adobe patched 254 security flaws in its software products, primarily affecting Experience Manager and Commerce/Magento. The vulnerabilities, including a critical reflected XSS flaw and an improper authorization issue, could lead to arbitrary code execution, privilege escalation, or security feature bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/adobe-releases-patch-fixing-254.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Details on How to Manage Your Digital Footprint</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-to-manage-your-digital-footprint/</link>
      <description>ESET highlights the importance of digital footprints, emphasizing both their benefits (personalized marketing, professional branding) and risks (privacy breaches, identity theft). The article stresses the need for robust strategies to manage and secure one's online presence, including regular audits, adjusting privacy settings, and leveraging advanced security tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141538</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover 20+ Configuration Risks, Including Five CVEs, in Salesforce Industry Cloud</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-uncover-20-configuration.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Salesforce Industry Cloud; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43697, CVE-2025-43698, CVE-2025-43699, CVE-2025-43700, CVE-2025-43701; Summary: Over 20 configuration-related risks were found in Salesforce Industry Cloud, exposing sensitive data to unauthorized parties. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to bypass security controls and extract sensitive customer or employee information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-uncover-20-configuration.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5060533 cumulative update released with 7 changes, fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5060533-cumulative-update-released-with-7-changes-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The KB5060533 cumulative update for Windows 10 22H2 and Windows 10 21H2 fixes seven zero-day vulnerabilities, including bringing seconds back to the time shown in the Calendar flyout, enhancing the Rich Calendar feature, and fixing issues with GDI/GDI+, Mobile Operator Profiles, and WinSaS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5060533-cumulative-update-released-with-7-changes-fixes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP NetWeaver Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-netweaver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP; CVE(s): 3600840; Summary: A critical vulnerability with a CVSS score of 9.6 in the SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP's Remote Function Call (RFC) framework allows authenticated attackers to bypass standard authorization checks and escalate privileges, potentially granting access to critical system functions and data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft June 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes exploited zero-day, 66 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-exploited-zero-day-66-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33053, CVE-2025-33073; Summary: Microsoft fixed two zero-day vulnerabilities in its June 2025 Patch Tuesday updates. The first is a Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WEBDAV) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability (CVE-2025-33053), which was actively exploited before the patch was available. The second is a Windows SMB Client Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-33073), which allows attackers to gain SYSTEM privileges on vulnerable devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-june-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-exploited-zero-day-66-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5060842 and KB5060999 cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060842-and-kb5060999-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the release of Windows 11 KB5060842 and KB5060999 cumulative updates for versions 24H2 and 23H2, which include fixes for 66 security vulnerabilities. The updates also introduce new features such as improved Windows Search, enhanced digital accessibility with AI-powered image descriptions in Narrator, and management of Energy Saver settings through group policies and MDM configurations using Microsoft Intune.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060842-and-kb5060999-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Instagram Growth Tools Stealing Login Credentials and Sending Them to Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-instagram-growth-tools-stealing-login-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: imad213 (Python package); CVE(s): None; Summary: The malicious Python package imad213, posing as an Instagram growth tool, tricks users into surrendering their credentials. Upon execution, it initiates a remote check and prompts users for their Instagram login details, saving them locally in plaintext. The malware then broadcasts these credentials to a network of Turkish bot services, which pose as legitimate platforms with professional interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141553</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean APT Hackers Target Users on Social Media to Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-apt-hackers-target-users/</link>
      <description>This article reports a highly sophisticated Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) campaign orchestrated by the North Korean state-sponsored hacking group Kimsuky, targeting individuals in South Korea through social media, email, and Telegram. The attackers use social engineering and tailored content to exploit trust, and employ a multi-stage infiltration strategy involving malicious files, decoy PDFs, and malware designed to bypass signature-based detection tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141545</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN6 Uses AWS-Hosted Fake Resumes on LinkedIn to Deliver More_eggs Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fin6-uses-aws-hosted-fake-resumes-on.html</link>
      <description>FIN6 is a financially motivated threat actor that uses fake resumes hosted on Amazon Web Services (AWS) infrastructure to deliver the More_eggs malware. The group initiates contact with recruiters through LinkedIn and Indeed, posing as job seekers, and then delivers phishing messages that lead to malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fin6-uses-aws-hosted-fake-resumes-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook to block more risky attachments used in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-outlook-to-block-more-risky-attachments-used-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Microsoft will block .library-ms and .search-ms file types in Outlook Web and the new Outlook for Windows starting next month to enhance security and prevent exploitation of Windows vulnerabilities. The blocked file types are rarely used, but may affect organizations that rely on them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-outlook-to-block-more-risky-attachments-used-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Dept. of Transportation breached, 300k crash records stolen</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/texas-dept-of-transportation-breached-300k-crash-records-stolen/</link>
      <description>The Texas Department of Transportation (TxDOT) suffered a data breach after a threat actor downloaded 300,000 crash records from its database using compromised credentials. The exposed data includes full names, physical addresses, driver's license numbers, and other information, which elevates the risk for social engineering, scamming, and phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/texas-dept-of-transportation-breached-300k-crash-records-stolen/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN6 hackers pose as job seekers to backdoor recruiters’ devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fin6-hackers-pose-as-job-seekers-to-backdoor-recruiters-devices/</link>
      <description>FIN6 hacking group impersonates job seekers to target recruiters, using social engineering campaigns to deliver "More Eggs" malware-as-a-service JavaScript backdoor for credential theft, system access, and ransomware deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fin6-hackers-pose-as-job-seekers-to-backdoor-recruiters-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Workspace Control hardcoded key flaws expose SQL credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-workspace-control-hardcoded-key-flaws-expose-sql-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Workspace Control (IWC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-5353, CVE-2025-22455, CVE-2025-22463; Summary: The IWC solution has three high-severity hardcoded key vulnerabilities that can lead to privilege escalation and system compromise following successful exploitation. Two flaws allow local authenticated attackers to decrypt stored SQL credentials, while the third enables decryption of the stored environment password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-workspace-control-hardcoded-key-flaws-expose-sql-credentials/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Heroku outage impacts web platforms worldwide</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-heroku-outage-impacts-web-platforms-worldwide/</link>
      <description>Heroku is experiencing a widespread outage that has lasted over six hours, affecting developers' ability to log in and use the platform. The outage impacts various services and websites, including SolarWinds, which cannot ingest logs due to the issue. Heroku has not yet provided details on the root cause or when services will be restored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/massive-heroku-outage-impacts-web-platforms-worldwide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Workspace Control Vulnerability Lets Attackers Remotely Exploit To Steal the Credential</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-workspace-control-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Workspace Control; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5353, CVE-2025-22463, CVE-2025-22455; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Ivanti Workspace Control prior to 10.19.10.0 allow local authenticated attackers to decrypt stored SQL credentials and environment passwords due to hardcoded cryptographic keys. Successful exploitation could lead to severe consequences, including unauthorized access to critical systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141554</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust-based Myth Stealer Malware Spread via Fake Gaming Sites Targets Chrome, Firefox Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rust-based-myth-stealer-malware-spread.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): None; Summary: Myth Stealer is a Rust-based information stealer that steals passwords, cookies, and autofill information from Chromium- and Gecko-based browsers. It's distributed through fake gaming websites and online forums, and attempts to terminate running processes associated with web browsers before exfiltrating stolen data to a remote server or Discord webhook. The malware contains anti-analysis techniques such as string obfuscation and system checks using filenames and usernames.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rust-based-myth-stealer-malware-spread.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is a data-breach time bomb, reveals new report</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ai-is-a-data-breach-time-bomb-reveals-new-report/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with AI, cloud environments, and SaaS apps. It highlights that 99% of organizations have sensitive data unnecessarily exposed to AI tools, and no organization was fully prepared for AI. The report emphasizes the importance of implementing effective security measures to prioritize data protection.

Note: There are no specific vulnerabilities mentioned in this article, but it focuses on the risks associated with AI and data exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ai-is-a-data-breach-time-bomb-reveals-new-report/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Persist in Using ConnectWise ScreenConnect Tool to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-persist-in-using-connectwise-screenconnect-tool/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise ScreenConnect; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers are exploiting a vulnerability in ScreenConnect versions 23.9.7 and prior, deploying malicious payloads, particularly targeting financial organizations, using phishing emails with invoice themes to trick users into downloading harmful executables. The exploitation involves signed malicious droppers, likely tied to the CHAINVERB backdoor associated with the UNC5952 threat group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141498</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI working to fix ChatGPT outage affecting users worldwide</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/openai-working-to-fix-chatgpt-outage-affecting-users-worldwide/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article reports on an ongoing outage impacting OpenAI's ChatGPT, causing errors and latency for users worldwide. The issue has been identified as a root cause and the company is working to implement a mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/openai-working-to-fix-chatgpt-outage-affecting-users-worldwide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe SAP NetWeaver Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Bypass Authorization Checks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/severe-sap-netweaver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): 3600840 (9.6), 3609271 (8.8), 3606484 (8.5), 3560693 (8.2), 3610006 (7.5), 3590887 (5.8); Summary: The June Patch Day from SAP addresses nineteen security patches, including critical vulnerabilities that can allow attackers to bypass authorization controls and escalate privileges across multiple enterprise systems. The most severe vulnerability affects the RFC framework in SAP NetWeaver Application Server AS ABAP, enabling authenticated attackers to bypass standard authorization controls and achieve privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141512</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-49113: Critical Roundcube Vulnerability Enables RCE Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-49113-roundcube-vulnerability-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49113; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability, CVE-2025-49113, affects all Roundcube versions before 1.5.10 and 1.6.x up to 1.6.10, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands on targeted systems after successful authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060866</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New SharePoint Phishing Campaigns Employing Deceptive Lick Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sharepoint-phishing-campaigns/</link>
      <description>Phishing campaigns leveraging Microsoft SharePoint to bypass modern detection systems have been identified, exploiting inherent trust users place in the platform. These attacks disguise phishing URLs as legitimate file-sharing links, tricking users into accessing credential-harvesting pages or downloading malware, and evade endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools and email security gateways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141482</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISPConfig Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation to Superadmin and PHP Code Injection Exploit</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ispconfig-vulnerability-allows-privilege-escalation-to-superadmin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ISPConfig version 3.2.12p1; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to escalate their privileges to that of a superadmin and execute arbitrary PHP code remotely, posing a serious risk to affected systems. Attackers can manipulate HTTP parameters when using the client_add and users_edit features, creating a client account with admin privileges, then modifying or assuming the identity of the superadmin user (ID 1), granting unrestricted access to the ISPConfig instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141481</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Lovable’s Security Policies Allows Malicious Code Injection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-lovables-security-policies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lovable; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability affects Lovable's AI-powered development platform, exposing sensitive user data and enabling malicious code injection across hundreds of applications. It stems from the platform's client-driven architecture and lack of proper Row Level Security (RLS) configurations, allowing unauthorized access to database contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141460</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/10/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24016, CVE-2025-33053; Summary: Two new vulnerabilities were added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog by CISA due to evidence of active exploitation. The vulnerabilities are a Wazuh Server Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability and a Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability. These types of vulnerabilities pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and all organizations are urged to prioritize timely remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23494</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinoTrack GPS Receiver</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-160-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SinoTrack Equipment; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5484, CVE-2025-5485; Summary: Weak authentication and observable response discrepancy vulnerabilities in all known SinoTrack devices allow an attacker to access device profiles without authorization through the common web management interface, enabling remote functions on connected vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/10/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories by CISA, providing information on current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23493</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670, 650, SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-160-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670, Relion 650, SAM600-IO Series; CVE(s): CVE-2022-4304; Summary: A timing-based side channel exists in the OpenSSL RSA decryption implementation, allowing an attacker to decrypt application data in transit by sending a large number of trial messages for decryption. This vulnerability affects all RSA padding modes: PKCS#1 v1.5, RSA-OEAP and RSASVE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23491</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroDicom DICOM Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-160-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MicroDicom DICOM Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5943; Summary: The DICOM Viewer suffers from an out-of-bounds write vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with user interaction. Successful exploitation could lead to the execution of arbitrary code on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23492</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five plead guilty to laundering $36 million stolen in investment scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/five-plead-guilty-to-laundering-36-million-stolen-in-investment-scams/</link>
      <description>Five men from China, the United States, and Turkey pleaded guilty to their involvement in an international crime ring and laundering nearly $37 million stolen from U.S. victims in cryptocurrency investment scams carried out from Cambodia. The scam involved accomplices reaching out to targets via unsolicited social media, phone calls, text messages, and online dating services to gain their trust, promoting fraudulent digital asset investments and falsely claiming that the victims' funds' value increased after they tricked them into investing, when, in fact, their money was stolen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/five-plead-guilty-to-laundering-36-million-stolen-in-investment-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Threat in Your Stack: Why Non-Human Identity Management is the Next Cybersecurity Frontier</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-threat-in-your-stack-why-non.html</link>
      <description>Non-human identities (NHIs), including application secrets, API keys, service accounts, and OAuth tokens, have increased in recent years due to the expanding array of apps and services. NHIs introduce unique risks and management challenges that security leaders must address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-threat-in-your-stack-why-non.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on Erlang/OTP SSH Server RCE Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-erlang-otp-ssh-server-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP SSH server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: The Erlang/OTP SSH server implementation has a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-32433) that allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands without authentication, bypassing standard security controls. This flaw enables unauthenticated remote code execution and is actively exploited in the wild, posing significant risks to organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141432</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Authorities Bust Cybercriminals Posing as Microsoft Tech Support</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-posing-as-microsoft-tech-support/</link>
      <description>The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) launched an operation targeting a tech support scam network impersonating Microsoft, resulting in the arrest of six key operatives and the shutdown of two illicit call centers. The operation was a result of international collaboration between the CBI, Japan's Cybercrime Control Center, National Police Agency, and Microsoft's Digital Crimes Unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141461</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Actors Exploit SoraAI’s Popularity &amp; GitHub to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-actors-exploit-soraais-popularity-github/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malware campaign that uses OpenAI's Sora video generation model as a social engineering tactic to distribute information-stealing malware. The attack chain involves multiple stages, including downloading malicious batch files and executing Python scripts, which target sensitive data such as browser cookies, passwords, and system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141441</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher Found Flaw to Discover Phone Numbers Linked to Any Google Account</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researcher-found-flaw-to-discover-phone.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Google's account recovery feature allowed attackers to brute-force a user's recovery phone number, potentially exposing their accounts to privacy and security risks. The exploit required several steps, including leaking the display name via Looker Studio, running the forgot password flow, and brute-forcing the phone number against the username recovery endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researcher-found-flaw-to-discover-phone.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Linux Binaries in Targeted Cloud Operations</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/elf-based-malware-targets-cloud/</link>
      <description>Unit 42 researchers have identified a growing threat to cloud security: Linux Executable and Linkage Format (ELF) files that threat actors are developing to target cloud infrastructure. The article highlights the types of malicious binaries that threat actors are developing for use in attacks against Linux-based environments, including backdoors, droppers, remote access Trojans (RATs), data wipers, and vulnerability-exploiting binaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142727</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware Deployment Campaigns: ‘Librarian Ghouls’ APT Group Targets Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/librarian-ghouls-apt-group-targets-organizations/</link>
      <description>The Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group "Librarian Ghouls" has been actively targeting organizations across Russia and the CIS with sophisticated malware deployment campaigns, utilizing targeted phishing emails as their primary infection vector. They employ legitimate third-party software to mask their activities and hinder detection, deploying remote access tools, stealing sensitive credentials, and installing crypto-mining malware like XMRig on compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141411</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP Security Patch Day: 14 Vulnerabilities Resolved Across Various Products</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sap-security-patch-day-14-vulnerabilities-resolved/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-42989 (Critical), CVE-2025-42982 (High), CVE-2025-23192 (High), CVE-2025-42977 (Medium), CVE-2025-42994, CVE-2025-42995, and CVE-2025-42996 (Medium); Summary: SAP's June 10, 2025 Security Patch Day addressed 14 vulnerabilities across the enterprise software portfolio, including a Critical vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP allowing unauthorized access to sensitive system functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141405</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploitation of Critical Wazuh Server RCE Vulnerability Leads to Mirai Variant Deployment</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploitation-of-critical-wazuh-server-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wazuh; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24016, CVE-2023-1389 (TP-Link Archer AX21), CVE-2017-17215 (Huawei HG532); Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Wazuh servers, identified as CVE-2025-24016 with a CVSS score of 9.9, allows attackers to execute arbitrary Python code via maliciously crafted JSON payloads. The vulnerability has been weaponized by two distinct botnets to propagate variants of the notorious Mirai malware, targeting primarily Internet of Things (IoT) devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141375</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion Stealer Rises, Android 0-Day for Sale, EDF Leak Exposed</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/fusion-stealer-rises-android-0-day-for-sale-edf-leak-exposed/</link>
      <description>The article highlights several concerning cybercriminal offerings on the dark web, including an alleged Android 0-day exploit, a stealer tool called Fusion Stealer, unauthorized VPN access to a US healthcare provider, admin panel access for multiple South American FinTech companies, and a massive alleged leak of EDF Energy's customer database. These discoveries emphasize the persistent and evolving threat landscape facing organizations and individuals worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060851</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 09:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensata Technologies Faces Disruption Due to Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sensata-technologies-faces-disruption/</link>
      <description>The article reports a significant cybersecurity incident at Sensata Technologies, involving an external system breach that compromised personal information of hundreds of individuals. The breach remained undetected for nearly two months before being discovered on May 23, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141366</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability in DanaBot Malware C2 Server Leaks Threat Actor Usernames and Crypto Keys</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vulnerability-in-danabot-malware-c2-server/</link>
      <description>A severe vulnerability in the command-and-control (C2) infrastructure of the DanaBot malware has been discovered, allowing for the exposure of usernames and cryptographic keys used by malicious operators. This breach could provide cybersecurity defenders with a rare glimpse into the inner workings of DanaBot operations and enable more effective disruption of this persistent banking trojan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141390</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 84,000 Roundcube Webmail Installations Exposed to Remote Code   Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-84000-roundcube-webmail-installations-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube Webmail; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49113; Summary: The critical vulnerability, designated as CVE-2025-49113, allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code remotely. It affects all Roundcube versions from 1.1.0 through 1.6.10 and has been exploited in targeted attacks, potentially conducted by state actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141374</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Werewolf APT Uses Legitimate Software in Attacks on Hundreds of Russian Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rare-werewolf-apt-uses-legitimate.html</link>
      <description>Rare Werewolf, an advanced persistent threat (APT) group, has been linked to a series of cyber attacks targeting Russia and CIS countries. The attacks aim to establish remote access to compromised hosts, steal credentials, and deploy the XMRig cryptocurrency miner. The group obtains initial access using phishing emails and leverages legitimate software to interact with infected systems, harvest passwords, and disable antivirus software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/rare-werewolf-apt-uses-legitimate.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus Vulnerability Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/manageengine-exchange-reporter-plus-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3835; Summary: The vulnerability, affecting all builds up to version 5721, allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on target servers, enabling remote code execution and potentially compromising system integrity. Successful exploitation could grant attackers complete control over the compromised system, enabling data breaches, regulatory compliance violations, and operational disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141358</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 05:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Erlang SSH and Roundcube Flaws to Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-adds-erlang-ssh-and-roundcube.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/Open Telecom Platform (OTP); CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: A missing authentication vulnerability in OTP SSH server allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands without valid credentials, potentially leading to unauthenticated remote code execution. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 10.0 and was fixed in April 2025.

Vulnerable Product: Roundcube Webmail; CVE(s): CVE-2024-42009; Summary: A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in RoundCube Webmail allows a remote attacker to steal and send emails of a victim via a crafted email message by taking advantage of a desanitization issue. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.3 and was fixed in August 2024.

FYSA: The article also mentions an unpatched account takeover vulnerability (CVE-2025-31022, CVSS score: 9.8) in the PayU CommercePro plugin for WordPress that enables an attacker to seize control of any user without authentication, with serious consequences if exploited successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-adds-erlang-ssh-and-roundcube.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 05:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Vulnerability Allowed Hackers to Access User Phone Numbers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google account recovery system; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allowed attackers to brute-force and obtain the phone numbers of any Google user by exploiting Google's username recovery form that still functioned without JavaScript, bypassing modern security protections. The attack leveraged two HTTP requests and exploited IP-based rate limiting and CAPTCHA challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141344</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 05:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Ticketmaster data from Snowflake attacks briefly for sale again</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stolen-ticketmaster-data-from-snowflake-attacks-briefly-for-sale-again/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Arkana Security extortion gang listing Ticketmaster data for sale, which was previously stolen during the 2024 Snowflake data theft attacks. It appears that the group is attempting to resell old stolen data, rather than conducting a new breach. The article also mentions the ShinyHunters group's involvement in various breaches and their potential ties to law enforcement arrests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stolen-ticketmaster-data-from-snowflake-attacks-briefly-for-sale-again/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 22:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 84,000 Roundcube instances vulnerable to actively exploited flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-84-000-roundcube-instances-vulnerable-to-actively-exploited-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49113; Summary: The Roundcube webmail installation is vulnerable to a critical remote code execution (RCE) flaw, patched on June 1, 2025. The vulnerability stems from unsanitized $_GET['_from'] input, enabling PHP object deserialization and session corruption when session keys begin with an exclamation mark. Exploitation requires authentication, but attackers claim valid credentials can be obtained via CSRF, log scraping, or brute-forced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-84-000-roundcube-instances-vulnerable-to-actively-exploited-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google patched bug leaking phone numbers tied to accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-patched-bug-leaking-phone-numbers-tied-to-accounts/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability allowed researchers to brute-force any Google account's recovery phone number by knowing the profile name and a partial phone number. The attack exploited a deprecated JavaScript-disabled version of the Google username recovery form, which lacked modern anti-abuse protections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-patched-bug-leaking-phone-numbers-tied-to-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentinelOne shares new details on China-linked breach attempt</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sentinelone-shares-new-details-on-china-linked-breach-attempt/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Cloud Service Appliances, Check Point gateways; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerabilities in exposed network devices were exploited by Chinese hackers in an attempted supply chain attack on SentinelOne.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sentinelone-shares-new-details-on-china-linked-breach-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Foundation unveils decentralized WordPress plugin manager</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/linux-foundation-unveils-decentralized-wordpress-plugin-manager/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the launch of FAIR Package Manager, an independent distribution system for trusted WordPress plugins and themes. This move is a response to controversy between Automattic (WordPress.com) and WP Engine over plugin updates. The FAIR Package Manager aims to decentralize the ecosystem, bringing control back to developers and hosts, while improving security features such as cryptographic measures, browser compatibility checking, and reliance on trusted source security salts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/linux-foundation-unveils-decentralized-wordpress-plugin-manager/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Reveals Chinese Hackers Attempted to Breach SentinelOne Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-reveals-chinese-hackers-attempted-to-breach/</link>
      <description>The article discusses SentinelLABS, a reconnaissance operation targeting SentinelOne, a leading cybersecurity vendor. The operation was linked to China-nexus threat actors and affected over 70 organizations worldwide. Despite the persistent efforts, SentinelOne's infrastructure remained uncompromised due to robust monitoring and rapid response mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141325</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensata Technologies says personal data stolen by ransomware gang</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sensata-technologies-says-personal-data-stolen-by-ransomware-gang/</link>
      <description>Sensata Technologies suffered a data breach after an April ransomware attack, affecting current and former employees and their dependents. The stolen data includes full name, address, Social Security Number (SSN), driver's license number, state ID card number, passport number, financial account information, payment card information, medical information, health insurance information, and date of birth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sensata-technologies-says-personal-data-stolen-by-ransomware-gang/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitter Malware Employs Custom-Built Tools to Evade Detection in Advanced Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bitter-malware-employs-custom-built-tools/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the malware arsenal of the Bitter group (TA397), a state-backed actor aligned with India's interests. The group has evolved from deploying rudimentary downloaders to sophisticated RATs and backdoors, showcasing technical prowess and adaptability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141301</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 70 Organizations Across Multiple Sectors Targeted by China-Linked Cyber Espionage Group</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-70-organizations-across-multiple.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of cyberattacks attributed to China-nexus threat actors, targeting various organizations across different sectors. The attacks are believed to be part of a broader campaign, with some connections to previously reported APT15 and UNC5174 groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-70-organizations-across-multiple.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skitnet Malware Actively Adopted by Ransomware Gangs to Enhance Operational Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/skitnet-malware-actively-adopted-by-ransomware-gangs/</link>
      <description>Skitnet malware (also known as Bossnet) is a post-exploitation package with an integrated server-side control panel that has emerged as a critical tool for ransomware gangs, showcasing increased operational efficiency for cybercriminals. It initiates its infection chain through social engineering tactics and uses various techniques to evade detection, including DLL hijacking, dynamic API resolution, and anti-forensic measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141291</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Warns of Surge in Cyberattacks Targeting US Users to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-warns-of-surge-in-cyberattacks-targeting-us-users/</link>
      <description>The article highlights a significant increase in cyberattacks and scams targeting US consumers, with a focus on stealing login credentials. Scammers are leveraging text messages and email as attack vectors, and users are increasingly relying on modern authentication methods like passkeys and social sign-ins to stay secure. Google is actively combating these threats through AI-driven security features, including blocking over 99.9% of spam, phishing, and malware in Gmail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141283</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Distinct Botnets Exploit Wazuh Server Vulnerability to Launch Mirai-Based Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/botnet-wazuh-server-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wazur Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24016; Summary: A critical security flaw (CVE-2025-24016) in the Wazuh server allows remote code execution, and has been exploited by threat actors to drop Mirai botnet variants and conduct DDoS attacks. The vulnerability was patched in February 2025, but attempts at exploitation were detected as early as March and May 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/botnet-wazuh-server-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Bypassed Privacy Protections to Track Android Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/meta-bypassed-privacy-protections/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Meta (formerly Facebook) and Yandex; CVE(s): None; Summary: Meta and Yandex exploited a design feature of Android's localhost ports to track users' web activity and link it to their real identities. The tracking technique, which bypasses typical privacy protections, allows apps to receive browser metadata and cookies, enabling the creation of a persistent profile of a user's browsing habits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141295</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Targets $7.7M in Crypto Tied to North Korean IT Worker Scam</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/u-s-targets-7-7m-in-crypto-tied/</link>
      <description>The United States Department of Justice has seized over $7.7 million in cryptocurrency and digital assets linked to a sophisticated global laundering operation orchestrated by North Korea. The operation involved the use of falsified identities, virtual private networks (VPNs), and advanced obfuscation techniques to conceal the origin of the funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141208</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT41 Hackers Leverage Google Calendar for Malware C2 in Attacks on Government Entities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt41-hackers-leverage-google-calendar-for-malware/</link>
      <description>This article describes an APT41 campaign that uses Google Calendar as a command-and-control (C2) mechanism to exfiltrate information and retrieve commands from attackers. The malware, named ToughProgress, employs advanced obfuscation techniques, process hollowing, and driver-like handling to achieve persistence and privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141247</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Blue Team playbooks with Wazuh for proactive incident response</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-blue-team-playbooks-with-wazuh-for-proactive-incident-response/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Blue Team playbooks, which are detailed guides outlining how to identify, contain, and remediate specific security incidents. The article highlights the importance of structured processes in incident response and mentions Wazuh, an open-source security platform that provides real-time threat detection, automated response, and comprehensive incident management capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-blue-team-playbooks-with-wazuh-for-proactive-incident-response/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Blue Team playbooks with Wazuh for proactive cyber defense</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-blue-team-playbooks-with-wazuh-for-proactive-cyber-defense/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Blue Team playbooks, which are detailed guides outlining how to identify, contain, and remediate specific security incidents. The article highlights the importance of structured processes in incident response and introduces Wazuh, an open-source security platform that provides real-time threat detection, automated response, and comprehensive incident management for various attack scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-blue-team-playbooks-with-wazuh-for-proactive-cyber-defense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blitz Malware Targets Windows Servers to Deploy Monero Miner</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-blitz-malware-targets-windows-servers/</link>
      <description>The Blitz malware is a Windows-based malware that deploys a Monero cryptocurrency miner, information-stealer, and DoS capability. It spreads through backdoored game cheats for the popular mobile game Standoff 2 and communicates via a REST API built on the FastAPI framework.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141219</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Shuts Down ChatGPT Accounts Linked to Russian, Iranian &amp; Chinese Cyber</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/openai-shuts-down-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in cybersecurity, highlighting its potential to detect and mitigate various threats such as social engineering campaigns, cyber espionage operations, scams, and spam. The organization uses AI-driven tools to analyze vast datasets, flag anomalies, and identify suspicious behaviors, with a focus on countering authoritarian regimes, child exploitation, and malicious cyber activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141207</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy FormBook Malware via Weaponized Excel Files to Target Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-formbook-malware-via-weaponized-excel-files/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2017-0199; Summary: A critical phishing campaign targets Windows users by exploiting a long-standing vulnerability in older versions of Microsoft Office (Office 2007/2010/2013/2016) using malicious Excel attachments. The exploit triggers an HTTP request to download additional payloads, ultimately unleashing the FormBook malware, which steals sensitive information and poses a severe threat to victims' devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141203</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 Employees Departed CISA Since Trump Administration Began</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-1000-employees-departed/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has lost nearly one-third of its workforce since the start of the Trump administration, with approximately 1,000 employees leaving due to buyouts, early retirements, and layoffs. This reduction in staff coincides with a proposed 17% to 30% reduction in CISA's budget, targeting critical programs such as continuous diagnostics and monitoring (CDM) tools and CyberSentry. The departures and funding cuts threaten the agency's ability to fulfill its core mission of defending federal networks, supporting critical infrastructure operators, and responding to cyber incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141205</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery wholesale giant United Natural Foods hit by cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/grocery-wholesale-giant-united-natural-foods-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>UNFI, North America's largest publicly traded wholesale distributor, was forced to shut down some systems following a recent cyberattack. The company reported $31 billion in annual revenues and has over 28,000 workers. An investigation is ongoing with the assistance of external cybersecurity experts, but no details have been released on the nature of the attack or whether data was stolen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/grocery-wholesale-giant-united-natural-foods-hit-by-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seraphic Security UnveilsBrowserTotal™ – Free AI-PoweredBrowser Security Assessment For Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/seraphic-security-unveilsbrowsertotal-free-ai-poweredbrowser-security-assessment-for-enterprises/</link>
      <description>Seraphic Security announces the launch of BrowserTotal, a browser security assessment tool that conducts over 120 tests to provide posture standing, emerging threat insights, and more. The platform is powered by AI and offers CISOs and security teams a comprehensive environment to test browser security defenses against today's most sophisticated threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141228</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health Confirms Interlock Ransomware Breach and Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kettering-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a ransomware attack on Kettering Health, a major Ohio-based healthcare provider, which resulted in unauthorized access to the network, encryption of critical patient care systems, and exfiltration of sensitive patient data. The incident highlights the importance of robust cybersecurity frameworks, rapid incident response, and transparent communication with patients and staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141192</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/09/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP SSH Server, RoundCube Webmail; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433, CVE-2024-42009; Summary: The two vulnerabilities added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog are a missing authentication for critical function vulnerability in Erlang/OTP SSH Server and a cross-site scripting vulnerability in RoundCube Webmail. These vulnerabilities pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and can be exploited by malicious cyber actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23481</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Chrome 0-Day, Data Wipers, Misused Tools and Zero-Click iPhone Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-data-wipers.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article appears to be a collection of cybersecurity-related news and updates from various sources. It covers a wide range of topics, including malware attacks, APT groups, and government efforts to combat cybercrime.

Some of the specific stories mentioned in the article include:

1. The alleged involvement of Taiwan's Democratic Progressive Party (DPP) in sponsoring five advanced persistent threat (APT) groups.
2. China accusing Taiwan of running these APT groups with US help, and issuing warrants for 20 Taiwanese people involved.
3. Colombian cybercriminals linked to vehicle insurance scams that use fake websites and ads on Facebook to deceive users.
4. The takedown of TrickBot, a notorious ransomware gang, by German authorities.
5. Microsoft Defender's Attack Surface Reduction (ASR) rules and how they can be enabled to block common malware techniques.

Overall, the article highlights the ongoing threat of cybercrime and the importance of staying vigilant in order to prevent attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-data-wipers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple QNAP Flaws Allow Remote Attackers to Hijack User Accounts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-qnap-flaws-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: QNAP Qsync Central; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22482, CVE-2025-29892; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities were found in Qsync Central, a file synchronization software used by QNAP NAS devices. The first vulnerability is a format string vulnerability that can allow attackers to obtain sensitive data or execute malicious code, while the second is an SQL injection vulnerability that can also lead to arbitrary code execution or command injection. Both require user-level access to exploit, but the impact is severe and prompt patching is essential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141169</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Your IdP or CASB Covers Shadow IT? These 5 Risks Prove Otherwise</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/think-your-idp-or-casb-covers-shadow-it.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses "shadow IT," which refers to unsanctioned software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications, dormant accounts, unmanaged identities, over-permissioned SaaS tools, and orphaned access that can be used by attackers to gain unauthorized access to enterprise systems. The risks include OAuth sprawl, shadow admins, GenAI access, and apps created directly in platforms like Google Workspace or Slack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/think-your-idp-or-casb-covers-shadow-it.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DuplexSpy RAT Gives Attackers Full Control Over Windows Machines</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-duplexspy-rat-gives-attackers/</link>
      <description>DuplexSpy is a Remote Access Trojan (RAT) that poses a significant threat to Windows-based systems. It offers attackers unprecedented control over compromised machines, featuring persistence mechanisms, stealthy execution, and surveillance tools. Its open-source nature and customization options make it a potent weapon in the hands of malicious actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141175</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenkins Gatling Plugin Flaw Allows CSP Bypass, Exposing Systems to Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jenkins-gatling-plugin-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jenkins Gatling Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5806; Summary: The Gatling Plugin in Jenkins allows for across-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities due to a bypass of Content-Security-Policy protections, enabling attackers with low-privileged access to inject malicious scripts that can execute in other users' browsers, leading to theft of sensitive session cookies and unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141154</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roles Here? Roles There? Roles Anywhere: Exploring the Security of AWS IAM Roles Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/aws-roles-anywhere/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the AWS IAM Roles Anywhere service, which enables external workloads to authenticate using X.509 digital certificates. The service allows organizations to securely access cloud APIs and can be used with Kubernetes pods or other external workloads. However, if not configured correctly, default configurations of this service can be exploited by attackers, allowing them to gain access to additional roles in the AWS account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142575</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 10:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware for Developers: 16 React Native Packages with Millions of Downloads Compromised Overnight</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/16-react-native-packages-with-millions-of-downloads-compromised/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm ecosystem; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports a large-scale attack targeting the npm ecosystem, compromising 16 popular React Native packages with over one million weekly downloads. The attack injected malicious payloads into widely used libraries, posing an immediate risk to developers and organizations relying on these dependencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141155</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Naval Operations Accidentally Jam New Zealand’s Internet and Radio</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/australian-naval-jam-new-zealands/</link>
      <description>The article describes a widespread outage of wireless internet and radio services in New Zealand caused by HMAS Canberra's advanced navigation radar system interfering with civilian devices operating on the 5 GHz band. The incident highlights the fragility of the shared spectrum environment, particularly for rural and regional communities dependent on fixed wireless broadband.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141130</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 09:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Utility Packages Enable Attackers to Wipe Production Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-npm-utility-packages-enable-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: Two malicious npm packages (express-api-sync and system-health-sync-api) were discovered by Socket's Threat Research Team. The packages, designed to masquerade as legitimate utilities, embed destructive backdoors that can annihilate production systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141127</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloTDS Malware Spread via FakeCaptcha Infrastructure Infects Millions of Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hellotds-malware-spread-via-fakecaptcha-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The HelloTDS (Traffic Direction System) infrastructure has been uncovered, delivering malicious campaigns to millions of users worldwide. It employs advanced fingerprinting techniques and social engineering to selectively target victims, infecting over 4.3 million devices in April and May 2025 alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141116</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Salesforce Vulnerability Exposes Global Users to SOQL Injection Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-salesforce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Salesforce Aura controller; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical SOQL injection vulnerability was discovered in a default Salesforce Aura controller, affecting potentially thousands of deployments and millions of user records. The vulnerability allowed for the extraction of sensitive data, such as user emails, names, addresses, and even password hashes, depending on the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141112</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Bans ChatGPT Accounts Used by Russian, Iranian and Chinese Hacker Groups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/openai-bans-chatgpt-accounts-used-by.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on multiple threat actors using ChatGPT accounts to develop malware, automate social media posts, research satellite communications technologies, and engage in other malicious activities. The account holders used temporary email addresses to sign up for ChatGPT, fine-tuned their code, and distributed AI-assisted malware through a publicly available code repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/openai-bans-chatgpt-accounts-used-by.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kali GPT – Revolutionizing Penetration Testing with AI on Kali Linux</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kali-gpt-revolutionizing/</link>
      <description>Kali GPT is an AI assistant specifically designed for the Kali Linux ecosystem, aimed at streamlining workflows, providing real-time insights, and automating capabilities for cybersecurity professionals. It uses natural language processing (NLP) to interact with users, offering contextual help, suggesting exploits or defensive measures, and generating technical instructions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141102</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky Strikes Again – Coordinated Attacks Target Facebook, Email, and Telegram</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-strikes/</link>
      <description>Kimsuky, a North Korea-aligned advanced persistent threat (APT) group, has been conducting a sophisticated cyber espionage campaign called "AppleSeed" since March to April 2025. The campaign targeted defense sector organizations, North Korea-related activists, and cryptocurrency exchanges, using social engineering and technical subterfuge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141090</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mirai botnet infect TBK DVR devices via command injection flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-mirai-botnet-infect-tbk-dvr-devices-via-command-injection-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TBK Vision DVR-4104 and DVR-4216; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3721; Summary: A command injection vulnerability (CVE-2024-3721) in TBK Vision's DVR-4104 and DVR-4216 digital video recording devices allows attackers to hijack devices using a specially crafted POST request. The exploit is being used by a new Mirai botnet variant to drop an ARM32 malware binary, which establishes communication with a command and control (C2) server to enlist the device in the botnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-mirai-botnet-infect-tbk-dvr-devices-via-command-injection-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Supply Chain Malware Operation Hits npm and PyPI Ecosystems, Targeting Millions Globally</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-supply-chain-malware-operation-hits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GlueStack packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports a supply chain attack targeting over a dozen packages associated with GlueStack, delivering malware that allows attackers to run shell commands, take screenshots, and upload files to infected machines. The impacted packages collectively account for nearly 1 million weekly downloads.

FYSA: This report highlights the emergence of threat actors focusing on system sabotage rather than financial gains, and their use of bogus libraries for information theft and credential harvesting. It also shows that attackers are leveraging email as a covert communication channel to blend in with legitimate application emails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-supply-chain-malware-operation-hits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals turn to “residential proxy” services to hide malicious traffic</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybercriminals-turn-to-residential-proxy-services-to-hide-malicious-traffic/</link>
      <description>Attackers have been increasingly using residential networks to mask their malicious activity, making it harder for organizations and law enforcement to detect and track suspicious traffic. This tactic uses decentralized platforms running on consumer hardware to reduce insight and control, allowing criminal actors to operate undetected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybercriminals-turn-to-residential-proxy-services-to-hide-malicious-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 11:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Browser Extensions Infect 722 Users Across Latin America Since Early 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/malicious-browser-extensions-infect-722.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GAS Tecnologia Warsaw; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious browser extension for Chromium-based web browsers was detected in a campaign targeting Brazilian users, allowing attackers to siphon user authentication data and potentially display loading screens or serve malicious QR codes on the bank's web page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/malicious-browser-extensions-infect-722.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain attack hits Gluestack NPM packages with 960K weekly downloads</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/supply-chain-attack-hits-gluestack-npm-packages-with-960k-weekly-downloads/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Gluestack "react-native-aria" packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A significant supply chain attack compromised 16 popular Gluestack packages on NPM, including over 950,000 weekly downloads. The malicious code acts as a remote access trojan (RAT), allowing attackers to execute commands and hijack systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/supply-chain-attack-hits-gluestack-npm-packages-with-960k-weekly-downloads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 19:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm packages posing as utilities delete project directories</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-packages-posing-as-utilities-delete-project-directories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm JavaScript package index; CVE(s): None; Summary: Two malicious packages, 'express-api-sync' and 'system-health-sync-api', were discovered in the npm JavaScript package index. These packages posed as database syncing and system health monitoring tools but contained backdoors that enabled remote data-wiping actions at infected hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-packages-posing-as-utilities-delete-project-directories/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of low-cost Android devices turn home networks into crime platforms</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/millions-of-low-cost-android-devices-turn-home-networks-into-crime-platforms/</link>
      <description>A coordinated effort by Google and others disrupted a new malware campaign, BadBox 2.0, affecting over 1 million off-brand Android devices not certified under Play Protect. The FBI warned consumers to evaluate their IoT devices for signs of compromise, such as automatic connections to malicious app markets or requests to disable Play Protect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/millions-of-low-cost-android-devices-turn-home-networks-into-crime-platforms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-331: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-331/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5036; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of RFA files due to a lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26852</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft shares script to restore inetpub folder you shouldn’t delete</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-script-to-restore-inetpub-folder-you-shouldnt-delete/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-21204, None; Summary: A high-severity Windows Process Activation privilege escalation vulnerability was mitigated by the creation of an empty "inetpub" folder. Removing this folder can make systems vulnerable again to the patched vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-shares-script-to-restore-inetpub-folder-you-shouldnt-delete/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax resolution firm Optima Tax Relief hit by ransomware, data leaked</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tax-resolution-firm-optima-tax-relief-hit-by-ransomware-data-leaked/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a Chaos ransomware attack against Optima Tax Relief, a US-based tax resolution firm. The attackers stole 69 GB of corporate and customer data, including sensitive personal information such as Social Security numbers, phone numbers, and home addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/tax-resolution-firm-optima-tax-relief-hit-by-ransomware-data-leaked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rust-Developed InfoStealer Drains Sensitive Data from Chromium-Based Browsers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-rust-developed-infostealer/</link>
      <description>RustStealer is an information-stealing malware designed to extract sensitive data from Chromium-based browsers such as Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge. It uses advanced obfuscation techniques, exploits unencrypted data stored in browser profiles, and can exfiltrate data to remote command-and-control servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141073</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leverage New ClickFix Tactic to Exploit Human Error with Deceptive Prompts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-leverage-new-clickfix-tactic-to-exploit-human-error/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated social engineering technique called ClickFix baiting has gained popularity among cybercriminals, targeting human end users as the weakest link in cybersecurity defenses. This method uses seemingly benign prompts to trick users into executing malicious commands, bypassing traditional security measures with ease. The attack chain involves spear phishing links, drive-by compromises, or fake CAPTCHA prompts that redirect users to malicious URLs, ultimately leading to the installation of malware families like XWorm, Lumma, and AsyncRAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141025</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Atomic macOS Stealer Campaign Exploits ClickFix to Target Apple Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-atomic-macos-stealer-campaign.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have detected a new malware campaign using the ClickFix social engineering tactic to distribute an information stealer malware, Atomic macOS Stealer (AMOS), on Apple macOS systems. The campaign leverages typosquat domains mimicking U.S.-based telecom provider Spectrum and tricks users into downloading the malware by serving malicious shell scripts designed to steal system passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-atomic-macos-stealer-campaign.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-326: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger MCU Command Parsing Misinterpretation of Input Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-326/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5747; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger devices. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the handling of command frames received by the MCU due to misinterpretation of input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26501</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-327: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger LAN OTA Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-327/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger; CVE(s): ZDI-25-327, ZDI-CAN-26349, CVE-2025-5748; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote code execution on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger through the exposure of a method for uploading crafted software images to the Tuya communications module. Although authentication is required, the existing mechanism can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26349</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-328: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger BLE Encryption Keys Uninitialized Variable Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-328/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5749; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger devices without requiring authentication. The specific flaw exists within the handling of cryptographic keys used in vendor-specific encrypted communications, resulting from an uninitialized variable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26295</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-329: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger tuya_svc_devos_activate_result_parse Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-329/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5750; Summary: The vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations without authentication. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26294</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Malicious GitHub Repos Targeting Novice Cybercriminals Traced to Single User</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hundreds-of-malicious-github-repos-targeting-novice-cybercriminals/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a campaign involving over 140 GitHub repositories laced with malicious backdoors orchestrated by a single threat actor. The backdoors employ four distinct types of backdoors, including PreBuild event scripts in Visual Basic project files, Python scripts, screensaver (.scr) files disguised as solution files, and JavaScript payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141010</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-330: (0Day) (Pwn2Own) WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger Management Card Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-330/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5751; Summary: This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of the WOLFBOX Level 2 EV Charger. The specific flaw exists within the handling of management cards, resulting from the lack of personalization of management cards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26292</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFix Attack Uses Fake Cloudflare Verification to Silently Deploy Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clickfix-attack-uses-fake-cloudflare-verification/</link>
      <description>A newly identified social engineering attack called "ClickFix" leverages fake Cloudflare verification pages to trick users into executing malicious code. The attack exploits user familiarity with Cloudflare's CAPTCHA interface, bypassing traditional security filters and delivering payloads such as info-stealers or remote access trojans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140996</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health confirms Interlock ransomware behind cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-confirms-interlock-ransomware-behind-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The Interlock ransomware group breached Kettering Health's network and stole sensitive information, including patient data, in a May cyberattack. The gang has been associated with other attacks on healthcare organizations and has deployed a previously unknown remote access trojan (RAT) called NodeSnake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-confirms-interlock-ransomware-behind-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonForce Ransomware Reportedly Compromised Over 120 Victims in the Past Year</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dragonforce-ransomware-reportedly-compromised-over-120-victims/</link>
      <description>DragonForce, a ransomware group, has claimed over 120 victims in the past year and is considered a critical threat to monitor in 2025. The group targets organizations across various industries using a calculated approach that includes exploiting vulnerabilities, phishing, credential stuffing, and leveraging legitimate tools for persistence and lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140982</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Fake AI Business Tools Spreading Hidden Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-ai-business-tools-spreading-hidden-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are deploying ransomware through deceptive campaigns targeting small businesses that adopt artificial intelligence (AI) tools. Attackers create fake websites and software installers that mimic popular AI services, leading to the installation of malware such as CyberLock, Lucky_Gh0$t, or Numero, which can render systems unusable or demand payment in cryptocurrency.

FYSA: Cybercriminals are capitalizing on the AI boom by targeting small businesses with ransomware attacks, posing a dual risk of immediate system compromise and long-term damage to confidence in digital tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140946</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PathWiper data wiper malware hits critical infrastructure in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-pathwiper-data-wiper-malware-hits-critical-infrastructure-in-ukraine/</link>
      <description>PathWiper is a newly discovered data wiper malware used in targeted attacks against critical infrastructure in Ukraine, aimed at disrupting operations. The payload was deployed through a legitimate endpoint administration tool and has similar functionality to HermeticWiper, previously deployed by the 'Sandworm' threat group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-pathwiper-data-wiper-malware-hits-critical-infrastructure-in-ukraine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Hackers Target Tech Company Help-Desk Administrators</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scattered-spider-hackers-target-tech-company/</link>
      <description>The Scattered Spider hacking group has launched a targeted campaign against help-desk administrators at major technology companies, using advanced social engineering techniques and APT methodologies to breach corporate defenses. The attackers leverage phishing, credential stuffing, and impersonation tactics to gain unauthorized access to critical systems, often exploiting human vulnerabilities as effectively as technical ones. This campaign highlights the importance of robust employee training, multi-factor authentication protocols, and continuous monitoring to detect anomalous behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140972</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mirai Variant Exploits TBK DVR Flaw for Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mirai-variant-exploits-tbk-dvr-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TBK DVR-4104 and DVR-4216 devices; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3721; Summary: A critical command injection vulnerability (CVE-2024-3721) in TBK DVR-4104 and DVR-4216 devices allows attackers to exploit unpatched firmware, deploy a modified Mirai variant designed for IoT device hijacking and DDoS operations, and execute ARM32 binaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=141005</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Unveils European Security Effort to Disrupt Cybercrime Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-unveils-european-security-effort/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows NTFS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24993; Summary: A critical heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the Windows NTFS allows attackers to execute arbitrary code with local user privileges by crafting malicious VHD files and mounting them. The exploit requires social engineering or misleading users into believing the file is safe, and successful exploitation can result in privilege escalation, system compromise, data exfiltration, service disruption, and lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140970</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViperSoftX Malware Used by Threat Actors to Steal Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vipersoftx-malware-used-by-threat-actor/</link>
      <description>ViperSoftX is a sophisticated PowerShell-based malware designed to infiltrate infected systems, execute remote commands, steal sensitive data, and target cryptocurrency-related information. It employs deceptive tactics, abuses Windows Task Scheduler, and communicates with C&amp;C servers using HTTP headers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140954</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Fortinet flaws now exploited in Qilin ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-fortinet-flaws-now-exploited-in-qilin-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2024-21762, CVE-2024-55591; Summary: The Qilin ransomware operation is exploiting two Fortinet vulnerabilities (CVE-2024-21762 and CVE-2024-55591) to bypass authentication on vulnerable devices and execute malicious code remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/critical-fortinet-flaws-now-exploited-in-qilin-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empower Users and Protect Against GenAI Data Loss</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/empower-users-and-protect-against-genai.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the increasing use of generative AI tools in the enterprise setting, despite attempts to block public AI apps. Employees have found workarounds to access AI systems, which creates a "Shadow AI" blind spot for organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/empower-users-and-protect-against-genai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Helps CBI Dismantle Indian Call Centers Behind Japanese Tech Support Scam</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-helps-cbi-dismantle-indian.html</link>
      <description>India's Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) has dismantled two illegal call centers engaged in a transnational tech support scam targeting Japanese citizens, arresting four individuals and seizing evidence. The scam involved advanced social engineering techniques and "technical subterfuge" to deceive victims into transferring funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-helps-cbi-dismantle-indian.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Offers $10M Bounty for Information on RedLine Malware Creator</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/u-s-offers-10m-bounty/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability. Instead, it discusses the RedLine infostealer malware and its alleged developer, Maxim Alexandrovich Rudometov, who is being sought with a $10 million reward under the Rewards for Justice program. The article details the malware's features, including configuration and C2 communication, host profiling, data exfiltration, remote execution and persistence, and anti-analysis measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140965</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANY.RUN Empowers Government Agencies with Real-Time Threat Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/any-run-empowers-government/</link>
      <description>Government agencies worldwide are facing an unprecedented wave of cyberattacks, with attackers employing advanced tactics to breach critical infrastructure and steal sensitive data. The most prevalent attack vector remains phishing emails, with spoofed domains and malicious attachments being used to deliver malware such as FormBook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140944</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical RCE Vulnerability in AWS Amplify Studio – PoC Now Public</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rce-vulnerability-in-aws-amplify-studio/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: @aws-amplify/codegen-ui; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4318; Summary: The AWS Amplify codegen package contained a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability due to improper input validation in expression-binding logic. The flaw allowed attackers to inject malicious expressions into component JSON files, enabling arbitrary code execution on backend build systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140936</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Mind of the Adversary: Why More Security Leaders Are Selecting AEV</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/inside-mind-of-adversary-why-more.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV), an advanced offense technology that simulates real-world attacker behaviors to identify vulnerabilities in an organization's defenses. AEV provides continuous and automated testing, allowing for more efficient prioritization and remediation of security issues. The technology is designed to mimic how attackers would exploit weaknesses, enabling organizations to build resilience against attacks and provide a stronger defense posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/inside-mind-of-adversary-why-more.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blitz Malware: A Tale of Game Cheats and Code Repositories</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/blitz-malware-2025/</link>
      <description>The article provides a detailed technical analysis of Blitz malware, which consists of two phases: the Blitz downloader and the Blitz bot. The malware was distributed through backdoored game cheats, and it abused Hugging Face to host C2 infrastructure. The author claims to have quit distributing the malware.

The article highlights the security risks associated with engaging in illegal software distribution, including cracked game cheats. It also provides information on how Palo Alto Networks customers can be better protected from Blitz malware through various security features and subscriptions.

In summary, this article is not discussing a vulnerability (software, hardware, or firmware), but rather providing threat intelligence and analysis of the Blitz malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=142254</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 10:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP Flaw Allows Code Execution or System Crash</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-freertos-plus-tcp-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5688; Summary: A critical memory corruption vulnerability exists in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP due to the lack of adequate length checking when processing LLMNR and mDNS queries with excessively long DNS names. This can lead to system crashes or arbitrary code execution, making embedded systems a high-value target for attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140917</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Extensions Flaw Exposes Sensitive API Keys, Secrets and Tokens</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-extensions-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Chrome Extensions; CVE(s): None; Summary: Numerous popular Chrome extensions contain a critical security flaw that exposes sensitive credentials such as API keys, secrets, and tokens in their source code, allowing attackers to exploit them and potentially cause data manipulation, financial losses, and privacy breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140918</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical RCE Flaw Found in HPE Insight Remote Support Tool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-rce-flaw-found/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett-Packard Enterprise (HPE) Insight Remote Support; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37097, CVE-2025-37098, and CVE-2025-37099; Summary: Multiple high-impact vulnerabilities in HPE's Insight Remote Support (IRS) software allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, traverse directories, and exfiltrate sensitive information. The flaws are due to directory traversal and XML external entity (XXE) injection in the IRS service's file upload mechanism and XML input processing during device registration. Successful exploitation can result in full remote code execution under the privileges of the IRS service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140884</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 09:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrests 20 suspects for distributing child sexual abuse content</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-arrests-20-suspects-for-distributing-child-sexual-abuse-content/</link>
      <description>Law enforcement authorities from over a dozen countries have arrested 20 suspects in an international operation targeting the production and distribution of child sexual abuse material. The operation, which started in late 2024, involved multiple instant messaging groups dedicated to the circulation of child sexual exploitation images. Additionally, another joint international investigation led by the State Criminal Police of Bavaria and Bavarian cybercrime prosecutors took down Kidflix, one of the largest child sexual abuse material platforms on the dark web.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-arrests-20-suspects-for-distributing-child-sexual-abuse-content/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New pathWiper Malware Targets Critical Infrastructure to Deploy Admin Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-pathwiper-malware-targets-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>This article reports a sophisticated cyberattack targeting Ukrainian critical infrastructure, deploying a previously unknown wiper malware dubbed "PathWiper." The attack is attributed to a Russia-nexus advanced persistent threat (APT) actor and showcases the evolving threat to Ukrainian critical infrastructure amid the ongoing conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140897</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PathWiper Data Wiper Malware Disrupts Ukrainian Critical Infrastructure in 2025 Attack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-pathwiper-data-wiper-malware.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a new data wiper malware named PathWiper that was used to target a critical infrastructure entity in Ukraine. The malware is designed to gather information about connected storage media, create threads for each drive and volume, and overwrite contents with randomized bytes. It also targets specific file systems and attempts to dismount volumes.

FYSA: A Russia-nexus advanced persistent threat (APT) actor has been identified as the perpetrator of a new data wiper malware attack on Ukraine, using legitimate endpoint administration frameworks to issue malicious commands and deploy PathWiper across connected endpoints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-pathwiper-data-wiper-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BADBOX 2.0 Malware Hits Over a Million Android Devices in Global Cyber Threat</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/badbox-2-0-malware-hits-over-a-million-android-devices/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a massive cyber fraud operation named BADBOX 2.0, which has infected over 1 million Android Open Source Project (AOSP) devices worldwide. The operation is attributed to four key threat actor groups working together through shared C2 infrastructure, and involves fraudulent activities such as ad fraud, click fraud, and the sale of residential proxy services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140885</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paste.ee Turned Cyber Weapon: XWorm and AsyncRAT Delivered by Malicious Actors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/paste-ee-turned-cyber-weapon/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new trend in phishing and malware delivery where attackers use the text-sharing website Paste.ee to host malicious payloads and scripts, often disguised as innocuous text snippets. This tactic allows threat actors to bypass traditional security defenses by exploiting the platform's accessibility and anonymity features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140870</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Released for Apache Tomcat DoS Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-tomcat-dos-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31650; Summary: A critical memory leak vulnerability in Apache Tomcat's HTTP/2 implementation allows unauthenticated denial-of-service attacks through malformed priority headers. The flaw affects Tomcat versions 9.0.76–9.0.102, 10.1.10–10.1.39, and 11.0.0-M2–11.0.5, and public exploits are already circulating.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Roundcube Vulnerability to Steal User Credentials via XSS Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-roundcube-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube; CVE(s): CVE-2024-42009, None; Summary: The Roundcube webmail platform has a critical Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability (CVE-2024-42009) that allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code, enabling credential theft and potential server takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140861</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s upcoming Gemini Kingfall is allegedly a coding beast</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/googles-upcoming-gemini-kingfall-is-allegedly-a-coding-beast/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article discusses the advancements in Google's AI models, specifically the "Gemini Kingfall" model that was briefly available before being taken down. It highlights the capabilities of Gemini Kingfall, such as generating a working single HTML file Minecraft game clone using a three-line prompt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/googles-upcoming-gemini-kingfall-is-allegedly-a-coding-beast/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 23:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT prepares o3-pro model for $200 Pro subscribers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-prepares-o3-pro-model-for-200-pro-subscribers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article does not mention any vulnerabilities. It discusses updates to ChatGPT models, including the new o3 Pro model, and their capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-prepares-o3-pro-model-for-200-pro-subscribers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proxy Services Feast on Ukraine’s IP Address Exodus</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/proxy-services-feast-on-ukraines-ip-address-exodus/</link>
      <description>The article discusses how Ukraine's Internet Protocol Version 4 (IPv4) address space has been affected by the Russian invasion. Many Ukrainian ISPs have sold or leased their IPv4 address blocks to proxy and anonymity services, which are now being used to route traffic from multiple countries, including those with a high incidence of cybercrime activity. This has resulted in many former Ukrainian IP addresses being used in cyberattacks against Ukraine and other enemies of Russia.

FYSA: The article highlights the vulnerability of Ukraine's Internet infrastructure to Russian control or manipulation, as well as the potential for proxy services to be abused for malicious purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71386</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: BADBOX 2.0 Android malware infects millions of consumer devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-badbox-20-android-malware-infects-millions-of-consumer-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BADBOX 2.0; CVE(s): None; Summary: The BADBOX 2.0 malware campaign has infected over 1 million home Internet-connected devices, converting consumer electronics into residential proxies used for malicious activity, such as ad fraud and credential stuffing. The malware infects devices preloaded with the botnet or through malicious Android applications that sneak onto Google Play and third-party app stores.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-badbox-20-android-malware-infects-millions-of-consumer-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian APT ‘BladedFeline’ Remains Hidden in Networks for 8 Years</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-apt-bladedfeline-remains-hidden/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the activities of BladedFeline, an Iranian-aligned Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group that has maintained covert access to the networks of Kurdish and Iraqi government officials for nearly eight years. The group uses various tools and techniques, including backdoors, reverse shells, and custom tunneling tools, to exploit vulnerabilities and exfiltrate data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140811</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-325: Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support processAttachmentDataStream Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-325/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37099; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations without authentication. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25954</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Chaos RAT Targets Linux and Windows Users to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-chaos-rat-targets-linux-and-windows-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Chaos RAT; CVE(s): CVE-2024-30850, CVE-2024-31839; Summary: Chaos RAT is a remote administration tool that allows attackers to deploy payloads across diverse systems. The latest variants target both Linux and Windows environments with sophisticated capabilities for espionage and data exfiltration. A critical vulnerability in its web panel (CVE-2024-30850) allows remote code execution on the server itself, while an XSS issue (CVE-2024-31839) underscores its dual-edged nature as a tool for attackers and a potential target for counter-exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140796</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViperSoftX Malware Enhances Modularity, Stealth, and Persistence Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vipersoftx-malware-enhances-modularity/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new variant of the ViperSoftX stealer malware that uses PowerShell and showcases advancements in modularity, stealth, and persistence mechanisms. It targets cryptocurrency users and enterprises, and its features include enhanced operational security, dynamic adaptability, and persistence mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140782</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Accuses Taiwan of Operating APT Groups with US Support</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/china-accuses-taiwan-of-operating-apt-groups/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article reports on Chinese allegations of Taiwan-based Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) groups conducting long-term cyber espionage and sabotage against critical infrastructure, government bodies, and key industries in China, Hong Kong, and Macao. These groups are accused of stealing sensitive intelligence, collaborating with the US government, and using tactics such as phishing campaigns, exploiting known vulnerabilities, and deploying open-source tools for initial access and persistence.

FYSA: The article discusses the alleged activities of Taiwan-based APT groups, referred to as "T-APTs," which are claimed to be supported by Taiwan's Information, Communications and Electronic Force Command (ICEFCOM) and have close ties with the United States. These groups are accused of conducting cyber warfare, public opinion manipulation, and cognitive warfare against China, acting as proxies for a so-called "color revolution."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140818</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone's on the cyber target list</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/everyones-on-the-cyber-target-list/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but it contains cybersecurity-relevant content. The summary should focus on threat actors, tactics, infrastructure, scams, or impacts.

FYSA: The article discusses the importance of cybersecurity awareness and the need for basic cyber hygiene. It highlights the fact that anyone can be a victim of a cyber attack and emphasizes the importance of ensuring endpoint security, monitoring for unusual administrative activity, and staying informed on evolving threats to mitigate potential risks. Additionally, the article mentions various cybersecurity-related events and conferences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68409ed526e1af0001c783cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Fake Zoom Client Downloads Granting Attackers Access to Your Computer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-fake-zoom-client-downloads-granting-attackers/</link>
      <description>This article describes a phishing campaign that exploits the popularity of Zoom by tricking users into downloading malicious software under the guise of a legitimate update. The attack begins with a fake Zoom meeting invitation and ultimately installs a malware payload that grants attackers unrestricted access to the compromised system, allowing for data theft, ransomware deployment, or further network infiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140770</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old AT&amp;T data leak repackaged to link SSNs, DOBs to 49M phone numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/old-atandt-data-leak-repackaged-to-link-ssns-dobs-to-49m-phone-numbers/</link>
      <description>A threat actor has re-released data from a 2021 AT&amp;T breach affecting 70 million customers, combining previously separate files to directly link Social Security numbers and birth dates to individual users. The leaked data is actually from the same 2021 breach that exposed 73 million customers' information, not a new leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/old-atandt-data-leak-repackaged-to-link-ssns-dobs-to-49m-phone-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Admins Cautioned About Fake Cache Plugin Stealing Admin Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wordpress-admins-cautioned-about-fake-cache-plugin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WordPress; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious plugin dubbed "wp-runtime-cache" targets WordPress sites to steal admin credentials. The plugin hides in the wp-content/plugins directory and activates during site login events, capturing user input and exfiltrating sensitive data to a remote server. It specifically targets high-privilege users and employs code obfuscation techniques to remain undetected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140751</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker selling critical Roundcube webmail exploit as tech info disclosed</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-selling-critical-roundcube-webmail-exploit-as-tech-info-disclosed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49113, CVE-2025-48745 (rejected as duplicate candidate); Summary: A critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-49113) exists in Roundcube open-source webmail application versions 1.1.0 through 1.6.10. The vulnerability allows attackers to execute malicious code after authentication, and an exploit is already available for sale on underground forums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-selling-critical-roundcube-webmail-exploit-as-tech-info-disclosed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Chrome Extensions Leak API Keys, User Data via HTTP and Hardcoded Credentials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/popular-chrome-extensions-leak-api-keys.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple Google Chrome extensions; CVE(s): None; Summary: Several popular Google Chrome extensions have been found to transmit sensitive data in HTTP, exposing users to privacy and security risks. The extensions hard-code secrets in their code, making them susceptible to adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) attacks, allowing malicious actors on the same network to intercept and modify the transmitted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/popular-chrome-extensions-leak-api-keys.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build a robust Windows service to block malware and ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-build-a-robust-windows-service-to-block-malware-and-ransomware/</link>
      <description>This article discusses designing a security-focused Windows Service with principles such as minimal attack surface, real-time monitoring and response, robustness and resilience, scalability and performance. It also explores the components involved in building a robust security service, including monitoring engine, analysis and detection module, response and mitigation unit, logging and reporting, and communication interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-build-a-robust-windows-service-to-block-malware-and-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Windows Service for Security</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-a-windows-service-for-security/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of designing a robust Windows Service with minimal attack surface, real-time monitoring, and response capabilities. It highlights five key design principles for developing an effective Windows Service: minimizing attack surface, real-time monitoring and response, robustness and resilience, scalability and performance, and logging and reporting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/designing-a-windows-service-for-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Detail Bitter APT’s Evolving Tactics as Its Geographic Scope Expands</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bitter-hacker-group-expands-cyber.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the threat actor Bitter, also known as APT-C-08, APT-Q-37, Hazy Tiger, Orange Yali, T-APT-17, and TA397. It is a state-backed hacking group that targets governments, diplomatic entities, and defense organizations to gather intelligence aligned with the interests of the Indian government. The group uses spear-phishing emails and masquerades as government and diplomatic entities from various countries to entice recipients into malware-laced attachments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bitter-hacker-group-expands-cyber.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odoo Employee Database Allegedly Exposed and Put Up for Sale on Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/odoo-database-allegedly-exposed/</link>
      <description>A data breach at Odoo, a Belgian provider of open-source business management software, has reportedly occurred. The breach allegedly involves a compromised employee database, with the seller demanding $25,000 in cryptocurrency for its release. The incident highlights the persistent threat posed by insiders in enterprise environments, emphasizing the importance of robust access controls and vigilant monitoring of privileged accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140748</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of ViLE Hacker Group Arrested for Hacking DEA Portal</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vile-hacker-group-arrested/</link>
      <description>Two members of the ViLE cybercriminal group were sentenced for a high-profile hacking and extortion scheme targeting a U.S. federal law enforcement web portal. The group specialized in "doxing" and used stolen credentials, impersonation, and social engineering tactics to obtain sensitive personal data and extort victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140747</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Dell PowerScale Vulnerability Allows Attackers Unauthorized Access to Filesystem</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-dell-powerscale-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dell Technologies PowerScale OneFS; CVE(s): CVE-2024-53298, CVE-2025-32753; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2024-53298) allows unauthenticated remote attackers to gain unauthorized access to the file system, potentially enabling them to read, modify, or delete arbitrary files. Another vulnerability (CVE-2025-32753) is an SQL injection issue that can be triggered by sending specially crafted requests to the affected application, allowing a low-privileged local attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140746</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TA397 Hackers Exploits Scheduled Tasks to Deploy Malware on Targeted Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ta397-hackers-exploits-scheduled-tasks-to-deploy-malware/</link>
      <description>A suspected state-backed threat actor, TA397 (also known as Bitter), has been identified by Proofpoint Threat Research. The group is believed to be aligned with Indian intelligence interests and targets entities in Europe and Asia, particularly those connected to China, Pakistan, and the Indian subcontinent. Their tactics include spearphishing, scheduled tasks for malware deployment, and manual payload delivery, showcasing adaptability and consistency in evading detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140714</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/05/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chromium V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5419; Summary: This out-of-bounds read and write vulnerability in Google Chromium V8 poses significant risks to the federal enterprise, as it is a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors. The vulnerability has been added to CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23475</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Seven Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/05/cisa-releases-seven-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>This article does not describe a specific vulnerability, but rather announces the release of seven Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories by CISA. These advisories provide information about current security issues and vulnerabilities in various ICS products from Hitachi Energy and Mitsubishi Electric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23479</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670, 650 Series and SAM600-IO Product</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-155-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670, Relion 650, SAM600-IO; CVE(s): CVE-2020-28895, CVE-2020-35198; Summary: Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerabilities in the memory allocator of Wind River VxWorks allow an attacker to cause memory corruption on affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23478</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberData 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-155-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CyberData Equipment 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30184, CVE-2025-26468, CVE-2025-30507, CVE-2025-30183, CVE-2025-30515; Summary: The 011209 SIP Emergency Intercom has multiple vulnerabilities, including authentication bypass, SQL injection, insufficiently protected credentials, and path traversal. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information, cause a denial-of-service condition, or achieve code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23477</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware NSX XSS Vulnerability Exposes Systems to Malicious Code Injection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-nsx-xss-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware NSX; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22243, CVE-2025-22244, and CVE-2025-22245; Summary: Three stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities were discovered in VMware NSX, affecting the NSX Manager UI, gateway firewall, and router port components. Authenticated attackers can inject malicious scripts that execute when affected interfaces are viewed by other users, exposing organizations to potential code injection attacks if left unpatched.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140694</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit New HTML Trick to Deceive Outlook Users into Clicking Malicious Links</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-new-html-trick-to-deceive-outlook-users/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals have employed a sophisticated phishing email campaign targeting Czech bank customers, using HTML conditional statements to exploit differences in email client rendering and bypass security measures. The tactic displays different links based on the email client or browser used, potentially tricking users into clicking malicious links. This approach highlights the attackers' understanding of user behavior and corporate security landscapes, emphasizing the importance of staying vigilant against evolving cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140700</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wireshark Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wireshark-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wireshark; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5601; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) by injecting malformed packets onto a network or by convincing a user to open a specially crafted capture file. The flaw stems from a bug in the column utility module used by Wireshark's dissectors, which can be triggered during live packet capture or when analyzing saved packet trace files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140723</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>830 Organizations Hacked via Glitch-hosted Phishing Attack Uses Telegram &amp; Fake CAPTCHAs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/830-organizations-hacked-via-glitch-hosted-phishing-attack/</link>
      <description>Netskope Threat Labs reported a significant increase in traffic to phishing pages hosted on the Glitch platform, targeting over 830 organizations and 3,000 users. The campaigns use sophisticated techniques, including Telegram's BotAPI for exfiltrating stolen data and custom-built fake CAPTCHAs to evade security tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140682</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany fines Vodafone $51 million for privacy, security breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-fines-vodafone-51-million-for-privacy-security-breaches/</link>
      <description>The article reports that Vodafone GmbH, a German subsidiary of the telecommunications company Vodafone, was fined €45 million for privacy and security violations. The fines were imposed due to malicious employees in partner agencies who brokered contracts with customers on behalf of Vodafone, resulting in fraud cases. Additionally, the company's MeinVodafone and hotline authentication vulnerabilities allowed attackers to access customer eSIM profiles.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-fines-vodafone-51-million-for-privacy-security-breaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Cyber Value: Why Business Impact Should Lead the Security Conversation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/redefining-cyber-value-why-business.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of a Business Value Assessment (BVA) for organizations to better understand their cybersecurity posture and financial exposure. It highlights the disconnect between security metrics and business outcomes, and how a BVA can bridge this gap by linking exposures to cost, prioritization to return, and prevention to tangible value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/redefining-cyber-value-why-business.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher Found 6 Critical Vulnerabilities in NetMRI Allow Attackers Gain Complete Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researcher-found-6-critical-vulnerabilities-in-netmri/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Infoblox NetMRI; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32813, CVE-2025-32814, CVE-2025-32815, CVE-2024-54188, CVE-2024-52874; Summary: Six critical vulnerabilities have been identified in Infoblox's NetMRI version 7.5.4.104695, including unauthenticated command injection, hardcoded credentials, arbitrary file read, and SQL injection flaws that can lead to complete administrative access and compromise of entire network infrastructures if exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140660</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran-Linked BladedFeline Hits Iraqi and Kurdish Targets with Whisper and Spearal Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-linked-bladedfeline-hits-iraqi-and.html</link>
      <description>None (This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather an Iran-aligned hacking group's cyber attacks targeting Kurdish and Iraqi government officials.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-linked-bladedfeline-hits-iraqi-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC6040 APT Hackers Steals Salesforce data Without Exploit Any Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/unc6040-apt-hackers-steals-salesforce-data/</link>
      <description>UNC6040 threat cluster uses voice phishing (vishing) campaigns to compromise Salesforce environments by manipulating human behavior and impersonating IT support personnel, leading to large-scale data theft and extortion attempts. The campaign relies on tricking victims into authorizing a malicious connected app, often using modified versions of Salesforce's Data Loader tool, and leveraging infrastructure like Mullvad VPN IPs and Okta phishing panels for lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140639</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IMC Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Gain Elevated Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-imc-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20261; Summary: A critical privilege escalation vulnerability in the IMC software allows an authenticated, remote attacker to gain elevated privileges and unauthorized access to internal services via SSH, potentially leading to full system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140654</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoJ Seizes 145 Domains Tied to BidenCash Carding Marketplace in Global Takedown</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/doj-seizes-145-domains-tied-to.html</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) seized cryptocurrency funds and domains associated with the illicit carding marketplace BidenCash, which allegedly supported over 117,000 customers, trafficked over 15 million payment card numbers, and generated $17 million in revenue. The platform specialized in selling compromised credentials and offered SSH services to buyers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/doj-seizes-145-domains-tied-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly identified wiper malware “PathWiper” targets critical infrastructure in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/pathwiper-targets-ukraine/</link>
      <description>The article describes a destructive attack on Ukrainian critical infrastructure, attributed to a Russia-nexus advanced persistent threat (APT) actor. The attack used a previously unknown wiper malware called "PathWiper" that was deployed via a legitimate endpoint administration framework. PathWiper overwrites file system artifacts and destroys files by writing random bytes to disk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">683efe9726e1af0001c7835f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViLE gang members sentenced for extortion, police portal breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vile-gang-members-sentenced-for-breaching-law-enforcement-portal/</link>
      <description>Two members of the cybercriminal group ViLE were sentenced for hacking into a federal law enforcement web portal and using obtained personal information to harass, threaten, or extort victims. The group used methods such as impersonation, fraudulent legal requests, bribing corporate insiders, and searching public and private online databases to collect sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vile-gang-members-sentenced-for-breaching-law-enforcement-portal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases TTPs &amp; IoCs for Play Ransomware That Hacked 900+ Orgs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-releases-ttps-iocs-for-play-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), FBI, and Australian Signals Directorate's Australian Cyber Security Centre (ASD’s ACSC) have released detailed Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures (TTPs) and Indicators of Compromise (IoCs) for the Play ransomware group. The report highlights the group's tactics, including exploiting vulnerabilities in public-facing applications, abusing valid accounts, and using tools like AdFind and Grixba to gain domain administrator access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140630</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Patches Severe Flaws in ISE (CVE-2025-20286) &amp; Other Products; PoC Exploits Confirmed for Some</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cisco-flaws-in-ise-cve-2025-20286-poc-exploits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20286; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Cisco ISE allows an unauthenticated attacker to access sensitive data, perform limited administrative tasks, modify configurations, or disrupt services. The vulnerability affects cloud deployments and has a CVSS score of 9.9, with proof-of-concept exploit code available.

Vulnerable Product: Cisco Integrated Management Controllers (IMC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20261; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in the Cisco IMC allows an authenticated attacker to elevate privileges on various UCS platforms, including Blade Servers, S-Series and C-Series Servers, and X-Series Modular Systems. The attacker can exploit SSH misconfigurations to gain unauthorized access to internal services and create new admin accounts.

Vulnerable Product: Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20163; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in the Cisco NDFC allows an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack to impersonate a managed device and intercept sensitive traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100060833</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Cisco Nexus Dashboard Vulnerability Lets Attackers Impersonate Managed Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-cisco-nexus-dashboard-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20163; Summary: The NDFC suffers from a critical SSH host key validation vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to impersonate managed devices. This enables MitM attacks on SSH connections, posing significant risks to data center infrastructure and potentially compromising user credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140653</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Alerts Users to Critical ISE Vulnerability Exposing Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-alerts-ise-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20286; Summary: The ISE vulnerability occurs when deployed on AWS, Azure, or OCI, allowing attackers to access other ISE instances with the same software release and platform using extracted credentials. This can lead to unauthorized access, data exposure, configuration changes, and service disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=140627</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
