<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Access Brokers Target Brazil Execs via NF-e Spam and Legit RMM Trials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/initial-access-brokers-target-brazil.html</link>
      <description>A new campaign targeting Portuguese-speaking users in Brazil uses trial versions of commercial remote monitoring and management (RMM) software as a lure to trick users into clicking on malicious content hosted in Dropbox. The attack chain begins with spam emails claiming to originate from financial institutions or cell phone carriers, warning of overdue bills or outstanding payments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/initial-access-brokers-target-brazil.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying AI Agents? Learn to Secure Them Before Hackers Strike Your Business</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deploying-ai-agents-learn-to-secure.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the growing concern about the security risks associated with AI agents, highlighting potential threats such as data leaks, identity theft, and malicious misuse. It emphasizes the need for companies to ensure the secure use of AI agents, citing their ability to work with sensitive data and make real-time decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deploying-ai-agents-learn-to-secure.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Packages Infect 3,200+ Cursor Users With Backdoor, Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-npm-packages-infect-3200.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm packages "sw-cur", "sw-cur1", and "aiide-cur"; CVE(s): None; Summary: Three malicious npm packages designed to target Apple macOS version of Cursor AI-powered source code editor steal user credentials, fetch encrypted payload, overwrite main.js file, and disable auto-updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-npm-packages-infect-3200.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealthy .NET Malware: Hiding Malicious Payloads as Bitmap Resources</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/malicious-payloads-as-bitmap-resources-hide-net-malware/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using steganography within bitmap resources embedded in 32-bit .NET applications to hide malicious payloads, creating a multi-stage chain of extracting, deobfuscating, loading and executing secondary payloads (dynamic-link libraries) eventually detonating the final payload (executable). This technique is used to evade detection and successfully execute popular malware families such as Agent Tesla variants, XLoader, and Remcos RAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=140363</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Vulnerability Management – Can You CVE What I CVE?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/beyond-vulnerability-management-cves.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges of vulnerability management, highlighting the reactive nature of current approaches. It proposes a shift from "vulnerability management" to "Threat Mitigation," focusing on risk reduction rather than reacting to individual vulnerabilities. The authors introduce the Exploit Prediction Scoring System (EPSS) and demonstrate its application in prioritizing vulnerabilities. They also emphasize the importance of considering threat actors' skills, persistence, and scalability when assessing risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/beyond-vulnerability-management-cves.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Host Header Injection to Breach Web Applications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-host-header-injection/</link>
      <description>A significant rise in web breaches has been reported due to Host Header Injection, a lesser-known technique. Hackers manipulate the HTTP Host header to compromise web applications, steal sensitive information, and manipulate website operations by injecting malicious values into the Host header, which can lead to exploits such as password reset poisoning, cache poisoning, and cross-site scripting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134412</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Windows Remote Management to Evade Detection in AD Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-windows-remote-management/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WinRM; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers are exploiting Windows Remote Management (WinRM) to move laterally and evade detection across enterprise networks. They use stolen or brute-forced credentials, execute commands that appear as routine administrative tasks, and hide their activity by spawning fresh processes under the user's context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134395</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Remote Code Execution Flaw in macOS – CVE-2024-44236</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-uncover-remote-code-execution-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS Scriptable Image Processing System (sips); CVE(s): CVE-2024-44236; Summary: A memory corruption vulnerability in sips allows arbitrary code execution via maliciously crafted ICC profile files. The flaw stems from improper validation of lutAToBType and lutBToAType tags, leading to out-of-bounds writes in heap memory that can be exploited by submitting a malformed ICC profile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache ActiveMQ Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Induce DoS Condition</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-activemq-vulnerability-allows-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache ActiveMQ; CVE(s): CVE-2024-XXXX; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Apache ActiveMQ allows attackers to exhaust system memory through specially crafted OpenWire commands, leading to denial-of-service (DoS) attacks. The flaw affects multiple legacy versions of the messaging platform and can be exploited by transmitting manipulated OpenWire packets containing excessively large buffer size values, forcing vulnerable brokers to allocate disproportionate memory resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133890</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaspersky Alerts on AI-Driven Slopsquatting as Emerging Supply Chain Threat</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kaspersky-alerts-on-ai-driven-slopsquatting/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a newly identified supply chain vulnerability called "slopsquatting" that emerges from the widespread adoption of AI-generated code. This phenomenon involves AI systems hallucinating non-existent software dependencies, which attackers can exploit by creating malicious packages with these phantom names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133866</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Government to Shift Away from Passwords in New Security Move</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uk-government-to-shift-away-from-passwords/</link>
      <description>The UK government plans to implement passkey technology across its digital services, aiming to enhance security and provide a more streamlined user experience. Passkeys are unique digital credentials linked to specific devices, eliminating the need for secondary verification codes sent via text message. This approach is expected to save several million pounds annually while strengthening national digital defenses against sophisticated cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133803</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Dismantles DDoS-for-Hire Network and Arrests Four Administrators</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/europol-dismantles-ddos-for-hire-network/</link>
      <description>Four individuals in Poland were arrested for allegedly operating six DDoS-for-hire platforms, responsible for thousands of attacks between 2022 and 2025. The platforms featured user-friendly interfaces and allowed customers to launch attacks without technical expertise, with prices starting at €10. The operation, part of "Operation PowerOFF," was a major disruption to the commercial DDoS marketplace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133773</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play Ransomware Deployed in the Wild Exploiting Windows 0-Day Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/play-ransomware-deployed-in-the-wild/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29824; Summary: The Common Log File System (CLFS) driver in Windows contains a use-after-free condition that enables privilege escalation. Attackers exploited this vulnerability to deploy the Grixba infostealer, establish persistence mechanisms, and evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133745</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Advanced Phishing Attack Exploits Discord to Target Crypto Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-advanced-phishing-attack-exploits-discord/</link>
      <description>Check Point Research has uncovered a sophisticated phishing campaign that leverages Discord to target cryptocurrency users. The attack redirects victims from legitimate Web3 websites to a fake Collab.Land bot and then to a phishing site, ultimately tricking them into signing malicious transactions. The campaign is linked to the notorious Inferno Drainer, which has continued operations despite publicly announcing its shutdown in late 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133692</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Linux Joins the Windows Subsystem for Linux Officially</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fedora-linux-joins-the-windows-subsystem/</link>
      <description>Fedora Linux is now available on the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), allowing users to seamlessly integrate Fedora's cutting-edge tools and development environment directly into Windows. The integration empowers developers to leverage Fedora's robust package management and software repositories while maintaining compatibility with Windows workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133667</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Rolls Out On-Device AI Protections to Detect Scams in Chrome and Android</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-rolls-out-on-device-ai.html</link>
      <description>Google is rolling out AI-powered countermeasures to combat scams across Chrome, Search, and Android. The tech giant will use its Gemini Nano large language model (LLM) to improve Safe Browsing in Chrome 137 on desktops, detecting remote tech support scams and other types of schemes. Additionally, Google has enhanced its AI-powered scam detection systems, reducing deceptive pages by over 80% and government service impersonation schemes by over 70%.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-rolls-out-on-device-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit SAP RCE Flaw CVE-2025-31324, Deploy Golang-Based SuperShell</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-sap-rce-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A recently disclosed vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver allows attackers to achieve remote code execution (RCE) by uploading web shells through a susceptible "/developmentserver/metadatauploader" endpoint. The vulnerability, with a CVSS score of 10.0, has been exploited by multiple threat actors, including Chaya_004, since April 29, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-exploit-sap-rce-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 04:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: End-of-life routers hacked for cybercrime proxy networks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-end-of-life-routers-hacked-for-cybercrime-proxy-networks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linksys and Cisco; CVE(s): None; Summary: The routers listed are vulnerable to exploitation by threat actors using publicly available exploits to inject persistent malware. Once compromised, the routers can be converted into proxies that route malicious traffic and are used for cybercrime-for-hire activities, cryptocurrency theft, and other illegal operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-end-of-life-routers-hacked-for-cybercrime-proxy-networks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco fixes max severity IOS XE flaw letting attackers hijack devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-fixes-max-severity-ios-xe-flaw-letting-attackers-hijack-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20188; Summary: The Cisco IOS XE Software for Wireless LAN Controllers has a hard-coded JSON Web Token (JWT) vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to take over devices, allowing uploads of files, path traversal, and execution of arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-fixes-max-severity-ios-xe-flaw-letting-attackers-hijack-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education giant Pearson hit by cyberattack exposing customer data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/education-giant-pearson-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-customer-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Pearson; CVE(s): None; Summary: Pearson suffered a cyberattack allowing threat actors to steal corporate data and customer information. The attack was carried out by compromising Pearson's developer environment through an exposed GitLab Personal Access Token (PAT) found in a public .git/config file, which gave attackers unauthorized access to internal repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/education-giant-pearson-hit-by-cyberattack-exposing-customer-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply chain attack hits npm package with 45,000 weekly downloads</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-package-with-45-000-weekly-downloads/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: rand-user-agent; CVE(s): None; Summary: The rand-user-agent package was compromised in a supply chain attack to inject obfuscated code that activates a remote access trojan (RAT) on the user's system. The malicious versions generate a hidden directory, open a persistent socket connection to the attacker's C2 server, and allow commands such as file uploads and shell execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/supply-chain-attack-hits-npm-package-with-45-000-weekly-downloads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPi package hides RAT malware, targets Discord devs since 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-hides-rat-malware-targets-discord-devs-since-2022/</link>
      <description>A malicious Python package named "discordpydebug" was discovered on the Python Package Index (PyPI) after over three years. The package, which masqueraded as an error logger utility, could be used to backdoor Discord developers' systems and provide attackers with data theft and remote code execution capabilities, downloaded over 11,000 times since its upload in March 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-pypi-package-hides-rat-malware-targets-discord-devs-since-2022/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE software engineer’s computer infected by info-stealing malware</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses potential security lapses by the Department of Governmental Employee (DOGE) and CISA, including public exposure of sensitive information due to weak credentials and operational security gaffes. Critics suggest that the leaks may be intentional, potentially benefiting specific individuals or groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IT help desk kindly requests you read this newsletter</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/the-it-help-desk-kindly-requests-you-read-this-newsletter/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of being cautious when receiving instructions or requests from individuals claiming to be authorities, as attackers often impersonate authoritative figures to trick victims into taking actions that benefit the attackers. It also highlights the need for threat hunting and the use of different approaches to identify potential threats early on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">681c9fb9f292a20001d3a4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Ubiquiti UniFi Protect Camera Allows Remote Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ubiquiti-unifi-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23123, CVE-2025-23164; Summary: Critical vulnerabilities in UniFi Protect surveillance ecosystem allow attackers to hijack cameras, execute malicious code remotely, and maintain unauthorized access to video feeds. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2025-23123) is a heap buffer overflow that can trigger remote code execution with full control over affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133917</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IXON VPN Client Vulnerability Allows Privilege Escalation for Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ixon-vpn-client-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IXON VPN Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26168, CVE-2025-26169; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in the IXON VPN client allows local privilege escalation attacks, enabling non-privileged users to gain root or SYSTEM-level access on Windows, Linux, and macOS systems. The flaw stems from improper handling of temporary configuration files, which can be exploited by replacing legitimate files with malicious versions containing arbitrary commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133994</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS Software SISF Vulnerability Could Enable Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-software-sisf-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CSCwk04230, CSCvq14413, CSCvo13585, CSCwj88828; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending specifically crafted DHCPv6 packets to targeted devices with SISF enabled, forcing the device to reload and disrupting network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seamless AI Communication: Microsoft Azure Adopts Google’s A2A Protocol</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-azure-integrates-googles-a2a-protocol/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft's support for the Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol, an open standard enabling seamless communication between AI agents across platforms, clouds, and organizational boundaries. The goal is to address the growing demand for interoperable AI systems in enterprise environments, with potential applications in areas such as customer service escalation, IT incident resolution, and supply chain management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134082</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radware Cloud Web App Firewall Flaw Allows Attackers to Bypass Security Filters</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/radware-cloud-web-app-firewall-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Radware Cloud Web Application Firewall (WAF); CVE(s): CVE-2024-56523, CVE-2024-56524; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in Radware's WAF allow attackers to bypass security filters and deliver malicious payloads to protected web applications. The first vulnerability exploits the WAF's failure to properly validate HTTP GET requests containing extraneous data, while the second vulnerability stems from improper input sanitization when processing requests containing non-alphanumeric characters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134145</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Reveals How to Spot Fake Calls Demanding Payment for ‘Missed Jury Duty’</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eset-reveals-how-to-spot-fake-calls-demanding-payment/</link>
      <description>Scammers are using fake government officials to demand payment for "missed jury duty" over phone and email. They use tactics like threatening language, phishing emails/texts, and requests for personal information. To protect yourself, do not engage with suspicious calls or emails, be skeptical of unsolicited communications, and never share personal or financial details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134208</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickidler employee monitoring software abused in ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kickidler-employee-monitoring-software-abused-in-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kickidler; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Kickidler employee monitoring software was exploited by ransomware operators to track victim activity, harvest credentials, and conduct reconnaissance. The attackers used the software to capture keystrokes, take screenshots, and create videos of the screen, enabling them to identify off-site cloud backups and obtain necessary passwords without being detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kickidler-employee-monitoring-software-abused-in-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38,000+ FreeDrain Subdomains Found Exploiting SEO to Steal Crypto Wallet Seed Phrases</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/38000-freedrain-subdomains-found.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses two separate cryptocurrency phishing operations, dubbed FreeDrain and Inferno Drainer. FreeDrain uses SEO manipulation, free-tier web services, and layered redirection techniques to target cryptocurrency wallets, while Inferno Drainer employs advanced anti-detection tactics and single-use smart contracts to bypass wallet security mechanisms and steal funds.

FYSA: The article highlights the sophistication of threat actors in conducting large-scale phishing operations, leveraging various platforms and tools to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/38000-freedrain-subdomains-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections of the India–Pakistan Kashmir Escalation on the Cyber World</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/india-pakistan-kashmir-escalation-on-cyber-world/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the escalation of a military standoff between India and Pakistan in Kashmir, with both sides engaging in physical clashes and online attacks. Hacktivist groups from both countries have begun to align their operations, launching website defacements, Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks, and leaking stolen data. The article highlights the growth of cyber activity related to India over the years, including hacktivist campaigns, Dark Web mentions, and sales of stolen information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100059892</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VC giant Insight Partners confirms investor data stolen in breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vc-giant-insight-partners-confirms-investor-data-stolen-in-breach/</link>
      <description>A venture capital firm, Insight Partners, has confirmed that a cyberattack occurred on January 16, 2025, resulting in the theft of sensitive employee and limited partner data. The incident was caused by a "sophisticated social engineering attack" and may have exposed various types of information, including fund details, personal data, and banking information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vc-giant-insight-partners-confirms-investor-data-stolen-in-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Turn the Tables: Scamming the Scammers in Telegram’s PigButchering Scheme</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scamming-the-scammers-in-telegrams-pigbutchering-scheme/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have developed an innovative approach to combat "PigButchering" scams on Telegram, which involves cultivating false relationships with victims and deceiving them at the opportune moment. The operation involved creating faux personas, executing a sting operation, gathering intelligence, and siphoning off funds from the scammers' wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134177</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Spam Campaign Leverages Remote Monitoring Tools to Exploit Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-spam-campaign-leverages-remote-monitoring-tools/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated spam campaign targeting Portuguese-speaking users in Brazil has been uncovered by Cisco Talos, exploiting commercial remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools to gain unauthorized access to victims' systems. The attackers use deceptive tactics to distribute malicious installers disguised as legitimate files related to Brazil's electronic invoice system, NF-e.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134127</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Attack Exploits X/Twitter Ad URL Feature to Deceive Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-attack-exploits-x-twitter-ad-url-feature/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Twitter; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Twitter's advertising display URL feature allows attackers to manipulate the platform's URL display mechanism, presenting a legitimate-looking link while redirecting users to a malicious cryptocurrency scam site. The exploit involves an inconsistent User Agent string and metadata retrieval process, allowing attackers to create a preview card that displays a trusted domain, masking the true, harmful landing page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134075</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess Which Browser Tops the List for Data Collection!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/which-browser-tops-the-list-for-data-collection/</link>
      <description>Google Chrome has emerged as the most data-intensive web browser among 10 popular browsers, collecting 20 different types of user data, including personal contact information, financial details, location data, and browsing history. Its dominance in the market, with a combined 90% share with Safari, raises concerns about users' privacy and highlights the need for evaluation of browser choices to prioritize security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134093</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall Patches 3 Flaws in SMA 100 Devices Allowing Attackers to Run Code as Root</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/sonicwall-patches-3-flaws-in-sma-100.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA 100; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32819, CVE-2025-32820, CVE-2025-32821; Summary: A remote authenticated attacker can chain these vulnerabilities to elevate privileges, make a sensitive system directory writable, and write an executable file to a system directory, resulting in root-level remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/sonicwall-patches-3-flaws-in-sma-100.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Leads April 2025 Ransomware Spike with 45 Breaches Using NETXLOADER Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/qilin-leads-april-2025-ransomware-spike.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors with ties to Qilin ransomware family have leveraged malware SmokeLoader and a previously undocumented .NET compiled loader, NETXLOADER, as part of a campaign observed in November 2024. The loaders are used to deploy additional malicious payloads, including Agenda ransomware, and are protected by .NET Reactor version 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/qilin-leads-april-2025-ransomware-spike.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Big Balls Ransomware Leverages Open-Source Tools and Custom Scripts for Multi-Stage Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/doge-big-balls-ransomware-leverages-open-source-tools/</link>
      <description>The article describes a highly complex ransomware variant called "DOGE Big Balls," which incorporates political statements and taunts in its payloads. The ransomware's infection chain utilizes custom PowerShell scripts, open-source tools, vulnerable driver exploits, and red team frameworks, with frequent updates to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google links new LostKeys data theft malware to Russian cyberspies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-links-new-lostkeys-data-theft-malware-to-russian-cyberspies/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the ColdRiver hacking group, a Russian state-backed threat actor that has been using new LostKeys malware to steal files in espionage attacks targeting Western governments, journalists, think tanks, and non-governmental organizations. The malware is delivered through social engineering attacks, such as ClickFix, which tricks targets into running malicious PowerShell scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-links-new-lostkeys-data-theft-malware-to-russian-cyberspies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) Emerges as a Leading Framework for Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/raas-emerges-as-a-leading-framework/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the rise of Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) frameworks, which have enabled even less-skilled actors to orchestrate sophisticated attacks. The article highlights the shift towards cross-platform attacks, data exfiltration, and double or triple extortion tactics, as well as the increase in average ransom demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133995</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hackers Posing as Model Agency to Target Victims</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hackers-posing-as-model-agency/</link>
      <description>Unit 42 has exposed a covert operation likely orchestrated by Iranian cyber actors that involves a fraudulent website designed to impersonate the Hamburg-based Mega Model Agency, with malicious JavaScript code aimed at harvesting detailed visitor data. The campaign suggests preparation for targeted social engineering and potentially aims to harvest credentials or deliver malware to specific victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134012</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian COLDRIVER Hackers Deploy LOSTKEYS Malware to Steal Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-coldriver-hackers-deploy-lostkeys-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated malware called LOSTKEYS, attributed to the Russian government-backed threat actor COLDRIVER. The malware is designed to exfiltrate files and harvest system information from targeted individuals and organizations, particularly those linked to Ukraine or Western governments. It uses a complex multi-stage infection chain, including CAPTCHA lures and PowerShell code execution, to evade detection and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133897</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven Fake Vulnerability Reports Flooding Bug Bounty Platforms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-driven-fake-vulnerability-reports/</link>
      <description>AI-generated bogus vulnerability reports, or "AI slop," are flooding bug bounty platforms, mimicking technical jargon convincingly enough to pass initial scrutiny but crumble under expert analysis. These fraudulent submissions rely on systemic vulnerabilities within bug bounty programs and can erode trust, divert resources from addressing genuine vulnerabilities, and potentially dismantle the bug bounty model.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=133927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Bookings Vulnerability Allows Unauthorized Changes to Meeting Details</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-bookings-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Bookings; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in Microsoft Bookings allows unauthorized modification of meeting details, posing risks such as phishing, calendar manipulation, and information leakage. The flaw arises from inadequate input validation and sanitization in several key fields used by Microsoft Bookings, allowing malicious actors to inject arbitrary HTML content into confirmation emails, Teams invitations, and attached ICS files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134115</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nmap 7.96 Released with Enhanced Scanning Capabilities and Updated Libraries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nmap-7-96-launches/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is about the release of Nmap 7.96, a network mapping and security auditing tool. The update brings improvements such as parallel forward DNS resolution, upgraded core libraries, new scripting capabilities, and enhanced compatibility across platforms, especially for Windows users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134099</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IOS XE Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Gain Elevated Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ios-xe-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20197, CVE-2025-20198, CVE-2025-20199, among others; Summary: The IOS XE Software has multiple privilege escalation vulnerabilities that could allow attackers with existing high-level device access to gain root privileges, jeopardizing enterprise networks. Insufficient input validation in the command-line interface (CLI) of IOS XE Software enables attackers to supply crafted input and escalate their privileges to root on the underlying system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134088</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric CC-Link IE TSN</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-128-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Link IE TSN Analog-Digital Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN Digital-Analog Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN FPGA module, and CC-Link IE TSN Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3511; Summary: A remote attacker could cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition by sending specially crafted UDP packets. The affected products are CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, Analog-Digital Converter module, Digital-Analog Converter module, FPGA module, and Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23329</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
