<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>US Homeland Security warns of escalating Iranian cyberattack risks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-homeland-security-warns-of-escalating-iranian-cyberattack-risks/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Homeland Security (DHS) issued a National Terrorism Advisory System bulletin warning about escalating cyberattack risks from Iran-backed hacking groups and pro-Iranian hacktivists, citing the ongoing conflict as a "heightened threat environment" with potential violent extremism and attacks on networks in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-homeland-security-warns-of-escalating-iranian-cyberattack-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo Chamber Jailbreak Tricks LLMs Like OpenAI and Google into Generating Harmful Content</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/echo-chamber-jailbreak-tricks-llms-like.html</link>
      <description>A new jailbreaking method called Echo Chamber can be used to trick large language models (LLMs) into generating undesirable responses. The attack uses indirect references and multi-step inference to manipulate the model's internal state, allowing for high success rates with little technical expertise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/echo-chamber-jailbreak-tricks-llms-like.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada says Salt Typhoon hacked telecom firm via Cisco flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canada-says-salt-typhoon-hacked-telecom-firm-via-cisco-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco IOS XE; CVE(s): CVE-2023-20198; Summary: The Chinese state-sponsored "Salt Typhoon" hacking group exploited a critical vulnerability (CVE-2023-20198) in February 2025, allowing remote attackers to create arbitrary accounts and gain admin-level privileges. This was the same vulnerability that had been previously exploited as a zero-day in October 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canada-says-salt-typhoon-hacked-telecom-firm-via-cisco-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Warns Pro-Iranian Hackers Likely to Target U.S. Networks After Iranian Nuclear Strikes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/dhs-warns-pro-iranian-hackers-likely-to.html</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist groups are likely to target US networks after the US launched airstrikes on Iranian nuclear sites. The Department of Homeland Security warns of a "heightened threat environment" and notes that both hacktivists and Iranian government-affiliated actors may conduct attacks against US networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/dhs-warns-pro-iranian-hackers-likely-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revil ransomware members released after time served on carding charges</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/revil-hackers-released-after-time-served-on-carding-charges/</link>
      <description>Four REvil ransomware members arrested in January 2022 were released by Russia on time served after they pleaded guilty to carding and malware distribution charges. The defendants were part of a group of eight members of the REvil ransomware operation apprehended by Russian authorities more than three years ago, with some being sentenced to over 4 years in prison for illegal circulation of means of payment and distributing malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/revil-hackers-released-after-time-served-on-carding-charges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McLaren Health Care Data Breach Exposes Personal Information of 743,000 Individuals</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mclaren-health-care-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A data breach at McLaren Health Care compromised personal information of 743,131 individuals, including 25 residents of Maine. The breach occurred on July 17, 2024, and was discovered on August 5, 2024. The incident highlights the growing threat of cyberattacks targeting the healthcare sector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143655</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-414: Ruby WEBrick read_header HTTP Request Smuggling Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-414/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ruby WEBrick; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6442; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests on affected installations of Ruby WEBrick when deployed behind an HTTP proxy. The issue results from inconsistent parsing of terminators of HTTP headers in the read_headers method, which can be exploited to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-21876</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-415: ServiceStack GetErrorResponse Improper Input Validation NTLM Relay Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-415/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6444; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of ServiceStack. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the GetErrorResponse method, resulting from improper input validation, which can lead to a type confusion condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25834</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-416: ServiceStack FindType Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-416/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6445; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ServiceStack. It exists within the implementation of the FindType method, which lacks proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25837</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparkKitty Targets iOS and Android Devices via App Store and Google Play Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sparkkitty-targets-ios-and-android-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unknown; CVE(s): None; Summary: SparkKitty is a sophisticated spyware campaign that targets both iOS and Android users, infiltrating official app stores like Google Play and the App Store. The malware steals sensitive data, primarily images from device galleries, by exploiting user trust and using various technical strategies to compromise devices across platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143617</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McLaren Health Care says data breach impacts 743,000 patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mclaren-health-care-says-data-breach-impacts-743-000-patients/</link>
      <description>McLaren Health Care suffered a data breach caused by the INC ransomware gang, affecting 743,000 patients. The attack was discovered on August 5, 2024, but forensic investigations determining who was impacted were only completed on May 5, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mclaren-health-care-says-data-breach-impacts-743-000-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDoS Attack on Financial Sector Triggers Multi-Day Service Outages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ddos-attack-on-financial-sector/</link>
      <description>Financial institutions are increasingly targeted by sophisticated Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks, which exploit complex vulnerabilities in digital infrastructures and APIs. Threat actors employ advanced tactics to mimic legitimate user behavior, making detection and mitigation harder. The DDoS Maturity Model, introduced by FS-ISAC and Akamai, helps organizations assess their cyber maturity and prioritize investments in cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143576</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Weaponize GitHub Infrastructure to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-weaponize-github-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated spearphishing campaign orchestrated by the North Korean threat group Kimsuky has been discovered, leveraging GitHub as a critical piece of attack infrastructure to distribute malware. The attackers use hardcoded GitHub Personal Access Tokens (PATs) with repository scope in the malware, granting read and write access to private repositories used as command and control (C&amp;C) infrastructure for storing malware, decoy files, and exfiltrated victim data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143594</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confucius Hackers Target Government and Military Entities Using WooperStealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/confucius-hackers-target-government-and-military-entities/</link>
      <description>Confucius hacking organization has been detected using a modular backdoor named "anondoor" paired with WooperStealer malware to target critical domestic units and industries in South and East Asia. The anondoor backdoor collects system information, downloads additional malicious components, and communicates with the command-and-control server using parameterized requests and custom delimiters, making tracing and defense challenging for security teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143569</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Teleport Vulnerability Allows Remote Authentication Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-teleport-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Teleport; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49825; Summary: The vulnerability in Teleport enables remote attackers to bypass authentication controls, potentially granting unauthorized access to sensitive systems. It affects versions up to 17.5.1 and earlier major releases, impacting self-hosted and cloud deployments, particularly those running Teleport SSH agents, OpenSSH-integrated deployments, and Teleport Git proxy setups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143653</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDigo Malware Exploits Windows LNK Flaw in Eastern European Government Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/xdigo-malware-exploits-windows-lnk-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25373; Summary: A remote code execution flaw in Microsoft Windows can be triggered when processing specially crafted LNK files. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the current user, and has been observed being used as part of a multi-stage procedure to deploy malware targeting government agencies in Eastern Europe and the Balkans.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/xdigo-malware-exploits-windows-lnk-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueNoroff Hackers Exploit Zoom App to Deploy Infostealer Malware in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bluenoroff-hackers-exploit-zoom-app-to-deploy-infostealer-malware/</link>
      <description>The BlueNoroff threat actor group has launched a targeted social engineering campaign against a Canadian online gambling provider, using Zoom platform impersonation and spoofed domains to deploy infostealer malware, compromising sensitive data including user credentials and browser profiles. The attack chain involved technical finesse, psychological manipulation, and the use of anti-forensic techniques to minimize the attacker's footprint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143560</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel giant Nucor confirms hackers stole data in recent breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-confirms-hackers-stole-data-in-recent-breach/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation, North America's largest steel producer and recycler, has confirmed a recent cybersecurity incident where attackers stole data from the company's network. The incident led to the temporary shutdown of some systems and production operations at various facilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-confirms-hackers-stole-data-in-recent-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCSC Issues Alert on ‘UMBRELLA STAND’ Malware Targeting Fortinet FortiGate Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ncsc-issues-alert-on-umbrella-stand-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiGate 100D series firewalls; CVE(s): None; Summary: The UMBRELLA STAND malware targets internet-facing FortiGate 100D series firewalls to establish long-term access to compromised networks. It features advanced capabilities such as remote shell execution, configurable beacon frequencies, and AES-encrypted communications with its command-and-control server, posing a significant threat to organizations relying on these embedded devices for network security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143547</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux-Based Firewall IPFire 2.29 Rolls Out Update 194 with Improved VPN Features</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/linux-based-firewall-ipfire-2-29-194-with-improved-vpn-features/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194, which brings native support for WireGuard VPN protocol, security enhancements, and package updates. The update aims to improve the firewall's performance, security, and usability, making it more accessible to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143614</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Enhances Defender for Office 365 with Detailed Spam and Phishing Analysis</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-enhances-defender-for-office-365-with-detailed-spam-and-phishing-analysis/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a significant upgrade to Microsoft Defender for Office 365, introducing AI-powered capabilities to provide clear explanations for email submission results. The new feature aims to enhance transparency, improve incident response, and boost user trust by making threat detection reasoning more accessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143604</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI-Enabled Workflow Automation Can Help SOCs Reduce Burnout</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-ai-enabled-workflow-automation-can.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the challenges faced by Security Operations Center (SOC) analysts, including burnout, tooling fragmentation, and lack of growth opportunities. It highlights the potential benefits of artificial intelligence (AI) in alleviating these issues, such as streamlining workflows, providing real-time feedback, and enabling adaptive automation. The article also emphasizes the importance of targeted support for SOC leaders to reduce burnout and improve team culture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-ai-enabled-workflow-automation-can.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel Giant Nucor Suffers Cyberattack, IT Systems Breached</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/steel-giant-nucor-suffers-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation suffered a significant cybersecurity breach that disrupted operations across multiple facilities, leading to the theft of limited company data. The incident involved unauthorized access to its information technology (IT) systems, and the attacker exfiltrated "limited data" before being prevented from further accessing the systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143586</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Reduces Windows 11 24H2 Restore Point Retention from 90 to 60 Days</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-reduces-windows-11-24h2-restore-point-retention/</link>
      <description>The article discusses changes to System Restore in Windows 11 version 24H2, specifically reducing the retention period of restore points from 90 days to 60 days. This change aims to balance storage usage and system reliability while providing a clear and predictable window for recovery. The update also includes security improvements, feature updates, and resolves recurring issues with Windows Hello for Business and Noto fonts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143584</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Allegedly Selling Intelbras Router 0-Day Exploit on Dark Web Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-allegedly-selling-intelbras-router-0-day-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intelbras routers; CVE(s): None; Summary: A previously unknown exploit targeting Intelbras routers has been put up for sale on dark web forums, allowing attackers to gain remote access or control over affected devices. The exact vulnerability remains undisclosed, but the exploit can be used to compromise routers remotely, potentially impacting consumers and organizations relying on these devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143583</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Adds Multi-Layered Defenses to Secure GenAI from Prompt Injection Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-adds-multi-layered-defenses-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article discusses various safety measures implemented by Google to mitigate emerging attack vectors on its generative AI systems, specifically indirect prompt injections. The measures include model hardening, machine learning models, and system-level safeguards, as well as additional guardrails such as content classifiers, spotlighting, and user confirmation frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-adds-multi-layered-defenses-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Chrome 0-Day, 7.3 Tbps DDoS, MFA Bypass Tricks, Banking Trojan and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-73-tbps-ddos.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article presents a collection of cybersecurity-related news and updates from various sources. It covers a range of topics, including data breaches, vulnerabilities, and security best practices.

Some notable points include:

* A breach at Viasat, a US satellite communications company, which was attributed to China-linked attackers.
* The discovery of over 46,000 internet-facing Grafana instances vulnerable to CVE-2025-4123.
* The use of legitimate platforms like Dropbox and Google Drive as "dead drop resolvers" by threat actors.
* A warning about the potential for AI agents to leak sensitive data without proper configuration.
* Guidance on securing Microsoft's System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM) to prevent silent domain takeover attacks.

Overall, the article provides a snapshot of current cybersecurity threats and vulnerabilities, along with practical advice on how to mitigate them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-73-tbps-ddos.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Family Safety Now Blocking All Versions of Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-family-safety-blocking-of-google-chrome/</link>
      <description>Microsoft's Family Safety feature is blocking all versions of Google Chrome from launching on Windows devices due to a bug in the feature. The issue affects only Chrome, while other browsers like Edge, Firefox, and Opera remain unaffected. The root cause is a bug in Microsoft's Family Safety feature, which prevents Chrome from running when enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143552</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former JBLM Soldier Admits Attempting to Leak U.S. Military Network Details to China</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/former-jblm-soldier-leak-u-s-military-network-details-to-china/</link>
      <description>A former US Army sergeant, Joseph Daniel Schmidt, has pleaded guilty to attempting to deliver sensitive military secrets to Chinese authorities. He held classified information while serving with the 109th Military Intelligence Battalion at Joint Base Lewis-McChord and later attempted to share this information with Chinese officials, including creating and offering documents containing "high-level secrets" during his time in Hong Kong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143545</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Snipping Tool Now Lets Users Export Captures as GIFs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-snipping-tool-export-captures-as-gifs/</link>
      <description>The article discusses an update to Microsoft's Snipping Tool that allows users to export screen recordings as animated GIFs. This feature aims to streamline the process of creating and sharing dynamic visual content, which can be particularly useful for remote work environments. The update is currently available in the Canary and Dev Channels for Windows 11 Insiders, with a broader rollout expected in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143537</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Flaws Expose AWS Credentials and Enable Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/amazon-eks-flaws-expose-aws-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS); CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses vulnerabilities in Amazon EKS that could expose sensitive AWS credentials and enable privilege escalation. Misconfigurations and excessive container privileges allow attackers to intercept plaintext credentials, capture AWS credentials using standard tools like tcpdump, or spoof APIs to harvest authorization tokens and obtain valid AWS credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143530</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Meshtastic Flaw Allows Attackers to Decrypt Private Messages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-meshtastic-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Meshtastic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52464; Summary: A severe cryptographic vulnerability in the Meshtastic project allows attackers to decrypt private messages and hijack nodes across LoRa mesh networks. The vulnerability stems from duplicated encryption keys and insufficient randomness during key generation, affecting multiple hardware platforms and posing significant risks to users relying on Meshtastic for secure off-grid communication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143527</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinMarketCap Doodle Image Vulnerability Lets Attackers Run Malicious Code via API Call</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coinmarketcap-doodle-image-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CoinMarketCap; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in a doodle image featured on CoinMarketCap's homepage allowed threat actors to inject malicious code, leading to a phishing campaign targeting user wallets. The exploit delivered a tampered JSON payload that embedded unauthorized JavaScript into the site's front end, prompting users to "Verify Wallet" and gain access to their crypto holdings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143523</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinMarketCap briefly hacked to drain crypto wallets via fake Web3 popup</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinmarketcap-briefly-hacked-to-drain-crypto-wallets-via-fake-web3-popup/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CoinMarketCap; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply chain attack was used to inject a malicious script into CoinMarketCap's website, which drained cryptocurrency from visitors' wallets when they connected them. The attack exploited a vulnerability in the site's "doodle" image and was executed through an API call, resulting in the execution of a wallet drainer script that stole assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinmarketcap-briefly-hacked-to-drain-crypto-wallets-via-fake-web3-popup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 21:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford City Council suffers breach exposing two decades of data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oxford-city-council-suffers-breach-exposing-two-decades-of-data/</link>
      <description>Oxford City Council suffered a data breach where attackers accessed personally identifiable information from legacy systems, affecting former and current Council officers' data between 2001 and 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oxford-city-council-suffers-breach-exposing-two-decades-of-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Snipping Tool now lets you create animated GIF recordings</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-snipping-tool-now-lets-you-create-animated-gif-recordings/</link>
      <description>The article discusses updates to Microsoft's Snipping Tool utility, including the addition of GIF export for screen recordings. It also mentions other recent features added to Snipping Tool, such as a Text Extractor and draw &amp; hold capabilities. There is no mention of vulnerabilities or cybersecurity-related threats in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-snipping-tool-now-lets-you-create-animated-gif-recordings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Repair For Outlook: A Comprehensive Review Of The Ultimate PST Repair Tool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/stellar-repair-for-outlook/</link>
      <description>The article reviews Stellar Repair for Outlook, a software designed to repair and recover corrupted Outlook PST files. It highlights the causes of PST file corruption, such as oversized files, improper shutdowns, malware attacks, and storage device issues. The review provides an in-depth evaluation of the software's features, performance, and usability, including its ability to handle large PST files, selective recovery, and export options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142783</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenVPN Driver Vulnerability Let Attackers Crash Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/openvpn-driver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenVPN; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50054; Summary: The OpenVPN 2.7_alpha2 release addresses a critical vulnerability in the Windows driver (CVE-2025-50054) that could allow attackers to crash systems, emphasizing the importance of timely updates and rigorous testing before deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143447</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli Social Media Users Targeted in Covert Iranian Influence Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/israeli-social-media-users-targeted-in-covert/</link>
      <description>A covert Iranian social media operation has been uncovered, targeting Israeli users on platform X with a psychological campaign designed to sow discord and despair. The operation uses AI tools like ChatGPT for translation and recommends account naming conventions to enhance authenticity. The campaign's technical sophistication allows it to evade detection by moderation systems, making it difficult to detect using traditional automated detection methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143440</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattermost Vulnerabilities Let Attackers Execute Remote Code Via Path Traversal</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mattermost-vulnerabilities-let-attackers-execute-remote-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mattermost; CVE(s): None; Summary: Mattermost has disclosed critical path traversal vulnerabilities that could allow attackers to execute remote code. The flaws can be exploited to access restricted directories and files, potentially compromising sensitive data or disrupting operations. The company urges users to prioritize upgrading to the latest fixed versions to safeguard their environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143433</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac Cyber Attack – Hackers May Have Stolen Personal And Health Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-may-have-stolen-personal-and-health-information/</link>
      <description>Unauthorized access was detected in Aflac Incorporated's network infrastructure, potentially exposing sensitive personal and health information. The incident did not involve ransomware, but the company is conducting a comprehensive review to assess the full extent of the breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143418</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberWarfare on the Rise With Surge in Hacktivist Activity Following Israel-Iran</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberwarfare-on-the-rise-with-surge-in-hacktivist/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the escalation of cyber operations between Israel and Iran in the context of their military conflict. Israeli-linked group Gonjeshke Darande (Predatory Sparrow) executed high-impact strikes on Iranian infrastructure, while Iran has responded with psychological warfare, hacktivist activities, disinformation campaigns, and propaganda efforts. The article highlights the blurring of lines between state cyberattacks, hacktivist disruptions, and influence campaigns, posing risks to critical infrastructure and global businesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143465</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo Browser’s Scam Blocker to Guard Against Phishing and Malware Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/duckduckgo-browsers-scam-blocker-to-guard/</link>
      <description>DuckDuckGo has updated its browser's Scam Blocker feature to provide advanced protection against online threats, including phishing sites, malware, and sophisticated scams. The new feature is integrated into the browser for desktop and mobile platforms and offers real-time protection without compromising user privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143424</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Directories Exposes Publically Available tools Used by Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/open-directories-exposes-publically-available-tools/</link>
      <description>A series of misconfigured web servers have been uncovered, revealing a treasure trove of publicly accessible tools and tactics employed by malicious actors targeting critical infrastructure. The findings show the technical prowess and intent behind these operations, which extend beyond Taiwan to other regions and institutions. The use of open-source offensive software, such as Afrog, Brute Ratel C4, and OneForAll, suggests a reliance on readily available tools for reconnaissance and attack planning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143453</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in XSS Cyberattacks Targets Popular Webmail Platforms, ESET Reports</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surge-in-xss-cyberattacks-targets-popular-webmail-platforms/</link>
      <description>The Russia-aligned Sednit group has been conducting a sophisticated cyber espionage campaign, dubbed Operation RoundPress, targeting high-value webmail platforms through cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. The operation compromises popular webmail services, stealing credentials, exfiltrating email content, and bypassing two-factor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143412</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Announces New Graph Powered Detection of Hybrid Attack Targeting Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-announces-new-graph-powered-detection/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has unveiled an innovative approach to detecting hybrid attacks that span on-premises and cloud environments. The Enterprise Exposure Graph provides contextual enrichment and enables Security Operations Center (SOC) teams to detect and respond to multi-faceted threats with unprecedented precision, addressing critical blind spots in traditional security frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143404</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hacktivist Attacking Israeli Military, Government, and Infrastructure Targets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hacktivist-attacking-israeli/</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist organizations launched a coordinated attack on Israeli military, government, and infrastructure targets, using tactics such as DDoS attacks, website defacements, and data breaches. The pro-Israeli groups responded with targeted infrastructure attacks against Iranian nuclear facilities and military assets, highlighting a significant imbalance in the ongoing digital conflict between the two nations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143396</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac Hit by Cyberattack: What You Need to Know About the Breach</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/aflac-cyberattack-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aflac; CVE(s): None; Summary: Aflac suffered a significant cybersecurity breach caused by social engineering tactics, resulting in unauthorized access to sensitive information on its network. The attackers accessed a range of Personally Identifiable Information (PII), including health insurance claims and medical-related data, Social Security numbers, and personal data associated with customers, beneficiaries, employees, agents, and potentially other individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061161</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 16:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian hackers bypass Gmail MFA using stolen app passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-bypass-gmail-mfa-using-stolen-app-passwords/</link>
      <description>Russian hackers bypassed multi-factor authentication and accessed Gmail accounts by leveraging app-specific passwords in advanced social engineering attacks that impersonated U.S. Department of State officials. The attackers used meticulously developed phishing messages, fake identities, and various materials to deceive victims into creating and sharing app-specific passwords, allowing the hackers full access to their Google accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-bypass-gmail-mfa-using-stolen-app-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Motors theme flaw mass-exploited to hijack admin accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-motors-theme-flaw-mass-exploited-to-hijack-admin-accounts/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The WordPress theme "Motors" contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to change administrator passwords, granting complete control of the targeted site. The flaw arises from improper user identity validation during password updating and affects all versions before and including 5.6.67.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-motors-theme-flaw-mass-exploited-to-hijack-admin-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Behind Cyberattacks on M&amp;S and Co-op, Causing Up to $592M in Damages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/scattered-spider-behind-cyberattacks-on.html</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather a cyber attack on UK retailers Marks &amp; Spencer and Co-op. The attacks were classified as a single combined cyber event by the Cyber Monitoring Centre (CMC), with an estimated financial impact of £270-440 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/scattered-spider-behind-cyberattacks-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target 700+ ComfyUI AI Image Generation Servers to Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-700-comfyui-ai-image-generation-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ComfyUI; CVE(s): None; Summary: Critical vulnerabilities in ComfyUI have been exploited by hacker groups, compromising at least 695 servers worldwide. The flaws allow attackers to steal sensitive AI-related data, execute remote commands, and establish reverse shell access, posing a significant risk of network intrusions and data breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143372</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack Disrupts Russian Dairy Supply Chain by Targeting Animal Certification System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattack-disrupts-russian-dairy-supply-chain/</link>
      <description>A suspected cyberattack has targeted Russia's national veterinary certification system (Mercury), forcing it into emergency operation mode. The attack has halted normal operations, prompting authorities to implement contingency measures to maintain the flow of goods while restoration efforts are underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143317</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prometei Botnet Targets Linux Servers for Cryptocurrency Mining Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/prometei-botnet-targets-linux-servers/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a renewed wave of attacks by the Prometei botnet targeting Linux servers. The malware has advanced capabilities such as a backdoor for remote control, DGA for resilient C2 infrastructure, and self-updating mechanisms to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143326</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Weaponized MSI Installer Masquerading as WhatsApp to Deliver XWorm RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-weaponized-msi-installer-masquerading-as-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>A China-based threat actor is targeting users across East and Southeast Asia with a trojanized MSI installer disguised as a legitimate WhatsApp setup file. The installer delivers a customized version of the XWorm Remote Access Trojan (RAT), which can steal sensitive data, maintain persistent access for attackers, and detect Telegram installations on compromised devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143293</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocha Manakin Uses Paste-and-Run Technique to Deceive Users into Downloading Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mocha-manakin-uses-paste-and-run-technique-to-deceive-users/</link>
      <description>Mocha Manakin is a malicious campaign using the "paste-and-run" technique to trick users into executing harmful scripts. The campaign employs sophisticated social engineering lures, exploiting digital conditioning to prompt users to copy and paste obfuscated PowerShell commands, which download malicious payloads from adversary-controlled infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143334</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Manipulate Google Search Results to Display Scammer’s Phone Number Instead of Real Number</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-manipulate-google-search-results/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting trust in sponsored search results to orchestrate scams, targeting popular brands and tech support services. They manipulate search engine results to display fake contact numbers and redirect users to malicious sites or fraudulent phone numbers, leading to financial losses, identity theft, and potential malware infections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143301</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record DDoS pummels site with once-unimaginable 7.3Tbps of junk traffic</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/record-ddos-pummels-site-with-once-unimaginable-7-3tbps-of-junk-traffic/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of reflection attacks in a record-breaking DDoS attack. Reflection attacks direct malicious traffic to third-party intermediaries, making it harder for targets to defend against the attack. The attack exploited various amplification vectors, including Network Time Protocol, Quote of the Day Protocol, Echo Protocol, and Portmapper services, as well as Mirai-based botnets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/record-ddos-pummels-site-with-once-unimaginable-7-3tbps-of-junk-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insomnia API Client Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary Code Execution via Template Injection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/insomnia-api-client-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Insomnia API Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1087; Summary: The Insomnia API Client has a severe security vulnerability allowing for arbitrary code execution through Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) due to its use of the Nunjucks templating engine. The flaw persists in version 11.2.0 and can be exploited via multiple vectors, including imported collection files, pasted data, server-provided cookies, and HTTP responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143308</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Vercel Hosting Platform to Distribute Remote Access Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-vercel-hosting-platform/</link>
      <description>CyberArmor has uncovered a sophisticated phishing campaign exploiting Vercel, a frontend hosting platform, to distribute a malicious variant of LogMeIn. The campaign targeted over 1,271 users with deceptive emails leading to fraudulent pages hosted on Vercel subdomains, tricking victims into downloading and installing the malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143286</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitoPro exchange links Lazarus hackers to $11 million crypto heist</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitopro-exchange-links-lazarus-hackers-to-11-million-crypto-heist/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cyberattack on Taiwanese cryptocurrency exchange BitoPro, allegedly carried out by the North Korean hacking group Lazarus. The attackers stole approximately $11 million worth of cryptocurrency and laundered it through decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and mixers. The incident involved social engineering, malware, and hijacked AWS session tokens to bypass multi-factor authentication (MFA).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitopro-exchange-links-lazarus-hackers-to-11-million-crypto-heist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TxTag Phishing Campaign Exploits .gov Domain to Deceive Employees</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/txtag-phishing-campaign-exploits-gov-domain/</link>
      <description>A new phishing campaign has emerged, using the credibility of a .gov domain to deceive employees into believing they owe unpaid tolls. The attack leverages the GovDelivery system and uses psychological manipulation, combined with technical deception, to maximize its impact. The campaign targets employees' personal data and corporate reputation, posing risks that traditional perimeter defenses often fail to detect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143269</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Loaders Use In-Memory Execution to Evade Disk-Based Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/powershell-loaders-use-in-memory-execution/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated PowerShell script named y1.ps1 has been discovered hosted in an open directory on a Chinese server. The script operates as a shellcode loader, employing advanced in-memory execution techniques to bypass traditional detection mechanisms. It uses various evasion techniques, including API hashing and forged User-Agent strings, to evade network monitoring and antivirus solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143261</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft investigates OneDrive bug that breaks file search</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft OneDrive; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some OneDrive users are experiencing blank search results or no results at all, even when searching for files they know exist. The issue affects a subset of users across most OneDrive platforms and there is currently no known workaround or estimated timeline for a fix.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Adds "Call Lawyer" Feature to Pressure Victims for Larger Ransoms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/qilin-ransomware-adds-call-lawyer.html</link>
      <description>Qilin ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) scheme is intensifying its activity, offering legal counsel for affiliates to put pressure on victims to pay up. The group's affiliate panel now includes features like "Call Lawyer" and spam services, positioning itself as a full-service cybercrime platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/qilin-ransomware-adds-call-lawyer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare blocks record 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack against hosting provider</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare mitigated a record-breaking distributed denial of service (DDoS) attack in May 2025 that peaked at 7.3 Tbps, targeting a hosting provider. The attack used multiple vectors, including UDP floods, QOTD reflection, Echo reflection, NTP amplification, Mirai botnet UDP flood, Portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification, each exploiting legacy or poorly configured services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac discloses breach amidst Scattered Spider insurance attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aflac; CVE(s): None; Summary: The systems of American insurance giant Aflac were breached by a sophisticated cybercrime group, potentially stealing personal and health information. The attack shows signs of being carried out by Scattered Spider, a group known for their social engineering attacks against high-profile organizations worldwide.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, so no CVEs are listed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can users reset their own passwords without sacrificing security?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the benefits of self-service password reset (SSPR) solutions in reducing helpdesk load, costs, and improving productivity. It highlights the importance of proper security considerations when implementing an SSPR solution, including strong identity verification measures and multi-factor authentication (MFA). The article also emphasizes the need for a user-friendly experience to promote adoption and minimize abandonment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive DDoS Attack Hits 7.3 Tbps Delivering 37.4 Terabytes in 45 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-ddos-attack-hits-7-3-tbps/</link>
      <description>A massive distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack peaked at 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps), overwhelming its target with 37.4 terabytes of data in just 45 seconds, targeting an unnamed hosting provider that relied on Cloudflare's Magic Transit service for network defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143273</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft to remove legacy drivers from Windows Update for security boost</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a specific vulnerability, but rather discusses Microsoft's plan to periodically remove legacy drivers from the Windows Update catalog to mitigate security and compatibility risks. The company aims to ensure the optimal set of drivers on Windows Update while maintaining its security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Misconfiguration Lets Attackers Take Over Cloud Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/azure-misconfiguration-take-over-cloud-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): None; Summary: A chain of misconfigurations in Microsoft Azure allows attackers to gain complete control over an organization's cloud infrastructure, from initial access to full tenant takeover. The attack path involves unauthenticated reconnaissance, exploiting public storage accounts, and leveraging dynamic group membership rules to achieve privilege escalation and lateral movement, ultimately leading to total ownership of the Azure environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143248</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's State TV Hijacked Mid-Broadcast Amid Geopolitical Tensions; $90M Stolen in Crypto Heist</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</link>
      <description>Iran's state-owned TV broadcaster was hacked to air videos calling for street protests against the Iranian government, while Israel accused Iran of launching cyber attacks. The incident is part of a larger cyber war between Israel and Iran that has been ongoing for over a decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AntiDot 3-in-1 Android Botnet Malware Grants Attackers Full Control Over Victim Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/antidot-3-in-1-android-botnet-malware-grants-attackers/</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a new Android botnet malware that grants cybercriminals control over infected devices. It has advanced capabilities such as screen recording, SMS interception, and credential theft through overlay attacks. The malware operates through at least 11 active command-and-control (C2) servers, managing over 3,775 infected devices across 273 distinct campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143233</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford City Council Hit by Cyberattack Exposing Employee Personal Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oxford-city-council-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Oxford City Council's network was targeted by a sophisticated cyberattack that exposed personal data of employees involved in council-administered elections over the past two decades. The attack allowed attackers to access historic data stored on legacy systems, affecting current and former council officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143245</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versa Director Flaws Let Attackers Execute Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/versa-director-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Networks' SD-WAN orchestration platform, Versa Director; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23171, CVE-2025-23172; Summary: Authenticated attackers can upload malicious files and execute arbitrary commands on affected systems due to insecure file upload and webhook functionalities. The first flaw allows remote code execution (RCE) if a webshell is uploaded and accessed, while the second vulnerability enables authenticated users to execute commands as the "versa" user with sudo privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143238</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GodFather Android Malware Uses On-Device Virtualization to Hijack Legitimate Banking Apps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/godfather-android-malware-uses-on-device-virtualization/</link>
      <description>The GodFather Android banking malware creates a fully isolated virtual environment on the victim's device, enabling attackers to monitor and manipulate user interactions in real-time. It employs a malicious "host" application that downloads and runs a copy of the targeted app within a controlled sandbox, capturing credentials and sensitive information with precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143210</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-411: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 DPAX File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-411/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47728; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPAX files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26167</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-412: Fuji Electric Smart Editor  X1 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-412/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41413; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor by writing past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26031</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-413: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-413/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 file parsing stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the processing of TL5 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26018</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgence of the Prometei Botnet</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/prometei-botnet-2025-activity/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Prometei Linux Botnet; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Prometei malware family, which includes both Linux and Windows variants, allows attackers to remotely control compromised systems for cryptocurrency mining (particularly Monero) and credential theft. The latest versions feature a backdoor that enables a variety of malicious activities, including brute-forcing administrator credentials, exploiting vulnerabilities, and self-updating features for stealth and evasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143713</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps to 24/7 In-House SOC Success</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors often target businesses during off-hours when security personnel are fewer or not present. A 24/7 Security Operations Center (SOC) can provide real-time threat detection and resolution, but requires a perfect balance of proven processes, advanced tools, and skilled professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Billion Password Leak, Not New, Still Dangerous: What You Need to Know?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/16-billion-password-leak-not-new-still-dangerous/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the exposure of 16 billion login credentials collected by infostealer malware over several years. The data includes usernames, passwords, cookies, tokens, and other sensitive information from various services like Google, Facebook, Apple, Microsoft, Telegram, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061153</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 7.3 Tbps DDoS Attack Delivers 37.4 TB in 45 Seconds, Targeting Hosting Provider</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</link>
      <description>Cloudflare reported blocking a 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack, targeting an unnamed hosting provider, which used a combination of UDP flood, QOTD reflection attack, echo reflection attack, NTP reflection attack, Mirai UDP flood attack, portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification attack. The attack originated from over 122,145 source IP addresses across 161 countries, with the largest portions coming from Brazil, Vietnam, Taiwan, China, Indonesia, Ukraine, Ecuador, Thailand, the United States, and Saudi Arabia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Introduces Enhanced Security Defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-introduces-enhanced-security-defaults-for-windows-365/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing new secure-by-default capabilities for Windows 365 Cloud PCs to fortify virtual desktop environments against modern cyber threats. The update includes default disabling of device redirections (clipboard, drive, USB, and printer) and enabling advanced security controls such as virtualization-based security, Credential Guard, and hypervisor-protected code integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143202</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dover Fueling Solutions Flaw Lets Attackers Control Fueling Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dover-fueling-solutions-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dover Fueling Solutions' ProGauge MagLink LX consoles; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5310; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-5310, allows remote attackers to seize control of fueling operations, manipulate tank monitoring, and deploy malware, posing a severe risk to transportation systems worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143199</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Billion Passwords Stolen From 320 Million+ Computers Leaked Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/16-billion-passwords-stolen-from-320-million-computers-leaked-online/</link>
      <description>A massive data breach has exposed approximately 16 billion login credentials, usernames, and passwords across various platforms, including Apple, Facebook, Google, Instagram, Telegram, GitHub, and government services. The compromised data can be used for account takeover, identity theft, targeted phishing attacks, and ransomware attacks.

FYSA: Cybercriminals have gained access to a massive dataset of login records, which can be exploited for account takeovers, identity theft, and targeted phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143181</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM QRadar SIEM Bug Lets Attackers Run Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-qradar-siem-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM Security QRadar SIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33117, None (other CVEs mentioned are not explicitly linked to the vulnerability); Summary: A critical flaw in IBM's QRadar SIEM platform allows privileged users to execute arbitrary commands on affected systems, enabling attackers to compromise sensitive data or gain unauthorized access. The vulnerability has been addressed in the latest interim fix (UP12 IF02), and customers are urged to update their installations to protect against potential exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143190</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ Trojanized GitHub Repositories Found in Campaign Targeting Gamers and Developers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new campaign of 67 GitHub repositories claiming to offer Python-based hacking tools, but delivering trojanized payloads instead. The repositories were taken down by GitHub, and the campaign is believed to target users searching for software such as account cleaning tools and game cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache SeaTunnel Flaw Lets Unauthorized Users Launch Deserialization Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-seatunnel-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache SeaTunnel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32896; Summary: The Apache SeaTunnel vulnerability (CVE-2025-32896) allows unauthorized users to exploit insecure REST API endpoints, enabling arbitrary file read and potentially remote code execution through deserialization attacks. This affects versions 2.3.1-2.3.10 and has been classified as moderate to critical in severity, depending on deployment context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143186</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Wall Connector Hacked Through Charging Port in Just 18 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tesla-wall-connector-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tesla Wall Connector; CVE(s): None; Summary: Security researchers from Synacktiv successfully hacked the Tesla Wall Connector through its charging port in just 18 minutes, exposing critical vulnerabilities in the device's firmware and communication protocols. The attack involved downgrading the Wall Connector's firmware to an older version with exposed debug features, including a TCP debug shell accessible over Wi-Fi, and exploiting a global buffer overflow in the shell's command parsing logic for code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143172</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Support Tickets Let Hackers Exploit Atlassian’s Model Context Protocol</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-support-tickets-let-hackers-exploit-atlassians-model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian Jira Service Management (JSM); CVE(s): None; Summary: A new class of cyberattack targets organizations using Atlassian's Model Context Protocol (MCP), exploiting AI-powered workflows in JSM. Malicious support tickets can be used to gain privileged access and exfiltrate sensitive data without breaching internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143168</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, the 16 billion credentials leak is not a new data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a massive compilation of previously stolen credentials, allegedly obtained through infostealers, data breaches, and credential-stuffing attacks. The compilation was briefly exposed online, containing over 64,000 credential pairs. The article warns users to adopt good cybersecurity habits, use unique and strong passwords, enable two-factor authentication (2FA), and monitor for known breaches using services like Have I Been Pwned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godfather Android malware now uses virtualization to hijack banking apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Godfather Android Malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Godfather Android malware creates isolated virtual environments on mobile devices to steal account data and transactions from legitimate banking apps, using tactics such as intent spoofing, StubActivity, and API hooking. The malware displays a fake lock screen overlay to trick users into entering their PIN/passwords and can record account credentials, passwords, PINs, touch events, and capture responses from the banking backend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100,000 WordPress Sites Exposed to Privilege Escalation via MCP AI Engine</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-100000-wordpress-sites-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jordy Meow AI Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5071; Summary: The AI Engine plugin has a severe vulnerability allowing authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access or higher to gain full control over the Model Context Protocol (MCP) module, enabling privilege escalation and potentially complete site compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143132</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Deploy Malware Using Weaponized Calendly and Google Meet Links</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-deploy-malware-using-weaponized-calendly/</link>
      <description>TA444, a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor group, has launched a sophisticated malware campaign targeting cryptocurrency foundations. The attack leverages weaponized Calendly links, deceptive Google Meet invitations, and deepfakes to deliver malicious payloads designed for macOS systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143141</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Fox APT Uses Weaponized Medical Software to Deploy Remote Access Tools and Disable AV</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silver-fox-apt-uses-weaponized-medical-software/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the China-based advanced persistent threat (APT) group Silver Fox's multi-stage campaign targeting healthcare delivery organizations (HDOs) and public sector entities. The campaign uses trojanized medical software, cloud infrastructure, and a custom remote access trojan (RAT) to deploy cyber espionage and data theft operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143124</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers Targeted! Fake Minecraft Mods Enable Attackers to Take Control of Your System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-minecraft-mods-enable-attackers-to-take-control/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Minecraft; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious campaign targeting Minecraft users has been discovered, using a Distribution as a Service (DaaS) platform to distribute malware disguised as legitimate mods. The malware initiates a multi-stage attack chain designed to steal sensitive data and compromise systems, exploiting the trust of gamers seeking to enhance their gaming experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143113</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android Malware Surge Hits Devices via Overlays, Virtualization Fraud and NFC Theft</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a financially motivated Android malware sold as a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) on underground forums, compromising over 3,775 devices across 273 unique campaigns. It features capabilities to record device screens, intercept SMS messages, extract sensitive data, conduct overlay attacks, and remotely control infected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Stolen credentials are the new front door to your network</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</link>
      <description>Credential-based attacks are becoming increasingly common, with threat actors using stolen credentials to breach networks. Infostealer malware campaigns have exploded in recent years, stealing billions of credentials and feeding a booming cybercrime marketplace. The webinar will explore how attackers are shifting from exploiting vulnerabilities to simply logging in using large-scale credential abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-409: RARLAB WinRAR Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-409/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RARLAB WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6218; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of RARLAB WinRAR, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists in the handling of file paths within archive files, allowing an attacker to traverse to unintended directories and execute code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27198</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-410: Allegra calculateTokenExpDate Password Recovery Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-410/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Allegra; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6216; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Allegra, with no required user interaction. The issue stems from a predictable value used in generating a password reset token within the application's password recovery mechanism, allowing attackers to exploit it and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27104</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Sam Altman discusses GPT-5 release date</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be an update about OpenAI's next big upgrade to ChatGPT, including the potential release of GPT-5 and improvements to the Operator Agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-tied Predatory Sparrow hackers are waging cyberwar on Iran’s financial system</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: Predatory Sparrow, a group believed to be linked to Israel's military or intelligence agencies, has been carrying out cyberattacks against Iran's critical infrastructure, including railways and gas stations. The group's recent attack on the Khouzestan steel mill caused significant physical damage. It is unclear why they have turned their attention to Iran's financial sector, but experts warn that this development may lead to more serious consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US recovers $225 million of crypto stolen in investment scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice has seized over $225 million in cryptocurrency linked to investment fraud and money laundering operations, the largest crypto seizure in the history of the U.S. Secret Service. The funds were traced using blockchain analysis and were laundered through a complex network of cryptocurrency addresses to obscure their origin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Webinar: Key Insights from Verizon’s 2025 DBIR</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report (DBIR) 2025, which highlights critical trends in cybersecurity, including rising GenAI-related risks, credential theft, and vulnerabilities from third-party partners. It also emphasizes the need for enterprises to adopt an updated, integrated approach to cybersecurity and provides insights on how to strengthen security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Cyber Attacks Targeting Manufacturing Industry in 2025</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/major-cyber-attacks-manufacturing-industry-in-2025/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article highlights the growing threat of cyberattacks in the manufacturing sector. In 2025, the global manufacturing industry faced a surge in cyberattacks, driven by ransomware gangs, espionage-motivated actors, and supply chain vulnerabilities. The cost of these attacks is increasing rapidly, with losses rising by 125% each year. The article also explores the tactics used by attackers and the key lessons for improving industrial cybersecurity.

Note: This summary does not fit into any specific format (vulnerability or threat actor-focused) as it does not specifically discuss a vulnerability or threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061085</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft unveils new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs, including disabling clipboard, drive, USB, and printer redirections by default to reduce risks of data theft and block malware attacks. Additionally, the company will start blocking access to SharePoint, OneDrive, and Office files via legacy authentication protocols in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jQuery Migrate Library Compromised to Steal Logins via Parrot Traffic Direction System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jquery-migrate-library-compromised-to-steal-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: jQuery Migrate; CVE(s): None; Summary: A weaponized version of the jQuery Migrate library was used in a sophisticated malware campaign that exploited the trust in the library. The attack delivered a malicious script through a compromised Middle Eastern business website, which stole sensitive data, logged keystrokes, and deployed additional threats such as cryptocurrency miners or click-fraud scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143096</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT will analyze Gmail emails, manage schedule on Google Calendar</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability, but rather mentions the testing of integration features between ChatGPT and Gmail/Google Calendar. The feature will allow users to summarize emails and create events, and may be tied to the ChatGPT Search feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Amatera Stealer Using Advanced Web Injection and Anti-Analysis Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-amatera-stealer-using-advanced-web-injection/</link>
      <description>Amatera Stealer is a rebranded information stealer malware that exhibits advanced features and stealth mechanisms. It is distributed through web injection campaigns, software cracks, and fake downloads, and can steal sensitive data from browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, email clients, and messaging apps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143084</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krispy Kreme Data Breach Exposes Customer Personal Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/krispy-kreme-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A ransomware attack on Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corporation's information technology systems exposed the personal information of over 160,000 individuals. The attackers claimed to have stolen 184 GB of sensitive data, including personal and financial information, client documents, payroll, and accounting records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143073</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Spyware SpyNote Masquerading as Google Translate Found in Open Directories</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/android-spyware-spynote-masquerading-as-google-translate/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the discovery of multiple SpyNote spyware samples in open directories across the internet, which can be disguised as legitimate Android applications. These malware files harvest sensitive data from unsuspecting users by exploiting accessibility services and device administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143069</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use VBScript Files to Deploy Masslogger Credential Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-vbscript-files-to-deploy-masslogger/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated variant of the Masslogger credential stealer malware that spreads through VBScript Encoded (.VBE) files. It uses evasive techniques such as fileless malware, heavy registry exploitation, and multi-stage execution to evade detection by traditional antivirus and signature-based methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143042</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo beefs up scam defense to block fake stores, crypto sites</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-beefs-up-scam-defense-to-block-fake-stores-crypto-sites/</link>
      <description>DuckDuckGo's Scam Blocker tool has been updated to protect against a broader range of online scams, including fake e-commerce, cryptocurrency exchanges, and "scareware" sites. The tool blocks known malware distribution and phishing URLs by default, and users can opt-in for additional protection across other internet apps when using the DuckDuckGo VPN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-beefs-up-scam-defense-to-block-fake-stores-crypto-sites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-5309: RCE in BeyondTrust Chat Feature Affects Remote Support and PRA</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-5309-beyondtrust-chat-feature-rs-pra/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BeyondTrust Remote Support and Privileged Remote Access; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5309; Summary: The vulnerability allows for Remote Code Execution (RCE) through a chat feature due to server-side template injection. It can be exploited remotely without authentication, with high potential for confidentiality and integrity impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061127</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telecom giant Viasat breached by China's Salt Typhoon hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telecom-giant-viasat-breached-by-chinas-salt-typhoon-hackers/</link>
      <description>The article reports that satellite communications company Viasat has been breached by China's Salt Typhoon state hackers. The breach occurred earlier this year and was discovered when a compromised device was found to have unauthorized access. Viasat claims the incident has been remediated and no customer impact was detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telecom-giant-viasat-breached-by-chinas-salt-typhoon-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viasat Targeted in Cyberattack by Salt Typhoon APT Group</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/viasat-targeted-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>A Chinese state-sponsored group known as Salt Typhoon has been linked to a sweeping cyberespionage campaign that compromised major telecommunications firms, including Viasat Inc., Verizon, AT&amp;T, and Lumen Technologies. The campaign targeted phone records, including those of then-presidential candidate Donald Trump and members of both major campaigns, and highlights the growing threat posed by advanced persistent threat (APT) actors targeting critical American infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143058</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueNoroff Deepfake Zoom Scam Hits Crypto Employee with MacOS Backdoor Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bluenoroff-deepfake-zoom-scam-hits.html</link>
      <description>BlueNoroff threat actor targets employee with deepfaked company executives in deceptive Zoom calls to trick them into installing malware on their Apple macOS devices. The attack involves the use of Calendly link, fake Zoom domain, and AppleScript that downloads next-stage payload and executes shell script, ultimately leading to the installation of eight distinct malicious binaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bluenoroff-deepfake-zoom-scam-hits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden SAML Attack: How Attackers Gain Control of Federation Server’s Private Key</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-attackers-gain-control-of-federation-servers-private-key/</link>
      <description>The Golden SAML attack is a sophisticated threat that exploits the trust mechanisms of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication to compromise every account within an organization by forging authentic-looking tokens. This attack targets the private key of federation servers, allowing attackers to impersonate any user and bypass security controls with stealth and precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Rises as Major Threat, Demanding $50M in Ransom</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-ransomware-rises-as-major-threat/</link>
      <description>The Qilin ransomware group has surged to the forefront of digital extortion, demanding ransoms as high as $50 million and disrupting critical services worldwide. With a robust Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) platform, recruiting affiliates through Russian-language forums, and offering lucrative revenue shares, Qilin has amassed over $50 million in ransom payments in 2024 alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143050</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Vibe Coding: The Complete New Guide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/secure-vibe-coding-complete-new-guide.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vibe Coding; CVE(s): None; Summary: Vibe coding, the use of natural language to generate software with AI, introduces "silent killer" vulnerabilities that evade traditional security tools. These exploitable flaws are created when AI generates code without explicit prompting for security features, leading to insecure patterns and functions that can be exploited in production environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/secure-vibe-coding-complete-new-guide.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actor Exploit GitHub and Hosted 60 GitHub Repositories with 100s of Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actor-exploit-github-and-hosted-60-github-repositories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub; CVE(s): None; Summary: Banana Squad exploited GitHub by hosting over 60 malicious repositories containing hundreds of trojanized Python files. The repositories used advanced evasion techniques to hide harmful content, making it nearly undetectable to casual inspection. All 67 repositories have been removed by GitHub, but the potential impact remains unclear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143003</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated Phishing Attack Uses ASP Pages to Target Prominent Russia Critics – Google</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophisticated-phishing-attack-uses-asp-pages/</link>
      <description>A Russia state-sponsored cyber threat actor, tracked as UNC6293, has been identified by Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) in a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting academics and critics of Russia. The campaign used advanced social engineering tactics to trick victims into creating and sharing Application Specific Passwords (ASPs), which granted persistent access to Gmail accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142986</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClamAV 1.4.3 and 1.0.9 Released with Fixes for Critical Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clamav-1-4-3-and-1-0-9-released-with-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ClamAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20260, CVE-2025-20234; Summary: The ClamAV development team has released two security patch releases, versions 1.4.3 and 1.0.9, to address significant vulnerabilities in the PDF file parser and UDF file parser. The flaws, identified as CVE-2025-20260 and CVE-2025-20234, have the potential to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or enable remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142951</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Cloudflare Tunnels to Infect Windows Systems With Python Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-cloudflare-tunnels-to-infect-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign dubbed SERPENTINE#CLOUD has emerged, using Cloudflare Tunnel infrastructure to deliver Python-based malware to Windows systems across Western nations. The campaign exploits trusted cloud services to bypass network defenses and maintain anonymity, featuring a complex, multi-stage infection chain designed for stealth and persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142938</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncover LOTS Attacks Hiding in Trusted Tools — Learn How in This Free Expert Session</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/uncover-lots-attacks-hiding-in-trusted.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a tactic called "Living Off Trusted Sites" (LOTS), where attackers blend in with legitimate traffic by hiding malicious code inside routine traffic on well-known platforms like Google, Microsoft, Dropbox, and Slack. LOTS tactics exploit common business tools, shortened URLs, and trusted cloud services to host malicious payloads, making it difficult for traditional defenses to detect them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/uncover-lots-attacks-hiding-in-trusted.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krispy Kreme says November data breach impacts over 160,000 people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/krispy-kreme-says-november-data-breach-impacts-over-160-000-people/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses a cyberattack on Krispy Kreme that resulted in the theft of personal information of over 160,000 individuals. The attackers, identified as the Play ransomware gang, claimed to have stolen sensitive data from the company's network and threatened to leak it online unless a ransom was paid. The breach was detected by Krispy Kreme on November 29 and notified affected individuals in May 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/krispy-kreme-says-november-data-breach-impacts-over-160-000-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Entra ID Adds Passkey (FIDO2) Support in Public Preview</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-entra-id-adds-passkey-fido2-support/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced an update to its identity platform, Microsoft Entra ID, which introduces expanded passkey (FIDO2) support. This update allows IT administrators to configure passkey authentication policies at a granular level, enabling organizations to tailor authentication methods for different user groups. The rollout is set to occur globally from mid-October to mid-November 2025 and will simplify the authentication process by unifying credentials from hardware keys, computers, and mobile devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142998</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CVE-2025-6018 and CVE-2025-6019 Enable Full Root Access on Linux</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-6018-and-cve-2025-6019-root-access-on-linux/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: openSUSE Leap 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise 15; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two newly discovered Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities in Linux distributions allow attackers to chain low-level access into full root control. The first vulnerability manipulates environment variables during login, allowing remote attackers to impersonate local users and gain permission to perform actions reserved for physical users. The second vulnerability abuses XFS file system resizing to gain root access using the udisk daemon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061109</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogMeIn Remote Access Abused in Targeted System Compromise</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/logmein-remote-access-abused/</link>
      <description>This article describes a sophisticated cyberattack campaign that leverages LogMeIn Resolve remote access software to gain unauthorized control over user systems. The attack begins with a convincingly crafted invoice-themed spam email, designed to trick recipients into opening a malicious PDF attachment, which installs the remote access tool and grants attackers full remote access to the compromised system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142983</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jitter-Trap: New Method Uncovers Stealthy Beacon Communications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jitter-trap-stealthy-beacon-communications/</link>
      <description>The article introduces Jitter-Trap, a detection technique that uses behavioral and network analysis to identify post-exploitation and command-and-control (C2) communication in cyberattacks. It leverages the randomness used by attackers to evade detection, turning it into a powerful detection tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142975</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian APT29 Exploits Gmail App Passwords to Bypass 2FA in Targeted Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/russian-apt29-exploits-gmail-app.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google account feature - Application Specific Passwords (ASPs); CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors with suspected ties to Russia are using a novel social engineering tactic that takes advantage of Google's application specific passwords (ASPs) to gain access to victims' email accounts. The tactic involves building rapport with targets, sending benign phishing emails disguised as meeting invitations, and tricking them into sharing the ASP passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/russian-apt29-exploits-gmail-app.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-3248 in Langflow Exploited to Deploy Flodrix Botnet</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-3248-in-langflow-deploy-flodrix-botnet/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Langflow's /api/v1/validate/code endpoint allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code directly on the server, granting remote control over the host. The vulnerability impacts Langflow versions prior to 1.3.0 and is particularly dangerous due to Langflow's popularity in cloud-hosted AI deployments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061100</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco AnyConnect VPN Flaw Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-anyconnect-vpn-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Meraki; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20271; Summary: The vulnerability stems from a variable initialization error that occurs when establishing SSL VPN sessions using client certificate authentication. Attackers can exploit this flaw by sending specially crafted HTTPS requests to affected devices, causing the Cisco AnyConnect VPN service to crash and restart, immediately disconnecting all active VPN users and forcing them to re-authenticate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142952</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 07:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Gang Busted by Authorities; Devices and Evidence Seized</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-gang-busted-by-authorities/</link>
      <description>Thai authorities dismantled a sophisticated criminal enterprise operating from the Antai Holiday Hotel in Pattaya, discovering a high-stakes gambling den and a ransomware cybercrime ring. The operation highlights the growing trend of cybercrime being intertwined with traditional organized crime, including gambling, money laundering, and identity theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142933</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Traffic Server Vulnerability Allows DoS Attacks Through Memory Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-traffic-server-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Software Foundation Apache Traffic Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49763; Summary: Attackers can exploit a flaw in the Edge Side Includes (ESI) plugin to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) attacks by exhausting server memory, affecting multiple versions of ATS 9.0.0 to 9.2.101 and 10.0.0 to 10.0.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryuk ransomware’s initial access expert extradited to the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ryuk-ransomwares-initial-access-expert-extradited-to-the-us/</link>
      <description>A member of the Ryuk ransomware operation, who specialized in gaining initial access to corporate networks, has been extradited to the United States. The individual was arrested in April 2025 and is suspected of earning $150 million while active between 2018 and 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ryuk-ransomwares-initial-access-expert-extradited-to-the-us/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Adds Passkey Login Support to Facebook for Android and iOS Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-adds-passkey-login-support-to.html</link>
      <description>Meta Platforms is adding support for passkeys on Facebook, allowing users to securely sign in with biometrics or device lock PIN code. This passwordless authentication solution is resistant to guessing or theft by malicious websites and effective against phishing and password spraying attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-adds-passkey-login-support-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Next SSRF Flaw in Cloudflare Lets Hackers Fetch Data from Any Host</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/open-next-ssrf-flaw-in-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: @opennextjs/cloudflare; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6087; Summary: The @opennextjs/cloudflare package contains a critical Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to proxy arbitrary remote content through the vulnerable site's domain, posing risks of phishing, data exposure, and domain abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142923</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 05:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Reset Link Poisoning Leads to Full Account Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/password-reset-link-poisoning/</link>
      <description>A critical vulnerability known as Password Reset Link Poisoning enables attackers to manipulate the domain in password reset links, redirecting users to malicious sites and capturing sensitive reset tokens. This allows for full account takeover, exposing web users and organizations to serious risks such as account takeover, phishing, and reputational damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142918</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 05:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Linux Flaws Enable Full Root Access via PAM and Udisks Across Major Distributions</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-linux-flaws-enable-full-root-access.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Qualys PAM and libblockdev; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two local privilege escalation (LPE) flaws were discovered by Qualys that can be exploited to gain root privileges on machines running major Linux distributions. CVE-2025-6018 allows an unprivileged user to elevate to the "allow_active" user and call Polkit actions, while CVE-2025-6019 enables an "allow_active" user to gain full root privileges by chaining it with CVE-2025-6018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-linux-flaws-enable-full-root-access.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAT V2: Updated DRAT Emerges in TAG-140’s Arsenal</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/drat-v2-updated-drat-emerges-tag-140s-arsenal</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a cybersecurity analysis report on the DRAT V2 malware used by the TAG-140 group. The report provides an in-depth analysis of the malware's technical and operational details, including its command structure, C2 obfuscation techniques, and communication protocol.

The report highlights several key differences between the original DRAT and DRAT V2 variants, such as the use of different command naming conventions, changes to system information response formats, and modifications to C2 obfuscation patterns. The analysis also notes that while both versions use Base64 encoding for C2 information, DRAT V2 prepends additional strings to the IP address prior to encoding, which may serve as rudimentary integrity checks or prevent trivial decoding by analysts and automated tools.

The report provides several detection rules and guidelines for security teams to detect and monitor TAG-140 activity, including Snort rules for detecting outbound C2 communication, Sigma rules for detecting persistence via registry run keys, and YARA rules for detecting files containing strings associated with the BroaderAspect malware. The analysis concludes that while DRAT V2 exhibits limited use of defensive evasion or anti-analysis techniques, security teams should remain vigilant and anticipate continued experimentation with malware tooling and infection chains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/drat-v2-updated-drat-emerges-tag-140s-arsenal</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Israel hackers hit Iran's Nobitex exchange, burn $90M in crypto</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-israel-hackers-hit-irans-nobitex-exchange-burn-90m-in-crypto/</link>
      <description>The "Predatory Sparrow" hacking group claims to have stolen over $90 million in cryptocurrency from Nobitex, Iran's largest crypto exchange, and intentionally burnt the funds by sending them to vanity addresses. The attack is believed to be politically motivated, with ties to the IRGC and Iranian leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-israel-hackers-hit-irans-nobitex-exchange-burn-90m-in-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Address bar shows hp.com. Browser displays scammers’ malicious text anyway.</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/tech-support-scammers-inject-malicious-phone-numbers-into-big-name-websites/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a scam that injects fake phone numbers into official websites through Google ads. Scammers buy ads with appended parameters that are not displayed in the ad itself, making it difficult for users to suspect anything is amiss. The injected phone number appears legitimate and can trick users into revealing personal or financial information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/tech-support-scammers-inject-malicious-phone-numbers-into-big-name-websites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean hackers deepfake execs in Zoom call to spread Mac malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-deepfake-execs-in-zoom-call-to-spread-mac-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BlueNoroff; CVE(s): None; Summary: The North Korean BlueNoroff hacking group is using deepfakes to trick employees into installing custom malware on their macOS devices. The attack involves a fake Zoom meeting and the installation of an AppleScript file that downloads a secondary payload, which includes malicious binaries such as Telegram 2, Root Troy V4, a (InjectWithDyld), XScreen (keyboardd), and CryptoBot (airmond).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-deepfake-execs-in-zoom-call-to-spread-mac-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-408: PEAK-System Driver PCANFD_ADD_FILTERS Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-408/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PEAK-System Driver PCANFD_ADD_FILTERS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6217; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PEAK-System Driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which is due to a lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24161</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chollima Hackers Target Windows and MacOS with New GolangGhost RAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chollima-hackers-target-windows-and-macos/</link>
      <description>The Famous Chollima group has launched a sophisticated remote access trojan (RAT) campaign targeting Windows and MacOS devices, with a focus on professionals in cryptocurrency and blockchain technologies. The attackers use a two-pronged strategy, creating fake job interview platforms to lure victims into executing malicious commands that download and launch the PylangGhost or GolangGhost variants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142888</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Revolutionizes PLA Military Intelligence with Rapid Deployment Across Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-revolutionizes-pla-military-intelligence/</link>
      <description>The People's Liberation Army (PLA) of China is adopting generative artificial intelligence (AI) to enhance its military operations, using advanced large language models (LLMs) for data processing, intelligence analysis, and decision-making support. This integration poses risks such as hallucination issues, ideological bias, and counterintelligence concerns, highlighting the need for rigorous experimentation and outcome assessment to ensure effective application of AI tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142881</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s Digital Arsenal: The Strategic Use of Private Companies and Hacktivists in Cyber Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/the-strategic-use-of-private-companies-and-hacktivists/</link>
      <description>Russia's sophisticated cyber warfare strategy emerges as a calculated blend of state power and non-state agility, leveraging private companies, hacktivists, and criminal proxies to amplify its digital dominance. The strategy involves concentric rings with state agencies at the core and a diverse array of non-state actors, including private IT firms, hacktivist groups, and eCrime collectives, which offers Moscow cost efficiency, flexibility, and access to cutting-edge skills, but also risks unpredictability and blurs the line between state and non-state action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142872</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A week with a "smart" car</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/a-week-with-a-smart-car/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the author's experience with advanced vehicle systems in a new car, highlighting issues with constant alerts and difficulty disabling features. It also touches on the importance of user experience and frictionless security tools.

FYSA: Cisco Talos has discovered that the North Korean-aligned threat actor Famous Chollima is targeting cryptocurrency and blockchain professionals through sophisticated phishing campaigns using Python-based malware (PylangGhost) and Golang-based variants. The campaign highlights the constant evolution of threat actors' tools, emphasizing the need for robust defenses and user education.

FYSA: AI scraping bots are breaking into libraries, archives, museums, and galleries, causing some collections to go offline. Additionally, a cybercriminal group leaked 7.4 million citizen records in Paraguay on the dark web, demanding $7.4 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68519c74813ef3000192102a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Security Honored with 2025 MSP Today Product of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/halo-security-honored-with-2025-msp-today-product-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <description>Halo Security's Attack Surface Management Platform has been named a 2025 MSP Today Product of the Year Award winner for its innovation, performance, and measurable impact on customers and partners alike. The platform enables organizations to discover, monitor, and secure their internet-facing assets, combining attacker-like discovery methods with ongoing security monitoring and vulnerability scanning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142902</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Fake CAPTCHA Windows Stealthily Install LightPerlGirl Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-captcha-windows-stealthily-install-lightperlgirl-malware/</link>
      <description>A newly identified malware strain, LightPerlGirl, uses deceptive fake CAPTCHA popups to infiltrate systems. It propagates through a social engineering tactic called the ClickFix attack, bypassing traditional security measures and exploiting user interaction. The attack begins with a compromised legitimate website serving malicious JavaScript, which triggers a fake CAPTCHA popup, tricking users into executing an obfuscated PowerShell command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142848</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Malware Campaign Uses Cloudflare Tunnels to Deliver RATs via Phishing Chains</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-malware-campaign-uses-cloudflare.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a new campaign using Cloudflare Tunnel subdomains to host malicious payloads and deliver them via phishing emails. The attack starts with sending payment-themed emails bearing a link to a zipped document containing a Windows shortcut file, which activates the infection sequence. The payload is executed in memory, allowing for evasion of detection.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-malware-campaign-uses-cloudflare.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 to block file access via legacy auth protocols by default</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-to-block-file-access-via-legacy-auth-protocols-by-default/</link>
      <description>This article does not mention a specific vulnerability. Instead, it discusses Microsoft's announcement to update security defaults for all Microsoft 365 tenants to block access to SharePoint, OneDrive, and Office files via legacy authentication protocols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-to-block-file-access-via-legacy-auth-protocols-by-default/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stargazers' use fake Minecraft mods to steal player passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stargazers-use-fake-minecraft-mods-to-steal-player-passwords/</link>
      <description>A large-scale malware campaign targets Minecraft players by distributing malicious mods and cheats that infect Windows devices with info-stealers. The campaign uses GitHub as a distribution platform, disguising the malware as legitimate Minecraft content, and can steal credentials, authentication tokens, and cryptocurrency wallets.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in this article, but rather a malicious campaign using social engineering tactics to spread malware to victims' devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stargazers-use-fake-minecraft-mods-to-steal-player-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500+ Minecraft Players Infected by Java Malware Masquerading as Game Mods on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/1500-minecraft-players-infected-by-java.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a multi-stage malware campaign targeting Minecraft users, which employs a Java-based malware using a distribution-as-service (DaaS) offering called Stargazers Ghost Network. The campaign's end goal is to trick players into downloading a Minecraft mod from GitHub and deliver a .NET information stealer with comprehensive data theft capabilities.

FYSA: The article highlights the use of an illicit offering, the Stargazers Ghost Network, which makes use of thousands of GitHub accounts to set up tainted repositories that masquerade as cracked software and game cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/1500-minecraft-players-infected-by-java.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainLink Phishing: How Trusted Domains Become Threat Vectors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chainlink-phishing-how-trusted-domains-become-threat-vectors/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolution of phishing attacks, specifically "ChainLink Phishing", which uses trusted infrastructure to funnel victims through a series of credible-looking prompts before harvesting credentials. It highlights how traditional defenses are insufficient against these attacks and emphasizes the need for real-time analysis of web pages and user interactions to effectively mitigate threats like zero-hour phishing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chainlink-phishing-how-trusted-domains-become-threat-vectors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA warns of attackers exploiting Linux flaw with PoC exploit</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-attackers-exploiting-linux-flaw-with-poc-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux kernel's OverlayFS subsystem; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) in the Linux kernel's OverlayFS subsystem allows attackers to gain root privileges. The flaw, caused by improper ownership management, was patched in January 2023 and publicly disclosed two months later. Multiple proof-of-concept exploits were shared on GitHub, making exploitation attempts easier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-attackers-exploiting-linux-flaw-with-poc-exploit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare SaaS firm says data breach impacts 5.4 million patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/episource-says-data-breach-impacts-54-million-patients/</link>
      <description>Episource, a healthcare services company, has reported a data breach that affected over 5 million people in the United States. The breach occurred between January 27 and February 6, 2025, when hackers accessed and exfiltrated sensitive health information, including full names, physical addresses, medical records, and social security numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/episource-says-data-breach-impacts-54-million-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperCard Malware Hijacks Android Devices to Steal Payment Card Data and Relay it to Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/supercard-malware-hijacks-android-devices/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the emergence of SuperCard, a malicious modification of the legitimate NFCGate program, which exploits Near Field Communication (NFC) traffic to intercept sensitive bank card data. The malware is distributed via a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) platform named SuperCard X and targets Android users globally, with recent attacks recorded in Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142823</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zyxel NWA50AX Pro Hit by N-Day Flaw Allowing Arbitrary File Deletion</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zyxel-nwa50ax-pro-hit-by-n-day-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zyxel NWA50AX Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2024-29974; Summary: The Zyxel NWA50AX Pro WiFi 6 access point contains an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability (CVE-2024-29974) that allows attackers to delete files without authentication by crafting a POST request with manipulated parameters. This can lead to further attacks, such as replacing configuration or password files, potentially causing privilege escalation or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142854</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Transit Mode in Apple Pay and GPay to Steal Money</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-apple-pay-and-gpay/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mobile Wallets (Apple Pay, Google Pay); CVE(s): None; Summary: The Express Transit mode in mobile wallets like Apple Pay and Google Pay allows for automatic charges without biometric checks or alerts, making it vulnerable to exploitation by hackers who can drain funds instantly and silently. Attackers can grab unlocked phones, mimic legitimate behavior, and exploit weak PINs to steal money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142853</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Enhances Office 365 Defender to Stop Email Bombing Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/office-365-defender-to-stop-email-bombing-campaigns/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new feature called Mail Bombing Detection in Microsoft Office 365 Defender, designed to combat email bombing attacks by automatically identifying and blocking massive volumes of emails. This feature is enabled by default and does not require manual configuration, providing enhanced protection against email-based threats without additional administrative overhead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142852</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITRE and Splunk Expose Critical Vulnerabilities in Open Source GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitre-and-splunk-expose-critical-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub Actions; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47928; Summary: The GitHub Actions workflows of several high-profile open source projects were found to be vulnerable due to the misuse of the pull_request_target trigger. This vulnerability allows attackers to access sensitive secrets and high-privilege tokens, potentially leading to full repository takeovers. The vulnerability was exploited in projects like spotipy-dev/spotipy and MITRE's Cyber Analytics Repository (CAR).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142812</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RapperBot Botnet Surges with 50,000+ Attacks Targeting Network Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rapperbot-botnet-surges-with-50000-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The RapperBot botnet has resurfaced with over 50,000 attacks targeting network edge devices, exploiting vulnerabilities in IoT devices such as routers, IP cameras, and other connected hardware. The botnet uses brute-force techniques and exploits known vulnerabilities to compromise devices, establishing persistence by downloading additional payloads and conducting DDoS attacks or serving as a gateway for further malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142777</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMV-Style Phishing Scams Target U.S. Citizens to Harvest Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dmv-style-phishing-scams-target-u-s-citizens/</link>
      <description>A highly coordinated phishing campaign targeting U.S. citizens has been discovered, utilizing SMS phishing (smishing) and impersonating state Departments of Motor Vehicles (DMVs). The attack threatened license suspension or legal action and attempted to steal personal information by directing victims to fake DMV websites. The campaign is attributed to a China-based threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142746</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware Unveils Cloud Foundation 9.0 With AI and Next-Gen Workloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-unveils-cloud-foundation-9-0/</link>
      <description>VMware has announced the general availability of VMware Cloud Foundation (VCF) 9.0, a private cloud technology designed to meet the demands of AI, data-intensive workloads, and modern enterprise operations. The new release offers a unified platform that merges the speed and flexibility of cloud with the performance, governance, and cost control required for on-premises environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142782</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedRAMP at Startup Speed: Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fedramp-at-startup-speed-lessons-learned.html</link>
      <description>None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fedramp-at-startup-speed-lessons-learned.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Vulnerabilities Enable Arbitrary Code Execution – Update Now!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-chrome-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): None; Summary: The update addresses three high-severity vulnerabilities, including an integer overflow in V8 and a use-after-free in Profiler, which could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, potentially leading to data theft or system compromise. If exploited, these vulnerabilities could enable attackers to bypass security controls and take control of a user's system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142773</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water Curse Hijacks 76 GitHub Accounts to Deliver Multi-Stage Malware Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/water-curse-hijacks-76-github-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Water Curse is a financially motivated threat actor that uses weaponized GitHub repositories to deliver multi-stage malware, enabling data exfiltration, remote access, and long-term persistence on infected systems. The actor's arsenal includes various tools and programming languages, and they employ anti-debugging techniques, privilege escalation methods, and persistence mechanisms to maintain a foothold on affected hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/water-curse-hijacks-76-github-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackHat AI Tool WormGPT Enhanced with Grok and Mixtral</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wormgpt-enhanced-with-grok-and-mixtral/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WormGPT; CVE(s): None; Summary: WormGPT is a notorious blackhat AI tool that has resurfaced in enhanced forms powered by advanced language models such as xAI's Grok and Mistral AI's Mixtral. The tool allows for the generation of human-like text, enabling malicious activities, and its variants have been introduced on underground forums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142766</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondTrust warns of pre-auth RCE in Remote Support software</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beyondtrust-warns-of-pre-auth-rce-in-remote-support-software/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BeyondTrust Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA) solutions; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5309; Summary: A high-severity Server-Side Template Injection vulnerability in the chat feature of BeyondTrust RS/PRA allows unauthenticated attackers to gain remote code execution on vulnerable servers. Exploitation does not require authentication, and administrators can mitigate the risk by enabling SAML authentication and enforcing session keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beyondtrust-warns-of-pre-auth-rce-in-remote-support-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-402: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-402/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 file parsing vulnerability is a stack-based buffer overflow that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, requiring user interaction. This occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25942</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When legitimate tools go rogue</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/when-legitimate-tools-go-rogue/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the trend of attackers using legitimate software, such as system tools (e.g., whoami, nltest, and nslookup) and remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools (e.g., ScreenConnect or AnyDesk), to carry out malicious actions. This tactic is referred to as "living off the land binaries" (LOLBins). The article highlights the importance of asset management, behavioral baselining, continuous monitoring, and threat intel alignment in detecting these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68517e4b813ef30001920ffc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-403: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-403/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26020</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-404: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-404/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26022</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-405: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-405/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 has a file parsing stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from improper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-406: SolarWinds Serv-U FTP Service Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-406/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds Serv-U; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45711; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of SolarWinds Serv-U. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25087</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-407: SolarWinds Web Help Desk AjaxProxy Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-407/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds Web Help Desk; CVE(s): CVE-2024-28988; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of SolarWinds Web Help Desk without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the AjaxProxy due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25346</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous Chollima deploying Python version of GolangGhost RAT</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/python-version-of-golangghost-rat/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Python-based remote access trojan (RAT) called "PylangGhost" used by a North Korean-aligned threat actor, Famous Chollima. The RAT targets employees with experience in cryptocurrency and blockchain technologies and is designed to steal browser credentials and session cookies from over 80 extensions, including password managers and cryptocurrency wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6851323e813ef30001920f8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Emerges as a Major Threat Targeting Windows, Linux, and ESXi Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-ransomware-emerges-as-a-major-threat/</link>
      <description>Qilin ransomware has emerged as a significant threat, leveraging a sophisticated Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model and advanced technical capabilities to target Windows, Linux, and ESXi systems. Its features include custom-built malware, configurable encryption modes, and services like data storage, spam tools, and legal assistance, positioning it as a comprehensive cybercrime ecosystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142720</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Leverage ClickFix Strategy to Deploy RATs and Data-Stealing Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-leverage-clickfix-strategy-to-deploy-rats/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting a social engineering technique called ClickFix to initiate multi-stage cyberattacks, delivering remote access trojans (RATs) and data-stealing malware with alarming efficiency. The technique manipulates users into executing malicious PowerShell commands by disguising them as routine prompts like CAPTCHA verifications or browser updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142689</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Privilege Escalation Flaws Grant Full Root Access on Multiple Linux Distros</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-privilege-escalation-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SUSE 15, openSUSE Leap 15; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two interconnected local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities enable attackers to gain full root access on a wide range of Linux distributions with minimal effort. The flaws impact both desktop and server installations, requiring only a local user session such as SSH for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142693</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Winos 4.0 Malware Strain Emerges as Major Threat to Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-winos-4-0-malware-strain-emerges-as-major-threat/</link>
      <description>FortiGuard Labs has uncovered a new strain of malware, dubbed Winos 4.0, targeting Microsoft Windows users with a focus on individuals in Taiwan, utilizing phishing tactics and masquerading as government or business entities; the malware is designed to steal sensitive user data and maintain persistence through registry keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142680</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Linux udisks flaw lets attackers get root on major Linux distros</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/new-linux-udisks-flaw-lets-attackers-get-root-on-major-linux-distros/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: openSUSE Leap 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise 15, Ubuntu, Debian, Fedora; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities were discovered in the Pluggable Authentication Modules (PAM) framework and libblockdev. Exploiting these flaws allows attackers to gain root privileges on systems running major Linux distributions, enabling agent tampering, persistence, and lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/new-linux-udisks-flaw-lets-attackers-get-root-on-major-linux-distros/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Claim Breach of Scania Financial Services, Leak Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-claim-breach-of-scania-financial-services/</link>
      <description>A threat actor claiming to be "hensi" infiltrated the subdomain insurance.scania.com of Scania Financial Services, exfiltrating sensitive files containing personal, financial, and potentially medical data. The breach is believed to have occurred when attackers exploited credentials belonging to an external IT partner using infostealer malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142688</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asana warns MCP AI feature exposed customer data to other orgs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asana-warns-mcp-ai-feature-exposed-customer-data-to-other-orgs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Asana; CVE(s): None; Summary: A logic flaw in the Model Context Protocol (MCP) feature of Asana's work management platform potentially exposed data from one organization to another, including task-level information and project metadata. The exposure occurred for over a month before being discovered on June 4 and has impacted around 1,000 customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asana-warns-mcp-ai-feature-exposed-customer-data-to-other-orgs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-23121: Critical RCE Vulnerability Patched in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-23121-rce-patched-veeam-backup-replication/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Backup &amp; Replication; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121 (CVSS 9.9), CVE-2025-24286 (CVSS 7.2), CVE-2025-24287 (CVSS 6.1); Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVE-2025-23121) allows authenticated domain users to remotely execute arbitrary code on Veeam Backup Servers, affecting systems that are domain-joined. Additionally, two other vulnerabilities were discovered, one allowing modification of backup jobs and another allowing local system users to modify directory contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061066</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts to Active Exploits of Linux Kernel Improper Ownership Management Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-to-active-exploits-of-linux-kernel-improper-ownership-management-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Linux distributions; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A critical Linux kernel vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) allows local users to escalate privileges and potentially gain root-level access. The flaw emerges when a user copies a file with special capabilities from a nosuid mount into another mount, due to the kernel's failure to properly clear setuid and setgid bits during the copy-up operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142676</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA Analyst Sentenced to 37 Months for Leaking Top Secret National Defense Documents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ex-cia-analyst-sentenced-to-37-months.html</link>
      <description>A former CIA analyst, Asif William Rahman, was sentenced to 37 months in prison for stealing and transmitting classified National Defense Information (NDI) without authorization. He retained multiple Secret and Top Secret documents on October 17, 2024, and wilfully sent them to individuals who did not have the necessary clearance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ex-cia-analyst-sentenced-to-37-months.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Warns of Active Exploitation of Linux Kernel Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: The Linux kernel contains an improper ownership management vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) that can be exploited to escalate privileges on susceptible systems. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 7.8, allows a local user to create SUID binaries owned by root and execute them, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Gerrit Platform Flaw Exposes 18 Google Projects, Including ChromiumOS, to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/googles-gerrit-platform-flaw-exposes-18-google-projects/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Gerrit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1568; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Google's Gerrit code-collaboration platform allows unauthorized code submissions by hackers, putting at least 18 major Google projects at risk. The flaw centers on misconfigured permissions and logic flaws in the review process, enabling attackers to inject malicious code without detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142671</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Patches CVE-2025-23121: Critical RCE Bug Rated 9.9 CVSS in Backup &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/veeam-patches-cve-2025-23121-critical.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121, CVE-2025-24286, CVE-2025-24287; Summary: A critical security flaw (CVE-2025-23121) in Veeam's Backup &amp; Replication software allows remote code execution under certain conditions. Another flaw (CVE-2025-24286) permits an authenticated user to modify backup jobs and execute arbitrary code, while a third vulnerability (CVE-2025-24287) enables local system users to modify directory contents and execute code with elevated permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/veeam-patches-cve-2025-23121-critical.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Slows Internet to Prevent Cyber Attacks Amid Escalating Regional Conflict</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-restricts-internet-access-to.html</link>
      <description>Iranian government has throttled internet access in the country, allegedly to prevent Israel's covert cyber operations. This development is part of an escalating digital conflict between Iran and Israel, with both sides engaging in retaliatory cyber attacks. The conflict also involves threat actors affiliated with Iran, who have launched malicious activities against U.S. critical infrastructure using IOCONTROL malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-restricts-internet-access-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Vulnerabilities Expose Backup Servers to Remote Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/veeam-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121, CVE-2025-24286, CVE-2025-24287; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-23121) allows remote code execution on a Veeam Backup Server, while two other vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-24286 and CVE-2025-24287) enable privilege escalation and local privilege escalation in the Veeam Agent for Microsoft Windows, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142667</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix NetScaler ADC &amp; Gateway Flaws Expose Sensitive Data to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/citrix-netscaler-adc-gateway-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5349, CVE-2025-5777; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities have been discovered in Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to critical management functions or read sensitive memory contents. The flaws can be exploited remotely and put enterprise networks at significant risk of data leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142663</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats to the 2025 NATO Summit</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/threats-2025-nato-summit</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a cybersecurity threat analysis report focused on Russian hybrid warfare tactics and potential threats to European critical infrastructure ahead of the 2025 NATO Summit. The report highlights various forms of sabotage, vandalism, and coercive military actions that Russia may employ to destabilize NATO member states.

Key findings include:

1. Russian-directed sabotage attacks targeting submarine cables in the Baltic Sea have increased since 2022.
2. Moscow is likely to continue attempting to weaponize refugee flows to foment domestic unrest and exploit concerns about immigration in countries bordering Russia and Belarus.
3. The Kremlin may increase its military presence and intelligence capabilities near Finland and the Baltic states.
4. Coercive military actions via incursions into NATO airspace will likely increase ahead of the 2025 NATO Summit.

The report concludes by emphasizing that Russian hybrid threats will continue to target European critical infrastructure, particularly in countries bordering Russia, if there is no significant action regarding Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/threats-2025-nato-summit</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity takes a big hit in new Trump executive order</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybersecurity-take-a-big-hit-in-new-trump-executive-order/</link>
      <description>FYSA:
The article discusses the impact of a recent Executive Order (EO) issued by former US President Trump on cybersecurity governance and regulations. The EO rolled back several requirements aimed at improving cybersecurity, including those related to quantum-resistant algorithms, Border Gateway Protocol security, and digital identity documents. Experts warn that these changes will weaken cybersecurity efforts and create vulnerabilities in existing infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybersecurity-take-a-big-hit-in-new-trump-executive-order/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paddle settles for $5 million over facilitating tech support scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paddle-settles-for-5-million-over-facilitating-tech-support-scams/</link>
      <description>Paddle.com and its US subsidiary will pay $5 million to settle FTC allegations that the company facilitated deceptive tech-support schemes that harmed many US consumers, including older adults. The schemes used fake virus alerts and pop-up warnings to lure consumers into buying unneeded software or tech support services, with Paddle processing over $37 million in transactions for affiliated merchants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paddle-settles-for-5-million-over-facilitating-tech-support-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-398: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-398/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49384; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations by creating a symbolic link, which can be used to delete files. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25876</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
