<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:02:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft warns of Windows update delays due to wrong timestamp</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-of-Windows-security-update-delays-due-to-incorrect-metadata-timestamp/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A known issue with incorrect metadata timestamp causes delivery delays for June 2025 Windows security updates on Windows 10 and Windows 11 systems using quality update deferral policies. This delay affects the timing of update availability, but does not impact the quality or applicability of the update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-of-Windows-security-update-delays-due-to-incorrect-metadata-timestamp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol helps disrupt $540 million crypto investment fraud ring</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-helps-disrupt-540-million-crypto-investment-fraud-ring/</link>
      <description>Spanish authorities have arrested five individuals suspected of laundering $540 million from illegal cryptocurrency investment schemes and defrauding over 5,000 victims. The investigation involved multiple countries, including Estonia, France, the U.S., and Europol. The operation also highlighted the growing use of artificial intelligence (AI) in scams, with Europol warning that online fraud is expected to surpass all other types of organized fraud in the coming years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-helps-disrupt-540-million-crypto-investment-fraud-ring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Cybercriminals steal health data posing as fraud investigators</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-cybercriminals-steal-health-data-posing-as-fraud-investigators/</link>
      <description>The FBI warns Americans of cybercriminals impersonating health fraud investigators to steal sensitive information. Scammers are emailing or messaging victims, disguising themselves as legitimate health insurers and investigative team members, to pressure them into providing personal or health data for fraudulent purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-cybercriminals-steal-health-data-posing-as-fraud-investigators/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and Partners Urge Critical Infrastructure to Stay Vigilant in the Current Geopolitical Environment</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/30/cisa-and-partners-urge-critical-infrastructure-stay-vigilant-current-geopolitical-environment</link>
      <description>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), in collaboration with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Department of Defense Cyber Crime Center (DC3), and the National Security Agency (NSA), released a Fact Sheet warning organizations to be vigilant against potential targeted cyber operations by Iranian state-sponsored or affiliated threat actors. The advisory recommends mitigations such as disconnecting operational technology devices from the public internet, using strong passwords, applying software patches, and implementing phishing-resistant multifactor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23558</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,200 Citrix servers unpatched against critical auth bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-200-citrix-servers-unpatched-against-critical-auth-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: Over 1,200 unpatched Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway appliances are vulnerable to a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) allowing threat actors to bypass authentication by hijacking user sessions. This out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability enables unauthenticated attackers to access restricted memory regions, potentially stealing session tokens, credentials, and other sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-200-citrix-servers-unpatched-against-critical-auth-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Posts Advertise Access to British Firms &amp; Data from Brazil, France, and CETDIGIT</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/access-british-firms-data-from-brazil-france-cetdigit/</link>
      <description>Multiple threats have been discovered on the dark web, including unauthorized access sales targeting British firms, leaked insurance data from Brazil, stolen French credit card records, and a large-scale database breach allegedly involving U.S.-based CRM provider CETDIGIT. The threats offer various types of compromised data, including remote command execution, file management, screen sharing, and personal metadata.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061436</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Credentials As Unique Identifiers: A Pragmatic Approach To NHI Inventories</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/leveraging-credentials-as-unique.html</link>
      <description>Non-human identities (NHIs) are becoming increasingly common in modern enterprises, outnumbering human identities by at least 50 to one. NHIs require unique identifiers, which are often their access keys. The article highlights the importance of securing machine identities and treating secrets as a mechanism to uniquely identify and govern non-human actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/leveraging-credentials-as-unique.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Airline Hacks, Citrix 0-Day, Outlook Malware, Banking Trojans and more</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-airline-hacks-citrix-0-day.html</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be a cybersecurity news roundup featuring various security-related topics, including vulnerabilities, attacks, and best practices. There are no specific software, hardware, or firmware products being discussed that I could identify as vulnerable.

However, some of the topics mentioned in the article do warrant attention from a cybersecurity perspective. For instance, the discussion on memory-safe languages (MSLs) such as Rust highlights the importance of language-level protections to mitigate memory-related vulnerabilities. Additionally, the mention of ultrasonic covert communication attacks and the use of smartwatches as receivers for these types of attacks serves as a reminder of the need for robust security measures in air-gapped environments.

In general, it is essential to stay informed about emerging cybersecurity threats and best practices to ensure the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-airline-hacks-citrix-0-day.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google rolls out Veo 3 video generator, try it for free using credits</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-veo-3-video-generator-try-it-for-free-using-credits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: This article contains no cybersecurity-relevant content. It appears to be a collection of news and updates from Google regarding various products and services, including Veo 3, Vertex AI, Tines, and others. There are no discussions of vulnerabilities, threats, or best practices for cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-veo-3-video-generator-try-it-for-free-using-credits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth flaws could let hackers spy through your microphone</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-flaws-could-let-hackers-spy-through-your-microphone/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Airoha systems on a chip (SoCs); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20700, CVE-2025-20701, CVE-2025-20702; Summary: Three vulnerabilities in the Airoha SoCs, affecting more than two dozen audio devices from ten vendors, can be exploited for eavesdropping or stealing sensitive information. The issues allow an attacker to take over a vulnerable product and extract call history and contacts on some phones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-flaws-could-let-hackers-spy-through-your-microphone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare open-sources Orange Meets with End-to-End encryption</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-open-sources-orange-meets-with-end-to-end-encryption/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article discusses Cloudflare's Orange Meets video calling app, which has implemented end-to-end encryption (E2EE) using Messaging Layer Security (MLS). The implementation enables continuous group key agreement, supporting secure group key exchange, forward secrecy, post-compromise security, and scalability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-open-sources-orange-meets-with-end-to-end-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Transform GIFTEDCROOK Stealer into an Intelligence-Gathering Tool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-transform-giftedcrook-stealer/</link>
      <description>GIFTEDCROOK infostealer, wielded by UAC-0226 threat group, has undergone rapid evolution from a rudimentary browser data stealer to a sophisticated intelligence-gathering tool. The malware's capabilities include exfiltrating proprietary documents and browser secrets, with the goal of supporting covert intelligence objectives during periods of diplomatic and military significance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144594</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Encrypt ends certificate expiry emails to cut costs, boost privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lets-encrypt-ends-certificate-expiry-emails-to-cut-costs-boost-privacy/</link>
      <description>Let's Encrypt has announced it will no longer send email notifications about certificate expirations due to high costs, privacy concerns, and unnecessary complexities. This decision is a result of the increasing adoption of automated renewal solutions and standards changes reducing certificate lifespans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lets-encrypt-ends-certificate-expiry-emails-to-cut-costs-boost-privacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Warns Cybercriminals Are Targeting NFC Data for Contactless Payments</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eset-warns-cybercriminals-are-targeting-nfc-data/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated attack vector exploiting Near Field Communication (NFC) data, initially targeting Czech banking customers but now spreading worldwide. Cybercriminals are using a tool called NFCGate to capture card data when victims place their cards near their smartphones, enabling attackers to emulate the card on their devices for unauthorized transactions or cash withdrawals. The attacks rely on social engineering and phishing attempts, and users can mitigate risks by setting low limits on contactless payment transactions, using RFID blockers, and deploying robust cybersecurity solutions like ESET HOME Security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144587</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Windows and Linux Server Vulnerabilities to Deploy Web Shells</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-windows-and-linux-server-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting file upload vulnerabilities to deploy web shells and advanced malware on Windows and Linux systems. The attack chain involves using tools like MeshAgent, SuperShell, and WogRAT to gain initial access, persistence, and lateral movement, ultimately allowing for command execution, reconnaissance, and potential data exfiltration or ransomware deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144576</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-448: (0Day) Mescius ActiveReports.NET ReadValue Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-448/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mescius ActiveReports.NET; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6810; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Mescius ActiveReports.NET through deserialization of untrusted data in the ReadValue method. The vulnerability can be exploited by interacting with the library, and attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25246</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-449: (0Day) Mescius ActiveReports.NET TypeResolutionService Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-449/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mescius ActiveReports.NET; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6811; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Mescius ActiveReports.NET by deserializing untrusted data. The issue exists within the TypeResolutionService class due to a lack of proper validation, which can be exploited to run code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25397</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-450: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole QLogicDownloadImpl Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion and Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-450/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6793; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files and disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the QLogicDownloadImpl class due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24912</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-451: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getAppFileBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-451/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6796; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage this to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24916</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-452: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole compressDriverFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-452/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6803; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited by an attacker to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24923</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-453: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole compressFirmwareDumpFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-453/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6804; Summary: The Marvell QConvergeConsole has an information disclosure vulnerability due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability without authentication, disclosing sensitive information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24924</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-454: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole saveAsText Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-454/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6794; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the saveAsText method, resulting from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24913</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-455: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadSize Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-455/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6795; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The issue arises from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24914</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-456: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-456/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6797; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the getFileUploadBytes method, which fails to properly validate user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24917</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-457: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole deleteAppFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-457/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6798; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited to delete files in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24918</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-458: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-458/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6799; Summary: The Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes method contains a directory traversal information disclosure vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24919</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-459: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole restoreESwitchConfig Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-459/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6800; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24920</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-460: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole saveNICParamsToFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-460/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6801; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication, by exploiting the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24921</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-461: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole deleteEventLogFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-461/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6805; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24925</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-462: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole decryptFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-462/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6806; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, affecting the decryptFile method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24979</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-463: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getDriverTmpPath Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-463/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6807; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It exists in the implementation of the getDriverTmpPath method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations, allowing an attacker to disclose SYSTEM-level information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24980</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-464: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileFromURL Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-464/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6802; Summary: The getFileFromURL method in the Marvell QConvergeConsole has an unrestricted file upload vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24922</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-465: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole readObjectFromConfigFile Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-465/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell, QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6808; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the readObjectFromConfigFile method, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25217</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-466: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole readNICParametersFromFile Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-466/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6809; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25218</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Trending TikTok Videos Promoting Pirated Apps That Deliver Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-trending-tiktok-videos-promoting-pirated-apps/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated social engineering campaign has surfaced on TikTok, leveraging AI-generated videos to distribute information-stealing malware Vidar and StealC. The campaign uses instructional videos to socially engineer victims into executing malicious PowerShell commands under the guise of activating pirated software, making it harder for traditional security tools to detect and block the threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144539</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Warns of Scattered Spider's Expanding Attacks on Airlines Using Social Engineering</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fbi-warns-of-scattered-spiders.html</link>
      <description>The FBI has revealed that the cybercrime group Scattered Spider is targeting the airline sector, using social engineering techniques to gain access and steal data. The group also targets third-party IT providers, putting trusted vendors at risk of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fbi-warns-of-scattered-spiders.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized DeepSeek Installers Deploy Sainbox RAT and Hidden Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-deepseek-installers/</link>
      <description>Fake software installers mimicking popular tools like DeepSeek, Sogou, and WPS Office are exploited to deliver malware payloads such as the Sainbox RAT (Gh0stRAT variant) and Hidden rootkit. The attack begins with phishing websites designed to mirror legitimate software portals, tricking users into downloading malicious installers that sideload a malware payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144557</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Exploit CapCut Popularity to Steal Apple ID Credentials and Credit Card Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-exploit-capcut-popularity/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have launched a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting CapCut users by impersonating legitimate invoices to extract Apple ID credentials and credit card information. The attack involves multiple stages, including a fake login page, credit card data request, and authentication code prompt, all designed to maximize the extraction of sensitive data while delaying suspicion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144525</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFTEDCROOK Malware Evolves: From Browser Stealer to Intelligence-Gathering Tool</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/giftedcrook-malware-evolves-from.html</link>
      <description>The GIFTEDCROOK malware has been updated to a potent intelligence-gathering tool, capable of exfiltrating sensitive documents from targeted devices, including proprietary files and browser secrets. The malware is used by the threat actor UAC-0226 to target Ukrainian governmental and military entities through phishing emails containing macro-laced Microsoft Excel documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/giftedcrook-malware-evolves-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook’s New AI Tool Asks to Upload Your Photos for Story Ideas, Sparking Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/facebooks-new-ai-tool-requests-photo.html</link>
      <description>Meta's new AI feature on Facebook allows users to upload photos from their phones to suggest collages, recaps, and other ideas using artificial intelligence. The feature is opt-in and can be disabled at any time, but experts have concerns about user privacy, as the processing happens in the cloud and there are risks with facial recognition and hidden details such as time or location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/facebooks-new-ai-tool-requests-photo.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Passlib Python Package Triggers Windows Shutdowns with Invalid Inputs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-passlib-python-package-triggers-windows-shutdowns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: umaraq psslib; CVE(s): None; Summary: The psslib package is a malicious Python library that poses as a legitimate password security solution. It can cause an immediate system shutdown on Windows environments when users input incorrect passwords, exploiting developer trust in security tools. The package remains active on the PyPI registry, highlighting the persistent danger of supply chain attacks in open-source ecosystems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144517</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Clickfix Tactics to Deploy Malicious AppleScripts for Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-clickfix-tactics-to-deploy-malicious-applescripts/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign called Odyssey Stealer has been discovered, targeting macOS users through a deceptive method known as Clickfix tactics. The malware harvests sensitive data, including browser cookies, saved passwords, cryptocurrency wallet information, and browser extensions, posing a severe threat to individuals engaged in financial and crypto activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144605</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Clickfix Tactics to Deploy Malicious AppleScripts for Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-clickfix-tactics/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign called Odyssey Stealer has been discovered targeting macOS users through a deceptive method known as Clickfix tactics. The campaign leverages typosquatted domains to trick users into executing harmful AppleScripts, which harvest sensitive data such as browser cookies, saved passwords, and cryptocurrency wallet information. The operation is linked to a command-and-control panel primarily hosted in Russia and prioritizes Western users, particularly those engaged in financial and crypto activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144605</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage Windows Task Scheduler to Embed Malware and Maintain Persistence</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-windows-task-scheduler/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a protracted cyberattack that targeted critical national infrastructure (CNI) in the Middle East. Threat actors exploited Windows Task Scheduler to embed malicious software and ensure persistence on compromised systems, using a variant of the Havoc framework to infiltrate and manipulate Windows environments with precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144509</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploitation of Microsoft 365 Direct Send to Deliver Phishing Emails as Internal Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploitation-of-microsoft-365-direct-send-to-deliver-phishing-emails/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a phishing campaign that exploits the Direct Send feature of Microsoft 365 to send spoofed internal emails without authentication. Attackers use publicly available information to craft emails that appear to originate from within the organization, bypassing traditional email security controls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144615</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 19:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider hackers shift focus to aviation, transportation firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scattered-spider-hackers-shift-focus-to-aviation-transportation-firms/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a group of threat actors, has expanded its targeting to the aviation and transportation industries, following previous attacks on insurance and retail sectors. They use social engineering tactics, MFA bombing, SIM swapping, and other methods to gain initial network access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scattered-spider-hackers-shift-focus-to-aviation-transportation-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is trying to get antivirus software away from the Windows kernel</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/microsoft-is-trying-to-get-antivirus-software-away-from-the-windows-kernel/</link>
      <description>This article discusses upcoming changes in Windows 11, including a new feature called "quick machine recovery" (QMR) that enables targeted remediations on affected devices via Windows RE, and a simplified unexpected restart screen with improved readability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/microsoft-is-trying-to-get-antivirus-software-away-from-the-windows-kernel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 SOHO Devices Hacked in China-linked LapDogs Cyber Espionage Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-1000-soho-devices-hacked-in-china.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2015-1548, CVE-2017-17663; Summary: The article describes a network of compromised small office and home office (SOHO) devices used by China-nexus hacking groups for cyber espionage. The Operational Relay Box (ORB) network, codenamed LapDogs, has been found to have over 1,000 infected devices across the US, Southeast Asia, Japan, South Korea, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-1000-soho-devices-hacked-in-china.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s throttling of Cloudflare makes sites inaccessible</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/russias-throttling-of-cloudflare-makes-sites-inaccessible/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare's infrastructure has been throttled by Russian ISPs, making websites and services inaccessible from Russia. The throttling affects all connection methods and protocols, including HTTP/1.1 to HTTP/3 on QUIC, and is outside of Cloudflare's control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/russias-throttling-of-cloudflare-makes-sites-inaccessible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM: A Strategic Guide to Continuous Threat Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/ctem-to-continuous-threat-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM), a proactive approach to cybersecurity that involves continuous monitoring and threat-informed actions. It highlights the benefits of CTEM, including reduced time to detect and remediate exposures, fewer exploitable assets over time, and successful red team or breach simulation outcomes. The article also touches on the challenges of implementing CTEM, such as limited skilled workforce, integration complexity with existing tools, budget constraints, and lack of stakeholder awareness or buy-in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061358</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 flaw now believed to be exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-now-believed-to-be-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The "Citrix Bleed 2" vulnerability, an out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777), allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive data from public-facing gateways and virtual servers, enabling session hijacking and bypassing multi-factor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-now-believed-to-be-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Peep #19: IntelBroker Indicted, and Ransomware Goes Corporate</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-peep-19-intelbroker-ransomware-corporate/</link>
      <description>This article does not describe a vulnerability. Instead, it discusses various cybersecurity-related topics, including threat actors, ransomware groups, data breaches, and insider leaks. The article provides insights into the activities of these threat actors and their tactics, as well as the consequences of their actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061341</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLOAD and Pubshell Malware Used in Mustang Panda's Tibet-Specific Attack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pubload-and-pubshell-malware-used-in.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cyber espionage campaign attributed to Mustang Panda, a China-linked threat actor, targeting the Tibetan community. The campaign uses spear-phishing attacks with Tibet-themed lures to distribute malware, including PUBLOAD and Pubshell, which are used to create reverse shells and execute commands on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pubload-and-pubshell-malware-used-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams to Auto-Detect Work Location Using Company Wi-Fi</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-to-auto-detect-work-location/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft Teams' new feature that automatically detects users' work locations when they connect to their organization's Wi-Fi network. The feature aims to streamline the hybrid workplace experience by eliminating manual updates and improving collaboration, resource management, and employee privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144558</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeds United And Reflectiz Partner To Share Insights On Proactive Web Security After Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/leeds-united-and-reflectiz-partner-to-share-insights-on-proactive-web-security-after-cyber-attack/</link>
      <description>The article announces an upcoming webinar between Leeds United FC and Reflectiz, discussing proactive web security measures after a Magecart attack on Leeds United's online shop. The webinar will feature Graham Peck, Head of IT and Security at Leeds United, and Isaac Moddel, VP Sales at Reflectiz, sharing insights and best practices to safeguard digital assets and customer data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144547</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Encrypt Launches 6-Day Certificates for IP-Based SSL Encryption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lets-encrypt-launches-6-day-certificates/</link>
      <description>Let's Encrypt is preparing to issue SSL/TLS certificates that include IP addresses in their Subject Alternative Name (SAN) fields, enabling secure communication for a wider range of internet-connected devices and services. The new certificates will have a short-lived validity period of six days to minimize the risk window in case of a key compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144545</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines Targeted in Cyberattack, Systems Compromised</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hawaiian-airlines-targeted-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines has experienced a significant cybersecurity incident that has disrupted parts of its IT infrastructure, with no group claiming responsibility or confirming whether ransomware was involved. Despite the disruption, flights are operating safely and as scheduled, with the airline engaging federal authorities and external cybersecurity experts to assist in investigating the breach and restoring affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144540</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt Electronic DVR Vulnerability Leaves Admin Credentials Unprotected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hunt-electronic-dvr-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hunt Electronics Hybrid DVRs; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6561; Summary: The hybrid DVRs from Hunt Electronics, specifically models HBF-09KD and HBF-16NK running firmware version V3.1.67_1786 BB11115 or earlier, contain a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-6561) that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to retrieve the system's configuration file, which contains administrator credentials in plaintext, granting full administrative access to the compromised DVR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144534</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Case for Agentic AI SOC Analysts</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/business-case-for-agentic-ai-soc.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges faced by Security Operations Centers (SOCs) in today's cybersecurity landscape, including an increase in complex threats, false positives, and staffing shortages. It highlights the benefits of using agentic AI-powered SOCs to automate routine tasks, filter out noise, and surface high-priority alerts for human analysts to focus on. The article also emphasizes the importance of maximizing the impact of existing skilled staff, reducing burnout, and improving operational efficiency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/business-case-for-agentic-ai-soc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Group Silver Fox Uses Fake Websites to Deliver Sainbox RAT and Hidden Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/chinese-group-silver-fox-uses-fake.html</link>
      <description>A Chinese-speaking threat actor, attributed with medium confidence to Silver Fox (aka Void Arachne), has been observed delivering Sainbox RAT and the open-source Hidden rootkit through phishing websites. The campaign leverages fake software installers, similar to previous attacks that targeted Chinese-speaking users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/chinese-group-silver-fox-uses-fake.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFix Attacks Soar by 500%: Hackers Intensify Use of This Manipulative Technique to Deceive Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-intensify-use-of-this-manipulative-technique-to-deceive-users/</link>
      <description>ClickFix is a novel social engineering technique that has surged in prevalence by 517% between 2024 and 2025, exploiting user trust in online verification processes. It tricks users into copying malicious scripts under the guise of resolving fake errors or completing verification checks, ultimately leading to severe system compromises. The threat operates by presenting users with counterfeit prompts mimicking legitimate services, and has been adopted by nation-state-aligned groups for initial access across Windows, macOS, and Linux platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144475</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT-C-36 Hackers Launching Cyberattacks on Government Entities, Financial Sectors, and Critical Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-c-36-hackers-launching-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2024-43451; Summary: The article discusses the threat group APT-C-36 (Blind Eagle) that exploits vulnerabilities with social engineering. They use phishing emails as an initial attack vector, deploying RATs and leveraging WebDAV requests to deliver malware. Although a related vulnerability was patched, Blind Eagle adapted and continued attacks.

FYSA: The article highlights Blind Eagle's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including the use of phishing emails, Remote Access Trojans (RATs), and WebDAV requests to deliver malware. It also emphasizes the importance of advanced security solutions capable of detecting and containing evolving threats in real-time to ensure robust defense against sophisticated actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144461</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 09:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail giant Ahold Delhaize says data breach affects 2.2 million people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/retail-giant-ahold-delhaize-says-data-breach-affects-22-million-people/</link>
      <description>Ahold Delhaize, a multinational food retail chain, has notified over 2.2 million individuals that their personal, financial, and health information was stolen in a November ransomware attack affecting its U.S. systems. The attackers gained access to the company's internal U.S. business systems on November 6, 2024, stealing data including internal employment records, contact information, government-issued identification numbers, financial account information, health information, and employment-related information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/retail-giant-ahold-delhaize-says-data-breach-affects-22-million-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Says Goodbye to Blue Screen of Death, Introduces Black Screen</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-says-goodbye-to-blue-screen-of-death/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is retiring the Blue Screen of Death (BSOD) in favor of a new Black Screen of Death, which will debut with Windows 11 version 24H2. The redesign aims to improve readability, reduce user anxiety, and provide better information for troubleshooting and recovery. The change comes after last year's CrowdStrike incident highlighted the need for clearer diagnostics and faster recovery options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144480</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric AC Flaw Lets Hackers Remotely Control Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitsubishi-electric-ac-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric air conditioning systems; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3699; Summary: A critical security vulnerability allows hackers to bypass authentication and remotely control affected units, enabling unauthorized access, system manipulation, and firmware tampering. Exploitation could disrupt climate control in offices or data centers, posing risks to safety, privacy, and operational continuity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144472</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-20281 &amp; CVE-2025-20282: Critical Cisco ISE Vulnerabilities Allow Root-Level RCE</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-20281-cve-2025-20282-critical-cisco-ise-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE (Identity Services Engine) and ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281 (CVSS 9.8), CVE-2025-20282 (CVSS 10.0); Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code as the root user, or upload and execute malicious files, without requiring credentials; exploitation details include unauthenticated access vectors and insufficient validation of user input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061310</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVEit Transfer Faces Increased Threats as Scanning Surges and CVE Flaws Are Targeted</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/moveit-transfer-faces-increased-threats.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Progress MOVEit Transfer; CVE(s): CVE-2023-34362, CVE-2023-36934; Summary: A surge in scanning activity targeting Progress MOVEit Transfer systems suggests attackers may be preparing for another mass exploitation campaign or probing for unpatched systems. The increase in scanning activity has been observed since May 27, 2025, with daily scanner IP volume remaining intermittently elevated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/moveit-transfer-faces-increased-threats.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5060829 update released with 38 new changes, fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060829-update-released-with-38-new-changes-fixes/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of Microsoft's KB5060829 preview cumulative update for Windows 11 24H2, which includes 38 changes and new features such as a PC-to-PC migration experience and improved taskbar functionality. It also mentions various bug fixes and improvements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5060829-update-released-with-38-new-changes-fixes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneClik Malware Targets Energy Sector Using Microsoft ClickOnce and Golang Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/oneclik-malware-targets-energy-sector.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft ClickOnce; CVE(s): None; Summary: Microsoft's ClickOnce software deployment technology can be leveraged by threat actors to compromise organizations within the energy, oil, and gas sectors. The attack chain begins with phishing emails containing a link to a fake hardware analysis website that serves as a conduit for delivering a ClickOnce application, which runs an executable using dfsvc.exe, ultimately resulting in the execution of an encrypted shellcode in memory to load the RunnerBeacon backdoor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/oneclik-malware-targets-energy-sector.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whole Foods supplier UNFI restores core systems after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/whole-foods-supplier-unfi-restores-core-systems-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>United Natural Foods (UNFI) has restored its core systems and electronic ordering/invoicing systems after a cyberattack, which is believed to have a material impact on its net income/loss and adjusted EBITDA for the year's fourth fiscal quarter of 2025. The company experienced reduced sales volume and increased operational costs during the incident, but expects to recover with the help of cybersecurity insurance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/whole-foods-supplier-unfi-restores-core-systems-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Auth Flaw in MongoDB Server Allows Attackers to Cause DoS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pre-auth-flaw-in-mongodb-server/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MongoDB Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6709; Summary: A pre-authentication vulnerability in OIDC authentication of MongoDB Server enables unauthenticated attackers to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by exploiting improper input validation. The flaw affects versions before 7.0.17, 8.0.5, and 6.0.21, allowing for complete server crashes or post-authentication DoS in affected environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144457</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Student Charged for Alleged Hacking and Data Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/university-student-charged-for-alleged-hacking/</link>
      <description>A former Western Sydney University student has been charged with 20 cyber offenses, including unauthorized access to restricted data, altering academic results, and threatening to sell confidential student information. The investigation was launched after the university reported suspicious incidents involving student data, and police executed a search warrant at the suspect's residence, seizing computer equipment and mobile devices believed to have been used in the commission of the offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144452</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 06:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines discloses cyberattack, flights not affected</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hawaiian-airlines-discloses-cyberattack-flights-not-affected/</link>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines is investigating a cyberattack that has disrupted access to some of its systems, but did not affect flight safety. The airline has hired external cybersecurity experts and contacted relevant authorities to assist in the investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hawaiian-airlines-discloses-cyberattack-flights-not-affected/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 05:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open VSX Marketplace Flaw Enables Millions of Developers at Risk of Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/open-vsx-marketplace-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Open VSX Registry; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Open VSX Registry, a marketplace for Visual Studio Code (VS Code) extensions, allowed attackers to seize control of the entire extensions marketplace, enabling the silent distribution of malicious updates to developer environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144446</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City Man Pleads Guilty After Hacking to Promote His Cybersecurity Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kansas-city-man-pleads-guilty-after-hacking/</link>
      <description>A 32-year-old man in Kansas City has pleaded guilty to federal charges for hacking into multiple organizations' computer systems to promote his cybersecurity services. The methods used were physical breaches and digital exploits rather than sophisticated cyberattacks. He accessed sensitive information, manipulated systems, and caused significant damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144443</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 04:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actively exploited vulnerability gives extraordinary control over server fleets</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/active-exploitation-of-ami-management-tool-imperils-thousands-of-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unknown; CVE(s): CVE-2024-54085; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to implant malicious code in the firmware of BMCs (Baseboard Management Controllers), enabling them to evade detection, move laterally within the network, and cause significant operational disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/active-exploitation-of-ami-management-tool-imperils-thousands-of-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 22:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC approves $126 million in Fortnite refunds over ‘dark patterns’</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/ftc-approves-126-million-in-fortnite-refunds-over-dark-patterns/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a settlement between the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and Epic Games regarding allegations of violating children's privacy laws and using "dark patterns" to trick users into making unwanted purchases in Fortnite. The FTC has approved $126 million in refunds for 969,173 eligible players and reopened the claims portal for a third round of refunds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/ftc-approves-126-million-in-fortnite-refunds-over-dark-patterns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian APT35 Hackers Targeting High-Profile Cybersecurity Experts and Professors in Israel</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-apt35-hackers-targeting-high-profile-cybersecurity-experts/</link>
      <description>Educated Manticore, an advanced persistent threat (APT) group associated with the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps' Intelligence Organization (IRGC-IO), has intensified its cyber-espionage operations targeting Israeli cybersecurity experts, computer science professors, and journalists. The group uses sophisticated spear-phishing campaigns, custom phishing kits, and legitimate-looking authentication flows to deceive victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144410</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM WebSphere Application Server Flaw Enables Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-websphere-application-server-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM WebSphere Application Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36038; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected systems by deserializing untrusted data. It affects versions 9.0 and 8.5 of the IBM WebSphere Application Server, posing a significant risk to organizations using this middleware platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144354</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nOAuth Exploit Enables Full Account Takeover of Entra Cross-Tenant SaaS Applications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/noauth-exploit-enables-full-account-takeover/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra App Gallery; CVE(s): None; Summary: The nOAuth vulnerability allows attackers to achieve full account takeover across tenant boundaries by exploiting a critical authentication misconfiguration in OpenID Connect (OIDC) implementations. Attackers can impersonate legitimate users by manipulating mutable attributes like email addresses, gaining unauthorized access to sensitive data and enabling persistence and lateral movement within the compromised application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144380</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother printer bug in 689 models exposes default admin passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brother-printer-bug-in-689-models-exposes-default-admin-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Brother (689 models), Fujifilm (53 models), Toshiba (2 models), Konica Minolta (6 models), Ricoh (5 models); CVE(s): CVE-2024-51978; Summary: The default administrator password of 689 printer models from Brother and other manufacturers can be generated by remote attackers, allowing them to take control of devices, perform remote code execution, or pivot within networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brother-printer-bug-in-689-models-exposes-default-admin-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a career in cybersecurity isn’t easy, but this can help</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/getting-a-career-in-cybersecurity-isnt-easy-but-this-can-help/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are increasingly exploiting Large Language Models (LLMs) by using uncensored versions, developing their own malicious LLMs or "jailbreaking" legitimate ones to bypass safety protocols. These compromised or malicious LLMs are then used to generate highly convincing phishing campaigns, create harmful code and automate various cybercrime operations, making attacks more sophisticated and scalable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685beb102e3f7200011b4a3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Weaponize and Obfuscate .NET Assemblies Using MacroPack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-weaponize-and-obfuscate-net-assemblies/</link>
      <description>BallisKit's MacroPack Pro tool introduces a scenario to obfuscate and weaponize .NET assemblies, making them less detectable by modern security solutions. The tool provides multiple obfuscation options, including converting static PInvoke imports into dynamic DInvoke imports and managing .NET's reflection capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144370</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Open VSX Registry Flaw Exposes Millions of Developers to Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/critical-open-vsx-registry-flaw-exposes.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Open VSX Registry; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Open VSX Registry contains a critical vulnerability that allows attackers to take control of the entire Visual Studio Code extensions marketplace by exploiting a CI issue in the publish-extensions repository. This could enable an attacker to publish malicious updates to every extension on Open VSX, posing a severe supply chain risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/critical-open-vsx-registry-flaw-exposes.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-student charged over hacking university for cheap parking, data breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ex-student-charged-over-hacking-university-for-cheap-parking-data-breaches/</link>
      <description>The article describes a hacking case involving Birdie Kingston, a 27-year-old former Western Sydney University (WSU) student, who allegedly hacked into the university's systems multiple times starting from 2021. She is accused of unauthorized access, data theft, and compromising university infrastructure, affecting hundreds of staff and students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ex-student-charged-over-hacking-university-for-cheap-parking-data-breaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 16:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco warns of max severity RCE flaws in Identity Services Engine</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-warns-of-max-severity-rce-flaws-in-identity-services-engine/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282; Summary: Two critical, unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities affect ISE and ISE-PIC versions 3.4 and 3.3, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands as the root user or upload and execute arbitrary files with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-warns-of-max-severity-rce-flaws-in-identity-services-engine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit ChatGPT, Cisco AnyConnect, Google Meet, and Teams in Attacks on SMBs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-chatgpt-cisco-anyconnect-google-meet-and-teams/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are leveraging the trusted names of popular software and services like ChatGPT, Cisco AnyConnect, Google Meet, and Microsoft Teams to orchestrate sophisticated cyberattacks against SMBs. The report reveals that approximately 8,500 SMB users faced attacks involving malware or potentially unwanted software (PUS) disguised as legitimate tools, with Zoom emerging as the most mimicked platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144398</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pleads guilty to hacking networks to pitch security services</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/man-pleads-guilty-to-hacking-networks-to-pitch-security-services/</link>
      <description>Nicholas Michael Kloster, a 32-year-old Kansas City man, has pleaded guilty to hacking multiple organizations to advertise his cybersecurity services. He accessed the networks of three organizations, including a health club and a Missouri nonprofit corporation, and used the access to offer his services as a cybersecurity consultant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/man-pleads-guilty-to-hacking-networks-to-pitch-security-services/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 key takeaways from the Scattered Spider attacks on insurance firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/3-key-takeaways-from-the-scattered-spider-attacks-on-insurance-firms/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a group of threat actors, has been linked to attacks on several US insurance companies, including Aflac, Philadelphia Insurance Companies, and Erie Insurance. The attackers used identity-based techniques, such as impersonating IT users or employees, to reset passwords and gain access to victim environments. This is not an isolated incident, as Scattered Spider has a history of high-profile breaches in the insurance industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/3-key-takeaways-from-the-scattered-spider-attacks-on-insurance-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp to Introduce AI-Powered Message Summaries for Faster Catch-Up</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/whatsapp-to-introduce-ai-powered-message-summaries/</link>
      <description>WhatsApp has announced the upcoming launch of "Message Summaries" - an AI-powered feature that provides concise summaries of unread messages. The feature is designed to help users quickly catch up on conversations without compromising privacy. The summaries are generated through "Private Processing" technology, which means neither Meta nor WhatsApp can see the messages or summaries, and users have control over whether to enable the feature and customize which chats are eligible for AI-powered summaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144388</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical RCE Flaws in Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC Allow Unauthenticated Attackers to Gain Root Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/critical-rce-flaws-in-cisco-ise-and-ise.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282; Summary: Two maximum-severity security flaws in Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user. The vulnerabilities stem from insufficient input validation and lack of file validation checks, and can be exploited by sending crafted API requests or uploading malicious files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/critical-rce-flaws-in-cisco-ise-and-ise.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Vulnerability Allows Remote Attackers to Execute Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-ise-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities (CVSS 10.0) in Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC platforms allow unauthenticated remote attackers to execute malicious commands as the root user, potentially taking complete control of affected systems. The flaws target specific APIs within Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC, enabling arbitrary code execution or file uploads with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144381</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FileFix Method Emerges as a Threat Following 517% Rise in ClickFix Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-filefix-method-emerges-as-threat.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the ClickFix social engineering tactic, which has seen a 517% increase in detections between 2024 and the first half of this year. It involves fake CAPTCHA verifications and deception tactics to trick victims into running malicious scripts.

FYSA: Threat actors have been advertising builders that provide ClickFix-weaponized landing pages, and researchers have demonstrated an alternative tactic called FileFix that works by tricking users into copying and pasting a file path into Windows File Explorer. Additionally, various phishing campaigns have been detected, including those using government domains, long-lived domains, malicious shortcut files, and impersonating U.S. state Departments of Motor Vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-filefix-method-emerges-as-threat.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 'Direct Send' abused to send phishing as internal users</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-365-direct-send-abused-to-send-phishing-as-internal-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Direct Send feature in Microsoft 365 allows on-premises devices or cloud services to send emails through a tenant's smart host as if they originated from the organization's domain. This feature is designed for use by printers, scanners, and other devices that need to send messages on behalf of the company, but it does not require authentication, allowing remote users to send internal-looking emails from the company's domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-365-direct-send-abused-to-send-phishing-as-internal-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams Adds Feature for Admins to Control 365 Certified Apps with Custom Rules</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-adds-feature-for-admins-to-control-365-certified-apps/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is rolling out an update to Microsoft Teams that allows administrators to manage third-party app availability through rule-based settings in the Teams admin center. This feature aims to enhance security and streamline app management by enabling granular control over certified apps based on permissions, publisher names, or other criteria. The default setting will allow all certified apps, but admins can customize availability using the new "Customize availability" option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144365</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrendMakers Sight Bulb Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-177-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TrendMakers Sight Bulb Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6521, CVE-2025-6522; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to capture sensitive information and execute arbitrary shell commands on the target device as root if connected to the local network segment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23556</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric Air Conditioning Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-177-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric air conditioning systems; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3699; Summary: An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Mitsubishi Electric air conditioning systems, allowing an attacker to control the system or disclose information by exploiting this vulnerability. Successful exploitation could also allow tampering with the firmware of affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23555</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/26/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories regarding Mitsubishi Electric Air Conditioning Systems and TrendMakers Sight Bulb Pro. These advisories provide information on current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS, and encourage users and administrators to review the technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23557</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Charge 25-Year-Old British National Linked to IntelBroker Hacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/authorities-charge-25-year-old-british-national-linked-to-intelbroker-hacks/</link>
      <description>A 25-year-old British national, Kai West, also known as "IntelBroker," has been charged and detained for allegedly leading a global campaign of data theft and cyber intrusions, targeting over 40 companies and organizations worldwide. West is accused of conspiring with other hackers to steal sensitive data and sell it on underground forums, causing estimated damages of over $25 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144353</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Exploit LLM Models to Enhance Hacking Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-exploit-llm-models/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are leveraging large language models (LLMs) to amplify their hacking operations by utilizing uncensored LLMs, custom-built criminal variants, and exploiting legitimate LLMs through jailbreaking techniques. This "arms race" between attackers and developers underscores the challenge of securing AI systems as new jailbreaking methods emerge, posing a critical challenge to cybersecurity defenses.

(Note: Since the article is not specifically about a vulnerability but contains cybersecurity-relevant content, I used the FYSA format)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144331</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPE OneView for VMware vCenter Vulnerability Allows Elevated Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hpe-oneview-for-vmware-vcenter-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) OneView for VMware vCenter; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37101; Summary: A critical vulnerability in HPE OneView for VMware vCenter allows attackers with read-only privileges to escalate access and perform administrative actions, putting enterprise IT environments at risk. The flaw affects all versions prior to 11.7 and has a CVSS score of 8.7 (High).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144341</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Risks of SaaS: Why Built-In Protections Aren't Enough for Modern Data Resilience</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-risks-of-saas-why-built-in.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of data resilience in SaaS platforms, highlighting the risks associated with data loss due to human error, ransomware attacks, and internal threats. It emphasizes that built-in protections in SaaS platforms are not enough to handle the level of complexity modern organizations face and that a unified platform is needed to secure, protect, and manage data wherever it resides.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/the-hidden-risks-of-saas-why-built-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Spear-Phishing Attack Impersonates Google, Outlook, and Yahoo Domains</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-spear-phishing-attack-impersonates-google/</link>
      <description>The article reports a renewed global spear-phishing campaign by the Iranian threat actor Educated Manticore (APT42), targeting high-value individuals with credential theft and bypassing multi-factor authentication through advanced social engineering tactics. The campaign poses a significant risk to academics, journalists, and geopolitical figures, particularly prominent Israeli figures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144323</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Deploy Pubload Malware Using Tibetan Community Lures and Weaponized Filenames</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-deploy-pubload-malware-using-tibetan-community-lures/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a targeted cyberattack campaign orchestrated by the China-aligned threat actor Hive0154. The campaign involves phishing attacks using culturally sensitive topics to manipulate trust and curiosity within the Tibetan community, as well as targeting other entities such as the U.S. Navy with lures referencing strategic military engagements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144293</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Outlook bug causing crashes when opening emails</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-outlook-bug-causing-crashes-when-opening-emails/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Outlook; CVE(s): None; Summary: A bug causes classic Outlook to crash when opening emails or starting a new message, affecting users across all Microsoft 365 Office channels who updated Outlook for Microsoft 365 earlier this month. The issue occurs because Outlook cannot open the Forms Library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-outlook-bug-causing-crashes-when-opening-emails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US University Targeted by Androxgh0st Botnet Operators for C2 Logger Hosting</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/us-university-targeted-by-androxgh0st-botnet-operators/</link>
      <description>The Androxgh0st botnet has been found to be a persistent and dynamic cyberthreat that has targeted the University of California, San Diego's "USArhythms" portal to host its command-and-control (C2) logger panels. The botnet exploits over 20 vulnerabilities, including Apache Shiro, Spring Framework, WordPress plugins, IoT devices, and others, to execute remote code, steal sensitive data, and deploy cryptomining payloads. It also utilizes webshells and OGNL payloads to maintain persistent access and facilitate further malware deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144245</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decrement by one to rule them all: AsIO3.sys driver exploitation</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/decrement-by-one-to-rule-them-all/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be an in-depth analysis of a privilege escalation exploit in a Windows kernel-mode driver. The author provides detailed information on the vulnerabilities and exploitation methods used, including the "decrement by one" primitive. The article also discusses the importance of proper security design and access controls in kernel-mode components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685ad99c178bd70001283c95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms Family Safety blocks Google Chrome from launching</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-family-safety-blocks-google-chrome-from-launching/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Family Safety; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Microsoft Family Safety parental control service is blocking users from launching Google Chrome and other web browsers on Windows systems due to a bug in its web filtering tool, which prompts children to ask for their parents' approval to use other browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-family-safety-blocks-google-chrome-from-launching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 09:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Use TeamFiltration Pentesting Framework to Breach Microsoft Teams, OneDrive, Outlook, and More</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-use-teamfiltration-pentesting-framework/</link>
      <description>The UNK_SneakyStrike account takeover campaign uses the TeamFiltration pentesting framework to target Microsoft Entra ID user accounts, exploiting credentials and gaining unauthorized access to critical native applications such as Microsoft Teams, OneDrive, and Outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144233</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on Active Exploitation of D-Link Path Traversal Flaw</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-d-link-path-traversal-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: D-Link DIR-859 WiFi Router; CVE(s): CVE-2024-0769; Summary: The vulnerability (CVE-2024-0769) is a path traversal vulnerability in the HTTP POST request handler of the router's hedwig.cgi file, allowing attackers to traverse directories and access sensitive configuration files, leading to unauthorized access and potential full control over affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144303</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian APT35 Hackers Targeting Israeli Tech Experts with AI-Powered Phishing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iranian-apt35-hackers-targeting-israeli.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a spear-phishing campaign attributed to the Iranian state-sponsored hacking group Educated Manticore (also known as APT35), targeting journalists, high-profile cybersecurity experts, and computer science professors in Israel. The attackers use social engineering tactics, posing as fictitious assistants or using AI-generated messages to trick victims into deploying malware on their systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iranian-apt35-hackers-targeting-israeli.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA: AMI MegaRAC bug enabling server hijacks exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-ami-megarac-bug-that-lets-hackers-brick-servers-now-actively-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AMI MegaRAC Baseboard Management Controller (BMC) software; CVE(s): CVE-2024-54085; Summary: A maximum severity vulnerability allows remote unauthenticated attackers to hijack and potentially brick unpatched servers, enabling attacks such as malware deployment, ransomware, firmware tampering, and server physical damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-ami-megarac-bug-that-lets-hackers-brick-servers-now-actively-exploited/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Demonstrate Windows Registry Manipulation via C++ Program</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-registry-manipulation-via-c-program/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a C++ program demonstrating how attackers manipulate the Windows Registry to establish persistence, evade defenses, and alter system behavior. The program uses Windows API functions to modify registry keys, simulating tactics employed by real-world malware while highlighting critical defense implications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144260</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM i Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Escalate Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-i-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36004; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code with administrator rights. It affects multiple versions of IBM i, including 7.5, 7.4, 7.3, and 7.2. An attacker can gain unauthorized access to sensitive system resources, compromise the integrity and availability of the system, and potentially take full control of the affected environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144261</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Criminals Exploit Open-Source Tools to Compromise Financial Institutions Across Africa</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cyber-criminals-exploit-open-source.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a series of cyber attacks targeting financial organizations across Africa, using open-source and publicly available tools to maintain access. The attackers use a mix of tools, including PoshC2, Chisel, and Classroom Spy, to commandeer machines and bypass firewalls, with the goal of selling initial access to other criminal actors on underground forums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cyber-criminals-exploit-open-source.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on ControlID iDSecure Flaws Enabling Bypass Authentication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-controlid-idsecure-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ControlID iDSecure On-premises; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49851, CVE-2025-49852, CVE-2025-49853; Summary: The software has multiple critical vulnerabilities that allow attackers to bypass authentication, leak sensitive data, and execute malicious SQL commands. Exploitation can lead to unauthorized access, data breaches, and disruption of critical operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144236</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds 3 Flaws to KEV Catalog, Impacting AMI MegaRAC, D-Link, Fortinet</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-adds-3-flaws-to-kev-catalog.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AMI MegaRAC; CVE(s): CVE-2024-54085; Summary: An authentication bypass vulnerability allows a remote attacker to take control of the Redfish Host Interface of AMI MegaRAC SPx, potentially leading to malicious actions such as deploying malware and tampering with device firmware. The flaw has a CVSS score of 10.0.

Vulnerable Product: D-Link DIR-859; CVE(s): CVE-2024-0769; Summary: A path traversal vulnerability in the D-Link DIR-859 router allows for privilege escalation and unauthorized control, potentially allowing an attacker to dump account names, passwords, groups, and descriptions for all users of the device. The router has reached end-of-life (EoL) as of December 2020.

Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiOS; CVE(s): CVE-2019-6693; Summary: A hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability in FortiOS allows an attacker with access to the CLI configuration or the CLI backup file to decrypt sensitive data, potentially leading to initial access for threat actors linked to the Akira ransomware scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-adds-3-flaws-to-kev-catalog.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVEit Transfer Systems Hit by Wave of Attacks Using Over 100 Unique IPs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/moveit-transfer-systems-hit-by-wave-of-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Progress Software MOVEit Transfer; CVE(s): CVE-2023-34362, CVE-2023-36934; Summary: The MOVEit Transfer file-sharing platform has been targeted by a surge in scanning and exploitation activity. Over 682 unique IP addresses have been detected targeting MOVEit Transfer systems, with the most intense activity beginning on May 27, 2025. Exploitation attempts have been linked to two previously disclosed vulnerabilities (CVE-2023-34362 and CVE-2023-36934).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144227</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 05:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Arrest Five Operators Behind Infamous BreachForums Cybercrime Hub</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/authorities-arrest-five-operators/</link>
      <description>Five key operators behind BreachForums, an online marketplace for stolen data, have been arrested by French authorities. The operation targeted suspects believed to be operating from Russian-speaking territories, but the core administrators were revealed to be four French nationals in their early twenties. The arrests are expected to disrupt the global trade in stolen data and serve as a warning to other cybercriminals who rely on such platforms for anonymity and profit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144221</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Adds AI-Powered Message Summaries for Faster Chat Previews</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/whatsapp-adds-ai-powered-message.html</link>
      <description>WhatsApp has introduced an AI-powered feature called Message Summaries that summarizes unread messages in chats using Meta AI's Private Processing technology. This feature is designed to preserve user privacy and prevent third-party access to message contents. The development comes as the U.S. House of Representatives added WhatsApp to a list of apps banned from government-issued devices due to security concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/whatsapp-adds-ai-powered-message.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker 'IntelBroker' charged in US for global data theft breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/british-hacker-intelbroker-charged-with-25m-in-cybercrime-damages/</link>
      <description>A British national, "IntelBroker" (Kai West), has been charged by the US for stealing and selling sensitive data worldwide, causing an estimated $25 million in damages. The stolen information included health records, internal files from companies, and user data from online platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/british-hacker-intelbroker-charged-with-25m-in-cybercrime-damages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 23:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-424: Mikrotik RouterOS VXLAN Source IP Improper Access Control Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-424/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mikrotik RouterOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6443; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass access restrictions on affected installations of Mikrotik RouterOS without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the handling of remote IP addresses when processing VXLAN traffic, allowing an attacker to gain access to internal network resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26415</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-425: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-425/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6640; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs when parsing U3D files due to the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26527</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-426: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-426/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6641; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of U3D files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26528</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-427: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-427/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6642; Summary: The PDF-XChange Editor U3D file parsing allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by reading past the end of an allocated object due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. User interaction is required, and the vulnerability can be exploited by visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26530</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-428: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-428/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6643; Summary: The PDF-XChange Editor U3D file parsing allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, requiring user interaction. The vulnerability occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26532</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-429: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-429/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6644; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists in the parsing of U3D files due to a lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26536</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-430: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-430/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6645; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by exploiting a use-after-free flaw in the parsing of U3D files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26642</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-431: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-431/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6646; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor through the parsing of U3D files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26643</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-432: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-432/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6647; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. It requires user interaction, such as visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, and is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26644</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-433: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-433/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6648; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by reading past the end of an allocated object due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in U3D file parsing. User interaction is required, and the issue can be exploited by visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26671</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-434: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-434/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6649; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of U3D files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26709</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-435: PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-435/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6650; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by exploiting an out-of-bounds read information disclosure flaw within the parsing of U3D files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in reading past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26712</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-436: PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-436/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6651; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by parsing out-of-bounds write JP2 files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26713</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-437: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-437/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6652; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by parsing PRC files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated object. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26724</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-438: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-438/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6653; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to an out-of-bounds read information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26726</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-439: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-439/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6654; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by parsing out-of-bounds write PRC files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26729</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-440: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-440/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6655; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. It requires user interaction, such as visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, and is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26730</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-441: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-441/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6656; Summary: The PDF-XChange Editor PRC file parsing allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information by exploiting an out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists within the parsing of PRC files and can be exploited in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26731</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-442: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-442/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6657; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information by reading past the end of an allocated buffer due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in PRC file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26732</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-443: PDF-XChange Editor GIF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-443/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6660; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by exploiting a heap-based buffer overflow in the GIF file parsing. User interaction is required, and the attack vector involves visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26763</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-444: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-444/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6658; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information by parsing out-of-bounds read information disclosure. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26733</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-445: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-445/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6659; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of PRC files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26734</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-446: PDF-XChange Editor App Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-446/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6661; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor by exploiting an App object use-after-free remote code execution flaw. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from a lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26823</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-447: PDF-XChange Editor PRC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-447/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PDF-XChange Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6662; Summary: The PDF-XChange Editor PRC file parsing allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information through an out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of PRC files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26985</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers turn ScreenConnect into malware using Authenticode stuffing</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-turn-screenconnect-into-malware-using-authenticode-stuffing/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise ScreenConnect; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are modifying the authenticode signature of the ConnectWise ScreenConnect installer to build signed remote access malware. The modified certificate table contains new malicious configuration information, allowing for stealthy access to infected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-turn-screenconnect-into-malware-using-authenticode-stuffing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-421: Microsoft Azure App Services Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-421/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure App Services; CVE(s): ZDI-25-421, ZDI-CAN-24622; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Microsoft Azure without authentication. The issue exists within Azure App Services due to the exposure of sensitive information, which can be leveraged by an attacker to disclose information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24622</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-422: Microsoft Azure Machine Learning Environments Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-422/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure Machine Learning Environments; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-24823, ZDI-25-422; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Microsoft Azure, without requiring authentication. The issue results from predictable Azure Container Registry names, which can be exploited to cause a denial-of-service condition on the AML workspace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24823</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-423: Microsoft WinJS winjsdevelop Uncontrolled Search Path Element Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-423/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WinJS; CVE(s): ZDI-25-423, ZDI-CAN-23719; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft WinJS without authentication. The flaw exists in the installation process when loading a non-existent cloud resource that can be taken over by an attacker, enabling them to execute code on dependent systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23719</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers abuse Microsoft ClickOnce and AWS services for stealthy attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oneclik-attacks-use-microsoft-clickonce-and-aws-to-target-energy-sector/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft ClickOnce software deployment tool; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a malicious campaign called OneClik that leverages Microsoft's ClickOnce software deployment tool and custom Golang backdoors to compromise organizations in the energy, oil, and gas sectors. The attackers use legitimate AWS cloud services to keep their command and control infrastructure hidden, and deploy a sophisticated Golang-based backdoor called RunnerBeacon via a .NET-based loader tracked as OneClikNet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oneclik-attacks-use-microsoft-clickonce-and-aws-to-target-energy-sector/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Malware Discovered Using Prompt Injection to Manipulate AI Models in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-malware-discovered-using-prompt-injection/</link>
      <description>Skynet malware employs a unique evasion tactic called prompt injection to manipulate AI models used in malware analysis. Although the sample is rudimentary, it highlights concerns about the future of AI in cybersecurity and signals an emerging trend of manipulating AI systems with adversarial input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144203</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-420: PaperCut NG web-print-hot-folder Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-420/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PaperCut NG; CVE(s): CVE-2024-8404; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of PaperCut NG by creating a symbolic link, which can be used to delete a file. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, and can leverage it to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26241</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Brother Device Vulnerabilities Allow Attackers to Execute Arbitrary HTTP Requests</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/multiple-brother-device-vulnerabilities-allow-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Brother Industries, Ltd. multifunction printers (MFPs) and related devices; CVE(s): CVE-2024-51978, CVE-2024-51981, CVE-2024-51979, CVE-2024-51977, CVE-2024-51982, CVE-2024-51983, CVE-2024-51984; Summary: The article reports on eight zero-day vulnerabilities in Brother MFPs and related devices, affecting 748 models from five major vendors. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2024-51978) allows an unauthenticated attacker to generate the device's default administrator password, while others permit arbitrary HTTP requests, bypass authentication, or enable remote code execution (RCE).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144186</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu disables Intel GPU security mitigations, promises 20% performance boost</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/ubuntu-disables-intel-gpu-security-mitigations-promises-20-performance-boost/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubuntu; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the potential security implications of disabling Spectre GPU mitigations in Ubuntu. Researchers agree that most Spectre attack scenarios are unlikely to be exploited, and that the mitigations built into the kernel will protect against attacks. However, some researchers suggest that for typical users, the risk from downloading malware is higher than any potential gain from disabling these mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/ubuntu-disables-intel-gpu-security-mitigations-promises-20-performance-boost/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Weaponized Wedding Invite Scams Delivering SpyMax RAT to Android Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-weaponized-wedding-invite-scams-delivering-spymax-rat/</link>
      <description>The "Wedding Invitation" Android phishing campaign targets mobile users in India by sending seemingly harmless digital wedding invitations that conceal malicious APK files. These files contain the SpyMax Remote Access Trojan (RAT) or similar malware, which can steal sensitive information and exfiltrate it to attackers through Telegram bots or C2 servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144150</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New wave of ‘fake interviews’ use 35 npm packages to spread malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-wave-of-fake-interviews-use-35-npm-packages-to-spread-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new wave of North Korean "Contagious Interview" campaign targets job seekers with malicious npm packages that infect dev's devices with info-stealers and backdoors. The packages load BeaverTail info-stealer and InvisibleFerret backdoor, allowing attackers to steal browser data, load keyloggers, and perform remote control and file theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-wave-of-fake-interviews-use-35-npm-packages-to-spread-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERPOL Cautions of Significant Increase in Cyber Attacks on Western and Eastern Africa</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/interpol-cautions-of-significant-increase-in-cyber-attacks/</link>
      <description>The INTERPOL 2025 Africa Cyberthreat Assessment Report highlights a significant surge in cybercrime across Africa, with over 30% of all documented criminal activities being cyber-related. The report emphasizes the urgent need for enhanced cybersecurity measures, citing emerging risks such as AI-driven fraud and a lack of adequate law enforcement capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144177</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Pose as Recruiters, Target Developers with 35 New Malicious npm Packages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-pose-as-recruiters-target-developers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm registry; CVE(s): None; Summary: A North Korean threat actor campaign has been exposed, targeting software developers through the npm registry. The campaign involves 35 malicious packages across 24 accounts, with six still active on the registry. These packages have collectively been downloaded over 4,000 times, posing a significant risk to unsuspecting developers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144167</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-419: TeamViewer Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-419/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeamViewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36537; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of TeamViewer. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which results from incorrect permissions on folders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26660</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Brief: Escalation of Cyber Risk Related to Iran</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/iranian-cyberattacks-2025/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the heightened risk of cyber spillover due to the recent conflict involving Iran, particularly its military engagements with Israel and the U.S. It highlights the potential for Iranian-directed cyberattacks, including destructive attacks, website defacements, DDoS attacks, data exfiltration, and wiper attacks. The article also identifies four key areas of potential cyber threat activity: Iranian nation-state hackers, hacktivists, cybercriminal groups, and other nation-state actors. It emphasizes the importance of a multi-layered defense and recommends foundational security hygiene, including increasing response to threat signals, ensuring internet-facing infrastructure is up-to-date, training employees on phishing and social engineering tactics, and preparing for business continuity plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=144269</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google releases Gemini CLI with free Gemini 2.5 Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-releases-gemini-cli-with-free-gemini-25-pro/</link>
      <description>Google has released Gemini 2.5 Pro-powered Gemini CLI, which allows users to use Gemini inside their terminal. The article also mentions other cybersecurity-relevant topics such as Google's text-to-image model Imagen 4, on-device AI for detecting tech support scams in Google Chrome, and the donation of A2A AI protocol to the Linux Foundation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-releases-gemini-cli-with-free-gemini-25-pro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 17:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix warns of NetScaler vulnerability exploited in DoS attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-of-netscaler-vulnerability-exploited-in-dos-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6543; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-6543) is being actively exploited, causing devices to enter a denial of service condition. The flaw impacts NetScaler ADC and Gateway versions 14.1 before 14.1-47.46, 13.1 before 13.1-59.19, and 13.1-FIPS and NDcPP before 13.1-37.236-FIPS and NDcPP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-of-netscaler-vulnerability-exploited-in-dos-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 17:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nOAuth Vulnerability Still Affects 9% of Microsoft Entra SaaS Apps Two Years After Discovery</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/noauth-vulnerability-still-affects-9-of.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft's Entra ID allows malicious actors to achieve account takeovers in susceptible software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications. It exploits a weakness in how SaaS applications implement OpenID Connect (OIDC), permitting attackers to change the mail attribute in an Entra ID account and hijack accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/noauth-vulnerability-still-affects-9-of.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinRAR patches bug letting malware launch from extracted archives</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/winrar-patches-bug-letting-malware-launch-from-extracted-archives/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6218, None (other issues); Summary: A directory traversal vulnerability in older versions of WinRAR's Windows version allows malware execution after extracting a malicious archive. The flaw requires user interaction and can be exploited to launch malicious code, steal sensitive data, or install persistence mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/winrar-patches-bug-letting-malware-launch-from-extracted-archives/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'CitrixBleed 2' NetScaler flaw let hackers hijack sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-let-hackers-hijack-sessions/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777, CVE-2025-5349; Summary: A critical flaw (CVE-2025-5777) allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive data from public-facing gateways and virtual servers, while a high-severity flaw (CVE-2025-5349) is an improper access control problem in the NetScaler Management Interface. The flaws impact devices running versions before 14.1-43.56, releases before 13.1-58.32, and also 13.1-37.235-FIPS/NDcPP and 2.1-55.328-FIPS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-let-hackers-hijack-sessions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Distribute Compromised SonicWall SSL VPN NetExtender to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-distribute-compromised-sonicwall-ssl-vpn-netextender/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall NetExtender; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious version of SonicWall's SSL VPN NetExtender application was discovered being disseminated by threat actors in a cyberattack. The tampered installer bypasses digital certificate checks and steals sensitive VPN configuration data, including usernames, passwords, and domain details, which can grant attackers unauthorized access to corporate networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144134</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Releases Emergency Patches for Actively Exploited CVE-2025-6543 in NetScaler ADC</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-releases-emergency-patches-for.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6543; Summary: The vulnerability is a critical memory overflow issue (CVSS score 9.2) affecting NetScaler ADC and Gateway versions prior to specific patches, allowing unintended control flow and denial-of-service. Successful exploitation requires the appliance to be configured as a Gateway or AAA virtual server. Exploits have been observed on unmitigated appliances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-releases-emergency-patches-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BreachForums hacking forum operators reportedly arrested in France</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breachforums-hacking-forum-operators-reportedly-arrested-in-france/</link>
      <description>The French police have arrested five operators of the BreachForum cybercrime forum, including ShinyHunters and IntelBroker, who were involved in multiple high-profile data breaches. The arrested threat actors allegedly operated BreachForums v2, a community for cybercriminals to trade, sell, and leak stolen data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breachforums-hacking-forum-operators-reportedly-arrested-in-france/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-5777 (CitrixBleed 2) Exposes NetScaler Gateway Devices to Remote Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-5777-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-gateway-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: A critical out-of-bounds read vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) in Citrix's NetScaler ADC and Gateway platforms allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely read sensitive memory content, including session tokens, which can be used to hijack sessions and bypass Multi-Factor Authentication. The vulnerability is being referred to as "CitrixBleed 2" due to its resemblance to the previously exploited CVE-2023-4966.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061288</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktivist Groups Target U.S. Companies and Military Domains in Retaliation for Iran Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacktivist-groups-target-u-s-companies-and-military-domains/</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist groups have claimed responsibility for a series of Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks targeting US military domains, major aerospace and defense corporations, and key financial institutions, in retaliation to US involvement in the Israel-Iran conflict. The cyber warfare has escalated with claims of data breaches, website defacements, and electronic interference with commercial navigation systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144125</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 Flaw Enables Token Theft; SAP GUI Flaws Risk Sensitive Data Exposure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-enables-token-theft.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP Graphical User Interface (GUI) for Windows and Java; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0055, CVE-2025-0056; Summary: The vulnerabilities allow attackers with administrative privileges or access to the user directory to access sensitive information stored in input history files. In SAP GUI for Windows, the data is weakly encrypted using XOR-based encryption, making it easily decodable. In SAP GUI for Java, the data is stored as unencrypted Java serialized objects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-enables-token-theft.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox 140 Launches with Critical Code Execution Bug Fix – Update Now</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/firefox-140-launches-with-critical-code-execution-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: The critical use-after-free vulnerability in the FontFaceSet component allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on a victim's machine, posing a major risk to user security. Additionally, two high-severity memory safety issues were patched, including memory corruption defects that could be exploited for remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144123</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Configuration Bug Freezes Update Scanning Process</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-configuration-bug-freezes-update-scanning-process/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "Scan for Updates" feature in Windows 11 version 24H2 can freeze unexpectedly, preventing devices from detecting and installing critical updates. This issue can leave systems vulnerable to threats. A temporary fix is restarting the computer, but a permanent resolution requires installing the May Windows non-security preview update (KB5058499) or subsequent updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144118</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are Initial Access Brokers (IABs)?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-are-initial-access-brokers-iabs/</link>
      <description>Initial Access Brokers (IABs) are specialized threat actors who focus on compromising corporate networks and selling access to other attackers, often ransomware operators. They typically operate in a structured way, identifying vulnerable targets using techniques like credential stuffing, vulnerability scanning, or phishing. Once they gain access, they maintain persistence through webshells or remote administration tools and prepare the access for sale on dark web forums or private communication channels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061272</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realtek Bluetooth Flaw Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks During Pairing</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/realtek-bluetooth-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Realtek RTL8762E BLE SDK v1.4.0; CVE(s): CVE-2024-48290; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Realtek's Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) implementation allows attackers to launch denial-of-service (DoS) attacks during device pairing, disrupting connections and blocking legitimate pairing attempts. The flaw occurs when attackers inject premature pairing data or send a crafted ll_terminate_ind packet, causing the target device's Bluetooth stack to crash and prevent subsequent connection attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144114</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Releases Security Patch for 11 Code Execution Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-releases-security-patch-for-11-code-execution-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): 11 (no specific CVEs listed); Summary: The Chrome team has released a critical security update addressing 11 code execution vulnerabilities that could put millions of users at risk. The update patches a range of vulnerabilities, including several discovered and reported by external security researchers, and is being distributed through the stable channel to reach users over the coming days and weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144106</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Three Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/25/cisa-adds-three-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added three new vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. CISA urges all organizations to prioritize timely remediation of these vulnerabilities as part of their vulnerability management practice, with a focus on reducing the risk of cyberattacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23550</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes Guide to Address Memory Safety Vulnerabilities in Modern Software Development</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-guide-to-address-memory-safety-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and National Security Agency (NSA) have released a comprehensive guide titled “Memory Safe Languages: Reducing Vulnerabilities in Modern Software Development.” The report highlights the importance of adopting Memory Safe Languages (MSLs) to combat memory safety vulnerabilities, which contribute to 66-75% of Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144065</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Manipulate Search Results, Exploit ChatGPT and Luma AI Popularity to Deliver Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-manipulate-search-results/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using AI-themed websites to distribute malware, such as Vidar Stealer, Lumma Stealer, and Legion Loader. The attack begins with a user clicking on a seemingly legitimate search result, leading to an AI-themed webpage embedded with malicious JavaScript that collects browser data and initiates a multi-layered redirection process to deliver the malware payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144058</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Iranian Hacktivist Group Leaks Personal Records from the 2024 Saudi Games</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pro-iranian-hacktivist-group-leaks.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a data breach allegedly carried out by the pro-Iranian hacktivist group Cyber Fattah, which published personal records of athletes and visitors of the Saudi Games online. The breach is believed to have originated from the official website of the Saudi Games 2024 and was shared on DarkForums, a cybercrime forum. The leaked data includes IT staff credentials, government official email addresses, and sensitive documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pro-iranian-hacktivist-group-leaks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes NodeRestriction Flaw Lets Nodes Bypass Resource Authorization</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kubernetes-noderestriction-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kubernetes; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4563; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in Kubernetes allows nodes to bypass authorization checks for dynamic resource allocation, enabling privilege escalation in affected clusters. The flaw resides in the NodeRestriction admission controller and affects kube-apiserver versions 1.32.0-1.32.5 and 1.33.0-1.33.1, with a CVSS score of 2.7 (Low severity).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144103</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NetNerve: AI-Powered Tool for Deep PCAP Threat Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/netnerve-ai-powered-tool/</link>
      <description>The article discusses NetNerve, an AI-powered platform that automates packet capture analysis, providing real-time insights and actionable recommendations to detect threats hidden in packet capture files. This platform addresses the limitations of traditional packet capture solutions by leveraging machine learning to identify potential security threats, eliminating manual review requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144093</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akamai Reveals New Strategies for Defenders to Combat Cryptominer Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/akamai-reveals-new-strategies-for-defenders/</link>
      <description>Akamai has developed two proactive strategies to disrupt malicious cryptominer operations by exploiting the design of common mining topologies. The first strategy targets mining proxies by submitting invalid mining job results, while the second method temporarily bans wallet addresses by flooding login requests. These techniques can halt botnet-driven cryptomining campaigns and potentially impact other cryptocurrencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144029</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware the Hidden Risk in Your Entra Environment</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/beware-hidden-risk-in-your-entra.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: A gap in access control in Microsoft Entra's subscription handling allows guest users to create and transfer subscriptions into the tenant they are invited into, while maintaining full ownership rights. This privilege escalation tactic allows a guest user to gain a foothold in an environment where they should only have limited access.

FYSA: The article discusses a surprising risk in Microsoft Entra ID that can allow guest users to escalate their privileges by creating and controlling subscriptions. The vulnerability is due to the fact that Microsoft's billing permissions are scoped at the billing account level, rather than the Entra directory. This allows an attacker with the right billing role to spin up or transfer subscriptions from their home tenant to gain control inside a target tenant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/beware-hidden-risk-in-your-entra.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Attackers Leverage Microsoft ClickOnce to Run Malware as Trusted Applications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-attackers-leverage-microsoft-clickonce/</link>
      <description>The article reports an Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) malware campaign dubbed “OneClik” targeting the energy, oil, and gas sectors. The campaign uses phishing attacks, exploits Microsoft ClickOnce, and employs "living off the land" tactics to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143998</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-418: Apple macOS CoreGraphics PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-418/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31196; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS by parsing PDF files without proper validation, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required for exploitation, and the issue can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26498</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal abuse of large language models</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/cybercriminal-abuse-of-large-language-models/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting artificial intelligence (AI) technologies such as large language models (LLMs) to aid in their criminal hacking activities. They use uncensored LLMs or custom-built criminal LLMs for illicit purposes, including generating malicious code, creating undetectable malware, and sending phishing emails. Some enterprising cybercriminals have developed their own LLMs without restrictions, marketing them to other cybercriminals on the dark web.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685ac23e178bd70001283c68</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall NetExtender Trojan and ConnectWise Exploits Used in Remote Access Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sonicwall-netextender-trojan-and.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SSL VPN NetExtender; CVE(s): None; Summary: The trojanized version of SonicWall's SSL VPN NetExtender application steals credentials from unsuspecting users by impersonating the latest version (10.3.2.27) and modifying components "NeService.exe" and "NetExtender.exe" to exfiltrate configuration information to a remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sonicwall-netextender-trojan-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Plans to Remove Chrome’s Tab Scrolling Feature</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-plans-to-remove-chromes-tab-scrolling-feature/</link>
      <description>The "Tab Scrolling" feature in Google's Chrome browser is being deprecated, which will allow tabs to compress into an unreadable strip again. Users who relied on this feature may need to explore alternative tab management solutions or adjust their browsing habits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144051</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Kibana Flaws Enable Heap Corruption and Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-kibana-flaws-enable-heap-corruption/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Elastic Kibana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2135; Summary: The critical vulnerability in Kibana's reporting engine, tracked as CVE-2025-2135, allows attackers to exploit heap memory corruption and potentially execute arbitrary code on the underlying system, posing a significant risk to data integrity and system security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144045</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CentOS Web Panel Vulnerability Allows Remote Code Execution – PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/centos-web-panel-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CentOS Web Panel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48703; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands, potentially leading to full server compromise. The flaw exploits two issues: improper enforcement of the authentication mechanism and a command injection vulnerability in the t_total parameter, which can be used to inject arbitrary commands and result in remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144040</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea-linked Supply Chain Attack Targets Developers with 35 Malicious npm Packages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/north-korea-linked-supply-chain-attack.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A total of 35 malicious npm packages have been discovered, linked to the Contagious Interview operation originating from North Korea. These packages contain a hex-encoded loader called HexEval, which collects host information and delivers a follow-on payload that downloads and executes a Python backdoor called InvisibleFerret, enabling remote control and data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/north-korea-linked-supply-chain-attack.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases New ICS Advisories Highlighting Ongoing Threats and Exploits</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-releases-new-ics-advisories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Industrial Control Systems (ICS) products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2566, CVE-2025-5087, CVE-2025-47724, CVE-2025-47725, CVE-2025-47726, CVE-2025-47727, CVE-2025-3898, CVE-2025-3116, CVE-2025-3899, CVE-2025-3905, CVE-2025-3117, CVE-2025-3112, CVE-2025-5740, CVE-2025-5741, CVE-2025-5742, CVE-2025-5743, CVE-2025-49851, CVE-2025-49852, CVE-2025-49853, CVE-2025-5015, CVE-2025-49151, CVE-2025-49152, CVE-2025-49153; Summary: The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released eight new Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories addressing critical vulnerabilities and ongoing threats to essential infrastructure. The advisories detail technical information and mitigation guidance for various ICS products used worldwide, including vulnerabilities that allow remote code execution, extract sensitive credentials, or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamViewer for Windows Vulnerability Lets Hackers Delete Files with SYSTEM Rights</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/teamviewer-for-windows-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeamViewer Remote Management for Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36537; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVSS score 7.0) in TeamViewer's Remote Management features allows a local unprivileged attacker to delete arbitrary files with SYSTEM-level privileges, posing a risk of privilege escalation or system compromise. The flaw stems from an incorrect permission assignment for critical resources in the TeamViewer Client, affecting installations with Backup, Monitoring, or Patch Management enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144012</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Megatron LM Flaw Allows Attackers to Inject Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nvidia-megatron-lm-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Megatron-LM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23264, CVE-2025-23265; Summary: The Megatron-LM framework has two critical vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-23264 and CVE-2025-23265) that allow attackers to inject and execute malicious code on affected systems. Attackers can exploit these flaws by providing a specially crafted file, which could lead to remote code execution, privilege escalation, information disclosure, and data tampering with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144001</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FileFix Exploit Uses Windows File Explorer to Run Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-filefix-exploit-uses-windows-file-explorer/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a newly discovered exploit called "FileFix" that uses Windows File Explorer to execute malicious commands without leaving the web browser. It is a social engineering attack that relies on users following instructions to copy and paste file paths or commands, which can lead to execution of PowerShell commands, potentially delivering malware like infostealers, ransomware, or other types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143993</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 05:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Extends Windows 10 Security Updates for One Year with New Enrollment Options</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-extends-windows-10-security.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft is extending Windows 10 Extended Security Updates (ESU) for an extra year, allowing users to pay a small fee or sync their PC settings to the cloud. The enrollment wizard will be available in July and mid-August, enabling users to continue receiving critical and important security updates after support ends on October 14, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-extends-windows-10-security.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google rolls out text-to-image model Imagen 4 for free</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-text-to-image-model-imagen-4-for-free/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's Imagen 4 text-to-image model, which is being rolled out for free on AI Studio. It also mentions two new Imagen models, Imagen 4 and Imagen 4 Ultra, which offer improvements in image generation quality. Additionally, the article touches on other cybersecurity-related topics such as patching automation and tech support scams detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-text-to-image-model-imagen-4-for-free/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Abuse Open-Source Tools To Target Africa’s Financial Sector</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/cybercriminals-attack-financial-sector-across-africa/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of attacks targeting financial organizations across Africa, attributed to an initial access broker. The threat actor uses a combination of open-source and publicly available tools, including PoshC2, Chisel, and Classroom Spy, to establish their attack framework and maintain persistence on compromised machines. The attackers create tunnels for network communication, perform remote administration, and disguise their tools to mask their malicious activities. Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected through various products and services, including Cortex XDR, XSIAM, Advanced WildFire, and the Unit 42 Deep and Dark Web Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=144003</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude catches up to ChatGPT with built-in memory support</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-catches-up-to-chatgpt-with-built-in-memory-support/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss any vulnerabilities, but rather mentions ChatGPT's memory feature and potential use by threat actors to write malware. 

(Note: Since the article is about ChatGPT's features and OpenAI's security measures, it does not fit into either of the other two formats)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-catches-up-to-chatgpt-with-built-in-memory-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
