<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:00:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Data Breach – Customers Personal Info, Government‑ID &amp; Transaction Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coinbase-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has been targeted by a sophisticated insider campaign that compromised sensitive customer account information and internal documentation. The breach occurred when several overseas contractors and employees were bribed to steal data from Coinbase's internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136196</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta to Train AI on E.U. User Data From May 27 Without Consent; Noyb Threatens Lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-to-train-ai-on-eu-user-data-from.html</link>
      <description>Meta's plan to train AI models using user data without explicit opt-in consent has been criticized by Austrian privacy non-profit noyb (none of your business), which sent a cease-and-desist letter threatening a class action lawsuit. The group argues that Meta is relying on an alleged "legitimate interest" instead of seeking consent, and that this approach violates the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Union.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-to-train-ai-on-eu-user-data-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Power confirms hackers stole customer data in cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nova-scotia-power-confirms-hackers-stole-customer-data-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nova Scotia Power suffered a data breach after threat actors stole sensitive customer data, including full names, phone numbers, and bank account numbers. The company discovered the incident on April 28, 2025, but it's believed to have occurred earlier on March 19, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nova-scotia-power-confirms-hackers-stole-customer-data-in-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Turla’s Uroboros Infrastructure and Tactics Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/inside-turlas-uroboros-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Uroboros rootkit, attributed to the APT group Turla, which showcases sophisticated and mastery over Windows kernel internals. The malware embeds itself into the operating system with strategic intent and architectural ingenuity, enabling long-term control and covert communication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136103</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Five Active Zero-Day Windows Vulnerabilities Being Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-five-active-zero-day-windows-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added five newly identified Windows 0-day vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, presenting significant risks for organizations relying on Microsoft Windows environments. The article highlights the potential impact of these vulnerabilities, including privilege escalation attacks and system takeover or additional malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136155</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Google Services to Send Malicious Law Enforcement Requests</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-google-services/</link>
      <description>Sophisticated phishing campaign uses Google services to create convincing law enforcement requests; attackers exploit trust associated with Google infrastructure to deceive companies and individuals into disclosing sensitive information. The campaign leverages Google Forms and Drive to craft and distribute fraudulent requests, posing a severe threat to data privacy and security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136121</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Open Source Packages to Deploy Malware in Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-open-source-packages-to-deploy-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a surge in supply chain attacks where threat actors weaponize open source software libraries to deliver malicious payloads. The attackers employ various techniques such as typosquatting, repository and caching abuse, obfuscation, and multi-stage malware to maximize their impact across package registries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136049</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-Breaking $27 Billion Black Market ‘Haowang Guarantee’ Deals Conducted Behind Closed Doors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/record-breaking-27-billion-black-market-haowang-guarantee-deals/</link>
      <description>Two of the world's largest illegal marketplaces, Huione Guarantee and Xinbi Guarantee, were forced offline by Telegram on May 13, 2025, disrupting the global online scam industry. These platforms enabled over $35 billion in transactions for various criminal activities, including money laundering, stolen data, human trafficking, and torture devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135987</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Active Exploitation of Zero-Day Vulnerability in Multiple Fortinet Products</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-active-exploitation-of-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in multiple Fortinet products (FortiVoice, FortiMail, FortiNDR, FortiRecorder, and FortiCamera) allows remote, unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands by sending specially crafted HTTP requests. The vulnerability has a CVSS v3 score of 9.6 and has been actively exploited in the wild, with initial attacks targeting FortiVoice appliances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136039</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 and Red Hat Linux hacked on first day of Pwn2Own</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-and-red-hat-linux-virtualbox-hacked-on-first-day-of-pwn2own/</link>
      <description>Security researchers were awarded over $260,000 after successfully demonstrating zero-day exploits for Windows 11, Red Hat Linux, and Oracle VirtualBox at Pwn2Own Berlin 2025. The competition will continue to target fully patched products in various categories, with a grand prize pool of over $1,000,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-and-red-hat-linux-virtualbox-hacked-on-first-day-of-pwn2own/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tor Oniux tool anonymizes any Linux app's network traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-tor-oniux-tool-anonymizes-any-linux-apps-network-traffic/</link>
      <description>Tor has announced Oniux, a command-line tool for routing any Linux application securely through the Tor network using Linux namespaces, providing kernel-enforced isolation and preventing data leaks. Unlike Torsocks, which relies on user-space tricks, Oniux achieves this by placing each app in its own network namespace with no access to the host's interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-tor-oniux-tool-anonymizes-any-linux-apps-network-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Steal Customers Banking Details in Nova Scotia Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-steal-customers-banking-details/</link>
      <description>A cyberattack was detected on March 19, 2025, which compromised Nova Scotia Power's IT infrastructure and exfiltrated sensitive customer data, including banking details from pre-authorized payment systems. The breach impacts an undisclosed number of customers and exposed personal identifiers, financial records, and operational data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136066</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New .NET Multi-Stage Loader Targets Windows Systems to Deploy Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-net-multi-stage-loader-targets-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>A .NET-based multi-stage loader has been discovered, capable of deploying commodity stealers, keyloggers, and Remote Access Trojans (RATs) such as AgentTesla, Formbook, Remcos, and 404Keylogger. The loader's complex architecture and ability to embed encrypted payloads make detection challenging for traditional security tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136075</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xerox Launches April 2025 Security Patch for FreeFlow Print Server v2</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xerox-launches-april-2025-security-patch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Xerox FreeFlow Print Server v2 running on Windows 10; CVE(s): CVE-2025-21191, CVE-2025-27732, CVE-2024-9143; Summary: The update addresses over 40 critical vulnerabilities in OpenJDK Java, Apache HTTP Server, and OpenSSL, while introducing stricter encryption protocols for secure file transfers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135907</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook Down – Millions of Business &amp; Personal Users Worldwide Impacted</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-outlook-down/</link>
      <description>A major outage hit Microsoft Outlook and other Microsoft 365 services, leaving millions of users unable to access their email, calendars, and productivity tools. The disruption affected various services, including Teams, Excel, PowerPoint, and the Microsoft Store, causing disruptions for businesses and individuals alike. The timing of the outage, coinciding with the end of the financial year in some regions, exacerbated its impact on business communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136101</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Agents Bribed, Data of ~1% Users Leaked; $20M Extortion Attempt Fails</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/coinbase-agents-bribed-data-of-1-users.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Coinbase; CVE(s): None; Summary: Unknown cyber actors stole account data for less than 1% of Coinbase's monthly transacting users by targeting customer support agents overseas. The goal was to gather a list of customers and deceive them into handing over their cryptocurrency assets, with the attackers attempting to extort $20 million from Coinbase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/coinbase-agents-bribed-data-of-1-users.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nucor Steel Manufacturer Halts Production After Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nucor-steel-manufacturer-halts-production/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Nucor Corporation (Operational Systems); CVE(s): None; Summary: Unauthorized access to Nucor's information technology systems compromised critical operational systems, disrupting production at multiple facilities. The breach highlights the escalating risks of cyber threats to industrial control systems and the delicate balance between maintaining operational continuity and mitigating cybersecurity risks in critical manufacturing sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135977</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Data Compromised in Dior Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/customer-data-compromised/</link>
      <description>Dior's customer database was breached by unauthorized external actors, exposing various categories of personal information. The breach did not expose financial details, but may have placed affected customers at risk of targeted attacks or identity theft attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135954</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enisa Launched New European Vulnerability Database to Strengthen Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/enisa-unveils-new-european-vulnerability-database/</link>
      <description>The European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA) has launched the European Vulnerability Database (EUVD), a platform designed to enhance digital security across the EU by aggregating and standardizing vulnerability information affecting Information and Communication Technology (ICT) products and services. The database is accessible to the public, aiming to raise cybersecurity standards and provide users with actionable details for mitigating vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135880</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xanthorox Emerging BlackHat AI Tool Empowering Hackers in Phishing and Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xanthorox-emerging-blackhat-ai-tool-empowering-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Xanthorox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Xanthorox is an artificial intelligence platform that enables the automated generation of phishing campaigns, malware, and hyperrealistic deepfakes. Its accessibility and affordability make it a potent tool for cybercriminals, allowing them to launch personalized attacks with ease. The platform's capabilities include generating ransomware code, crafting phishing emails, and producing deepfake audio or video for impersonation scams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135860</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vulnerability Enables Attackers to Crash Processes and Disrupt Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/node-js-vulnerability-enables-attackers-to-crash-processes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Node.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23166, CVE-2025-23167, CVE-2025-23165; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities in Node.js could allow attackers to crash server processes and disrupt critical services. CVE-2025-23166 affects improper error handling in asynchronous cryptographic operations, while CVE-2025-23167 updates the llhttp HTTP parser library to version 9.2.0, addressing security and robustness issues. CVE-2025-23165 addresses a resource cleanup issue in uv_fs_req_cleanup, which could lead to resource leaks or process instability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious NPM package uses Unicode steganography to evade detection</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-package-uses-unicode-steganography-to-evade-detection/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: os-info-checker-es6; CVE(s): None; Summary: The malicious Node Package Manager (NPM) package, os-info-checker-es6, uses invisible Unicode characters to hide malicious code and a Google Calendar link to host the command-and-control location. It delivers a sophisticated C2 mechanism that drops a malware payload, which is executed using eval() and includes persistence mechanisms in the system's temporary directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-package-uses-unicode-steganography-to-evade-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase data breach exposes customer info and government IDs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-discloses-breach-faces-up-to-400-million-in-losses/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Coinbase; CVE(s): None; Summary: Rogue support agents stole customer data and demanded a $20 million ransom, which Coinbase refused to pay. The attackers exfiltrated personally identifiable information of up to 1% of Coinbase's customer base (around 1 million individuals), but could not steal private keys or passwords, nor access Coinbase Prime accounts and hot or cold wallets.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-discloses-breach-faces-up-to-400-million-in-losses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Exploit XSS Vulnerabilities to Inject Malicious Code into Email Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-hackers-exploit-xss-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube, Horde, MDaemon, Zimbra; CVE(s): CVE-2020-35730, CVE-2024-11182; Summary: Sednit group exploited known and zero-day XSS vulnerabilities in webmail servers to steal sensitive data. The campaign, dubbed Operation RoundPress, targets governmental and defense entities worldwide using spearphishing emails that inject malicious JavaScript payloads into victims' webmail interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136009</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized Google Calendar Invites Deliver Malicious Payload Using a Single Character</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-google-calendar-invites-deliver-malicious-payload/</link>
      <description>Malware distribution method leverages Google Calendar invites to deliver malicious payloads through seemingly innocuous links. The attack uses obfuscation techniques, including base64 encoding and binary trickery, to fetch payloads from a Google-hosted calendar event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135863</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Defender Application Control Bypassed Through Browser Exploit Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-defender-application-control-bypassed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers from X-Force Red Adversary Simulation team discovered a novel method to bypass Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) by exploiting vulnerabilities in trusted Electron applications using the V8 engine. This technique allows attackers to execute native shellcode, effectively sidestepping WDAC's stringent controls and introducing malicious payloads into tightly controlled systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135981</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Officials Probe Rogue Communication Devices in Solar Power Inverters</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/u-s-officials-probe-rogue-communication-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Chinese-manufactured power inverters; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports that Chinese-manufactured power inverters contain undocumented communication equipment, which could allow remote access to manipulate or disable the devices, potentially destabilizing power grids and causing widespread blackouts. Experts warn that these hidden channels could bypass firewall protections, allowing malicious actors to alter inverter settings or shut them down en masse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135847</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransferLoader Malware Enables Attackers to Execute Arbitrary Commands on Infected Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/transferloader-malware-enables-attackers/</link>
      <description>TransferLoader is a sophisticated malware loader that has been active since at least February 2025. It consists of multiple components, including a downloader, backdoor, and specialized loader for the backdoor module. The malware allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on compromised systems and has been linked to the deployment of Morpheus ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135960</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkCloud Stealer Employs AutoIt to Evade Detection and Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/darkcloud-stealer-employs-autoit-to-evade-detection/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of attacks involving the DarkCloud Stealer malware, which uses AutoIt scripting and multi-stage payloads to bypass traditional detection mechanisms. The malware targets sensitive data such as login credentials, credit card information, and browser data, and has impacted sectors like government, high tech, and finance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135881</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chihuahua Stealer Exploits Google Drive Document to Harvest Browser Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chihuahua-stealer-exploits-google-drive-document/</link>
      <description>Chihuahua Stealer is a .NET-based infostealer that uses sophisticated techniques to infiltrate systems and exfiltrate sensitive data. It targets browser data, including login credentials, cookies, autofill information, and browsing history, as well as crypto wallet extensions. The malware's approach utilizes Google Drive as an initial infection vector, multi-stage payload delivery, scheduled task persistence, and advanced encryption methods, making it a significant challenge for cybersecurity professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interlock Ransomware Targeting Defense Contractors and Supply Chain Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/interlock-ransomware-targeting-defense-contractors/</link>
      <description>The Interlock Ransomware group has emerged as a significant threat targeting defense contractors and their supply chain networks, exploiting geopolitical tensions and local conflicts for espionage or strategic disruption. The group's attacks have exposed sensitive information about global defense supply chains, including connections to major players like Raytheon, SpaceX, Thales, and Leonardo, posing a direct threat to national security by enabling adversaries to map military supply chains, redirect shipments, or gain strategic insights during ongoing geopolitical conflicts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135808</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies hack high-value mail servers using an exploit from yesteryear</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/spies-hack-high-value-mail-servers-using-an-exploit-from-yesteryear/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Operation RoundPress, a cyberespionage campaign that exploited cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in mail servers to steal email secrets. The malicious code was embedded in HTML portions of emails and only ran when the email was viewed from a vulnerable webmail instance, with no persistence but repeatable exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/spies-hack-high-value-mail-servers-using-an-exploit-from-yesteryear/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808 Devices</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808 Devices; CVE(s): CVE-2024-32122, CVE-2024-52963; Summary: Insufficiently protected credentials and out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in FortiOS may allow an attacker to retrieve LDAP credentials or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23365</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens MS/TP Point Pickup Module</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-16</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens MS/TP Point Pickup Module; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24510; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker residing in the same BACnet network to send a specially crafted MSTP message that results in a denial of service condition of the targeted device, requiring a power cycle to restore normal operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23380</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens INTRALOG WMS</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens INTRALOG WMS; CVE(s): CVE-2024-0056, CVE-2024-20672, CVE-2024-30105, CVE-2024-35264, CVE-2024-38081, CVE-2024-38095, CVE-2024-43483, CVE-2024-43485; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to bypass security features, cause a denial-of-service condition, or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23366</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Twenty-Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/15/cisa-releases-twenty-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple products from Siemens, Schneider Electric, Mitsubishi Electric, and ECOVACS; CVE(s): None; Summary: CISA released 22 ICS advisories on May 15, 2025, regarding vulnerabilities and exploits affecting various industrial control systems (ICS) products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23385</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Build Rapsody</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-20</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Build Rapsody; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3916; Summary: A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the EcoStruxure Power Build Rapsody, allowing local attackers to execute arbitrary code by opening a malicious project file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23384</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Desigo</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Desigo CC; CVE(s): CVE-2024-23815; Summary: A vulnerability in the Siemens Desigo CC server allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the server database via the event port (default: 4998/tcp). Successful exploitation could allow the attacker to modify the client binary and access the server database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23368</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens OZW Web Servers</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-10</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens OZW672 and OZW772; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26389, CVE-2025-26390; Summary: The web service in affected devices has improper input sanitization, allowing an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23374</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Teamcenter Visualization</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Teamcenter Visualization; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32454; Summary: An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Siemens Teamcenter Visualization products allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process, with a low attack complexity. The affected products include all versions prior to V14.3.0.14, V2312.0010, V2406.0008, and V2412.0004.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23370</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens SIPROTEC and SICAM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SIPROTEC and SICAM products; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3596; Summary: A vulnerability in the RADIUS protocol used by Siemens SIPROTEC and SICAM products allows a local attacker to modify Access-Reject or Access-Accept responses using a chosen-prefix collision attack against MD5 Response Authenticator signature, potentially granting unauthorized access to networks. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to bypass authentication and authorization mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23369</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens User Management Component (UMC)</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-09</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens User Management Component (UMC); CVE(s): CVE-2025-30174, CVE-2025-30175, CVE-2025-30176; Summary: The affected products contain out-of-bound read and write buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the integrated UMC component. Successful exploitation could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23373</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens BACnet ATEC Devices</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens BACnet ATEC Devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40556; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker on the same network to send a specially crafted MSTP message, resulting in a denial of service condition of the targeted device. Affected devices improperly handle specific incoming BACnet MSTP messages, requiring a power cycle to restore normal operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23367</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens APOGEE PXC and TALON TC Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-14</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens APOGEE PXC and TALON TC Series; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40555; Summary: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to cause a partial denial of service and reduce network availability by sending unsolicited BACnet broadcast messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23378</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Polarion</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-11</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Polarion V2310, V2404; CVE(s): CVE-2024-51444, CVE-2024-51445, CVE-2024-51446, CVE-2024-51447; Summary: The affected application contains several vulnerabilities, including SQL injection, XXE injection, cross-site scripting, and observable response discrepancy. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow attackers to extract data, conduct cross-site scripting attacks, or find valid usernames.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23375</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens RUGGEDCOM ROX II</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-17</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens RUGGEDCOM ROX series products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32469, CVE-2025-33024, and CVE-2025-33025; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker with a legitimate account to execute arbitrary code with root privileges. The vulnerabilities are due to missing server-side input sanitation in the 'ping', 'tcpdump', and 'traceroute' tools on affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23381</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECOVACS DEEBOT Vacuum and Base Station</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-19</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ECOVACS DEEBOT Vacuum and Base Station; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30198, CVE-2025-30199, CVE-2025-30200; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to send malicious updates to the devices or execute code. The vulnerabilities include using a hard-coded cryptographic key and downloading code without integrity checks. Affected products include X1S PRO, X1 PRO OMNI, X1 OMNI, X1 TURBO, T10 Series, and T30 Series.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23383</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens IPC RS-828A</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SIMATIC IPC RS-828A; CVE(s): CVE-2024-54085; Summary: An authentication bypass vulnerability in the BMC of Siemens' SIMATIC IPC RS-828A rugged industrial PCs allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access, compromising confidentiality, integrity, and availability. Successful exploitation could lead to a loss of these security properties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23371</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens VersiCharge AC Series EV Chargers</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-08</link>
      <description>The article discusses two vulnerabilities in Siemens electric vehicle charging devices and systems. The first vulnerability, CVE-2025-31929, allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the device's settings and configuration, potentially leading to further exploitation of other vulnerabilities or data theft. The second vulnerability, CVE-2025-31930, is a denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability that could cause the charging device to malfunction or crash.

The affected devices include various models of Siemens electric vehicle chargers and systems, including IEC 1Ph and IEC 3Ph devices, as well as UL Commercial Cellular 48A NTEP and other products. The vulnerabilities were discovered through internal testing and external reporting.

Siemens has released updates to fix the vulnerabilities, with some devices requiring a firmware update to V2.135 or later. Users are advised to update their devices and take defensive measures to minimize the risk of exploitation, such as minimizing network exposure for all control system devices and/or systems.

In general, Siemens recommends protecting network access to devices with appropriate mechanisms and configuring the environment according to their operational guidelines for industrial security and following recommendations in the product manuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23372</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Mendix OIDC SSO</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-135-15</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Mendix OIDC SSO; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40571; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to modify the system and gain administrator read/write privileges. It affects all versions of Mendix 9 compatible OIDC SSO and all versions before V4.0.0 of Mendix 10 compatible OIDC SSO.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23379</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
