<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways Identity-based Attacks Are Breaching Retail</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/5-ways-identity-based-attacks-are.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses recent high-profile data breaches in retail, where attackers exploited overprivileged access and unmonitored service accounts using social engineering tactics. The attacks targeted third-party customer service providers, resulting in the exposure of customer data, including names, email addresses, and order details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/5-ways-identity-based-attacks-are.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RondoDox Botnet Exploits Flaws in TBK DVRs and Four-Faith Routers to Launch DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/rondodox-botnet-exploits-flaws-in-tbk.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TBK Digital Video Recorders (DVRs) - DVR-4104 and DVR-4216; Four-Faith routers - F3x24 and F3x36; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3721, CVE-2024-12856; Summary: Medium-severity command injection vulnerabilities in TBK DVRs and Four-Faith routers allow attackers to deploy different Mirai botnet variants. The flaws have been publicly disclosed and are actively being targeted, posing serious risks to device security and overall network integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/rondodox-botnet-exploits-flaws-in-tbk.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaitTrap: Over 17,000 Fake News Websites Caught Fueling Investment Fraud Globally</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/baittrap-over-17000-fake-news-websites.html</link>
      <description>A large-scale scam operation utilizing fake news websites (Baiting News Sites) has been discovered, targeting users across 50 countries with online investment fraud. The scammers use sponsored ads and fake articles to lure victims into fraudulent trading platforms, followed by a two-phase structure of building trust and extracting maximum value before the victim realizes it's a trap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/baittrap-over-17000-fake-news-websites.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoldMelody’s Hidden Chords: Initial Access Broker In-Memory IIS Modules Revealed</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/initial-access-broker-exploits-leaked-machine-keys/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a threat brief on an Initial Access Broker (IAB) group known as TGR-CRI-0045, which is leveraging in-memory IIS techniques for persistent access. The article discusses the group's use of ASP.NET View State deserialization vulnerabilities and its exploitation of exposed Machine Keys.

The article provides details on the group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including the use of reflective .NET assemblies, TxPortMap tooling, and GodPotato privilege escalation technique. It also discusses the group's post-exploitation activities, such as code injection attacks using publicly disclosed ASP.NET machine keys.

The article concludes by highlighting the need for organizations to prioritize identifying and remediating compromised Machine Keys, as outlined by Microsoft. It also mentions that Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected from these threats through various products and features.

Overall, this article is not discussing a specific vulnerability (software, hardware, or firmware), but rather providing insights on an IAB group's TTPs and the need for organizations to be aware of these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=145084</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Batavia Windows Spyware Stealing Documents from Russian Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/researchers-uncover-batavia-windows.html</link>
      <description>The article describes two separate cyberattacks, one delivering Batavia Windows spyware and another delivering NordDragonScan Windows stealer malware. Both attacks use phishing emails to deliver malicious payloads that steal sensitive data from compromised hosts.

FYSA: Russian organizations have been targeted by a campaign delivering the previously undocumented Windows spyware called Batavia. The attack uses bait emails containing malicious links, which download an archive file containing a Visual Basic Encoded script (.VBE) file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/researchers-uncover-batavia-windows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Critical Vulnerabilities to KEV Catalog Due to Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-four-critical-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): CVE-2014-3931, CVE-2016-10033, CVE-2019-5418, CVE-2019-9621; Summary: Four security flaws have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The vulnerabilities include a buffer overflow in MRLG, command injection in PHPMailer, path traversal in Ruby on Rails' Action View, and SSRF in Zimbra Collaboration Suite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-four-critical-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Chinese hacker tied to Silk Typhoon arrested for cyberespionage</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/alleged-chinese-hacker-tied-to-silk-typhoon-arrested-for-cyberespionage/</link>
      <description>A Chinese national, Xu Zewei, was arrested in Italy for allegedly being linked to the state-sponsored Silk Typhoon hacking group, responsible for cyberattacks against American organizations and government agencies. The group is accused of targeting infectious disease researchers and healthcare organizations, as well as the U.S. Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control and the Committee on Foreign Investment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/alleged-chinese-hacker-tied-to-silk-typhoon-arrested-for-cyberespionage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 01:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unless users take action, Android will let Gemini access third-party apps</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/unless-users-take-action-android-will-let-gemini-access-third-party-apps/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Google Gemini app's data collection capabilities and provides remedies for users who want to prevent data collection. Disabling app activity or uninstalling the app can be done through command-line terminal or using Android debug bridge, but some users may encounter errors like "DELETE_FAILED_INTERNAL_ERROR".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/unless-users-take-action-android-will-let-gemini-access-third-party-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 23:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public exploits released for Citrix Bleed 2 NetScaler flaw, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-exploits-released-for-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The CitrixBleed2 vulnerability allows attackers to retrieve memory contents by sending malformed POST requests during login attempts. This can lead to the theft of user session tokens and potentially exploit sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-exploits-released-for-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 22:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee gets $920 for credentials used in $140 million bank heist</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/employee-gets-920-for-credentials-used-in-140-million-bank-heist/</link>
      <description>The article reports a social engineering attack on an employee at C&amp;M, a company that offers financial connectivity solutions. The attackers bribed the employee to gain access to confidential systems and steal nearly $140 million from six banks in Brazil. The incident highlights the importance of employee awareness and training in preventing such attacks.

FYSA: The article discusses a sophisticated social engineering attack on an employee at C&amp;M, a company that offers financial connectivity solutions. The attackers bribed the employee to gain access to confidential systems and steal nearly $140 million from six banks in Brazil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/employee-gets-920-for-credentials-used-in-140-million-bank-heist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-474: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-474/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7223; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VPM files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25044</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-475: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-475/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7224; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VPM files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25045</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-476: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-476/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7225; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VPM files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25047</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-477: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-477/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7226; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by parsing VPM files with an out-of-bounds write. User interaction is required, and the issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in writing past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25048</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-478: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-478/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parser; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7227; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required, and the attack can be initiated through a malicious page or file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25550</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-479: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-479/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT, VT-Designer PM3 File Parser; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7228; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting an out-of-bounds write issue in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25571</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-480: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-480/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7229; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by parsing PM3 files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25722</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-481: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-481/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7230; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting a type confusion condition in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25723</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-482: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-482/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7231; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer. It requires user interaction, such as visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, and is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the parsing of PM3 files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25724</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic macOS infostealer adds backdoor for persistent attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atomic-macos-infostealer-adds-backdoor-for-persistent-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atomic macOS Stealer; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Atomic macOS info-stealer (AMOS) has been updated with a backdoor, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary remote commands, survive reboots, and maintain control over infected hosts indefinitely. The malware can log keystrokes, introduce additional payloads, or perform lateral movement. It also features string obfuscation and checks for sandbox or virtual machine environments to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atomic-macos-infostealer-adds-backdoor-for-persistent-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“No honor among thieves”: M&amp;S hacking group starts turf war</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-honor-among-thieves-ms-hacking-group-starts-turf-war/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a potential conflict between two ransomware groups, DragonForce and RansomHub, which could lead to increased risk of cyberattacks and double extortions. The instability in the extortion ecosystem can have serious implications for ransomware and data theft extortion victims. Additionally, the global cost of cybercrime is estimated to reach $10 trillion by 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-honor-among-thieves-ms-hacking-group-starts-turf-war/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEO Poisoning Campaign Targets 8,500+ SMB Users with Malware Disguised as AI Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/seo-poisoning-campaign-targets-8500.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article does not describe a vulnerability in any specific product. Instead, it discusses various malicious campaigns and tactics used by threat actors to spread malware, steal sensitive information, and commit financial fraud. The article highlights the use of search engine optimization (SEO) poisoning techniques, malvertising, and social engineering tactics to deliver malware loaders like Oyster, Vidar, Lumma, and Legion Loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/seo-poisoning-campaign-targets-8500.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qantas is being extorted in recent data-theft cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-is-being-extorted-in-recent-data-theft-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Qantas has confirmed a cyberattack that potentially exposed 6 million customers' data, with threat actors demanding extortion. The attack did not expose financial information or sensitive details, but warned customers to be cautious of scams and phishing emails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-is-being-extorted-in-recent-data-theft-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Batavia' Windows spyware campaign targets dozens of Russian orgs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/batavia-windows-spyware-campaign-targets-dozens-of-russian-orgs/</link>
      <description>The article describes a previously undocumented spyware called "Batavia" that targets large industrial enterprises in Russia through phishing email campaigns. The malware has multiple stages, including profile gathering, data exfiltration, and additional payload downloads, indicating an espionage operation on Russia's industrial activity.

FYSA: The article highlights the effectiveness of simple techniques used by threat actors, even as cloud attacks become more sophisticated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/batavia-windows-spyware-campaign-targets-dozens-of-russian-orgs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers abuse leaked Shellter red team tool to deploy infostealers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-abuse-leaked-shellter-red-team-tool-to-deploy-infostealers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Shellter; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers used Shellter Elite, a commercial AV/EDR evasion loader for penetration testing, in attacks after a customer leaked a copy of the software. The misuse was discovered by security researchers and an update has been released to address the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-abuse-leaked-shellter-red-team-tool-to-deploy-infostealers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-473: Parallels Client Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-473/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Parallels Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6812; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Client by exploiting an uncontrolled search path element in the AppServer service, which loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability and execute arbitrary code in the context of a target user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25039</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/07/cisa-adds-four-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple products; CVE(s): CVE-2014-3931, CVE-2016-10033, CVE-2019-5418, CVE-2019-9621; Summary: The Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog has added four new vulnerabilities, including a Multi-Router Looking Glass Buffer Overflow, PHPMailer Command Injection, Rails Ruby on Rails Path Traversal, and Synacor Zimbra Collaboration Suite Server-Side Request Forgery. These vulnerabilities are frequently targeted by malicious actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and other organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23600</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Chrome 0-Day, Ivanti Exploits, MacOS Stealers, Crypto Heists and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-ivanti.html</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a collection of various cybersecurity-related news and developments, covering topics such as malware attacks, phishing campaigns, data breaches, and security updates from major technology companies. There are no specific vulnerabilities mentioned in the article.

However, it's worth noting that the article does discuss some common attack vectors and tactics used by malicious actors, including smishing campaigns, email bombing, and file system redirection attacks. It also highlights the importance of robust cybersecurity measures and the need for organizations to stay vigilant against emerging threats.

Overall, while this article is not focused on a specific vulnerability, it provides valuable insights into the current state of cybersecurity and the types of threats that organizations may face in today's digital landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-ivanti.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Security: Why Default Passwords Must Go</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/manufacturing-security-why-default.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the risks associated with using default passwords in various devices and software systems. It emphasizes that default passwords provide an easy entry point for attackers, allowing them to recruit botnets, launch ransomware attacks, and compromise entire networks or partner systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/manufacturing-security-why-default.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSO 0-Day &amp; Fortinet Exploits, Allianz Breach, Social Media Ban Service Listed on Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/sso-0-day-fortinet-exploits-allianz-breach-social-media-ban-service/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apereo CAS, Jasig, Keycloak with the CAS plugin; CVE(s): None; Summary: An alleged 0-day redirect vulnerability exists in major Single Sign-On (SSO) platforms, potentially allowing attackers to redirect users from trusted login portals to attacker-controlled domains, enabling phishing, session hijacking, or login bypass. The issue affects over 12,000 live systems across government, healthcare, finance, and international organizations.

FYSA: Threat actors are advertising exploits targeting known Fortinet CVEs (CVE-2024-55591) and a stolen database linked to Allianz Seguros Spain, potentially containing approximately 4.6 million records. Additionally, a social media ban service is being promoted, offering targeted takedowns across multiple platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061689</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 09:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAG-140 Deploys DRAT V2 RAT, Targeting Indian Government, Defense, and Rail Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/tag-140-deploys-drat-v2-rat-targeting.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of a modified variant of a remote access trojan (RAT) called DRAT V2, used by the threat actor TAG-140 to target Indian government organizations. The malware, which is part of an "interchangeable suite" of RATs, allows for harvesting sensitive data and complicates attribution, detection, and monitoring efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/tag-140-deploys-drat-v2-rat-targeting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI says GPT-5 will unify breakthroughs from different models</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-says-gpt-5-will-unify-breakthroughs-from-different-models/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it provides information on OpenAI's plans to unify multiple models into one, creating GPT-5, and improves the existing models.

FYSA: Threat actors are using simple techniques to succeed in cloud attacks, with 8 key techniques revealed by Wiz's detections across thousands of organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-says-gpt-5-will-unify-breakthroughs-from-different-models/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands on with Windows 11 Notepad's new markdown support</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-windows-11-notepads-new-markdown-support/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the addition of markdown text formatting in Windows 11's Notepad app. The feature allows users to apply different formatting options such as headings, bold and italic styling, and hyperlinks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-windows-11-notepads-new-markdown-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is testing disruptive Study Together feature</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-testing-disruptive-study-together-feature/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article does not contain information about a vulnerability. Instead, it discusses new features and updates related to OpenAI's ChatGPT, including the potential introduction of "Study together" mode, new connectors for GPT Search and Deep Research, and upcoming developments with GPT-5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-testing-disruptive-study-together-feature/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingram Micro outage caused by SafePay ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-outage-caused-by-safepay-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>The article reports on an ongoing outage at Ingram Micro caused by a SafePay ransomware attack. The attack led to the shutdown of internal systems and ransom notes were found on employee devices, although it's unclear if devices were actually encrypted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-outage-caused-by-safepay-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 15:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan NSB Alerts Public on Data Risks from TikTok, Weibo, and RedNote Over China Ties</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/taiwan-nsb-alerts-public-on-data-risks.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Taiwan's National Security Bureau (NSB) warned about various Chinese-developed applications; CVE(s): None; Summary: The NSB detected excessive data collection, privacy infringement, and unauthorized data transmission from apps like RedNote, Weibo, TikTok, WeChat, and Baidu Cloud to China. These apps breached security indicators, including personal data collection, permission usage, data transmission, system information extraction, and biometric data access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/taiwan-nsb-alerts-public-on-data-risks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alert: Exposed JDWP Interfaces Lead to Crypto Mining, Hpingbot Targets SSH for DDoS</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/alert-exposed-jdwp-interfaces-lead-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple applications (TeamCity, Jenkins, Selenium Grid, Elasticsearch, Quarkus, Spring Boot, Apache Tomcat); CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting exposed Java Debug Wire Protocol (JDWP) interfaces to obtain code execution capabilities and deploy cryptocurrency miners on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/alert-exposed-jdwp-interfaces-lead-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Deep Research tests new connectors for more context</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-deep-research-tests-new-connectors-for-more-context/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article discusses the integration of Slack with ChatGPT, a research AI agent. It mentions potential use cases for the integration, such as allowing ChatGPT to access an organization's chat and use messages in the context of research.

(Note: Since there is no vulnerability mentioned in the article, I summarized it using the FYSA format)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-deep-research-tests-new-connectors-for-more-context/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 22:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingram Micro suffers global outage as internal systems inaccessible</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-suffers-global-outage-as-internal-systems-inaccessible/</link>
      <description>Ingram Micro's global outage impacting its websites and internal systems, with customers concerned it may be a cyberattack. The company remains silent on the cause of the issue. Some customers and employees claim the outage is due to a potential ransomware attack or breach, but this has not been confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-suffers-global-outage-as-internal-systems-inaccessible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker leaks Telefónica data allegedly stolen in a new breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-leaks-telef-nica-data-allegedly-stolen-in-a-new-breach/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability but rather reports on a potential data breach at Telefónica, a Spanish telecommunications company. The hacker, known as "Rey," claims to have stolen 106GB of internal data and has released a 2.6GB archive to prove the breach occurred.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-leaks-telef-nica-data-allegedly-stolen-in-a-new-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NightEagle APT Exploits Microsoft Exchange Flaw to Target China's Military and Tech Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/nighteagle-apt-exploits-microsoft.html</link>
      <description>No vulnerability is mentioned in this article. Instead, it discusses a threat actor called NightEagle (APT-Q-95) that targets Microsoft Exchange servers as part of a zero-day exploit chain to gather intelligence from government, defense, and technology sectors in China. The attackers use a bespoke version of the Chisel utility and implant a Trojan into the Internet Information Server (IIS) service of the Microsoft Exchange Server to gain unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/nighteagle-apt-exploits-microsoft.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your AI Agents Might Be Leaking Data — Watch this Webinar to Learn How to Stop It</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/your-ai-agents-might-be-leaking-data.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article is not about a specific vulnerability, but rather highlights the potential risks of using generative AI (GenAI) systems without proper access controls, governance policies, and oversight. It discusses how well-meaning AI agents can unintentionally leak sensitive data to the wrong users or the internet, and emphasizes the importance of securing AI agents to prevent data exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/your-ai-agents-might-be-leaking-data.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Sudo Vulnerabilities Let Local Users Gain Root Access on Linux, Impacting Major Distros</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-sudo-vulnerabilities-let-local.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sudo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32462, CVE-2025-32463; Summary: Two security flaws were discovered in Sudo, a command-line utility for Linux and Unix-like operating systems. The vulnerabilities allow local attackers to escalate their privileges to root on susceptible machines. CVE-2025-32462 enables listed users to execute commands on unintended machines, while CVE-2025-32463 allows local users to obtain root access by using the --chroot option with a user-controlled directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-sudo-vulnerabilities-let-local.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Ordered to Pay $314M for Misusing Android Users' Cellular Data Without Permission</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ordered-to-pay-314m-for-misusing.html</link>
      <description>Google has been ordered by a California court to pay $314 million over allegations that it misused Android device users' cellular data when idle, sending information to the company without permission. The verdict marks an end to a legal class-action complaint filed in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ordered-to-pay-314m-for-misusing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaks hint at Operator-like tool in ChatGPT ahead of GPT-5 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leaks-hint-at-operator-like-tool-in-chatgpt-ahead-of-gpt-5-launch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: There are no cybersecurity-relevant vulnerabilities or threats discussed in this article. Instead, it appears to be a collection of unrelated news and updates about OpenAI's ChatGPT and cloud security. The article mentions the possibility of an "Operator-like tool" being developed by OpenAI, but does not provide any information about potential vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leaks-hint-at-operator-like-tool-in-chatgpt-ahead-of-gpt-5-launch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 23:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-469: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-469/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47724; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26718</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-470: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-470/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47725; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26719</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-471: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-471/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47727; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft by parsing DPB files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, requiring the target to visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26842</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-472: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-472/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47726; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft, requiring user interaction. It exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26720</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-467: GStreamer H266 Codec Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-467/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GStreamer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6663; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GStreamer. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of H266 sei messages, resulting from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27381</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-468: GFI Archiver Telerik Web UI Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-468/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GFI, Archiver; CVE(s): CVE-2019-18935, CVE-2017-11317, CVE-2014-2217; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the use of a vulnerable version of Telerik Web UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26061</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provider of covert surveillance app spills passwords for 62,000 users</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/provider-of-covert-surveillance-app-spills-passwords-for-62000-users/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a stalkerware service called Catwatchful that has a hidden backdoor allowing users to uninstall the app by inputting specific numbers on their device's keyboard. The app uploads content in real-time and can be viewed from a web dashboard, and the service's operators were identified through a database dump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/provider-of-covert-surveillance-app-spills-passwords-for-62000-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI prepares Grok 4 Code as it plans to take on Claude and Gemini</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/xai-prepares-grok-4-code-as-it-plans-to-take-on-claude-and-gemini/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the upcoming release of Grok 4, a new state-of-the-art language model from xAI. It also highlights various cloud-based threat actor techniques used to launch attacks on organizations. Additionally, the article mentions other AI-related updates and releases from Google and Vibe coding company.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/xai-prepares-grok-4-code-as-it-plans-to-take-on-claude-and-gemini/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A message from Bruce the mechanical shark</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/a-message-from-bruce-the-mechanical-shark/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article is a mix of cybersecurity-related content and non-security related information. The main focus is on cybersecurity, with discussions about phishing attacks, email threat detection engine updates, and malicious PowerShell scripts. Additionally, the article touches on a data breach at Ahold Delhaize, Europol's dismantling of a cryptocurrency fraud network, and an international cyberattack against the International Criminal Court.

However, the article also includes non-security related content, such as a nostalgic story about the movie "Jaws" and its mechanical shark, Bruce. The article concludes with a mention of upcoming conferences and events in the cybersecurity industry. Overall, the article is a collection of various topics, with some being more cybersecurity-focused than others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68667978511eb7000145d3ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dismantles investment fraud ring stealing €10 million</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/police-dismantles-investment-fraud-ring-stealing-10-million/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a large-scale investment fraud operation that was dismantled by the Spanish police, resulting in the arrest of 21 individuals and the confiscation of luxury vehicles and cash. The scammers used tactics similar to "romance baiting" scams, luring victims into fake investments through social media ads and manipulated websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/police-dismantles-investment-fraud-ring-stealing-10-million/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grafana releases critical security update for Image Renderer plugin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/grafana-releases-critical-security-update-for-image-renderer-plugin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grafana Image Renderer and Synthetic Monitoring Agent; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5959, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2025-6191, CVE-2025-6192; Summary: Four high-severity Chromium vulnerabilities have been addressed in critical security updates for the Grafana Image Renderer plugin and Synthetic Monitoring Agent. The issues allow remote code execution, arbitrary memory read/write, out-of-bounds memory access, and heap corruption exploitable via crafted HTML pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/grafana-releases-critical-security-update-for-image-renderer-plugin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech’s Mixed Response to U.S. Treasury Sanctions</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/big-techs-mixed-response-to-u-s-treasury-sanctions/</link>
      <description>Liu "Steve" Lizhi, a 40-year-old Chinese national, was sanctioned by the U.S. Department of the Treasury for operating a cloud provider linked to virtual currency investment scams known as "pig butchering." Despite being sanctioned, Lizhi maintains active accounts on Facebook, GitHub, PayPal, and Twitter/X, which continue to operate without issue. The article highlights concerns that big tech companies are not doing enough to cut ties with sanctioned individuals like Lizhi, potentially putting users at risk of financial losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71564</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Android Fraud Operations Uncovered: IconAds, Kaleidoscope, SMS Malware, NFC Scams</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/mobile-security-alert-352-iconads-fraud.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses several mobile ad fraud operations, including IconAds, Kaleidoscope, NGate, SuperCard X, and Qwizzserial. These operations involve the distribution of malicious apps through various means, including third-party app stores, fake websites, and social media platforms. The malware targets Android devices and steals user data, injects ads, and conducts fraudulent transactions.

FYSA: IconAds, a mobile ad fraud operation, has been disrupted by HUMAN. Kaleidoscope is another ad fraud scheme that uses the "evil twin" technique to distribute malicious apps. NGate and SuperCard X are malware families that abuse NFC technology for financial fraud. Qwizzserial is an SMS stealer that targets users in Uzbekistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/mobile-security-alert-352-iconads-fraud.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdeaLab confirms data stolen in ransomware attack last year</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/idealab-confirms-data-stolen-in-ransomware-attack-last-year/</link>
      <description>IdeaLab, a California-based technology startup incubator, has been impacted by a data breach incident where hackers accessed sensitive information. The Hunters International ransomware group claimed the breach and leaked the stolen data on the dark web, affecting current and former employees, contractors, and their dependents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/idealab-confirms-data-stolen-in-ransomware-attack-last-year/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft investigates ongoing SharePoint Online access issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-ongoing-sharepoint-online-access-issues/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article reports on an ongoing incident affecting SharePoint Online, a cloud-based collaboration platform. Users are experiencing intermittent access issues, with errors such as "Something went wrong." Microsoft is investigating the root cause of the issue, which appears to be related to authentication-related cookies. The company has not disclosed the affected regions or extent of the issue but has suggested possible workarounds using incognito mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-ongoing-sharepoint-online-access-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-20309: Cisco Unified CM Flaw Enables Remote Root Access</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-20309-cisco-unified-cm-remote-root-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Communications Manager platforms; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20309; Summary: A vulnerability in the static root account credentials allows an attacker to access a vulnerable device via SSH without authentication, granting full system compromise. This could enable deeper lateral movement across the network and jeopardize the integrity and confidentiality of communication platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Exchange Server Subscription Edition now available</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-exchange-server-subscription-edition-now-available/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced the availability of Exchange Server Subscription Edition (SE) to all customers, which introduces changes to licensing and servicing. The new edition will be an evergreen release with continuous support, replacing previous versions that will reach end-of-life soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-exchange-server-subscription-edition-now-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric MELSOFT Update Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-184-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric MELSOFT Update Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2024-11477, CVE-2025-0411; Summary: The MELSOFT Update Manager contains an Integer Underflow vulnerability in 7-zip that could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, disclose or alter information, or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. Additionally, there is a Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability that could also lead to the same impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23593</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Four Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/03/cisa-releases-four-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA has released four Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 3, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories are specific to certain products from Hitachi Energy and Mitsubishi Electric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23595</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy MicroSCADA X SYS600</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-184-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy MicroSCADA X SYS600; CVE(s): CVE-2025-39201, CVE-2025-39202, CVE-2025-39203, CVE-2025-39204, CVE-2025-39205; Summary: The product contains multiple vulnerabilities that could allow an attacker to tamper with system files, overwrite files, create a denial-of-service condition, or leak file content. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could have severe impacts, including data corruption and unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23592</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650 and SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-184-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650 and SAM600-IO series, Hitachi Energy; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1718; Summary: An authenticated user with file access privilege via FTP access can cause the devices to reboot due to improper disk space management. The vulnerability has a CVSS v4 score of 7.1 and affects various versions of the products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23591</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric MELSEC iQ-F Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-184-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5241; Summary: A denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the MELSEC iQ-F series due to an overly restrictive account lockout mechanism. A remote attacker could lockout a legitimate user for a certain period of time by repeatedly attempting to login with an incorrect password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23594</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunters International ransomware shuts down after World Leaks rebrand</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hunters-international-ransomware-shuts-down-after-world-leaks-rebrand/</link>
      <description>The Hunters International Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation has officially closed down and will offer free decryptors to help victims recover their data without paying a ransom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hunters-international-ransomware-shuts-down-after-world-leaks-rebrand/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 40 Malicious Firefox Extensions Target Cryptocurrency Wallets, Stealing User Assets</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/over-40-malicious-firefox-extensions.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a large-scale campaign involving over 40 malicious browser extensions for Mozilla Firefox, designed to steal cryptocurrency wallet secrets. The extensions impersonate legitimate wallet tools and employ tactics such as artificially inflating their popularity and cloning open-source code to extract wallet keys and seed phrases from targeted websites.

FYSA: The article highlights a sophisticated threat actor group using a low-effort, high-impact approach to steal users' digital assets by distributing malicious browser extensions. The campaign's success relies on the ability of these extensions to operate inside the user's browser, making them harder to detect or block with traditional endpoint tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/over-40-malicious-firefox-extensions.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Weaknesses in AI SOC Tools that No One Talks About</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/the-hidden-weaknesses-in-ai-soc-tools.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of pre-trained AI models in security operations centers (SOCs) and highlights the benefits of adaptive AI, which learns to triage and respond to any alert type. Adaptive AI uses semantic classification, research agents, and multiple large language models to provide accurate, efficient, and context-aware triage. It also enables continuous learning and improvement by benchmarking model performance on real-world SOC tasks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/the-hidden-weaknesses-in-ai-soc-tools.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft asks users to ignore Windows Firewall config errors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-asks-users-to-ignore-windows-firewall-config-errors/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft, Windows Firewall; CVE(s): None; Summary: The June 2025 preview update of Windows causes incorrect Windows Firewall errors to appear in the Event Viewer after system reboots. These errors are logged as 'Event 2042' and can be safely ignored as they do not impact any Windows processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-asks-users-to-ignore-windows-firewall-config-errors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Under the Lens: Tomcat’s Partial PUT and Camel’s Header Hijack</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/apache-cve-2025-24813-cve-2025-27636-cve-2025-29891/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses multiple vulnerabilities in Apache Tomcat and Apache Camel, including CVE-2025-24813, CVE-2025-27636, and CVE-2025-29891. The vulnerabilities allow for potential remote code execution, which can lead to data breaches and lateral movement within the network.

The analysis reveals that most of the exploit attempts use a six-character session name and a specific value for the Content-Range header. The Nuclei Scanner, a freely available scanner, is being used by attackers to check for the vulnerability.

Palo Alto Networks customers are protected from these threats through various products, including the Next Generation Firewall with an Advanced Threat Prevention subscription, Advanced URL Filtering, and Cortex Xpanse.

The article also highlights the importance of immediate action in addressing these vulnerabilities, as they can be exploited by less-skilled adversaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=144810</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 10:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit Ivanti CSA Zero-Days in Attacks on French Government, Telecoms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-exploit-ivanti-csa-zero.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance (CSA) devices; CVE(s): CVE-2024-8963, CVE-2024-9380, and CVE-2024-8190; Summary: A Chinese hacking group, codenamed Houken, exploited zero-day vulnerabilities in Ivanti CSA devices to gain access to target networks. The attackers used a rootkit and various tools to maintain persistence and conduct reconnaissance, with the goal of selling valuable data to state-linked actors or conducting lucrative operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-exploit-ivanti-csa-zero.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Cisco Vulnerability in Unified CM Grants Root Access via Static Credentials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-cisco-vulnerability-in-unified.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Communications Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20309; Summary: A maximum-severity vulnerability in Cisco Unified Communications Manager (Unified CM) and Unified Communications Manager Session Management Edition (Unified CM SME) allows an attacker to log in as the root user, gaining elevated privileges. The flaw is due to static user credentials for the root account and can be exploited by using the account to log in to an affected system, allowing the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-cisco-vulnerability-in-unified.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 04:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NimDoor crypto-theft macOS malware revives itself when killed</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nimdoor-crypto-theft-macos-malware-revives-itself-when-killed/</link>
      <description>North Korean state-backed hackers are using a new family of macOS malware called NimDoor in a campaign targeting web3 and cryptocurrency organizations. The attack chain involves contacting victims via Telegram, delivering fake Zoom SDK updates via Calendly and email, and deploying a persistence mechanism that uses signal-based techniques to ensure the malware remains active even after attempts to terminate it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nimdoor-crypto-theft-macos-malware-revives-itself-when-killed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T rolls out Wireless Account Lock protection to curb the SIM-swap scourge</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/att-rolls-out-wireless-account-lock-protection-to-curb-the-sim-swap-scourge/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AT&amp;T; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses SIM-swap scams targeting cryptocurrency and bank account holders who store large sums of digital coin. Criminals take control of phone numbers to trigger password resets, draining accounts. AT&amp;T's Wireless Account Lock feature prevents changes to SIM cards until it is manually turned off again, aiming to curb these types of scams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/att-rolls-out-wireless-account-lock-protection-to-curb-the-sim-swap-scourge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ investigates ex-ransomware negotiator over extortion kickbacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/doj-investigates-ex-ransomware-negotiator-over-extortion-kickbacks/</link>
      <description>A former employee of DigitalMint, a company that specializes in ransomware negotiation and cryptocurrency payments, is under criminal investigation for allegedly working with ransomware gangs to profit from extortion payment deals. The investigation suggests potential abuse of business models that incentivize larger transaction volumes and higher transaction sizes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/doj-investigates-ex-ransomware-negotiator-over-extortion-kickbacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain arrests hackers who targeted politicians and journalists</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spain-arrests-hackers-who-targeted-politicians-and-journalists/</link>
      <description>The Spanish police have arrested two individuals suspected of cybercrime, including data theft from the government and high-ranking officials. They allegedly leaked stolen data online to increase its value and were involved in selling access to databases and credentials. The arrests are part of a larger effort by the Spanish authorities to track and apprehend cybercriminals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/spain-arrests-hackers-who-targeted-politicians-and-journalists/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 17:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Target Web3 with Nim Malware and Use ClickFix in BabyShark Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-target-web3-with.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses North Korean threat actors using malware written in Nim programming language to target Web3 and cryptocurrency-related businesses. The malware uses process injection technique, remote communications via wss protocol, and a novel persistence mechanism. It also includes social engineering tactics, such as scheduling Zoom meetings and executing AppleScript that acts as a delivery vehicle for a second-stage script.

FYSA: North Korean threat actors have been observed targeting Web3 and cryptocurrency-related businesses with malware written in Nim programming language. The attacks involve social engineering tactics, process injection technique, and remote communications via wss protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-target-web3-with.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco warns that Unified CM has hardcoded root SSH credentials</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-removes-unified-cm-callManager-backdoor-root-account/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Communications Manager (Unified CM) and Unified CM SME; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20309; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-20309, is a backdoor account with static user credentials for the root account, allowing remote attackers to log in with root privileges. This flaw affects Cisco Unified CM and Unified CM SME releases 15.0.1.13010-1 through 15.0.1.13017-1, regardless of device configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-removes-unified-cm-callManager-backdoor-root-account/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 17:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix warns of login issues after NetScaler auth bypass patch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-of-login-issues-after-netscaler-auth-bypass-patch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777, CVE-2025-6543; Summary: The patch for recently disclosed vulnerabilities in NetScaler ADC and Gateway appliances may also break login pages due to the enabling of Content Security Policy (CSP) header by default. This can cause authentication bypass and denial-of-service attacks. Disabling the CSP header temporarily resolves the issue, but administrators are advised to reach out to Citrix Support if the problem persists.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-warns-of-login-issues-after-netscaler-auth-bypass-patch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 16:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forminator plugin flaw exposes WordPress sites to takeover attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/forminator-plugin-flaw-exposes-wordpress-sites-to-takeover-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WPMU DEV Forminator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6463; Summary: The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to an unauthenticated arbitrary file deletion flaw, tracked as CVE-2025-6463. This high-severity vulnerability (CVSS 8.8 score) allows attackers to delete critical files, such as wp-config.php, and take over the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/forminator-plugin-flaw-exposes-wordpress-sites-to-takeover-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 15:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-49596: Critical Flaw in Anthropic’s MCP Inspector Leads to RCE</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-49596-flaw-anthropics-mcp-inspector-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Anthropic's MCP Inspector; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49596; Summary: The vulnerability in Anthropic's MCP Inspector allows Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to overly lenient security defaults, including unauthenticated connections and lack of encryption. This can lead to full control over affected machines, making it a critical issue that needs to be addressed promptly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061652</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 14:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes ‘Print to PDF’ feature broken by Windows update</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-print-to-pdf-feature-broken-by-windows-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11 24H2; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "Print to PDF" feature on Windows 11 24H2 systems is broken after installing the April 2025 preview update, causing the Microsoft Print to PDF printer to no longer appear under Settings and returning error code 0x800f0922.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-print-to-pdf-feature-broken-by-windows-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of fake wallet add-ons flood Firefox store to drain crypto</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dozens-of-fake-wallet-add-ons-flood-firefox-store-to-drain-crypto/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: More than 40 fake extensions in Firefox's official add-ons store are impersonating popular cryptocurrency wallets, stealing wallet credentials and sensitive data by sending stolen information to attacker-controlled servers. The extensions include malicious code that monitors for sensitive data inputs from the victim, checks for realistic wallet keys/seed phrases, and exfiltrates data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dozens-of-fake-wallet-add-ons-flood-firefox-store-to-drain-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok 4 spotted ahead of launch with special coding features</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-spotted-ahead-of-launch-with-special-coding-features/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article does not contain information about a specific vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware.

FYSA: The article mentions xAI releasing Grok 4, which could potentially be the best model from the company. It also highlights that cloud attacks may be growing more sophisticated, but attackers still succeed with surprisingly simple techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-spotted-ahead-of-launch-with-special-coding-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: DNS issue blocks delivery of Exchange Online OTP codes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-links-dns-issue-to-exchange-online-otp-delivery-failures/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: Microsoft is experiencing DNS misconfiguration issues affecting OTP message delivery in Exchange Online, impacting some users who may not receive OTP emails for encrypted messages. The issue affects users with a process set up to perform DNS checks on incoming email messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-links-dns-issue-to-exchange-online-otp-delivery-failures/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/02/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chromium V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6554; Summary: A type confusion vulnerability in Google Chromium V8 has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog, indicating active exploitation. This type of vulnerability is a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors and poses significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23590</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Network Traffic Looks Legit, But it Could be Hiding a Serious Threat</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/that-network-traffic-looks-legit-but-it.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of multi-layered detection strategies in cybersecurity operations centers (SOCs) to detect and respond to evolving threats. It highlights the limitations of traditional endpoint detection and response (EDR) solutions and introduces network detection and response (NDR) as a complementary approach that provides visibility into network-based attacks. The article also explains different types of detections, including signature-based, threat intelligence, malware detection, behavioral detection, machine learning, anomaly detection, and search-based detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/that-network-traffic-looks-legit-but-it.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-6554: Chrome’s New Zero-Day Under Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-6554-chromes-new-zero-day-exploitation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6554; Summary: A high-severity type confusion vulnerability (CVE-2025-6554) in Google Chrome's V8 JavaScript engine allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on the victim's machine, potentially leading to full system compromise. The vulnerability is actively being exploited and affects all major desktop platforms running Chrome, including Windows, macOS, and Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061633</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 10:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Using PDFs to Impersonate Microsoft, DocuSign, and More in Callback Phishing Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-using-pdfs-to-impersonate.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a surge in phishing campaigns impersonating popular brands, including Microsoft and Docusign. The attacks use social engineering tactics, such as telephone-oriented attack delivery (TOAD), where victims are tricked into calling phone numbers operated by threat actors. These calls often employ scripted call center tactics, hold music, and spoofed caller IDs to gain the victim's trust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-using-pdfs-to-impersonate.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Shortcut (LNK) Malware Strategies</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/lnk-malware/</link>
      <description>This article provides an in-depth analysis of different types of LNK malware, which are a type of Windows executable files that can be used to launch malicious payloads. The article discusses four main techniques used by attackers to execute overlay content, including using find/findstr, mshta, and PowerShell commands/intrinsics.

The article also provides information on how Palo Alto Networks customers can protect themselves from these types of threats through the use of certain products, such as Next-Generation Firewall with cloud-delivered security services and Advanced Threat Prevention. Additionally, the article mentions that Palo Alto Networks has shared its findings with fellow Cyber Threat Alliance (CTA) members to rapidly deploy protections to their customers.

Overall, this article is a valuable resource for cybersecurity professionals looking to gain a deeper understanding of LNK malware and how to protect against these types of threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=144445</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 10:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFs: Portable documents, or perfect deliveries for phish?</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/pdfs-portable-documents-or-perfect-deliveries-for-phish/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the trend of brand impersonation in email threats using PDF payloads, including social engineering techniques such as TOAD (Telephone-Oriented Attack Delivery) and QR code phishing. It highlights the use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) numbers to remain anonymous and the reuse of phone numbers on consecutive days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685957b84c0b2400017d9b51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 10:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Sanctions Russian Bulletproof Hosting Provider for Supporting Cybercriminals Behind Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-sanctions-russian-bulletproof.html</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) has levied sanctions against Russia-based bulletproof hosting (BPH) service provider Aeza Group and its subsidiaries, along with four individuals linked to the company, for assisting threat actors in their malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-sanctions-russian-bulletproof.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel's v0 AI Tool Weaponized by Cybercriminals to Rapidly Create Fake Login Pages at Scale</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/vercels-v0-ai-tool-weaponized-by.html</link>
      <description>Unknown threat actors are using Vercel's generative AI tool v0 to design fake sign-in pages that impersonate legitimate counterparts, creating convincing replicas of login pages. This allows low-skilled attackers to build phishing sites at scale without requiring coding skills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/vercels-v0-ai-tool-weaponized-by.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 05:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qantas discloses cyberattack amid Scattered Spider aviation breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-discloses-cyberattack-amid-scattered-spider-aviation-breaches/</link>
      <description>Qantas detected a cyberattack on its third-party customer servicing platform, which contained customer data. Threat actors gained access to the platform after targeting a Qantas call centre and stole a "significant" amount of data, including names, email addresses, phone numbers, birth dates, and frequent flyer numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-discloses-cyberattack-amid-scattered-spider-aviation-breaches/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T rolls out "Wireless Lock" feature to block SIM swap attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atandt-rolls-out-wireless-lock-feature-to-block-sim-swap-attacks/</link>
      <description>This article is about a security feature called "Wireless Lock" launched by AT&amp;T to protect customers from SIM swapping attacks. The feature prevents changes to account information and phone number porting while it's enabled, and has been rolled out to all AT&amp;T customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atandt-rolls-out-wireless-lock-feature-to-block-sim-swap-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 20:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US critical infrastructure exposed as feds worn of possible attacks from Iran</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/feds-warn-of-possible-cyber-attacks-by-iran-on-us-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unitronics, Orpak SiteOmat, Red Lion, Tridium Niagara framework; CVE(s): None; Summary: Devices from these manufacturers ship or previously shipped with default credentials, making it easy for threat actors to access and exploit them. The devices are widely used in the US and can be exposed to internet scans. Proper configuration and strong passwords are recommended to harden control systems against attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/feds-warn-of-possible-cyber-attacks-by-iran-on-us-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 19:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft open-sources VS Code Copilot Chat extension on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-open-sources-vs-code-copilot-chat-extension-on-github/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Microsoft's decision to release the source code for the GitHub Copilot Chat extension for VS Code under the MIT license, providing transparency into the implementation of the chat-based coding assistant and telemetry collection mechanisms. This move is considered a milestone in Microsoft's plan to integrate AI features directly into the popular open-source code editor, with openness seen as superior from a security perspective.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-open-sources-vs-code-copilot-chat-extension-on-github/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 19:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Anthropic's MCP Exposes Developer Machines to Remote Exploits</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Anthropic Model Context Protocol (MCP) Inspector; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49596; Summary: The MCP Inspector contains a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that allows an attacker to gain complete access to the host by chaining a known security flaw affecting modern web browsers, dubbed 0.0.0.0 Day, with a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Inspector. The vulnerability can be exploited by visiting a malicious website, which can execute arbitrary commands on the machine running the tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-vulnerability-in-anthropics.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelly Benefits says 2024 data breach impacts 550,000 customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kelly-benefits-says-2024-data-breach-impacts-550-000-customers/</link>
      <description>The Kelly &amp; Associates Insurance Group (dba Kelly Benefits) has suffered a data breach that compromised the personal information of 553,660 individuals. The breach is believed to have occurred between December 12-17 and may have exposed full names, Social Security numbers, tax ID numbers, dates of birth, medical information, health insurance information, and financial account information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kelly-benefits-says-2024-data-breach-impacts-550-000-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aeza Group sanctioned for hosting ransomware, infostealer servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aeza-group-sanctioned-for-hosting-ransomware-infostealer-servers/</link>
      <description>The US Department of the Treasury has sanctioned Russian hosting company Aeza Group and four operators for allegedly providing services to ransomware gangs, infostealer operations, darknet drug markets, and Russian disinformation campaigns. The sanctions aim to disrupt these cybercriminal activities and prevent further exploitation of US-based assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aeza-group-sanctioned-for-hosting-ransomware-infostealer-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FileFix attack runs JScript while bypassing Windows MoTW alerts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-filefix-attack-runs-jscript-while-bypassing-windows-motw-alerts/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new attack called FileFix allows executing malicious scripts by exploiting how browsers handle saved HTML webpages. The attack tricks users into saving an HTML page as ".HTA" and renaming it to auto-execute embedded JScript via mshta.exe, bypassing the Mark of the Web (MoTW) protection in Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-filefix-attack-runs-jscript-while-bypassing-windows-motw-alerts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TA829 and UNK_GreenSec Share Tactics and Infrastructure in Ongoing Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ta829-and-unkgreensec-share-tactics-and.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the tactical similarities between two threat actor groups, TA829 and UNK_GreenSec, which have been observed delivering different malware strains. The article highlights their use of similar infrastructure, delivery tactics, and email lure themes to deliver malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ta829-and-unkgreensec-share-tactics-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Criminal Court hit by new 'sophisticated' cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/international-criminal-court-hit-by-new-sophisticated-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The International Criminal Court (ICC) is investigating a new "sophisticated" cyberattack that targeted its systems last week. The incident was contained through the ICC's alert and response mechanisms, but further details about the nature of the attack, impact, or any data exfiltration are not yet available. This is the second cyberattack targeting the ICC in recent years, following a breach in September 2023 attributed to cyber espionage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/international-criminal-court-hit-by-new-sophisticated-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Free IoC Search &amp; Enrichment Platforms</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/top-10-free-ioc-search-enrichment-platforms/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of Indicators of Compromise (IoCs) in cybersecurity and provides a list of 10 free platforms for searching and enriching IoCs. The platforms featured include AlienVault OTX, Pulsedive, AbuseIPDB, ThreatMiner, IOC Radar, threatfox, URLhaus, GreyNoise, MISP, VirusTotal, and ThreatBook. These platforms provide various capabilities such as search, enrichment, and integration with other security tools to help analysts detect and respond to threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100046856</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US disrupts North Korean IT worker "laptop farm" scheme in 16 states</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-disrupts-north-korean-it-worker-laptop-farm-scheme-in-16-states/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) took coordinated law enforcement actions against North Korea's fund-raising operations using remote IT workers, compromising the identities of over 80 U.S. citizens and generating more than $5 million in illicit revenue. Sensitive data, including US military tech regulated under ITAR, was accessed and exfiltrated by North Koreans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-disrupts-north-korean-it-worker-laptop-farm-scheme-in-16-states/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 13:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Flaw in IDEs Like Visual Studio Code Lets Malicious Extensions Bypass Verified Status</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-flaw-in-ides-like-visual-studio.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Visual Studio Code; CVE(s): None; Summary: Flawed verification checks in Visual Studio Code allow attackers to add malicious functionality to extensions while maintaining a verified icon, enabling remote code execution and opening up a low-barrier entry point for attackers. The vulnerability can be exploited by creating a malicious extension with the same verifiable values as an already verified extension and bypassing trust checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-flaw-in-ides-like-visual-studio.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Esse Health says recent data breach affects over 263,000 patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/esse-health-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-263-000-patients/</link>
      <description>Esse Health suffered a cyberattack that compromised personal and health information of over 263,000 patients. The attackers stole a wide range of sensitive data, including personal information, health insurance information, medical record numbers, and some health information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/esse-health-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-263-000-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 13:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/01/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage TM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48927, CVE-2025-48928; Summary: Two vulnerabilities in TeleMessage TM SGNL have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. These vulnerabilities pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23583</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voltronic Power and PowerShield UPS Monitoring Software</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Voltronic Power Viewpower, Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro, Powershield NetGuard; CVE(s): CVE-2022-31491, CVE-2021-43110; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an unauthenticated attacker remotely to make configuration changes, including shutting down connected UPS devices or execution of arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23578</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650 and SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650 and SAM600-IO series devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2403; Summary: A denial-of-service vulnerability exists due to improper prioritization of network traffic over protection mechanism, allowing attackers to cause critical functions like LDCM (Line Distance Communication Module) to malfunction. Successful exploitation could disrupt critical functions in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23579</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Seven Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/01/cisa-releases-seven-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple products from various vendors (FESTO, Hitachi Energy, Voltronic); CVE(s): None; Summary: CISA released seven ICS advisories covering vulnerabilities and exploits in industrial control systems products from FESTO, Hitachi Energy, and Voltronic. The advisories provide technical details and mitigation strategies for the identified issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23581</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FESTO Automation Suite, FluidDraw, and Festo Didactic Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: FESTO, FESTO Didactic (various products); CVE(s): CVE-2023-3935; Summary: A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in Wibu CodeMeter Runtime network service allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to achieve RCE and gain full access of the host system. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to gain full control of the host system, including remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23575</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy MSM</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Modular Switchgear Monitoring (MSM); CVE(s): CVE-2020-11022; Summary: The vulnerability is a Cross-site Scripting issue that allows attackers to execute untrusted code, potentially leading to unauthorized actions or system compromise. Successful exploitation could be done remotely with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23580</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FESTO Hardware Controller, Hardware Servo Press Kit</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Festo; CVE(s): CVE-2022-30311, CVE-2022-30310, CVE-2022-30309, CVE-2022-30308; Summary: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities exist in multiple versions of Festo Controller CECC-X-M1 product family. Successful exploitation could allow unauthorized system command execution with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23577</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FESTO Didactic CP, MPS 200, and MPS 400 Firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: FESTO Didactic, Siemens Simatic S7-1500 / ET200SP; CVE(s): CVE-2020-15782; Summary: A memory protection bypass vulnerability in the products allows an attacker to write arbitrary data and code to protected memory areas or read sensitive data to launch further attacks. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to write arbitrary data and code to protected memory areas or read sensitive data to launch further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23574</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FESTO CODESYS</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-182-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Festo, CODESYS Gateway Server V2; CVE(s): CVE-2022-31802, CVE-2022-31803, CVE-2022-31804; Summary: Three vulnerabilities in the CODESYS Gateway Server V2 allow an attacker to block legitimate user connections, crash the application, or authenticate without proper credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23576</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson Controls starts notifying people affected by 2023 breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/johnson-controls-starts-notifying-people-affected-by-2023-breach/</link>
      <description>Johnson Controls suffered a massive ransomware attack in September 2023, resulting in the theft of sensitive documents and disruption to its global operations. The attackers, linked to the Dark Angels ransomware group, demanded $51 million for a decryptor and threatened to publish stolen data online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/johnson-controls-starts-notifying-people-affected-by-2023-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 11:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Are North Korean IT Workers Hacking the Global Remote Job Market?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/north-korean-it-workers-hack-global-remote-job-market/</link>
      <description>North Korean threat actors are using AI tools to create fake digital identities, resumes, and profiles to infiltrate companies and gain access to internal systems. They pose as remote IT workers and use stolen or fake identities to pass background checks. Once hired, they access sensitive information, extract valuable data, and redirect profits to the regime.

FYSA: North Korean threat actors are using AI tools to enhance documents, modify voices, and alter photos to pass identity checks. They blend into freelance platforms and IT roles, creating serious risks for organizations that unknowingly give them access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061564</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 11:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Maturity Model for Browser Security: Closing the Last-Mile Risk</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/a-new-maturity-model-for-browser.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the vulnerability of enterprise browsers, highlighting that 85% of modern work happens within the browser and most security programs struggle to govern this area. It presents a new framework, "Secure Enterprise Browser Maturity Guide", to help CISOs and security teams assess, prioritize, and operationalize browser-layer security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/a-new-maturity-model-for-browser.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google fixes fourth actively exploited Chrome zero-day of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-fourth-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-of-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6554; Summary: A high-severity type confusion weakness in the Chrome V8 JavaScript engine was fixed, marking the fourth actively exploited Google Chrome zero-day patch since the start of the year. The vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on unpatched devices and can lead to browser crashes after successful exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-fourth-actively-exploited-chrome-zero-day-of-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Patches Critical Zero-Day Flaw in Chrome’s V8 Engine After Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-patches-critical-zero-day-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6554; Summary: A type confusing flaw in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine of Google Chrome allows a remote attacker to perform arbitrary read/write via a crafted HTML page, which can lead to unexpected software behavior, execution of arbitrary code, and program crashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-patches-critical-zero-day-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing SOCRadar MCP Server: AI-Powered Cybersecurity Intelligence for Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/socradar-mcp-server-ai-cybersecurity-intelligence/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the launch of SOCRadar's Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server, which integrates artificial intelligence into cybersecurity operations. The MCP Server enables security teams to access over 35 specialized tools across eight security domains, providing real-time threat analysis, report generation, and incident management capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061551</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 08:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Arrests Facilitator in North Korean IT Worker Scheme; Seizes 29 Domains and Raids 21 Laptop Farms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-arrests-key-facilitator-in-north.html</link>
      <description>The US Department of Justice (DoJ) announced a coordinated action targeting the North Korean information technology (IT) worker scheme, resulting in the arrest of one individual and seizure of financial accounts, websites, and computers. The scheme involves North Korean IT workers obtaining employment with US companies using stolen or fictitious identities, stealing sensitive data, and extorting employers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-arrests-key-facilitator-in-north.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Removes Password Management from Authenticator App Starting August 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-removes-password-management.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft is ending support for passwords in its Authenticator app, part of a shift away from traditional password-based logins. The changes aim to streamline autofill and improve security through technologies like passkeys, Windows Hello, and FIDO2-based authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-removes-password-management.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. warns of Iranian cyber threats on critical infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-warns-of-iranian-cyber-threats-on-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The US government issued an urgent warning about potential cyberattacks from Iranian-affiliated hackers targeting U.S. critical infrastructure, citing the current unrest in the Middle East and previous cyber attacks linked to Iran. The advisory warns that Iranian threat actors are known to exploit unpatched vulnerabilities or utilize default passwords to gain access to systems, and urges organizations to adopt best practices to protect against these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-warns-of-iranian-cyber-threats-on-critical-infrastructure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 22:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican drug cartel hacked FBI official’s phone to track informant, report says</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/mexican-drug-cartel-hacked-fbi-officials-phone-to-track-informant-report-says/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the United States Treasury (UST) threat, which involves using credit or debit card transaction reports to identify individuals. It also mentions a data breach at the FBI that aided UTS efforts, but details about the breach are redacted. The report recommends improving training and coordination within the FBI to address the evolving UTS threat. Additionally, it highlights the use of sophisticated technical means by Mexican drug cartels to track law enforcement officials and conceal their own activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/mexican-drug-cartel-hacked-fbi-officials-phone-to-track-informant-report-says/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany asks Google, Apple to remove DeepSeek AI from app stores</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-asks-google-apple-remove-deepseek-ai-from-app-stores/</link>
      <description>The article is not about a vulnerability, but rather concerns GDPR violations by the Chinese AI platform DeepSeek AI. The Berlin Commissioner for Data Protection has requested Google and Apple to remove the app from their stores due to unlawful data collection and transfer from Germany to China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-asks-google-apple-remove-deepseek-ai-from-app-stores/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Chides FBI for Weak Advice on Mobile Security</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/senator-chides-fbi-for-weak-advice-on-mobile-security/</link>
      <description>Sen. Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) is urging the FBI to provide more comprehensive cybersecurity guidance to Senate staffers, including enabling anti-spyware defenses built into mobile devices like Apple's Lockdown Mode and Google's Advanced Protection Mode. The senator argues that the current guidance is insufficient in protecting lawmakers and their staff against sophisticated cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71553</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Agencies Warn of Rising Iranian Cyberattacks on Defense, OT Networks, and Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-agencies-warn-of-rising-iranian.html</link>
      <description>U.S. cybersecurity and intelligence agencies have issued a joint advisory warning of potential cyber-attacks from Iranian state-sponsored or affiliated threat actors, which may target Defense Industrial Base (DIB) companies, especially those with ties to Israeli research and defense firms. The agencies emphasize the need for "increased vigilance" and provide mitigation steps to prevent attacks, including implementing strong passwords, multi-factor authentication, and keeping systems up-to-date with the latest software patches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-agencies-warn-of-rising-iranian.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for Office 365 now blocks email bombing attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-defender-for-office-365-now-blocks-email-bombing-attacks/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing a new detection capability in Defender for Office 365 to automatically detect and block email bombing attacks. This feature aims to protect organizations from malicious threats by flooding mailboxes with high volumes of emails, which can obscure important messages or overwhelm systems. The new "Mail Bombing" feature started rolling out in late June 2025 and will be toggled on by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-defender-for-office-365-now-blocks-email-bombing-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland says government data stolen in ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/switzerland-says-government-data-stolen-in-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Radix; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Radix organization has been targeted by the Sarcoma ransomware group in a phishing attack that resulted in the theft and encryption of sensitive information. The stolen data was later published on the dark web, exposing sensitive information from various federal offices in Switzerland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/switzerland-says-government-data-stolen-in-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Dismantles $540 Million Cryptocurrency Fraud Network, Arrests Five Suspects</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/europol-dismantles-540-million.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cryptocurrency investment fraud ring that laundered €460 million from over 5,000 victims worldwide. The ring used various tactics such as social engineering, fake trading dashboards, and scripted conversations to convince victims to invest in fake crypto platforms. Additionally, the article highlights the increasing use of artificial intelligence (AI) technologies by transnational criminal groups involved in cyber-enabled fraud, which is a complex and alarming trend observed in Southeast Asia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/europol-dismantles-540-million.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hikvision Canada ordered to cease operations over security risks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hikvision-canada-ordered-to-cease-operations-over-security-risks/</link>
      <description>The Canadian government has ordered Hikvision's subsidiary, Hikvision Canada Inc., to cease all operations in Canada due to a national security risk, citing concerns about its ties to the Chinese government and potential for collecting intelligence or espionage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hikvision-canada-ordered-to-cease-operations-over-security-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Attack Surface Threat Assessment (ASTA)?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-is-attack-surface-threat-assessment-asta/</link>
      <description>SOCRadar has launched ASTA (Attack Surface Threat Assessment), a module in their CTEM (Continuous Threat Exposure Management) platform. ASTA provides real-time visibility and control over vulnerabilities across an organization's digital attack surface, helping teams detect issues earlier, respond faster, and build a security posture that adapts to a constantly changing threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061530</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft warns of Windows update delays due to wrong timestamp</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-of-Windows-security-update-delays-due-to-incorrect-metadata-timestamp/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A known issue with incorrect metadata timestamp causes delivery delays for June 2025 Windows security updates on Windows 10 and Windows 11 systems using quality update deferral policies. This delay affects the timing of update availability, but does not impact the quality or applicability of the update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-warns-of-Windows-security-update-delays-due-to-incorrect-metadata-timestamp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Eagle Uses Proton66 Hosting for Phishing, RAT Deployment on Colombian Banks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/blind-eagle-uses-proton66-hosting-for.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on the threat actor Blind Eagle, which uses the Russian bulletproof hosting service Proton66 as an initial attack vector. The group uses Visual Basic Script (VBS) files to install off-the-shelf remote access trojans (RATS) and targets entities in South America, particularly Colombia and Ecuador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/blind-eagle-uses-proton66-hosting-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol helps disrupt $540 million crypto investment fraud ring</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-helps-disrupt-540-million-crypto-investment-fraud-ring/</link>
      <description>Spanish authorities have arrested five individuals suspected of laundering $540 million from illegal cryptocurrency investment schemes and defrauding over 5,000 victims. The investigation involved multiple countries, including Estonia, France, the U.S., and Europol. The operation also highlighted the growing use of artificial intelligence (AI) in scams, with Europol warning that online fraud is expected to surpass all other types of organized fraud in the coming years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-helps-disrupt-540-million-crypto-investment-fraud-ring/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Cybercriminals steal health data posing as fraud investigators</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-cybercriminals-steal-health-data-posing-as-fraud-investigators/</link>
      <description>The FBI warns Americans of cybercriminals impersonating health fraud investigators to steal sensitive information. Scammers are emailing or messaging victims, disguising themselves as legitimate health insurers and investigative team members, to pressure them into providing personal or health data for fraudulent purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-warns-cybercriminals-steal-health-data-posing-as-fraud-investigators/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/30/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6543; Summary: A buffer overflow vulnerability in Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway allows for active exploitation, posing significant risks to the federal enterprise. This vulnerability has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog, requiring Federal Civilian Executive Branch agencies to remediate by a specified due date.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23571</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and Partners Urge Critical Infrastructure to Stay Vigilant in the Current Geopolitical Environment</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/30/cisa-and-partners-urge-critical-infrastructure-stay-vigilant-current-geopolitical-environment</link>
      <description>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), in collaboration with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Department of Defense Cyber Crime Center (DC3), and the National Security Agency (NSA), released a Fact Sheet warning organizations to be vigilant against potential targeted cyber operations by Iranian state-sponsored or affiliated threat actors. The advisory recommends mitigations such as disconnecting operational technology devices from the public internet, using strong passwords, applying software patches, and implementing phishing-resistant multifactor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23558</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,200 Citrix servers unpatched against critical auth bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-200-citrix-servers-unpatched-against-critical-auth-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: Over 1,200 unpatched Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway appliances are vulnerable to a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) allowing threat actors to bypass authentication by hijacking user sessions. This out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability enables unauthenticated attackers to access restricted memory regions, potentially stealing session tokens, credentials, and other sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-200-citrix-servers-unpatched-against-critical-auth-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Posts Advertise Access to British Firms &amp; Data from Brazil, France, and CETDIGIT</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/access-british-firms-data-from-brazil-france-cetdigit/</link>
      <description>Multiple threats have been discovered on the dark web, including unauthorized access sales targeting British firms, leaked insurance data from Brazil, stolen French credit card records, and a large-scale database breach allegedly involving U.S.-based CRM provider CETDIGIT. The threats offer various types of compromised data, including remote command execution, file management, screen sharing, and personal metadata.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061436</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Credentials As Unique Identifiers: A Pragmatic Approach To NHI Inventories</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/leveraging-credentials-as-unique.html</link>
      <description>Non-human identities (NHIs) are becoming increasingly common in modern enterprises, outnumbering human identities by at least 50 to one. NHIs require unique identifiers, which are often their access keys. The article highlights the importance of securing machine identities and treating secrets as a mechanism to uniquely identify and govern non-human actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/leveraging-credentials-as-unique.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Airline Hacks, Citrix 0-Day, Outlook Malware, Banking Trojans and more</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-airline-hacks-citrix-0-day.html</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be a cybersecurity news roundup featuring various security-related topics, including vulnerabilities, attacks, and best practices. There are no specific software, hardware, or firmware products being discussed that I could identify as vulnerable.

However, some of the topics mentioned in the article do warrant attention from a cybersecurity perspective. For instance, the discussion on memory-safe languages (MSLs) such as Rust highlights the importance of language-level protections to mitigate memory-related vulnerabilities. Additionally, the mention of ultrasonic covert communication attacks and the use of smartwatches as receivers for these types of attacks serves as a reminder of the need for robust security measures in air-gapped environments.

In general, it is essential to stay informed about emerging cybersecurity threats and best practices to ensure the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-airline-hacks-citrix-0-day.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google rolls out Veo 3 video generator, try it for free using credits</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-veo-3-video-generator-try-it-for-free-using-credits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: This article contains no cybersecurity-relevant content. It appears to be a collection of news and updates from Google regarding various products and services, including Veo 3, Vertex AI, Tines, and others. There are no discussions of vulnerabilities, threats, or best practices for cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-veo-3-video-generator-try-it-for-free-using-credits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth flaws could let hackers spy through your microphone</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-flaws-could-let-hackers-spy-through-your-microphone/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Airoha systems on a chip (SoCs); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20700, CVE-2025-20701, CVE-2025-20702; Summary: Three vulnerabilities in the Airoha SoCs, affecting more than two dozen audio devices from ten vendors, can be exploited for eavesdropping or stealing sensitive information. The issues allow an attacker to take over a vulnerable product and extract call history and contacts on some phones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-flaws-could-let-hackers-spy-through-your-microphone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 16:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare open-sources Orange Meets with End-to-End encryption</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-open-sources-orange-meets-with-end-to-end-encryption/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article discusses Cloudflare's Orange Meets video calling app, which has implemented end-to-end encryption (E2EE) using Messaging Layer Security (MLS). The implementation enables continuous group key agreement, supporting secure group key exchange, forward secrecy, post-compromise security, and scalability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-open-sources-orange-meets-with-end-to-end-encryption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Transform GIFTEDCROOK Stealer into an Intelligence-Gathering Tool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-transform-giftedcrook-stealer/</link>
      <description>GIFTEDCROOK infostealer, wielded by UAC-0226 threat group, has undergone rapid evolution from a rudimentary browser data stealer to a sophisticated intelligence-gathering tool. The malware's capabilities include exfiltrating proprietary documents and browser secrets, with the goal of supporting covert intelligence objectives during periods of diplomatic and military significance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144594</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Encrypt ends certificate expiry emails to cut costs, boost privacy</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lets-encrypt-ends-certificate-expiry-emails-to-cut-costs-boost-privacy/</link>
      <description>Let's Encrypt has announced it will no longer send email notifications about certificate expirations due to high costs, privacy concerns, and unnecessary complexities. This decision is a result of the increasing adoption of automated renewal solutions and standards changes reducing certificate lifespans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lets-encrypt-ends-certificate-expiry-emails-to-cut-costs-boost-privacy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESET Warns Cybercriminals Are Targeting NFC Data for Contactless Payments</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eset-warns-cybercriminals-are-targeting-nfc-data/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated attack vector exploiting Near Field Communication (NFC) data, initially targeting Czech banking customers but now spreading worldwide. Cybercriminals are using a tool called NFCGate to capture card data when victims place their cards near their smartphones, enabling attackers to emulate the card on their devices for unauthorized transactions or cash withdrawals. The attacks rely on social engineering and phishing attempts, and users can mitigate risks by setting low limits on contactless payment transactions, using RFID blockers, and deploying robust cybersecurity solutions like ESET HOME Security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144587</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Windows and Linux Server Vulnerabilities to Deploy Web Shells</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-windows-and-linux-server-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting file upload vulnerabilities to deploy web shells and advanced malware on Windows and Linux systems. The attack chain involves using tools like MeshAgent, SuperShell, and WogRAT to gain initial access, persistence, and lateral movement, ultimately allowing for command execution, reconnaissance, and potential data exfiltration or ransomware deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144576</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-448: (0Day) Mescius ActiveReports.NET ReadValue Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-448/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mescius ActiveReports.NET; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6810; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Mescius ActiveReports.NET through deserialization of untrusted data in the ReadValue method. The vulnerability can be exploited by interacting with the library, and attack vectors may vary depending on the implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25246</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-449: (0Day) Mescius ActiveReports.NET TypeResolutionService Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-449/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mescius ActiveReports.NET; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6811; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Mescius ActiveReports.NET by deserializing untrusted data. The issue exists within the TypeResolutionService class due to a lack of proper validation, which can be exploited to run code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25397</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-450: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole QLogicDownloadImpl Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion and Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-450/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6793; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files and disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the QLogicDownloadImpl class due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24912</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-451: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getAppFileBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-451/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6796; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage this to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24916</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-452: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole compressDriverFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-452/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6803; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited by an attacker to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24923</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-453: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole compressFirmwareDumpFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-453/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6804; Summary: The Marvell QConvergeConsole has an information disclosure vulnerability due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability without authentication, disclosing sensitive information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24924</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-454: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole saveAsText Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-454/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6794; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the saveAsText method, resulting from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24913</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-455: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadSize Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-455/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6795; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The issue arises from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24914</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-456: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-456/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6797; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the getFileUploadBytes method, which fails to properly validate user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24917</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-457: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole deleteAppFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-457/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6798; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, which can be exploited to delete files in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24918</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-458: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-458/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6799; Summary: The Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileUploadBytes method contains a directory traversal information disclosure vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to disclose sensitive information without authentication. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24919</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-459: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole restoreESwitchConfig Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-459/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6800; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24920</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-460: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole saveNICParamsToFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-460/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6801; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication, by exploiting the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24921</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-461: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole deleteEventLogFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-461/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6805; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24925</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-462: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole decryptFile Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-462/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6806; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations, affecting the decryptFile method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24979</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-463: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getDriverTmpPath Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-463/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6807; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It exists in the implementation of the getDriverTmpPath method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to using them in file operations, allowing an attacker to disclose SYSTEM-level information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24980</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-464: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole getFileFromURL Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-464/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6802; Summary: The getFileFromURL method in the Marvell QConvergeConsole has an unrestricted file upload vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24922</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-465: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole readObjectFromConfigFile Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-465/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell, QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6808; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. It occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the readObjectFromConfigFile method, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25217</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-466: (0Day) Marvell QConvergeConsole readNICParametersFromFile Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-466/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Marvell QConvergeConsole; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6809; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole without authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25218</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Trending TikTok Videos Promoting Pirated Apps That Deliver Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-trending-tiktok-videos-promoting-pirated-apps/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated social engineering campaign has surfaced on TikTok, leveraging AI-generated videos to distribute information-stealing malware Vidar and StealC. The campaign uses instructional videos to socially engineer victims into executing malicious PowerShell commands under the guise of activating pirated software, making it harder for traditional security tools to detect and block the threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144539</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Warns of Scattered Spider's Expanding Attacks on Airlines Using Social Engineering</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fbi-warns-of-scattered-spiders.html</link>
      <description>The FBI has revealed that the cybercrime group Scattered Spider is targeting the airline sector, using social engineering techniques to gain access and steal data. The group also targets third-party IT providers, putting trusted vendors at risk of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fbi-warns-of-scattered-spiders.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized DeepSeek Installers Deploy Sainbox RAT and Hidden Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-deepseek-installers/</link>
      <description>Fake software installers mimicking popular tools like DeepSeek, Sogou, and WPS Office are exploited to deliver malware payloads such as the Sainbox RAT (Gh0stRAT variant) and Hidden rootkit. The attack begins with phishing websites designed to mirror legitimate software portals, tricking users into downloading malicious installers that sideload a malware payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144557</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Exploit CapCut Popularity to Steal Apple ID Credentials and Credit Card Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-exploit-capcut-popularity/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have launched a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting CapCut users by impersonating legitimate invoices to extract Apple ID credentials and credit card information. The attack involves multiple stages, including a fake login page, credit card data request, and authentication code prompt, all designed to maximize the extraction of sensitive data while delaying suspicion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144525</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFTEDCROOK Malware Evolves: From Browser Stealer to Intelligence-Gathering Tool</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/giftedcrook-malware-evolves-from.html</link>
      <description>The GIFTEDCROOK malware has been updated to a potent intelligence-gathering tool, capable of exfiltrating sensitive documents from targeted devices, including proprietary files and browser secrets. The malware is used by the threat actor UAC-0226 to target Ukrainian governmental and military entities through phishing emails containing macro-laced Microsoft Excel documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/giftedcrook-malware-evolves-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook’s New AI Tool Asks to Upload Your Photos for Story Ideas, Sparking Privacy Concerns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/facebooks-new-ai-tool-requests-photo.html</link>
      <description>Meta's new AI feature on Facebook allows users to upload photos from their phones to suggest collages, recaps, and other ideas using artificial intelligence. The feature is opt-in and can be disabled at any time, but experts have concerns about user privacy, as the processing happens in the cloud and there are risks with facial recognition and hidden details such as time or location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/facebooks-new-ai-tool-requests-photo.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Passlib Python Package Triggers Windows Shutdowns with Invalid Inputs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-passlib-python-package-triggers-windows-shutdowns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: umaraq psslib; CVE(s): None; Summary: The psslib package is a malicious Python library that poses as a legitimate password security solution. It can cause an immediate system shutdown on Windows environments when users input incorrect passwords, exploiting developer trust in security tools. The package remains active on the PyPI registry, highlighting the persistent danger of supply chain attacks in open-source ecosystems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144517</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Clickfix Tactics to Deploy Malicious AppleScripts for Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-clickfix-tactics-to-deploy-malicious-applescripts/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign called Odyssey Stealer has been discovered, targeting macOS users through a deceptive method known as Clickfix tactics. The malware harvests sensitive data, including browser cookies, saved passwords, cryptocurrency wallet information, and browser extensions, posing a severe threat to individuals engaged in financial and crypto activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144605</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Use Clickfix Tactics to Deploy Malicious AppleScripts for Stealing Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-use-clickfix-tactics/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign called Odyssey Stealer has been discovered targeting macOS users through a deceptive method known as Clickfix tactics. The campaign leverages typosquatted domains to trick users into executing harmful AppleScripts, which harvest sensitive data such as browser cookies, saved passwords, and cryptocurrency wallet information. The operation is linked to a command-and-control panel primarily hosted in Russia and prioritizes Western users, particularly those engaged in financial and crypto activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144605</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage Windows Task Scheduler to Embed Malware and Maintain Persistence</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-windows-task-scheduler/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a protracted cyberattack that targeted critical national infrastructure (CNI) in the Middle East. Threat actors exploited Windows Task Scheduler to embed malicious software and ensure persistence on compromised systems, using a variant of the Havoc framework to infiltrate and manipulate Windows environments with precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144509</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploitation of Microsoft 365 Direct Send to Deliver Phishing Emails as Internal Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploitation-of-microsoft-365-direct-send-to-deliver-phishing-emails/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a phishing campaign that exploits the Direct Send feature of Microsoft 365 to send spoofed internal emails without authentication. Attackers use publicly available information to craft emails that appear to originate from within the organization, bypassing traditional email security controls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144615</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 19:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider hackers shift focus to aviation, transportation firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scattered-spider-hackers-shift-focus-to-aviation-transportation-firms/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a group of threat actors, has expanded its targeting to the aviation and transportation industries, following previous attacks on insurance and retail sectors. They use social engineering tactics, MFA bombing, SIM swapping, and other methods to gain initial network access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scattered-spider-hackers-shift-focus-to-aviation-transportation-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft is trying to get antivirus software away from the Windows kernel</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/microsoft-is-trying-to-get-antivirus-software-away-from-the-windows-kernel/</link>
      <description>This article discusses upcoming changes in Windows 11, including a new feature called "quick machine recovery" (QMR) that enables targeted remediations on affected devices via Windows RE, and a simplified unexpected restart screen with improved readability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/microsoft-is-trying-to-get-antivirus-software-away-from-the-windows-kernel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 SOHO Devices Hacked in China-linked LapDogs Cyber Espionage Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-1000-soho-devices-hacked-in-china.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2015-1548, CVE-2017-17663; Summary: The article describes a network of compromised small office and home office (SOHO) devices used by China-nexus hacking groups for cyber espionage. The Operational Relay Box (ORB) network, codenamed LapDogs, has been found to have over 1,000 infected devices across the US, Southeast Asia, Japan, South Korea, Hong Kong, and Taiwan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/over-1000-soho-devices-hacked-in-china.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s throttling of Cloudflare makes sites inaccessible</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/russias-throttling-of-cloudflare-makes-sites-inaccessible/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare's infrastructure has been throttled by Russian ISPs, making websites and services inaccessible from Russia. The throttling affects all connection methods and protocols, including HTTP/1.1 to HTTP/3 on QUIC, and is outside of Cloudflare's control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/russias-throttling-of-cloudflare-makes-sites-inaccessible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM: A Strategic Guide to Continuous Threat Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/ctem-to-continuous-threat-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM), a proactive approach to cybersecurity that involves continuous monitoring and threat-informed actions. It highlights the benefits of CTEM, including reduced time to detect and remediate exposures, fewer exploitable assets over time, and successful red team or breach simulation outcomes. The article also touches on the challenges of implementing CTEM, such as limited skilled workforce, integration complexity with existing tools, budget constraints, and lack of stakeholder awareness or buy-in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061358</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 flaw now believed to be exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-now-believed-to-be-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The "Citrix Bleed 2" vulnerability, an out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777), allows unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive data from public-facing gateways and virtual servers, enabling session hijacking and bypassing multi-factor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-now-believed-to-be-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Peep #19: IntelBroker Indicted, and Ransomware Goes Corporate</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-peep-19-intelbroker-ransomware-corporate/</link>
      <description>This article does not describe a vulnerability. Instead, it discusses various cybersecurity-related topics, including threat actors, ransomware groups, data breaches, and insider leaks. The article provides insights into the activities of these threat actors and their tactics, as well as the consequences of their actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061341</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLOAD and Pubshell Malware Used in Mustang Panda's Tibet-Specific Attack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pubload-and-pubshell-malware-used-in.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cyber espionage campaign attributed to Mustang Panda, a China-linked threat actor, targeting the Tibetan community. The campaign uses spear-phishing attacks with Tibet-themed lures to distribute malware, including PUBLOAD and Pubshell, which are used to create reverse shells and execute commands on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pubload-and-pubshell-malware-used-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams to Auto-Detect Work Location Using Company Wi-Fi</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-to-auto-detect-work-location/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft Teams' new feature that automatically detects users' work locations when they connect to their organization's Wi-Fi network. The feature aims to streamline the hybrid workplace experience by eliminating manual updates and improving collaboration, resource management, and employee privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144558</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leeds United And Reflectiz Partner To Share Insights On Proactive Web Security After Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/leeds-united-and-reflectiz-partner-to-share-insights-on-proactive-web-security-after-cyber-attack/</link>
      <description>The article announces an upcoming webinar between Leeds United FC and Reflectiz, discussing proactive web security measures after a Magecart attack on Leeds United's online shop. The webinar will feature Graham Peck, Head of IT and Security at Leeds United, and Isaac Moddel, VP Sales at Reflectiz, sharing insights and best practices to safeguard digital assets and customer data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144547</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 12:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Encrypt Launches 6-Day Certificates for IP-Based SSL Encryption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lets-encrypt-launches-6-day-certificates/</link>
      <description>Let's Encrypt is preparing to issue SSL/TLS certificates that include IP addresses in their Subject Alternative Name (SAN) fields, enabling secure communication for a wider range of internet-connected devices and services. The new certificates will have a short-lived validity period of six days to minimize the risk window in case of a key compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144545</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian Airlines Targeted in Cyberattack, Systems Compromised</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hawaiian-airlines-targeted-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Hawaiian Airlines has experienced a significant cybersecurity incident that has disrupted parts of its IT infrastructure, with no group claiming responsibility or confirming whether ransomware was involved. Despite the disruption, flights are operating safely and as scheduled, with the airline engaging federal authorities and external cybersecurity experts to assist in investigating the breach and restoring affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144540</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt Electronic DVR Vulnerability Leaves Admin Credentials Unprotected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hunt-electronic-dvr-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hunt Electronics Hybrid DVRs; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6561; Summary: The hybrid DVRs from Hunt Electronics, specifically models HBF-09KD and HBF-16NK running firmware version V3.1.67_1786 BB11115 or earlier, contain a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-6561) that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to retrieve the system's configuration file, which contains administrator credentials in plaintext, granting full administrative access to the compromised DVR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144534</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Case for Agentic AI SOC Analysts</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/business-case-for-agentic-ai-soc.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges faced by Security Operations Centers (SOCs) in today's cybersecurity landscape, including an increase in complex threats, false positives, and staffing shortages. It highlights the benefits of using agentic AI-powered SOCs to automate routine tasks, filter out noise, and surface high-priority alerts for human analysts to focus on. The article also emphasizes the importance of maximizing the impact of existing skilled staff, reducing burnout, and improving operational efficiency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/business-case-for-agentic-ai-soc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Group Silver Fox Uses Fake Websites to Deliver Sainbox RAT and Hidden Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/chinese-group-silver-fox-uses-fake.html</link>
      <description>A Chinese-speaking threat actor, attributed with medium confidence to Silver Fox (aka Void Arachne), has been observed delivering Sainbox RAT and the open-source Hidden rootkit through phishing websites. The campaign leverages fake software installers, similar to previous attacks that targeted Chinese-speaking users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/chinese-group-silver-fox-uses-fake.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFix Attacks Soar by 500%: Hackers Intensify Use of This Manipulative Technique to Deceive Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-intensify-use-of-this-manipulative-technique-to-deceive-users/</link>
      <description>ClickFix is a novel social engineering technique that has surged in prevalence by 517% between 2024 and 2025, exploiting user trust in online verification processes. It tricks users into copying malicious scripts under the guise of resolving fake errors or completing verification checks, ultimately leading to severe system compromises. The threat operates by presenting users with counterfeit prompts mimicking legitimate services, and has been adopted by nation-state-aligned groups for initial access across Windows, macOS, and Linux platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144475</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT-C-36 Hackers Launching Cyberattacks on Government Entities, Financial Sectors, and Critical Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-c-36-hackers-launching-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): CVE-2024-43451; Summary: The article discusses the threat group APT-C-36 (Blind Eagle) that exploits vulnerabilities with social engineering. They use phishing emails as an initial attack vector, deploying RATs and leveraging WebDAV requests to deliver malware. Although a related vulnerability was patched, Blind Eagle adapted and continued attacks.

FYSA: The article highlights Blind Eagle's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including the use of phishing emails, Remote Access Trojans (RATs), and WebDAV requests to deliver malware. It also emphasizes the importance of advanced security solutions capable of detecting and containing evolving threats in real-time to ensure robust defense against sophisticated actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144461</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 09:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
