<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-287: JetBrains TeamCity Diagnostics Data Directory Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-287/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: JetBrains TeamCity; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46618; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary script on affected installations of JetBrains TeamCity. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists in the handling of filenames in the diagnostics functionality due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25977</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio denies breach following leak of alleged Steam 2FA codes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/twilio-denies-breach-following-leak-of-alleged-steam-2fa-codes/</link>
      <description>A threat actor claims to have accessed over 89 million Steam user records with one-time access codes, allegedly obtained from Twilio's SMS system. The authenticity of the data and the source of the breach are unclear, but experts suggest a possible supply-chain compromise involving Twilio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/twilio-denies-breach-following-leak-of-alleged-steam-2fa-codes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-285: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer SLDPRT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-285/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1884; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer by parsing SLDPRT files. User interaction is required, and the attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26029</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-286: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer OBJ File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-286/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1883; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of OBJ files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26017</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday May 2025 Released With the Fixes for 72 Flaws With 5 Actively Exploited 0-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709; Summary: Microsoft has released May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates addressing 72 security vulnerabilities, including 5 zero-day vulnerabilities actively exploited in the wild. The flaws include Remote Code Execution, Elevation of Privilege, Information Disclosure, Denial of Service, and Security Feature Bypass, with Windows components being heavily targeted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135368</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti fixes EPMM zero-days chained in code execution attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-fixes-epmm-zero-days-chained-in-code-execution-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Ivanti EPMM has two security vulnerabilities chained together to gain remote code execution. The first is an authentication bypass in the API component, allowing attackers to access protected resources on vulnerable devices. The second is a remote code execution vulnerability that allows threat actors to execute arbitrary code on targeted systems via maliciously crafted API requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-fixes-epmm-zero-days-chained-in-code-execution-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft May 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes 5 exploited zero-days, 72 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-5-exploited-zero-days-72-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709, CVE-2025-30397; Summary: Microsoft fixed five actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities and 67 other flaws in its May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates. The vulnerable products include Windows DWM Core Library, Windows Common Log File System Driver, Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock, and Microsoft Scripting Engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-5-exploited-zero-days-72-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Released Security Updates to Fix for the Mutiple RCE Vulnerabilities – Patch Now</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-released-security-updates-for-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428, CVE-2025-22462, CVE-2025-22460 (None); Summary: Ivanti released critical security updates to address vulnerabilities in Endpoint Manager Mobile, Neurons for ITSM, Cloud Services Application, and Neurons for MDM. The vulnerabilities could allow attackers to execute remote code, gain administrative access, escalate privileges, or edit unauthorized resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135337</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5058411 and KB5058405 cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058411-and-kb5058405-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various updates and features in Windows 11, including improved search functionality, new widgets on Lock experience, and pivot-based curated views on File Explorer Home. It also mentions the availability of Windows 11 24H2 for everyone and resolves issues with Roblox on ARM PCs, but does not discuss any specific vulnerabilities or cybersecurity threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058411-and-kb5058405-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 16 expands 'Advanced Protection' with device-level security</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-16-expands-advanced-protection-with-device-level-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the improvements to the Advanced Protection feature in Android 16, which strengthens defenses against sophisticated spyware attacks. This includes device-level security hardening, verified boot and runtime integrity checks, strong sandboxing, USB port lockdown, app isolation, and other features that prevent disabling or weakening of individual security settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-16-expands-advanced-protection-with-device-level-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058379 update fixes SgrmBroker errors in Event Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-fixes-sgrmbroker-errors-in-event-viewer/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5058379 cumulative update includes four changes and fixes, including one for an SGRMBroker bug, seven zero-day vulnerabilities, and updates to the Windows Kernel Vulnerable Driver Blocklist. One known issue is fixed, which may cause Windows updates to fail if Citrix Session Recording Agent (SRA) version 2411 is installed on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-fixes-sgrmbroker-errors-in-event-viewer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet FortiVoice Zero-day Vulnerability Actively Exploited in The Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortinet-fortivoice-o-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CWE-121; Summary: A critical stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability (CWE-121) was discovered in multiple Fortinet products, including FortiVoice, FortiMail, FortiNDR, FortiRecorder, and FortiCamera. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands remotely through specially crafted HTTP requests, posing a significant threat to affected organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135352</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet fixes critical zero-day exploited in FortiVoice attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fortinet-fixes-critical-zero-day-exploited-in-fortivoice-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-32756) was exploited as a zero-day in attacks targeting FortiVoice enterprise phone systems, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands via maliciously crafted HTTP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fortinet-fixes-critical-zero-day-exploited-in-fortivoice-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks Surge by 123% Amid Evolving Tactics and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-attacks-surge-by-123-amid/</link>
      <description>The article reports a surge in ransomware attacks through third-party vendor ecosystems, driven by exploitation of weak links in vendor networks. The report highlights the importance of robust third-party risk management (TPRM) practices to mitigate risks and provide actionable strategies for organizations to fortify their defenses against these advanced persistent threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135327</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Introduce Mythic Framework Agent to Enhance Pentesting Tool Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-introduce-mythic-framework-agent/</link>
      <description>The article discusses advancements in penetration testing tools with the introduction of a new agent for the Mythic framework. The agent enhances detection evasion and operational efficiency by integrating sophisticated evasion techniques and modularity. It allows security experts to conduct operations with reduced risk of detection, making it a valuable tool for ethical hackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135308</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swan Vector APT Targets Organizations with Malicious LNK and DLL Implants</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/swan-vector-apt-targets-organizations/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a newly identified advanced persistent threat (APT) campaign called "Swan Vector" that targets educational institutions and mechanical engineering industries in East Asia. The campaign uses social engineering tactics, spearphishing attachments, and a multi-stage infection chain to evade detection and establish persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135275</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Weaponize KeePass Password Manager to Spread Malware and Steal Passwords</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-weaponize-keepass-password-manager-to-spread-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: KeePass; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors successfully exploited KeePass to spread malware and facilitate large-scale password theft by modifying and re-signing installers with trusted certificates. The attack involved a custom malware loader dubbed KeeLoader, which modified executable files to incorporate malicious functionality, exfiltrate user credentials, and set up an autorun registry key for persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135295</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti warns of critical Neurons for ITSM auth bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Neurons for ITSM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22462, CVE-2025-22460; Summary: The vulnerability (CVE-2025-22462) is a critical authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to gain administrative access to unpatched systems in low-complexity attacks. Ivanti also patched a default credentials security flaw (CVE-2025-22460) in its Cloud Services Appliance (CSA) that can let local authenticated attackers escalate privileges on vulnerable systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked APTs Exploit SAP CVE-2025-31324 to Breach 581 Critical Systems Worldwide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A critical security flaw in SAP NetWeaver is being exploited by multiple China-nexus nation-state actors to target critical infrastructure networks. The vulnerability allows for remote code execution and has been used to deploy web shells, reverse shells, and backdoors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Intel CPU flaws leak sensitive data from privileged memory</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intel CPUs; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45332; Summary: A "Branch Privilege Injection" flaw in modern Intel CPUs allows attackers to leak sensitive data from memory regions allocated to privileged software. The vulnerability, tracked under CVE-2024-45332, is a race condition on the branch predictor subsystem and affects all Intel CPUs from the 9th generation onward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI Package Posing as Solana Tool Stole Source Code in 761 Downloads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Python Package Index (PyPI) repository had a malicious package named solana-token that was designed to steal source code and developer secrets. When installed, it attempts to exfiltrate data from the developer's machine to a hard-coded IP address, suggesting a target on developers creating their own blockchains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft will update Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has extended its support for Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028, allowing users to continue receiving security updates and using the applications without having to upgrade to Windows 11 immediately. The decision comes as many users are reluctant to switch due to requirements such as TPM 2.0 support. The company will also provide updates beyond October 2025 for Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) and Long-Term Servicing Branch (LTSB) releases, catering to specialized devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increase Red Team Operations 10X with Adversarial Exposure Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of traditional red team engagements in identifying critical security gaps and proposes an alternative approach called Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV). AEV combines Breach and Attack Simulation (BAS) and Automated Penetration Testing to provide continuous, scalable, and automated offensive testing. This approach allows for repeatable and on-demand testing, enabling faster remediation, continuous benchmarking, and the agility to respond to new threats without waiting for the next audit or assessment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks &amp; Spencer Confirms Customer Data Breach in Recent Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/marks-spencer-confirms-customer-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A cyber attack against Marks &amp; Spencer (M&amp;S) has compromised customer personal data, including names, dates of birth, telephone numbers, home addresses, and online order histories. The attackers used a "double extortion" method, exfiltrating sensitive data and encrypting company systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135277</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;S says customer data stolen in cyberattack, forces password resets</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</link>
      <description>Marks and Spencer (M&amp;S) confirmed a cyberattack occurred on April 22, 2025, involving DragonForce ransomware affiliates using the Scattered Spider social engineering tactic. The attackers stole sensitive customer information, including full names, email addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, dates of birth, online order history, household information, and "masked" payment card details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Workplace Apps Flaws Allow Hackers to Gain Elevated Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zoom-workplace-apps-flaws-allow-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zoom Workplace Apps; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30663, CVE-2025-30664, CVE-2025-30665, CVE-2025-30666, CVE-2025-46785; Summary: The Zoom Workplace Apps contain seven newly discovered vulnerabilities, including a high-severity Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability that could lead to privilege escalation when exploited successfully. The vulnerabilities include improper neutralization of special elements, NULL pointer dereference, and buffer over-read flaws, which could potentially allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, elevate privileges, or cause denial of service conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135248</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Published for macOS Sandbox Escape Vulnerability (CVE-2025-31258)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/macos-sandbox-escape-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31258; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-31258, is a sandbox escape flaw that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code outside application sandbox constraints. It affects macOS Ventura 13.4 through Sonoma 14.2 and can be exploited by launching a malicious app, which could grant read/write access to protected directories like ~/Library and limited command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135083</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Hackers Caught Exploiting Old Routers as Proxy Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/four-hackers-caught-exploiting-old-routers/</link>
      <description>The article reports a global cybercrime scheme that hijacked outdated wireless routers to create malicious proxy networks, generating over $46 million by selling access to infected devices. The scheme exploited security vulnerabilities in older-model routers and allowed the hackers to covertly reconfigure them and resell access through subscription-based platforms.

FYSA: Threat actors targeted residential and business routers, including devices in Oklahoma, by exploiting security vulnerabilities to install malicious firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135172</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents that autonomously trade cryptocurrency aren’t ready for prime time</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/ai-agents-that-autonomously-trade-cryptocurrency-arent-ready-for-prime-time/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ChatGPT, Gemini; CVE(s): None; Summary: An untrusted user can plant false memories in the long-term conversation memory of ChatGPT or similar LLM-based agents, causing the chatbot to send all user input to an attacker-controlled channel. This vulnerability was demonstrated through a proof-of-concept attack that abused the built-in conversation memory feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/ai-agents-that-autonomously-trade-cryptocurrency-arent-ready-for-prime-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F5 BIG-IP Vulnerability Allows Remote Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/f5-big-ip-vulnerability-allows-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: F5; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31644; Summary: The vulnerability allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary system commands, bypassing security boundaries, by exploiting an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint and BIG-IP TMOS Shell command. This can enable attackers to create or delete files, execute system commands, and create a significant security bypass mechanism with a CVSS v3.1 score of 8.7 and a CVSS v4.0 score.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135092</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Launches Supply Chain Attacks on UK Retail Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scattered-spider-launches-supply-chain-attacks/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider is a financially motivated threat actor targeting UK retail organizations with sophisticated social engineering and technical exploitation tactics. They leverage third-party vendor dependencies, seasonal vulnerabilities, and advanced techniques like cloud exploitation and endpoint detection evasion to gain initial access and persist within networks. Their attacks often involve ransomware deployment, victim communication pressure, and data exfiltration tools, posing a significant risk to high-impact targets during critical sales periods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135217</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Service Suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache HTTP Server, Hitachi Energy Service Suite; CVEs: CVE-2022-26377, CVE-2023-31122, and others (see below); CVSS scores: 5.3-8.7.

A comprehensive list of vulnerabilities affecting the Apache HTTP Server and Hitachi Energy Service Suite has been published. The affected products are versions prior to 2.4.55. The listed CVEs include:

* CVE-2022-26377: An inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP request smuggling') vulnerability in mod_proxy_ajp that allows an attacker to smuggle requests to the AJP server it forwards requests to.
* CVE-2023-31122: Another inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP request smuggling') vulnerability in mod_proxy_ajp that also allows an attacker to smuggle requests to the AJP server it forwards requests to.

The other CVEs listed include:

* CVE-2022-37436
* CVE-2023-43622
* CVE-2022-28614
* CVE-2022-28330

These vulnerabilities have been assigned CVSS scores ranging from 5.3 to 8.7, indicating varying levels of severity.

Recommendations:

1. Update to version 9.8.1.4 or later.
2. Implement security practices and firewall configurations to help protect process control networks from external attacks.
3. Ensure that process control systems are physically protected from unauthorized personnel, have no direct connections to the Internet, and are separated from other networks by a firewall system with a minimal number of exposed ports.

No known public exploitation specifically targeting these vulnerabilities has been reported to CISA at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23352</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy MACH GWS Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy MACH GWS products; CVE(s): CVE-2024-4872, CVE-2024-3980, CVE-2024-3982, CVE-2024-7940; Summary: The MACH GWS product contains multiple vulnerabilities that allow an attacker to inject code, read or modify files, hijack user sessions, or access exposed ports without authentication. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could result in a range of impacts, including the ability to access or modify system files or other critical files, hijack user sessions, or inject code towards persistent data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23354</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650/SAM600-IO Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Relion 670/650/SAM600-IO Series; CVE(s): CVE-2023-4518; Summary: A buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability exists in the input validation of GOOSE messages, allowing an attacker to reboot the device and cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23353</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABB Automation Builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-133-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ABB Automation Builder; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3394, CVE-2025-3395; Summary: Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource vulnerabilities in Automation Builder allow an attacker to overrule user management. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized access and changes to automation projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23355</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Abuse PyInstaller to Deploy Stealthy macOS Infostealer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-abuse-pyinstaller-to-deploy-stealthy/</link>
      <description>A novel macOS infostealer that exploits PyInstaller has been identified. The malware uses strings like ‘_MEIPASS’ to indicate embedded archives extracted at runtime and orchestrates malicious logic through PyInstaller's bootloader. It exhibits nefarious behaviors including AppleScript dialogs coercing user passwords, system volume mutting, and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135204</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake Defense in the Age of AI</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deepfake-defense-in-age-of-ai.html</link>
      <description>AI-generated social engineering attacks are increasingly sophisticated and prevalent, utilizing large language models (LLMs) to impersonate trusted individuals. Attackers use voice phishing (vishing) tactics to automate social engineering at scale, posing a significant threat to trust in virtual collaboration platforms.

FYSA: Threat actors are leveraging generative AI to impersonate trusted individuals, automating social engineering tactics and driving a surge in voice phishing attacks. This trend is fueled by the convergence of AI-driven deception, virtual collaboration tools that assume trust, and defenses that rely on probability rather than proof.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/deepfake-defense-in-age-of-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Konni APT Targets Ukraine with Malware to track Russian Invasion Progress</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/north-korean-konni-apt-targets-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>The North Korea-linked threat actor, Konni APT, has been attributed to a phishing campaign targeting government entities in Ukraine. The goal of the campaign is to collect intelligence on the "trajectory of the Russian invasion." The threat group, also known as Opal Sleet, Osmium, TA406, and Vedalia, has a history of targeting entities in South Korea, the United States, and Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/north-korean-konni-apt-targets-ukraine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PupkinStealer Targets Windows Users to Steal Browser Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pupkinstealer-targets-windows-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PupkinStealer; CVE(s): None; Summary: A newly identified information-stealing malware, PupkinStealer, targets Windows users by stealing sensitive data including browser credentials, desktop documents, and full-screen screenshots. It uses Telegram's Bot API for data exfiltration and relies on social engineering tactics to trick victims into executing the malicious file. The malware can pilfer login credentials from Chromium-based browsers, hijack Telegram sessions, extract authentication tokens from Discord clients, and capture desktop screenshots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135176</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeated Firmware Key-Management Failures Undermine Intel Boot Guard and UEFI Secure Boot</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/repeated-firmware-key-management-failures/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: UEFI firmware ecosystem; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3052, None; Summary: The security of the UEFI firmware ecosystem has been questioned due to persistent cryptographic key management issues. Private keys have been exposed and unpatched vulnerabilities affecting millions of devices across vendors like Lenovo, MSI, Gigabyte, and Supermicro have been found. These issues leave systems open to pre-OS malware and bootkit attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135145</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INE Security Alert: Top 5 Takeaways from RSAC 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ine-security-alert-top-5-takeaways-from-rsac-2025/</link>
      <description>INE Security provides comprehensive training and certification programs to address top cybersecurity priorities, including AI security, multi-cloud vulnerabilities, zero-trust architecture, crisis response, and continuous skill development. The company's platform offers hands-on labs, cutting-edge technology, and world-class instructors to help teams develop the expertise needed to address modern cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135179</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Flags Hidden Functionality Flaw in TeleMessage TM SGNL on KEV List</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-flags-hidden-functionality-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage TM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47729; Summary: A critical hidden functionality vulnerability in TeleMessage's archiving backend exposes cleartext copies of user messages, enabling unauthorized access to sensitive communications. The flaw persists even if end-to-end encryption is implemented at the application layer, violating zero-trust principles. Organizations have until June 2, 2025, to apply vendor-provided mitigations or discontinue TM SGNL usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135166</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Flags Hidden Functionality Flaw in TeleMessage TM SGNL on KEV List</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-flags-hidden-functionality-flaw-in-telemessage/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage TM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47729; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthorized access to sensitive communications by retaining unencrypted message copies within the archiving infrastructure. This flaw enables exploitation of zero-trust principles, and CISA has given organizations until June 2, 2025, to apply vendor-provided mitigations or discontinue usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135166</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus One-Click Flaw Exposes Users to Remote Code Execution Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-one-click-flaw-exposes-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462 (8.4), CVE-2025-3463 (9.4); Summary: A critical vulnerability in ASUS DriverHub allowed attackers to execute arbitrary code with administrator privileges by visiting a specially crafted website, bypassing origin checking mechanisms. The vulnerability originated from an inadequate domain validation mechanism, allowing any website with a matching subdomain pattern to download and execute malicious files without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135127</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus One-Click Flaw Exposes Users to Remote Code Execution Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-one-click-flaw-exposes-users-to-remote-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS DriverHub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3462 (8.4), CVE-2025-3463 (9.4); Summary: A critical security vulnerability in ASUS DriverHub software allowed attackers to execute arbitrary code with administrator privileges through a simple web visit, bypassing origin checking mechanisms. The exploit chain permitted attackers to compromise systems running the ASUS driver management utility by visiting a specially crafted domain, and was patched within 10 days of being reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135127</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining a new methodology for modeling and tracking compartmentalized threats</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/compartmentalized-threat-modeling/</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be an analysis of a cyberattack campaign that involved multiple attackers and various tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The authors utilize the extended Diamond Model to clarify the distinct activities and roles of these attackers across different stages of the attack kill chain.

The article discusses a campaign dubbed "ToyMaker" that spanned six days, during which an initial access group compromised a server, exfiltrated credentials, and deployed a proprietary backdoor. Subsequently, a second wave of attacks began three weeks later, attributed to Cactus ransomware. The authors present several hypotheses regarding the relationship between the two waves of activity, ultimately concluding that the initial access group (ToyMaker) provided initial access for the Cactus group.

The article highlights various TTPs and indicators of compromise (IOCs) observed during the investigation, including differences in tools and infrastructure used by the two attacker groups. The authors' analysis suggests that there was a handoff of access between the initial access group and the ransomware actor, with shared stolen credentials facilitating the transition.

In summary, this article presents an in-depth analysis of a complex cyberattack campaign involving multiple attackers and TTPs, highlighting the importance of understanding the relationships between different attack groups and their TTPs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68093d6e0264c50001a1da04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining IABs: Impacts of compartmentalization on threat tracking and modeling</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/redefining-initial-access-brokers/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a threat analysis and modeling piece focused on initial access brokers (IABs) and their categories: financially motivated IABs (FIA), state-sponsored IABs (SIA), and opportunistic IABs (OIA). The authors provide an in-depth examination of the characteristics, tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), as well as the interactions between these different types of IAGs. The article aims to provide a clearer understanding of how IAGs operate within the broader threat landscape and how this information can be used for improved intrusion analysis and attribution.

The main focus of the article is on the differences between FIA, SIA, and OIA groups, highlighting their motivations, target selection, toolsets, and collaboration levels. The authors also provide real-world examples to illustrate these concepts and demonstrate how understanding these categories can aid in threat modeling and analysis.

In summary, this article does not discuss a vulnerability but rather delves into the realm of threat analysis and modeling, providing valuable insights into the world of initial access brokers and their various forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68093e340264c50001a1da12</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Remote IT Job Fraud Scheme Involving North Korean Nationals</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-uncover-remote-it-job-fraud-scheme/</link>
      <description>North Korean nationals have been indicted for orchestrating a scheme to secure remote IT jobs at American companies and nonprofits using stolen identities, funneling at least $88 million USD to the North Korean government over six years. The operation employed tactics such as fake companies, malware infections, and remote access software, with signs of coordination and tradecraft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135109</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Leverage Unpatched Output Messenger 0‑Day to Deliver Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-leverage-unpatched-output/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Srimax Output Messenger; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27920, CVE-2025-27921; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in the Output Messenger Server Manager allows authenticated attackers to upload malicious files directly into the server's startup directory. The vulnerability can be exploited to deliver malicious payloads, collect sensitive user data, and exfiltrate information from compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135093</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobalt Strike 4.11.1 Released With SSL Checkbox Fix</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cobalt-strike-4-11-1-released-with-ssl-checkbox-fix/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cobalt Strike; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cobalt Strike 4.11.1 addresses several critical issues, including a module stomping issue that caused system crashes, resolves problems with the "Enable SSL" checkbox functionality, and adds clearer deprecation warnings for stomp reflective loaders. The update also ensures more stable operation during penetration testing activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135073</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
