<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft investigates OneDrive bug that breaks file search</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft OneDrive; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some OneDrive users are experiencing blank search results or no results at all, even when searching for files they know exist. The issue affects a subset of users across most OneDrive platforms and there is currently no known workaround or estimated timeline for a fix.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare blocks record 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack against hosting provider</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare mitigated a record-breaking distributed denial of service (DDoS) attack in May 2025 that peaked at 7.3 Tbps, targeting a hosting provider. The attack used multiple vectors, including UDP floods, QOTD reflection, Echo reflection, NTP amplification, Mirai botnet UDP flood, Portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification, each exploiting legacy or poorly configured services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac discloses breach amidst Scattered Spider insurance attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aflac; CVE(s): None; Summary: The systems of American insurance giant Aflac were breached by a sophisticated cybercrime group, potentially stealing personal and health information. The attack shows signs of being carried out by Scattered Spider, a group known for their social engineering attacks against high-profile organizations worldwide.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, so no CVEs are listed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can users reset their own passwords without sacrificing security?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the benefits of self-service password reset (SSPR) solutions in reducing helpdesk load, costs, and improving productivity. It highlights the importance of proper security considerations when implementing an SSPR solution, including strong identity verification measures and multi-factor authentication (MFA). The article also emphasizes the need for a user-friendly experience to promote adoption and minimize abandonment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive DDoS Attack Hits 7.3 Tbps Delivering 37.4 Terabytes in 45 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-ddos-attack-hits-7-3-tbps/</link>
      <description>A massive distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack peaked at 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps), overwhelming its target with 37.4 terabytes of data in just 45 seconds, targeting an unnamed hosting provider that relied on Cloudflare's Magic Transit service for network defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143273</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft to remove legacy drivers from Windows Update for security boost</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a specific vulnerability, but rather discusses Microsoft's plan to periodically remove legacy drivers from the Windows Update catalog to mitigate security and compatibility risks. The company aims to ensure the optimal set of drivers on Windows Update while maintaining its security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Misconfiguration Lets Attackers Take Over Cloud Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/azure-misconfiguration-take-over-cloud-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): None; Summary: A chain of misconfigurations in Microsoft Azure allows attackers to gain complete control over an organization's cloud infrastructure, from initial access to full tenant takeover. The attack path involves unauthenticated reconnaissance, exploiting public storage accounts, and leveraging dynamic group membership rules to achieve privilege escalation and lateral movement, ultimately leading to total ownership of the Azure environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143248</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's State TV Hijacked Mid-Broadcast Amid Geopolitical Tensions; $90M Stolen in Crypto Heist</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</link>
      <description>Iran's state-owned TV broadcaster was hacked to air videos calling for street protests against the Iranian government, while Israel accused Iran of launching cyber attacks. The incident is part of a larger cyber war between Israel and Iran that has been ongoing for over a decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AntiDot 3-in-1 Android Botnet Malware Grants Attackers Full Control Over Victim Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/antidot-3-in-1-android-botnet-malware-grants-attackers/</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a new Android botnet malware that grants cybercriminals control over infected devices. It has advanced capabilities such as screen recording, SMS interception, and credential theft through overlay attacks. The malware operates through at least 11 active command-and-control (C2) servers, managing over 3,775 infected devices across 273 distinct campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143233</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford City Council Hit by Cyberattack Exposing Employee Personal Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oxford-city-council-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Oxford City Council's network was targeted by a sophisticated cyberattack that exposed personal data of employees involved in council-administered elections over the past two decades. The attack allowed attackers to access historic data stored on legacy systems, affecting current and former council officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143245</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versa Director Flaws Let Attackers Execute Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/versa-director-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Networks' SD-WAN orchestration platform, Versa Director; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23171, CVE-2025-23172; Summary: Authenticated attackers can upload malicious files and execute arbitrary commands on affected systems due to insecure file upload and webhook functionalities. The first flaw allows remote code execution (RCE) if a webshell is uploaded and accessed, while the second vulnerability enables authenticated users to execute commands as the "versa" user with sudo privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143238</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GodFather Android Malware Uses On-Device Virtualization to Hijack Legitimate Banking Apps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/godfather-android-malware-uses-on-device-virtualization/</link>
      <description>The GodFather Android banking malware creates a fully isolated virtual environment on the victim's device, enabling attackers to monitor and manipulate user interactions in real-time. It employs a malicious "host" application that downloads and runs a copy of the targeted app within a controlled sandbox, capturing credentials and sensitive information with precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143210</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-411: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 DPAX File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-411/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47728; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPAX files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26167</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-412: Fuji Electric Smart Editor  X1 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-412/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41413; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor by writing past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26031</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-413: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-413/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 file parsing stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the processing of TL5 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26018</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgence of the Prometei Botnet</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/prometei-botnet-2025-activity/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Prometei Linux Botnet; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Prometei malware family, which includes both Linux and Windows variants, allows attackers to remotely control compromised systems for cryptocurrency mining (particularly Monero) and credential theft. The latest versions feature a backdoor that enables a variety of malicious activities, including brute-forcing administrator credentials, exploiting vulnerabilities, and self-updating features for stealth and evasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143713</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps to 24/7 In-House SOC Success</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors often target businesses during off-hours when security personnel are fewer or not present. A 24/7 Security Operations Center (SOC) can provide real-time threat detection and resolution, but requires a perfect balance of proven processes, advanced tools, and skilled professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 7.3 Tbps DDoS Attack Delivers 37.4 TB in 45 Seconds, Targeting Hosting Provider</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</link>
      <description>Cloudflare reported blocking a 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack, targeting an unnamed hosting provider, which used a combination of UDP flood, QOTD reflection attack, echo reflection attack, NTP reflection attack, Mirai UDP flood attack, portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification attack. The attack originated from over 122,145 source IP addresses across 161 countries, with the largest portions coming from Brazil, Vietnam, Taiwan, China, Indonesia, Ukraine, Ecuador, Thailand, the United States, and Saudi Arabia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Introduces Enhanced Security Defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-introduces-enhanced-security-defaults-for-windows-365/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing new secure-by-default capabilities for Windows 365 Cloud PCs to fortify virtual desktop environments against modern cyber threats. The update includes default disabling of device redirections (clipboard, drive, USB, and printer) and enabling advanced security controls such as virtualization-based security, Credential Guard, and hypervisor-protected code integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143202</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dover Fueling Solutions Flaw Lets Attackers Control Fueling Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dover-fueling-solutions-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dover Fueling Solutions' ProGauge MagLink LX consoles; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5310; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-5310, allows remote attackers to seize control of fueling operations, manipulate tank monitoring, and deploy malware, posing a severe risk to transportation systems worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143199</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Billion Passwords Stolen From 320 Million+ Computers Leaked Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/16-billion-passwords-stolen-from-320-million-computers-leaked-online/</link>
      <description>A massive data breach has exposed approximately 16 billion login credentials, usernames, and passwords across various platforms, including Apple, Facebook, Google, Instagram, Telegram, GitHub, and government services. The compromised data can be used for account takeover, identity theft, targeted phishing attacks, and ransomware attacks.

FYSA: Cybercriminals have gained access to a massive dataset of login records, which can be exploited for account takeovers, identity theft, and targeted phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143181</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM QRadar SIEM Bug Lets Attackers Run Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-qradar-siem-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM Security QRadar SIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33117, None (other CVEs mentioned are not explicitly linked to the vulnerability); Summary: A critical flaw in IBM's QRadar SIEM platform allows privileged users to execute arbitrary commands on affected systems, enabling attackers to compromise sensitive data or gain unauthorized access. The vulnerability has been addressed in the latest interim fix (UP12 IF02), and customers are urged to update their installations to protect against potential exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143190</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ Trojanized GitHub Repositories Found in Campaign Targeting Gamers and Developers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new campaign of 67 GitHub repositories claiming to offer Python-based hacking tools, but delivering trojanized payloads instead. The repositories were taken down by GitHub, and the campaign is believed to target users searching for software such as account cleaning tools and game cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache SeaTunnel Flaw Lets Unauthorized Users Launch Deserialization Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-seatunnel-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache SeaTunnel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32896; Summary: The Apache SeaTunnel vulnerability (CVE-2025-32896) allows unauthorized users to exploit insecure REST API endpoints, enabling arbitrary file read and potentially remote code execution through deserialization attacks. This affects versions 2.3.1-2.3.10 and has been classified as moderate to critical in severity, depending on deployment context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143186</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Wall Connector Hacked Through Charging Port in Just 18 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tesla-wall-connector-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tesla Wall Connector; CVE(s): None; Summary: Security researchers from Synacktiv successfully hacked the Tesla Wall Connector through its charging port in just 18 minutes, exposing critical vulnerabilities in the device's firmware and communication protocols. The attack involved downgrading the Wall Connector's firmware to an older version with exposed debug features, including a TCP debug shell accessible over Wi-Fi, and exploiting a global buffer overflow in the shell's command parsing logic for code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143172</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Support Tickets Let Hackers Exploit Atlassian’s Model Context Protocol</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-support-tickets-let-hackers-exploit-atlassians-model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian Jira Service Management (JSM); CVE(s): None; Summary: A new class of cyberattack targets organizations using Atlassian's Model Context Protocol (MCP), exploiting AI-powered workflows in JSM. Malicious support tickets can be used to gain privileged access and exfiltrate sensitive data without breaching internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143168</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, the 16 billion credentials leak is not a new data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a massive compilation of previously stolen credentials, allegedly obtained through infostealers, data breaches, and credential-stuffing attacks. The compilation was briefly exposed online, containing over 64,000 credential pairs. The article warns users to adopt good cybersecurity habits, use unique and strong passwords, enable two-factor authentication (2FA), and monitor for known breaches using services like Have I Been Pwned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godfather Android malware now uses virtualization to hijack banking apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Godfather Android Malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Godfather Android malware creates isolated virtual environments on mobile devices to steal account data and transactions from legitimate banking apps, using tactics such as intent spoofing, StubActivity, and API hooking. The malware displays a fake lock screen overlay to trick users into entering their PIN/passwords and can record account credentials, passwords, PINs, touch events, and capture responses from the banking backend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100,000 WordPress Sites Exposed to Privilege Escalation via MCP AI Engine</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-100000-wordpress-sites-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jordy Meow AI Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5071; Summary: The AI Engine plugin has a severe vulnerability allowing authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access or higher to gain full control over the Model Context Protocol (MCP) module, enabling privilege escalation and potentially complete site compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143132</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Deploy Malware Using Weaponized Calendly and Google Meet Links</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-deploy-malware-using-weaponized-calendly/</link>
      <description>TA444, a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor group, has launched a sophisticated malware campaign targeting cryptocurrency foundations. The attack leverages weaponized Calendly links, deceptive Google Meet invitations, and deepfakes to deliver malicious payloads designed for macOS systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143141</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Fox APT Uses Weaponized Medical Software to Deploy Remote Access Tools and Disable AV</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silver-fox-apt-uses-weaponized-medical-software/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the China-based advanced persistent threat (APT) group Silver Fox's multi-stage campaign targeting healthcare delivery organizations (HDOs) and public sector entities. The campaign uses trojanized medical software, cloud infrastructure, and a custom remote access trojan (RAT) to deploy cyber espionage and data theft operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143124</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers Targeted! Fake Minecraft Mods Enable Attackers to Take Control of Your System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-minecraft-mods-enable-attackers-to-take-control/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Minecraft; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious campaign targeting Minecraft users has been discovered, using a Distribution as a Service (DaaS) platform to distribute malware disguised as legitimate mods. The malware initiates a multi-stage attack chain designed to steal sensitive data and compromise systems, exploiting the trust of gamers seeking to enhance their gaming experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143113</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android Malware Surge Hits Devices via Overlays, Virtualization Fraud and NFC Theft</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a financially motivated Android malware sold as a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) on underground forums, compromising over 3,775 devices across 273 unique campaigns. It features capabilities to record device screens, intercept SMS messages, extract sensitive data, conduct overlay attacks, and remotely control infected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Stolen credentials are the new front door to your network</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</link>
      <description>Credential-based attacks are becoming increasingly common, with threat actors using stolen credentials to breach networks. Infostealer malware campaigns have exploded in recent years, stealing billions of credentials and feeding a booming cybercrime marketplace. The webinar will explore how attackers are shifting from exploiting vulnerabilities to simply logging in using large-scale credential abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-409: RARLAB WinRAR Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-409/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RARLAB WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6218; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of RARLAB WinRAR, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists in the handling of file paths within archive files, allowing an attacker to traverse to unintended directories and execute code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27198</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-410: Allegra calculateTokenExpDate Password Recovery Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-410/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Allegra; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6216; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Allegra, with no required user interaction. The issue stems from a predictable value used in generating a password reset token within the application's password recovery mechanism, allowing attackers to exploit it and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27104</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Sam Altman discusses GPT-5 release date</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be an update about OpenAI's next big upgrade to ChatGPT, including the potential release of GPT-5 and improvements to the Operator Agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-tied Predatory Sparrow hackers are waging cyberwar on Iran’s financial system</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: Predatory Sparrow, a group believed to be linked to Israel's military or intelligence agencies, has been carrying out cyberattacks against Iran's critical infrastructure, including railways and gas stations. The group's recent attack on the Khouzestan steel mill caused significant physical damage. It is unclear why they have turned their attention to Iran's financial sector, but experts warn that this development may lead to more serious consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US recovers $225 million of crypto stolen in investment scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice has seized over $225 million in cryptocurrency linked to investment fraud and money laundering operations, the largest crypto seizure in the history of the U.S. Secret Service. The funds were traced using blockchain analysis and were laundered through a complex network of cryptocurrency addresses to obscure their origin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Webinar: Key Insights from Verizon’s 2025 DBIR</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report (DBIR) 2025, which highlights critical trends in cybersecurity, including rising GenAI-related risks, credential theft, and vulnerabilities from third-party partners. It also emphasizes the need for enterprises to adopt an updated, integrated approach to cybersecurity and provides insights on how to strengthen security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft unveils new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs, including disabling clipboard, drive, USB, and printer redirections by default to reduce risks of data theft and block malware attacks. Additionally, the company will start blocking access to SharePoint, OneDrive, and Office files via legacy authentication protocols in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jQuery Migrate Library Compromised to Steal Logins via Parrot Traffic Direction System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jquery-migrate-library-compromised-to-steal-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: jQuery Migrate; CVE(s): None; Summary: A weaponized version of the jQuery Migrate library was used in a sophisticated malware campaign that exploited the trust in the library. The attack delivered a malicious script through a compromised Middle Eastern business website, which stole sensitive data, logged keystrokes, and deployed additional threats such as cryptocurrency miners or click-fraud scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143096</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT will analyze Gmail emails, manage schedule on Google Calendar</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability, but rather mentions the testing of integration features between ChatGPT and Gmail/Google Calendar. The feature will allow users to summarize emails and create events, and may be tied to the ChatGPT Search feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Amatera Stealer Using Advanced Web Injection and Anti-Analysis Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-amatera-stealer-using-advanced-web-injection/</link>
      <description>Amatera Stealer is a rebranded information stealer malware that exhibits advanced features and stealth mechanisms. It is distributed through web injection campaigns, software cracks, and fake downloads, and can steal sensitive data from browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, email clients, and messaging apps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143084</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krispy Kreme Data Breach Exposes Customer Personal Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/krispy-kreme-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A ransomware attack on Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corporation's information technology systems exposed the personal information of over 160,000 individuals. The attackers claimed to have stolen 184 GB of sensitive data, including personal and financial information, client documents, payroll, and accounting records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143073</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Spyware SpyNote Masquerading as Google Translate Found in Open Directories</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/android-spyware-spynote-masquerading-as-google-translate/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the discovery of multiple SpyNote spyware samples in open directories across the internet, which can be disguised as legitimate Android applications. These malware files harvest sensitive data from unsuspecting users by exploiting accessibility services and device administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143069</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use VBScript Files to Deploy Masslogger Credential Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-vbscript-files-to-deploy-masslogger/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated variant of the Masslogger credential stealer malware that spreads through VBScript Encoded (.VBE) files. It uses evasive techniques such as fileless malware, heavy registry exploitation, and multi-stage execution to evade detection by traditional antivirus and signature-based methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143042</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo beefs up scam defense to block fake stores, crypto sites</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-beefs-up-scam-defense-to-block-fake-stores-crypto-sites/</link>
      <description>DuckDuckGo's Scam Blocker tool has been updated to protect against a broader range of online scams, including fake e-commerce, cryptocurrency exchanges, and "scareware" sites. The tool blocks known malware distribution and phishing URLs by default, and users can opt-in for additional protection across other internet apps when using the DuckDuckGo VPN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/duckduckgo-beefs-up-scam-defense-to-block-fake-stores-crypto-sites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telecom giant Viasat breached by China's Salt Typhoon hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telecom-giant-viasat-breached-by-chinas-salt-typhoon-hackers/</link>
      <description>The article reports that satellite communications company Viasat has been breached by China's Salt Typhoon state hackers. The breach occurred earlier this year and was discovered when a compromised device was found to have unauthorized access. Viasat claims the incident has been remediated and no customer impact was detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/telecom-giant-viasat-breached-by-chinas-salt-typhoon-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viasat Targeted in Cyberattack by Salt Typhoon APT Group</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/viasat-targeted-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>A Chinese state-sponsored group known as Salt Typhoon has been linked to a sweeping cyberespionage campaign that compromised major telecommunications firms, including Viasat Inc., Verizon, AT&amp;T, and Lumen Technologies. The campaign targeted phone records, including those of then-presidential candidate Donald Trump and members of both major campaigns, and highlights the growing threat posed by advanced persistent threat (APT) actors targeting critical American infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143058</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueNoroff Deepfake Zoom Scam Hits Crypto Employee with MacOS Backdoor Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bluenoroff-deepfake-zoom-scam-hits.html</link>
      <description>BlueNoroff threat actor targets employee with deepfaked company executives in deceptive Zoom calls to trick them into installing malware on their Apple macOS devices. The attack involves the use of Calendly link, fake Zoom domain, and AppleScript that downloads next-stage payload and executes shell script, ultimately leading to the installation of eight distinct malicious binaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/bluenoroff-deepfake-zoom-scam-hits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden SAML Attack: How Attackers Gain Control of Federation Server’s Private Key</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-attackers-gain-control-of-federation-servers-private-key/</link>
      <description>The Golden SAML attack is a sophisticated threat that exploits the trust mechanisms of Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication to compromise every account within an organization by forging authentic-looking tokens. This attack targets the private key of federation servers, allowing attackers to impersonate any user and bypass security controls with stealth and precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Rises as Major Threat, Demanding $50M in Ransom</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-ransomware-rises-as-major-threat/</link>
      <description>The Qilin ransomware group has surged to the forefront of digital extortion, demanding ransoms as high as $50 million and disrupting critical services worldwide. With a robust Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) platform, recruiting affiliates through Russian-language forums, and offering lucrative revenue shares, Qilin has amassed over $50 million in ransom payments in 2024 alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143050</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Vibe Coding: The Complete New Guide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/secure-vibe-coding-complete-new-guide.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vibe Coding; CVE(s): None; Summary: Vibe coding, the use of natural language to generate software with AI, introduces "silent killer" vulnerabilities that evade traditional security tools. These exploitable flaws are created when AI generates code without explicit prompting for security features, leading to insecure patterns and functions that can be exploited in production environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/secure-vibe-coding-complete-new-guide.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actor Exploit GitHub and Hosted 60 GitHub Repositories with 100s of Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actor-exploit-github-and-hosted-60-github-repositories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub; CVE(s): None; Summary: Banana Squad exploited GitHub by hosting over 60 malicious repositories containing hundreds of trojanized Python files. The repositories used advanced evasion techniques to hide harmful content, making it nearly undetectable to casual inspection. All 67 repositories have been removed by GitHub, but the potential impact remains unclear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143003</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated Phishing Attack Uses ASP Pages to Target Prominent Russia Critics – Google</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophisticated-phishing-attack-uses-asp-pages/</link>
      <description>A Russia state-sponsored cyber threat actor, tracked as UNC6293, has been identified by Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) in a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting academics and critics of Russia. The campaign used advanced social engineering tactics to trick victims into creating and sharing Application Specific Passwords (ASPs), which granted persistent access to Gmail accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142986</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClamAV 1.4.3 and 1.0.9 Released with Fixes for Critical Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clamav-1-4-3-and-1-0-9-released-with-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ClamAV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20260, CVE-2025-20234; Summary: The ClamAV development team has released two security patch releases, versions 1.4.3 and 1.0.9, to address significant vulnerabilities in the PDF file parser and UDF file parser. The flaws, identified as CVE-2025-20260 and CVE-2025-20234, have the potential to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or enable remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142951</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Cloudflare Tunnels to Infect Windows Systems With Python Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-cloudflare-tunnels-to-infect-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated malware campaign dubbed SERPENTINE#CLOUD has emerged, using Cloudflare Tunnel infrastructure to deliver Python-based malware to Windows systems across Western nations. The campaign exploits trusted cloud services to bypass network defenses and maintain anonymity, featuring a complex, multi-stage infection chain designed for stealth and persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142938</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncover LOTS Attacks Hiding in Trusted Tools — Learn How in This Free Expert Session</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/uncover-lots-attacks-hiding-in-trusted.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a tactic called "Living Off Trusted Sites" (LOTS), where attackers blend in with legitimate traffic by hiding malicious code inside routine traffic on well-known platforms like Google, Microsoft, Dropbox, and Slack. LOTS tactics exploit common business tools, shortened URLs, and trusted cloud services to host malicious payloads, making it difficult for traditional defenses to detect them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/uncover-lots-attacks-hiding-in-trusted.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krispy Kreme says November data breach impacts over 160,000 people</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/krispy-kreme-says-november-data-breach-impacts-over-160-000-people/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses a cyberattack on Krispy Kreme that resulted in the theft of personal information of over 160,000 individuals. The attackers, identified as the Play ransomware gang, claimed to have stolen sensitive data from the company's network and threatened to leak it online unless a ransom was paid. The breach was detected by Krispy Kreme on November 29 and notified affected individuals in May 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/krispy-kreme-says-november-data-breach-impacts-over-160-000-people/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Entra ID Adds Passkey (FIDO2) Support in Public Preview</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-entra-id-adds-passkey-fido2-support/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced an update to its identity platform, Microsoft Entra ID, which introduces expanded passkey (FIDO2) support. This update allows IT administrators to configure passkey authentication policies at a granular level, enabling organizations to tailor authentication methods for different user groups. The rollout is set to occur globally from mid-October to mid-November 2025 and will simplify the authentication process by unifying credentials from hardware keys, computers, and mobile devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142998</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CVE-2025-6018 and CVE-2025-6019 Enable Full Root Access on Linux</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-6018-and-cve-2025-6019-root-access-on-linux/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: openSUSE Leap 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise 15; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two newly discovered Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities in Linux distributions allow attackers to chain low-level access into full root control. The first vulnerability manipulates environment variables during login, allowing remote attackers to impersonate local users and gain permission to perform actions reserved for physical users. The second vulnerability abuses XFS file system resizing to gain root access using the udisk daemon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061109</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogMeIn Remote Access Abused in Targeted System Compromise</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/logmein-remote-access-abused/</link>
      <description>This article describes a sophisticated cyberattack campaign that leverages LogMeIn Resolve remote access software to gain unauthorized control over user systems. The attack begins with a convincingly crafted invoice-themed spam email, designed to trick recipients into opening a malicious PDF attachment, which installs the remote access tool and grants attackers full remote access to the compromised system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142983</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jitter-Trap: New Method Uncovers Stealthy Beacon Communications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jitter-trap-stealthy-beacon-communications/</link>
      <description>The article introduces Jitter-Trap, a detection technique that uses behavioral and network analysis to identify post-exploitation and command-and-control (C2) communication in cyberattacks. It leverages the randomness used by attackers to evade detection, turning it into a powerful detection tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142975</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian APT29 Exploits Gmail App Passwords to Bypass 2FA in Targeted Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/russian-apt29-exploits-gmail-app.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google account feature - Application Specific Passwords (ASPs); CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors with suspected ties to Russia are using a novel social engineering tactic that takes advantage of Google's application specific passwords (ASPs) to gain access to victims' email accounts. The tactic involves building rapport with targets, sending benign phishing emails disguised as meeting invitations, and tricking them into sharing the ASP passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/russian-apt29-exploits-gmail-app.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-3248 in Langflow Exploited to Deploy Flodrix Botnet</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-3248-in-langflow-deploy-flodrix-botnet/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Langflow's /api/v1/validate/code endpoint allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code directly on the server, granting remote control over the host. The vulnerability impacts Langflow versions prior to 1.3.0 and is particularly dangerous due to Langflow's popularity in cloud-hosted AI deployments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061100</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco AnyConnect VPN Flaw Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-anyconnect-vpn-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Meraki; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20271; Summary: The vulnerability stems from a variable initialization error that occurs when establishing SSL VPN sessions using client certificate authentication. Attackers can exploit this flaw by sending specially crafted HTTPS requests to affected devices, causing the Cisco AnyConnect VPN service to crash and restart, immediately disconnecting all active VPN users and forcing them to re-authenticate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142952</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 07:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Gang Busted by Authorities; Devices and Evidence Seized</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-gang-busted-by-authorities/</link>
      <description>Thai authorities dismantled a sophisticated criminal enterprise operating from the Antai Holiday Hotel in Pattaya, discovering a high-stakes gambling den and a ransomware cybercrime ring. The operation highlights the growing trend of cybercrime being intertwined with traditional organized crime, including gambling, money laundering, and identity theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142933</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Traffic Server Vulnerability Allows DoS Attacks Through Memory Exhaustion</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-traffic-server-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Software Foundation Apache Traffic Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49763; Summary: Attackers can exploit a flaw in the Edge Side Includes (ESI) plugin to trigger denial-of-service (DoS) attacks by exhausting server memory, affecting multiple versions of ATS 9.0.0 to 9.2.101 and 10.0.0 to 10.0.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142927</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryuk ransomware’s initial access expert extradited to the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ryuk-ransomwares-initial-access-expert-extradited-to-the-us/</link>
      <description>A member of the Ryuk ransomware operation, who specialized in gaining initial access to corporate networks, has been extradited to the United States. The individual was arrested in April 2025 and is suspected of earning $150 million while active between 2018 and 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ryuk-ransomwares-initial-access-expert-extradited-to-the-us/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Adds Passkey Login Support to Facebook for Android and iOS Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-adds-passkey-login-support-to.html</link>
      <description>Meta Platforms is adding support for passkeys on Facebook, allowing users to securely sign in with biometrics or device lock PIN code. This passwordless authentication solution is resistant to guessing or theft by malicious websites and effective against phishing and password spraying attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/meta-adds-passkey-login-support-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 06:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Next SSRF Flaw in Cloudflare Lets Hackers Fetch Data from Any Host</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/open-next-ssrf-flaw-in-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: @opennextjs/cloudflare; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6087; Summary: The @opennextjs/cloudflare package contains a critical Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to proxy arbitrary remote content through the vulnerable site's domain, posing risks of phishing, data exposure, and domain abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142923</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 05:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Reset Link Poisoning Leads to Full Account Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/password-reset-link-poisoning/</link>
      <description>A critical vulnerability known as Password Reset Link Poisoning enables attackers to manipulate the domain in password reset links, redirecting users to malicious sites and capturing sensitive reset tokens. This allows for full account takeover, exposing web users and organizations to serious risks such as account takeover, phishing, and reputational damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142918</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 05:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Linux Flaws Enable Full Root Access via PAM and Udisks Across Major Distributions</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-linux-flaws-enable-full-root-access.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Qualys PAM and libblockdev; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two local privilege escalation (LPE) flaws were discovered by Qualys that can be exploited to gain root privileges on machines running major Linux distributions. CVE-2025-6018 allows an unprivileged user to elevate to the "allow_active" user and call Polkit actions, while CVE-2025-6019 enables an "allow_active" user to gain full root privileges by chaining it with CVE-2025-6018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-linux-flaws-enable-full-root-access.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Israel hackers hit Iran's Nobitex exchange, burn $90M in crypto</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-israel-hackers-hit-irans-nobitex-exchange-burn-90m-in-crypto/</link>
      <description>The "Predatory Sparrow" hacking group claims to have stolen over $90 million in cryptocurrency from Nobitex, Iran's largest crypto exchange, and intentionally burnt the funds by sending them to vanity addresses. The attack is believed to be politically motivated, with ties to the IRGC and Iranian leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/pro-israel-hackers-hit-irans-nobitex-exchange-burn-90m-in-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Address bar shows hp.com. Browser displays scammers’ malicious text anyway.</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/tech-support-scammers-inject-malicious-phone-numbers-into-big-name-websites/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a scam that injects fake phone numbers into official websites through Google ads. Scammers buy ads with appended parameters that are not displayed in the ad itself, making it difficult for users to suspect anything is amiss. The injected phone number appears legitimate and can trick users into revealing personal or financial information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/tech-support-scammers-inject-malicious-phone-numbers-into-big-name-websites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean hackers deepfake execs in Zoom call to spread Mac malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-deepfake-execs-in-zoom-call-to-spread-mac-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BlueNoroff; CVE(s): None; Summary: The North Korean BlueNoroff hacking group is using deepfakes to trick employees into installing custom malware on their macOS devices. The attack involves a fake Zoom meeting and the installation of an AppleScript file that downloads a secondary payload, which includes malicious binaries such as Telegram 2, Root Troy V4, a (InjectWithDyld), XScreen (keyboardd), and CryptoBot (airmond).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-hackers-deepfake-execs-in-zoom-call-to-spread-mac-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-408: PEAK-System Driver PCANFD_ADD_FILTERS Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-408/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PEAK-System Driver PCANFD_ADD_FILTERS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6217; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PEAK-System Driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which is due to a lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-24161</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chollima Hackers Target Windows and MacOS with New GolangGhost RAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chollima-hackers-target-windows-and-macos/</link>
      <description>The Famous Chollima group has launched a sophisticated remote access trojan (RAT) campaign targeting Windows and MacOS devices, with a focus on professionals in cryptocurrency and blockchain technologies. The attackers use a two-pronged strategy, creating fake job interview platforms to lure victims into executing malicious commands that download and launch the PylangGhost or GolangGhost variants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142888</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Revolutionizes PLA Military Intelligence with Rapid Deployment Across Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-revolutionizes-pla-military-intelligence/</link>
      <description>The People's Liberation Army (PLA) of China is adopting generative artificial intelligence (AI) to enhance its military operations, using advanced large language models (LLMs) for data processing, intelligence analysis, and decision-making support. This integration poses risks such as hallucination issues, ideological bias, and counterintelligence concerns, highlighting the need for rigorous experimentation and outcome assessment to ensure effective application of AI tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142881</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia’s Digital Arsenal: The Strategic Use of Private Companies and Hacktivists in Cyber Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/the-strategic-use-of-private-companies-and-hacktivists/</link>
      <description>Russia's sophisticated cyber warfare strategy emerges as a calculated blend of state power and non-state agility, leveraging private companies, hacktivists, and criminal proxies to amplify its digital dominance. The strategy involves concentric rings with state agencies at the core and a diverse array of non-state actors, including private IT firms, hacktivist groups, and eCrime collectives, which offers Moscow cost efficiency, flexibility, and access to cutting-edge skills, but also risks unpredictability and blurs the line between state and non-state action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142872</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A week with a "smart" car</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/a-week-with-a-smart-car/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the author's experience with advanced vehicle systems in a new car, highlighting issues with constant alerts and difficulty disabling features. It also touches on the importance of user experience and frictionless security tools.

FYSA: Cisco Talos has discovered that the North Korean-aligned threat actor Famous Chollima is targeting cryptocurrency and blockchain professionals through sophisticated phishing campaigns using Python-based malware (PylangGhost) and Golang-based variants. The campaign highlights the constant evolution of threat actors' tools, emphasizing the need for robust defenses and user education.

FYSA: AI scraping bots are breaking into libraries, archives, museums, and galleries, causing some collections to go offline. Additionally, a cybercriminal group leaked 7.4 million citizen records in Paraguay on the dark web, demanding $7.4 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68519c74813ef3000192102a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halo Security Honored with 2025 MSP Today Product of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/halo-security-honored-with-2025-msp-today-product-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <description>Halo Security's Attack Surface Management Platform has been named a 2025 MSP Today Product of the Year Award winner for its innovation, performance, and measurable impact on customers and partners alike. The platform enables organizations to discover, monitor, and secure their internet-facing assets, combining attacker-like discovery methods with ongoing security monitoring and vulnerability scanning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142902</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Fake CAPTCHA Windows Stealthily Install LightPerlGirl Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-captcha-windows-stealthily-install-lightperlgirl-malware/</link>
      <description>A newly identified malware strain, LightPerlGirl, uses deceptive fake CAPTCHA popups to infiltrate systems. It propagates through a social engineering tactic called the ClickFix attack, bypassing traditional security measures and exploiting user interaction. The attack begins with a compromised legitimate website serving malicious JavaScript, which triggers a fake CAPTCHA popup, tricking users into executing an obfuscated PowerShell command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142848</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Malware Campaign Uses Cloudflare Tunnels to Deliver RATs via Phishing Chains</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-malware-campaign-uses-cloudflare.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a new campaign using Cloudflare Tunnel subdomains to host malicious payloads and deliver them via phishing emails. The attack starts with sending payment-themed emails bearing a link to a zipped document containing a Windows shortcut file, which activates the infection sequence. The payload is executed in memory, allowing for evasion of detection.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-malware-campaign-uses-cloudflare.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 to block file access via legacy auth protocols by default</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-to-block-file-access-via-legacy-auth-protocols-by-default/</link>
      <description>This article does not mention a specific vulnerability. Instead, it discusses Microsoft's announcement to update security defaults for all Microsoft 365 tenants to block access to SharePoint, OneDrive, and Office files via legacy authentication protocols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-365-to-block-file-access-via-legacy-auth-protocols-by-default/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stargazers' use fake Minecraft mods to steal player passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stargazers-use-fake-minecraft-mods-to-steal-player-passwords/</link>
      <description>A large-scale malware campaign targets Minecraft players by distributing malicious mods and cheats that infect Windows devices with info-stealers. The campaign uses GitHub as a distribution platform, disguising the malware as legitimate Minecraft content, and can steal credentials, authentication tokens, and cryptocurrency wallets.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in this article, but rather a malicious campaign using social engineering tactics to spread malware to victims' devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/stargazers-use-fake-minecraft-mods-to-steal-player-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500+ Minecraft Players Infected by Java Malware Masquerading as Game Mods on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/1500-minecraft-players-infected-by-java.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a multi-stage malware campaign targeting Minecraft users, which employs a Java-based malware using a distribution-as-service (DaaS) offering called Stargazers Ghost Network. The campaign's end goal is to trick players into downloading a Minecraft mod from GitHub and deliver a .NET information stealer with comprehensive data theft capabilities.

FYSA: The article highlights the use of an illicit offering, the Stargazers Ghost Network, which makes use of thousands of GitHub accounts to set up tainted repositories that masquerade as cracked software and game cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/1500-minecraft-players-infected-by-java.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainLink Phishing: How Trusted Domains Become Threat Vectors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chainlink-phishing-how-trusted-domains-become-threat-vectors/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolution of phishing attacks, specifically "ChainLink Phishing", which uses trusted infrastructure to funnel victims through a series of credible-looking prompts before harvesting credentials. It highlights how traditional defenses are insufficient against these attacks and emphasizes the need for real-time analysis of web pages and user interactions to effectively mitigate threats like zero-hour phishing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chainlink-phishing-how-trusted-domains-become-threat-vectors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA warns of attackers exploiting Linux flaw with PoC exploit</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-attackers-exploiting-linux-flaw-with-poc-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux kernel's OverlayFS subsystem; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) in the Linux kernel's OverlayFS subsystem allows attackers to gain root privileges. The flaw, caused by improper ownership management, was patched in January 2023 and publicly disclosed two months later. Multiple proof-of-concept exploits were shared on GitHub, making exploitation attempts easier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-attackers-exploiting-linux-flaw-with-poc-exploit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare SaaS firm says data breach impacts 5.4 million patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/episource-says-data-breach-impacts-54-million-patients/</link>
      <description>Episource, a healthcare services company, has reported a data breach that affected over 5 million people in the United States. The breach occurred between January 27 and February 6, 2025, when hackers accessed and exfiltrated sensitive health information, including full names, physical addresses, medical records, and social security numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/episource-says-data-breach-impacts-54-million-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperCard Malware Hijacks Android Devices to Steal Payment Card Data and Relay it to Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/supercard-malware-hijacks-android-devices/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the emergence of SuperCard, a malicious modification of the legitimate NFCGate program, which exploits Near Field Communication (NFC) traffic to intercept sensitive bank card data. The malware is distributed via a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) platform named SuperCard X and targets Android users globally, with recent attacks recorded in Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142823</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zyxel NWA50AX Pro Hit by N-Day Flaw Allowing Arbitrary File Deletion</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zyxel-nwa50ax-pro-hit-by-n-day-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zyxel NWA50AX Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2024-29974; Summary: The Zyxel NWA50AX Pro WiFi 6 access point contains an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability (CVE-2024-29974) that allows attackers to delete files without authentication by crafting a POST request with manipulated parameters. This can lead to further attacks, such as replacing configuration or password files, potentially causing privilege escalation or denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142854</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Transit Mode in Apple Pay and GPay to Steal Money</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-apple-pay-and-gpay/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mobile Wallets (Apple Pay, Google Pay); CVE(s): None; Summary: The Express Transit mode in mobile wallets like Apple Pay and Google Pay allows for automatic charges without biometric checks or alerts, making it vulnerable to exploitation by hackers who can drain funds instantly and silently. Attackers can grab unlocked phones, mimic legitimate behavior, and exploit weak PINs to steal money.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142853</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Enhances Office 365 Defender to Stop Email Bombing Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/office-365-defender-to-stop-email-bombing-campaigns/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new feature called Mail Bombing Detection in Microsoft Office 365 Defender, designed to combat email bombing attacks by automatically identifying and blocking massive volumes of emails. This feature is enabled by default and does not require manual configuration, providing enhanced protection against email-based threats without additional administrative overhead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142852</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITRE and Splunk Expose Critical Vulnerabilities in Open Source GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitre-and-splunk-expose-critical-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitHub Actions; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47928; Summary: The GitHub Actions workflows of several high-profile open source projects were found to be vulnerable due to the misuse of the pull_request_target trigger. This vulnerability allows attackers to access sensitive secrets and high-privilege tokens, potentially leading to full repository takeovers. The vulnerability was exploited in projects like spotipy-dev/spotipy and MITRE's Cyber Analytics Repository (CAR).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142812</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RapperBot Botnet Surges with 50,000+ Attacks Targeting Network Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rapperbot-botnet-surges-with-50000-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The RapperBot botnet has resurfaced with over 50,000 attacks targeting network edge devices, exploiting vulnerabilities in IoT devices such as routers, IP cameras, and other connected hardware. The botnet uses brute-force techniques and exploits known vulnerabilities to compromise devices, establishing persistence by downloading additional payloads and conducting DDoS attacks or serving as a gateway for further malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142777</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMV-Style Phishing Scams Target U.S. Citizens to Harvest Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dmv-style-phishing-scams-target-u-s-citizens/</link>
      <description>A highly coordinated phishing campaign targeting U.S. citizens has been discovered, utilizing SMS phishing (smishing) and impersonating state Departments of Motor Vehicles (DMVs). The attack threatened license suspension or legal action and attempted to steal personal information by directing victims to fake DMV websites. The campaign is attributed to a China-based threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142746</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware Unveils Cloud Foundation 9.0 With AI and Next-Gen Workloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-unveils-cloud-foundation-9-0/</link>
      <description>VMware has announced the general availability of VMware Cloud Foundation (VCF) 9.0, a private cloud technology designed to meet the demands of AI, data-intensive workloads, and modern enterprise operations. The new release offers a unified platform that merges the speed and flexibility of cloud with the performance, governance, and cost control required for on-premises environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142782</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedRAMP at Startup Speed: Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fedramp-at-startup-speed-lessons-learned.html</link>
      <description>None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/fedramp-at-startup-speed-lessons-learned.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Vulnerabilities Enable Arbitrary Code Execution – Update Now!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-chrome-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): None; Summary: The update addresses three high-severity vulnerabilities, including an integer overflow in V8 and a use-after-free in Profiler, which could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, potentially leading to data theft or system compromise. If exploited, these vulnerabilities could enable attackers to bypass security controls and take control of a user's system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142773</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water Curse Hijacks 76 GitHub Accounts to Deliver Multi-Stage Malware Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/water-curse-hijacks-76-github-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Water Curse is a financially motivated threat actor that uses weaponized GitHub repositories to deliver multi-stage malware, enabling data exfiltration, remote access, and long-term persistence on infected systems. The actor's arsenal includes various tools and programming languages, and they employ anti-debugging techniques, privilege escalation methods, and persistence mechanisms to maintain a foothold on affected hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/water-curse-hijacks-76-github-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackHat AI Tool WormGPT Enhanced with Grok and Mixtral</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wormgpt-enhanced-with-grok-and-mixtral/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WormGPT; CVE(s): None; Summary: WormGPT is a notorious blackhat AI tool that has resurfaced in enhanced forms powered by advanced language models such as xAI's Grok and Mistral AI's Mixtral. The tool allows for the generation of human-like text, enabling malicious activities, and its variants have been introduced on underground forums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142766</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondTrust warns of pre-auth RCE in Remote Support software</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beyondtrust-warns-of-pre-auth-rce-in-remote-support-software/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BeyondTrust Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA) solutions; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5309; Summary: A high-severity Server-Side Template Injection vulnerability in the chat feature of BeyondTrust RS/PRA allows unauthenticated attackers to gain remote code execution on vulnerable servers. Exploitation does not require authentication, and administrators can mitigate the risk by enabling SAML authentication and enforcing session keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/beyondtrust-warns-of-pre-auth-rce-in-remote-support-software/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-402: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-402/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 file parsing vulnerability is a stack-based buffer overflow that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code, requiring user interaction. This occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data length prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25942</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When legitimate tools go rogue</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/when-legitimate-tools-go-rogue/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the trend of attackers using legitimate software, such as system tools (e.g., whoami, nltest, and nslookup) and remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools (e.g., ScreenConnect or AnyDesk), to carry out malicious actions. This tactic is referred to as "living off the land binaries" (LOLBins). The article highlights the importance of asset management, behavioral baselining, continuous monitoring, and threat intel alignment in detecting these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68517e4b813ef30001920ffc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-403: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-403/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26020</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-404: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-404/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26022</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-405: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-405/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1 has a file parsing stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from improper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-406: SolarWinds Serv-U FTP Service Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-406/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds Serv-U; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45711; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of SolarWinds Serv-U. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25087</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-407: SolarWinds Web Help Desk AjaxProxy Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-407/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SolarWinds Web Help Desk; CVE(s): CVE-2024-28988; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of SolarWinds Web Help Desk without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the AjaxProxy due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25346</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous Chollima deploying Python version of GolangGhost RAT</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/python-version-of-golangghost-rat/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Python-based remote access trojan (RAT) called "PylangGhost" used by a North Korean-aligned threat actor, Famous Chollima. The RAT targets employees with experience in cryptocurrency and blockchain technologies and is designed to steal browser credentials and session cookies from over 80 extensions, including password managers and cryptocurrency wallets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6851323e813ef30001920f8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Emerges as a Major Threat Targeting Windows, Linux, and ESXi Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-ransomware-emerges-as-a-major-threat/</link>
      <description>Qilin ransomware has emerged as a significant threat, leveraging a sophisticated Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) model and advanced technical capabilities to target Windows, Linux, and ESXi systems. Its features include custom-built malware, configurable encryption modes, and services like data storage, spam tools, and legal assistance, positioning it as a comprehensive cybercrime ecosystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142720</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Leverage ClickFix Strategy to Deploy RATs and Data-Stealing Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-leverage-clickfix-strategy-to-deploy-rats/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting a social engineering technique called ClickFix to initiate multi-stage cyberattacks, delivering remote access trojans (RATs) and data-stealing malware with alarming efficiency. The technique manipulates users into executing malicious PowerShell commands by disguising them as routine prompts like CAPTCHA verifications or browser updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142689</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Privilege Escalation Flaws Grant Full Root Access on Multiple Linux Distros</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-privilege-escalation-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SUSE 15, openSUSE Leap 15; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two interconnected local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities enable attackers to gain full root access on a wide range of Linux distributions with minimal effort. The flaws impact both desktop and server installations, requiring only a local user session such as SSH for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142693</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Winos 4.0 Malware Strain Emerges as Major Threat to Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-winos-4-0-malware-strain-emerges-as-major-threat/</link>
      <description>FortiGuard Labs has uncovered a new strain of malware, dubbed Winos 4.0, targeting Microsoft Windows users with a focus on individuals in Taiwan, utilizing phishing tactics and masquerading as government or business entities; the malware is designed to steal sensitive user data and maintain persistence through registry keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142680</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Linux udisks flaw lets attackers get root on major Linux distros</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/new-linux-udisks-flaw-lets-attackers-get-root-on-major-linux-distros/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: openSUSE Leap 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise 15, Ubuntu, Debian, Fedora; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6018, CVE-2025-6019; Summary: Two local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerabilities were discovered in the Pluggable Authentication Modules (PAM) framework and libblockdev. Exploiting these flaws allows attackers to gain root privileges on systems running major Linux distributions, enabling agent tampering, persistence, and lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/linux/new-linux-udisks-flaw-lets-attackers-get-root-on-major-linux-distros/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Claim Breach of Scania Financial Services, Leak Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-claim-breach-of-scania-financial-services/</link>
      <description>A threat actor claiming to be "hensi" infiltrated the subdomain insurance.scania.com of Scania Financial Services, exfiltrating sensitive files containing personal, financial, and potentially medical data. The breach is believed to have occurred when attackers exploited credentials belonging to an external IT partner using infostealer malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142688</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asana warns MCP AI feature exposed customer data to other orgs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asana-warns-mcp-ai-feature-exposed-customer-data-to-other-orgs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Asana; CVE(s): None; Summary: A logic flaw in the Model Context Protocol (MCP) feature of Asana's work management platform potentially exposed data from one organization to another, including task-level information and project metadata. The exposure occurred for over a month before being discovered on June 4 and has impacted around 1,000 customers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/asana-warns-mcp-ai-feature-exposed-customer-data-to-other-orgs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-23121: Critical RCE Vulnerability Patched in Veeam Backup &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-23121-rce-patched-veeam-backup-replication/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Backup &amp; Replication; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121 (CVSS 9.9), CVE-2025-24286 (CVSS 7.2), CVE-2025-24287 (CVSS 6.1); Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVE-2025-23121) allows authenticated domain users to remotely execute arbitrary code on Veeam Backup Servers, affecting systems that are domain-joined. Additionally, two other vulnerabilities were discovered, one allowing modification of backup jobs and another allowing local system users to modify directory contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061066</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts to Active Exploits of Linux Kernel Improper Ownership Management Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-to-active-exploits-of-linux-kernel-improper-ownership-management-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Linux distributions; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A critical Linux kernel vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) allows local users to escalate privileges and potentially gain root-level access. The flaw emerges when a user copies a file with special capabilities from a nosuid mount into another mount, due to the kernel's failure to properly clear setuid and setgid bits during the copy-up operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142676</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA Analyst Sentenced to 37 Months for Leaking Top Secret National Defense Documents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ex-cia-analyst-sentenced-to-37-months.html</link>
      <description>A former CIA analyst, Asif William Rahman, was sentenced to 37 months in prison for stealing and transmitting classified National Defense Information (NDI) without authorization. He retained multiple Secret and Top Secret documents on October 17, 2024, and wilfully sent them to individuals who did not have the necessary clearance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/ex-cia-analyst-sentenced-to-37-months.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Warns of Active Exploitation of Linux Kernel Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: The Linux kernel contains an improper ownership management vulnerability (CVE-2023-0386) that can be exploited to escalate privileges on susceptible systems. The flaw, which has a CVSS score of 7.8, allows a local user to create SUID binaries owned by root and execute them, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Gerrit Platform Flaw Exposes 18 Google Projects, Including ChromiumOS, to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/googles-gerrit-platform-flaw-exposes-18-google-projects/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Gerrit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1568; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Google's Gerrit code-collaboration platform allows unauthorized code submissions by hackers, putting at least 18 major Google projects at risk. The flaw centers on misconfigured permissions and logic flaws in the review process, enabling attackers to inject malicious code without detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142671</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Patches CVE-2025-23121: Critical RCE Bug Rated 9.9 CVSS in Backup &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/veeam-patches-cve-2025-23121-critical.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121, CVE-2025-24286, CVE-2025-24287; Summary: A critical security flaw (CVE-2025-23121) in Veeam's Backup &amp; Replication software allows remote code execution under certain conditions. Another flaw (CVE-2025-24286) permits an authenticated user to modify backup jobs and execute arbitrary code, while a third vulnerability (CVE-2025-24287) enables local system users to modify directory contents and execute code with elevated permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/veeam-patches-cve-2025-23121-critical.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Slows Internet to Prevent Cyber Attacks Amid Escalating Regional Conflict</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-restricts-internet-access-to.html</link>
      <description>Iranian government has throttled internet access in the country, allegedly to prevent Israel's covert cyber operations. This development is part of an escalating digital conflict between Iran and Israel, with both sides engaging in retaliatory cyber attacks. The conflict also involves threat actors affiliated with Iran, who have launched malicious activities against U.S. critical infrastructure using IOCONTROL malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/iran-restricts-internet-access-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Vulnerabilities Expose Backup Servers to Remote Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/veeam-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121, CVE-2025-24286, CVE-2025-24287; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-23121) allows remote code execution on a Veeam Backup Server, while two other vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-24286 and CVE-2025-24287) enable privilege escalation and local privilege escalation in the Veeam Agent for Microsoft Windows, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142667</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix NetScaler ADC &amp; Gateway Flaws Expose Sensitive Data to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/citrix-netscaler-adc-gateway-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5349, CVE-2025-5777; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities have been discovered in Citrix NetScaler ADC and NetScaler Gateway, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to critical management functions or read sensitive memory contents. The flaws can be exploited remotely and put enterprise networks at significant risk of data leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142663</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 05:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats to the 2025 NATO Summit</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/threats-2025-nato-summit</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a cybersecurity threat analysis report focused on Russian hybrid warfare tactics and potential threats to European critical infrastructure ahead of the 2025 NATO Summit. The report highlights various forms of sabotage, vandalism, and coercive military actions that Russia may employ to destabilize NATO member states.

Key findings include:

1. Russian-directed sabotage attacks targeting submarine cables in the Baltic Sea have increased since 2022.
2. Moscow is likely to continue attempting to weaponize refugee flows to foment domestic unrest and exploit concerns about immigration in countries bordering Russia and Belarus.
3. The Kremlin may increase its military presence and intelligence capabilities near Finland and the Baltic states.
4. Coercive military actions via incursions into NATO airspace will likely increase ahead of the 2025 NATO Summit.

The report concludes by emphasizing that Russian hybrid threats will continue to target European critical infrastructure, particularly in countries bordering Russia, if there is no significant action regarding Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/threats-2025-nato-summit</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity takes a big hit in new Trump executive order</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybersecurity-take-a-big-hit-in-new-trump-executive-order/</link>
      <description>FYSA:
The article discusses the impact of a recent Executive Order (EO) issued by former US President Trump on cybersecurity governance and regulations. The EO rolled back several requirements aimed at improving cybersecurity, including those related to quantum-resistant algorithms, Border Gateway Protocol security, and digital identity documents. Experts warn that these changes will weaken cybersecurity efforts and create vulnerabilities in existing infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/cybersecurity-take-a-big-hit-in-new-trump-executive-order/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paddle settles for $5 million over facilitating tech support scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paddle-settles-for-5-million-over-facilitating-tech-support-scams/</link>
      <description>Paddle.com and its US subsidiary will pay $5 million to settle FTC allegations that the company facilitated deceptive tech-support schemes that harmed many US consumers, including older adults. The schemes used fake virus alerts and pop-up warnings to lure consumers into buying unneeded software or tech support services, with Paddle processing over $37 million in transactions for affiliated merchants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/paddle-settles-for-5-million-over-facilitating-tech-support-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-398: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-398/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Internet Security Platinum Host Service; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49384; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations by creating a symbolic link, which can be used to delete files. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25876</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-399: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-399/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V8; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor by exploiting a stack-based buffer overflow. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26026</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-400: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-400/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32412; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data that can result in a read past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26032</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-401: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V10 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-401/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor V10; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41413; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists in the parsing of V10 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26028</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-397: Delta Electronics COMMGR Insufficient Randomization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-397/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics COMMGR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3495; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Delta Electronics COMMGR, making it possible for an attacker to exploit the system without requiring a login. The specific flaw exists within the PLC simulator service, which can be exploited through brute force attacks at moderate expense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25049</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sorillus RAT Targets European Organizations Through Tunneling Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sorillus-rat-targets-european-organizations/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malicious infection chain using the Sorillus Remote Access Trojan (RAT) that targets organizations across Europe. The campaign employs invoice-themed phishing emails to deliver the malware, which uses legitimate services like OneDrive and Ngrok to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142610</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Zero-Day CVE-2025-2783 Exploited by TaxOff to Deploy Trinper Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-2783.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2783; Summary: A sandbox escape vulnerability (CVE-2025-2783) in Google Chrome was exploited by threat actor TaxOff to deploy a backdoor codenamed Trinper. The vulnerability had a CVSS score of 8.3 and was used as part of a phishing campaign targeting Russian organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-2783.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scania confirms insurance claim data breach in extortion attempt</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scania-confirms-insurance-claim-data-breach-in-extortion-attempt/</link>
      <description>Scania, a major Swedish manufacturer of heavy trucks and buses, suffered a cybersecurity incident where threat actors used compromised credentials to breach its Financial Services systems and steal insurance claim documents. The attackers emailed several Scania employees, threatening to leak the data online unless their demands were met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/scania-confirms-insurance-claim-data-breach-in-extortion-attempt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New KimJongRAT Stealer Uses Weaponized LNK File to Deploy PowerShell-Based Dropper</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-kimjongrat-stealer-uses-weaponized-lnk-file/</link>
      <description>The article discusses new variants of the KimJongRAT stealer malware that emerged in 2019. These variants use a weaponized Windows shortcut (LNK) file as an initial infection vector to deploy multi-stage droppers, aiming to steal sensitive user data, including cryptocurrency wallet extensions and system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142599</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Chaos RAT Variants Targeting Windows and Linux Systems to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-chaos-rat-variants-targeting-windows-and-linux-systems/</link>
      <description>Chaos RAT is a remote administration tool (RAT) that targets both Windows and Linux systems. It spreads through phishing campaigns, utilizing malicious PDF attachments embedded in emails to lure unsuspecting users into initiating the infection process. The malware grants attackers extensive control over infected systems, enabling capabilities such as keylogging, screen capture, file exfiltration, and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142564</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Sophisticated Multi-Stage Malware Campaign Uses VBS Files to Execute PowerShell Script</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-sophisticated-multi-stage-malware-campaign-uses-vbs-files/</link>
      <description>A multi-stage malware campaign has been discovered, utilizing heavily obfuscated Visual Basic Script (VBS) files to deploy remote access trojans (RATs). The campaign involves a three-stage process of obfuscation, dynamic script generation, and remote payload downloads, highlighting the evolving tactics of modern cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142587</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LangSmith Bug Could Expose OpenAI Keys and User Data via Malicious Agents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/langchain-langsmith-bug-let-hackers.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LangChain's LangSmith platform; CVE(s): None; Summary: The LangSmith platform contains a vulnerability that allows attackers to capture sensitive data, including API keys and user prompts. The vulnerability can be exploited by creating an artificial intelligence (AI) agent with a malicious proxy server, which can then intercept all user communications without the victim's knowledge.

FYSA: Threat actors have released two new variants of WormGPT, powered by xAI Grok and Mistral AI Mixtral, designed to facilitate malicious activities such as creating tailored phishing emails and writing snippets of malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/langchain-langsmith-bug-let-hackers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware: Weaponized Research Papers Delivering Malware Through Password-Protected Documents</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-weaponized-research-papers-delivering-malware/</link>
      <description>Kimsuky hacking organization is linked to a phishing email campaign targeting individuals with a password-protected HWP document embedded with a malicious OLE object. The attack chain includes the deployment of additional components, including executables and PowerShell scripts, designed to evade detection and establish persistent access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky and Konni APT Groups Lead Active Attacks Targeting East Asia</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-and-konni-apt-groups-lead-active-attacks/</link>
      <description>APT groups Kimsuky, Konni, Sidewinder, and Lazarus have been identified as the most active players in various regions, including East Asia, South Asia, Middle East, and Eastern Europe. These groups are using sophisticated intrusion techniques, spear phishing, and exploiting vulnerabilities to target government agencies, financial institutions, research bodies, and diplomats. The report highlights the need for enhanced threat intelligence and robust security frameworks to counter these persistent and evolving threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142549</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram ads mimicking BMO, EQ Bank are finance scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-ads-mimicking-bmo-eq-bank-are-finance-scams/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Instagram; CVE(s): None; Summary: Scammers are using Instagram ads, some featuring AI-powered deepfakes, to target Canadian consumers with phishing scams and investment fraud. The ads impersonate financial institutions like Bank of Montreal (BMO) and EQ Bank, prompting users to submit personal information or banking credentials.

FYSA: Scammers are targeting Canadian consumers with Instagram ads that appear to be run by reputable financial institutions but are actually fraudulent. These ads use official branding and color schemes to drive traffic outside of the platform to illicit domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-ads-mimicking-bmo-eq-bank-are-finance-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram ads mimicking BMO, EQ Banks are finance scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-ads-mimicking-bmo-eq-banks-are-finance-scams/</link>
      <description>Instagram ads impersonating financial institutions like Bank of Montreal (BMO) and EQ Bank are being used to target Canadian consumers with phishing scams and investment fraud, using AI-powered deepfake videos and official branding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-ads-mimicking-bmo-eq-banks-are-finance-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram 'BMO' ads use AI deepfakes to scam banking customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-bmo-ads-use-ai-deepfakes-to-scam-banking-customers/</link>
      <description>Instagram ads impersonating financial institutions like Bank of Montreal (BMO) and EQ Bank (Equitable Bank) are being used to target Canadian consumers with phishing scams and investment fraud. The ads use AI-powered deepfake videos or official branding to drive traffic outside the platform to lookalike illicit domains that are not affiliated with banks, attempting to collect personal information or banking credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/instagram-bmo-ads-use-ai-deepfakes-to-scam-banking-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDSpy Threat Actors Exploit Windows LNK Zero-Day Vulnerability to Target Windows System Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xdspy-threat-actors-exploit-windows-lnk-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25373; Summary: The Windows LNKzero-day vulnerability (ZDI-CAN-25373) is exploited by the XDSpy threat actor to target governmental entities in Eastern Europe and Russia. The vulnerability manipulates the Windows Explorer UI to conceal malicious commands through excessive whitespace padding, allowing hidden command execution that evades user interface visibility and third-party parsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Veeam RCE flaw lets domain users hack backup servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-veeam-rce-flaw-lets-domain-users-hack-backup-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23121; Summary: Veeam Backup &amp; Replication 12 or later contains a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability that can be exploited by authenticated domain users in low-complexity attacks to gain code execution remotely on the Backup Server. The flaw only impacts domain-joined installations and was fixed in version 12.3.2.3617, which was released earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-veeam-rce-flaw-lets-domain-users-hack-backup-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitecore CMS exploit chain starts with hardcoded 'b' password</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sitecore-cms-exploit-chain-starts-with-hardcoded-b-password/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform (XP); CVE(s): None; Summary: A chain of three pre-auth remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities allows attackers to breach and hijack servers without authentication. The vulnerabilities hinge on an internal user with a hardcoded password, a Zip Slip flaw in the Upload Wizard, and a vulnerability in the Sitecore PowerShell Extensions (SPE) module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sitecore-cms-exploit-chain-starts-with-hardcoded-b-password/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 15:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK fines 23andMe for ‘profoundly damaging’ breach exposing genetics data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-fines-23andme-for-profoundly-damaging-breach-exposing-genetics-data/</link>
      <description>The UK's Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) fined genetic testing provider 23andMe £2.31 million ($3.12 million) for serious security failings that led to a data breach in 2023, exposing sensitive personal information of thousands of people in the UK and Germany.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-fines-23andme-for-profoundly-damaging-breach-exposing-genetics-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Surface Hub boot issues with emergency update</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-surface-hub-boot-issues-with-emergency-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Surface Hub v1; CVE(s): None; Summary: The June 2025 Windows security update (KB5060533) causes startup failures for some Surface Hub v1 devices running Windows 10, version 22H2, resulting in Secure Boot Violation errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-surface-hub-boot-issues-with-emergency-update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to automate IT ticket handling with AI and Tines</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-automate-it-ticket-handling-with-ai-and-tines/</link>
      <description>This article is about a workflow orchestration and AI platform called Tines, specifically highlighting a pre-built ticket-handling workflow developed by Connor Brewer. The workflow aims to streamline IT issue handling by automating routine tasks, reducing manual triage, and enabling analysts to focus on more complex challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-automate-it-ticket-handling-with-ai-and-tines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker steals 1 million Cock.li user records in webmail data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-1-million-cockli-user-records-in-webmail-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cock.li Roundcube webmail platform; CVE(s): CVE-2021-44026; Summary: The Cock.li email hosting provider suffered a data breach after threat actors exploited an old SQL injection vulnerability in its now-retired Roundcube webmail platform, exposing over 1 million user records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-1-million-cockli-user-records-in-webmail-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Cyber Attacks in Review: May 2025</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/major-cyber-attacks-in-review-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cetus Protocol; CVE(s): None; Summary: Attackers exploited a vulnerability in the smart contract of Cetus Protocol's liquidity pools, stealing approximately $223 million in virtual assets. The flaw originated from an open-source library used in the liquidity provider's smart contract, allowing hackers to manipulate pool prices and repeatedly drain token reserves.

FYSA: LockBit was hacked, leaking thousands of Bitcoin addresses and chats. This leak offered law enforcement and analysts key data to trace ransom movements and disrupt operations, while also damaging LockBit's reputation after recent infrastructure takedowns.

Vulnerable Product: SK Shieldus; CVE(s): None; Summary: Malware in SK Shieldus software enabled the exposure of 27 million phone numbers through external Command and Control (C2) servers. The attack targeted SK Shieldus, a security affiliate spun off in 2021, affecting hundreds of corporate clients using its endpoint protection software.

FYSA: Phishing scams often use fake emails, websites, or social profiles to impersonate trusted brands and steal data. SOCRadar's Brand Protection detects these threats early by monitoring across channels and alerts your team instantly.

Vulnerable Product: Coinbase; CVE(s): None; Summary: Coinbase revealed that cybercriminals collaborated with rogue support agents to steal sensitive data from approximately 69,461 customers. The breach involved insiders at Coinbase's overseas retail support centers who accessed and exfiltrated customer information without authorization.

FYSA: The attacks impersonated major brands like Amazon, PayPal, Apple, and financial institutions, using spoofed emails with urgent calls to action linked to convincing fake login pages designed to harvest credentials and payment data. CoGUI's sophistication lies in its conditional redirection – links activate only if the victim's device matches attacker-set criteria like IP location, browser language, or device type, otherwise redirecting to the real brand website to evade detection.

FYSA: Major UK retailers, including Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, Harrods, and Dior, fell victim to a wave of cyber attacks attributed to the Scattered Spider group and DragonForce Ransomware affiliates. The attacks exploited social engineering tactics focused on service desk teams, tricking staff into granting access that allowed threat actors to deploy ransomware, steal customer data, and disrupt critical services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061053</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Fox APT Targets Taiwan with Complex Gh0stCringe and HoldingHands RAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/silver-fox-apt-targets-taiwan-with.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers are warning of a new phishing campaign targeting users in Taiwan with malware families such as HoldingHands RAT and Gh0stCringe. The campaign delivers malware via phishing emails impersonating Taiwan's National Taxation Bureau, using lures related to taxes, invoices, and pensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/silver-fox-apt-targets-taiwan-with.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondTrust Tools RCE Vulnerability Allows Attackers Execute Arbitrary Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beyondtrust-tools-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: BeyondTrust; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5309; Summary: The Remote Support (RS) and Privileged Remote Access (PRA) products from BeyondTrust contain a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected servers via the chat feature. This high-severity issue, tracked as CVE-2025-5309, could have far-reaching consequences for organizations relying on these access management solutions and requires prompt patching or configuration changes to mitigate exploitation risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142578</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerabilities in Sitecore Could Lead to Widespread Enterprise Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerabilities-in-sitecore/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform (XP); CVE(s): CVE-2025-27218, WT-2025-0024, WT-2025-0032, WT-2025-0025; Summary: A series of critical vulnerabilities in Sitecore XP allow for remote code execution and unauthorized access. The most severe vulnerability is a pre-authentication RCE flaw due to unsafe deserialization, while other flaws include hardcoded credentials, path traversal, and unrestricted file uploads. Unpatched systems are exposed to attacks that could lead to data theft, lateral movement, and operational disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142575</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Warns of Scattered Spider Attacks Targeting IT Support Teams at U.S. Insurance Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-warns-of-scattered-spider.html</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a cybercrime group known for using advanced social engineering tactics, has shifted its focus from retailers to insurance companies. The group is believed to have forged an alliance with the DragonForce ransomware cartel and targets organizations with large help desks and outsourced IT functions. To mitigate these attacks, enhanced authentication, rigorous identity controls, access restrictions, and employee verification are recommended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-warns-of-scattered-spider.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Manipulate Search Engines to Push Malicious Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-manipulate-search-engines/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated SEO poisoning operation has been exposed, where hackers manipulate search engine algorithms to push malicious websites to the top of search results. The platform Hacklink allows cybercriminals to buy access to thousands of compromised websites and inject code designed to deceive both users and search engines. This campaign targets high-traffic search terms related to online gambling and pharmaceuticals, artificially boosting the credibility and search ranking of malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142554</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/17/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux Kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2023-0386; Summary: A vulnerability in the Linux Kernel, identified as CVE-2023-0386, has been added to CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. This type of vulnerability is a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors and poses significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23527</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Mendix Studio Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Mendix Studio Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40592; Summary: A path traversal vulnerability in the module installation process of Studio Pro allows an attacker to write or modify arbitrary files in directories outside a developer's project directory, which could be exploited by crafting a malicious module and distributing it via the Mendix Marketplace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23520</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuji Electric Smart Editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32412, CVE-2025-41413, CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor is vulnerable to out-of-bounds read, out-of-bounds write, and stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23523</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Five Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/17/cisa-releases-five-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released five Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 17, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories cover specific products from Siemens, LS Electric, Fuji Electric, and Dover Fueling Solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23525</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dover Fueling Solutions ProGauge MagLink LX Consoles</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dover Fueling Solutions ProGauge MagLink LX consoles; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5310; Summary: The ProGauge MagLink LX consoles have a missing authentication vulnerability, allowing an attacker to create, delete, or modify files and potentially execute code remotely. Successful exploitation could result in control of the monitoring device, manipulation of fueling operations, deletion of system configurations, or deployment of malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23524</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LS Electric GMWin 4</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-168-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LS Electric GMWin 4; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49848, CVE-2025-49849, CVE-2025-49850; Summary: Successful exploitation of the Out-of-Bounds Write, Out-of-Bounds Read, and Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities in LS Electric GMWin 4 could allow an attacker to disclose information or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23521</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Forgotten AD Service Accounts Leaving You at Risk?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/are-forgotten-ad-service-accounts.html</link>
      <description>Forgotten Active Directory (AD) service accounts are often overlooked, allowing them to quietly persist with non-expiring or stale passwords. Attackers seek out these forgotten service accounts as they can serve as silent gateways for attack paths and lateral movement across enterprise environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/are-forgotten-ad-service-accounts.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp’s Status Tab Set to Feature Ads as Meta Monetizes Platform</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/whatsapps-status-tab-set-to-feature-ads/</link>
      <description>WhatsApp, with over 2 billion monthly active users, is introducing advertisements within its Updates tab, marking a significant shift in monetization. The ads will appear in the Status section, allowing businesses to promote products through ephemeral stories that disappear after 24 hours. Personal messaging remains untouched, and Meta emphasizes that privacy is built into these new features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142541</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Fake Verification Prompt and Clickfix Technique to Deploy Fileless AsyncRAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-fake-verification-prompt-and-clickfix-technique/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are distributing a fileless variant of AsyncRAT remote access Trojan using deceptive tactics such as fake verification prompts. The malware uses obfuscated PowerShell scripts, in-memory execution, and registry persistence to evade detection and maintain covert access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142513</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASUS Armoury Crate Vulnerability Lets Hackers Gain System-Level Access on Windows</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/asus-armoury-crate-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ASUS Armoury Crate; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3464; Summary: A critical vulnerability in ASUS's Armoury Crate software allows attackers to bypass security controls and gain SYSTEM-level privileges, exposing millions of Windows users to system-level compromise. The flaw can be exploited by creating a hard link from a benign application to a trusted executable, tricking the driver into granting privileged access to malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142520</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Coded 'b' Password in Sitecore XP Sparks Major RCE Risk in Enterprise Deployments</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hard-coded-b-password-in-sitecore-xp.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sitecore Experience Platform; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discloses three security flaws in Sitecore Experience Platform that could be chained to achieve pre-authenticated remote code execution. The vulnerabilities include hard-coded credentials, post-authenticated remote code execution via path traversal, and post-authenticated remote code execution via Sitecore PowerShell Extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hard-coded-b-password-in-sitecore-xp.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backups Are Under Attack: How to Protect Your Backups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-protect-your-backups-from-ransomware-attacks.html</link>
      <description>Ransomware attacks are increasingly targeting backup infrastructure, attempting to cripple recovery capabilities. Threat actors disable backup agents, delete snapshots, modify retention policies, encrypt backup volumes, and exploit vulnerabilities in integrated backup platforms. To defend against this, IT pros should implement a resilient backup strategy that includes isolation, offsite or immutable copies, and regular verification and monitoring of backups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-to-protect-your-backups-from-ransomware-attacks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water Curse Hacker Group Uses 76 GitHub Accounts to Spread Multistage Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/water-curse-hacker-group-uses-76-github-accounts/</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as Water Curse has been linked to a campaign utilizing at least 76 GitHub accounts to distribute malware, targeting a diverse range of victims including cybersecurity professionals. The group's sophisticated attack methodology poses a significant supply chain risk, embedding malicious payloads within seemingly legitimate tools and scripts hosted on GitHub.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142500</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical sslh Vulnerabilities Allow Remote Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sslh-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: sslh; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46807, CVE-2025-46806; Summary: The sslh protocol multiplexer has two critical vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-46807 and CVE-2025-46806, which could allow remote attackers to crash the service or render it unavailable, resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) for legitimate users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142511</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-381: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic CreateTrace SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-381/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27495; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the CreateTrace method, which fails to properly validate a user-supplied string before constructing SQL queries, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25911</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-382: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateProject SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-382/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32475; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which can be bypassed to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25912</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-383: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic VerifyUser SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-383/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27539; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the flaw exists within the implementation of the VerifyUser method due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25914</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-384: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic Authenticate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-384/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27540; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic without authentication. The flaw exists in the implementation of the Authenticate method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25913</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-385: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic RestoreFromBackup SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-385/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29905; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by injecting SQL commands through the RestoreFromBackup method. The flaw is due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25923</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-386: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateConnectionVariables SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-386/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30002; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, bypassing authentication and disclosing stored credentials. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25909</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-387: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateProjectConnections SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-387/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30003; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used in SQL queries, enabling attackers to disclose stored credentials and potentially leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25910</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-388: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic ImportDatabase SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-388/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30030; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries, which can be used to disclose stored credentials leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25924</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-389: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateUsers SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-389/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30031; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by exploiting a SQL injection information disclosure vulnerability in the UpdateUsers method, which can be bypassed. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25922</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-390: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateDatabaseSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-390/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30032; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic, which can be used to compromise further. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25921</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-391: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateTcmSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-391/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31343; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Although authentication is required, the existing mechanism can be bypassed. The flaw exists in the UpdateTcmSettings method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings used to construct SQL queries, allowing disclosure of stored credentials leading to further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25920</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-392: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateSmtpSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-392/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31349; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic through SQL injection, bypassing authentication. The issue is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied strings before constructing SQL queries, which could lead to stored credentials being disclosed and further compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25919</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-393: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateBufferingSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-393/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31350; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, by exploiting a SQL injection flaw in the UpdateBufferingSettings method. Authentication is required but can be bypassed, making it possible for an attacker to leverage this issue and disclose sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25918</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-394: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic CreateProject SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-394/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31351; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic by bypassing the existing authentication mechanism and leveraging a SQL injection flaw in the CreateProject method, which lacks proper validation of user-supplied strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25917</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-395: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateGateways SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-395/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31352; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information, including stored credentials, by exploiting a SQL injection issue in the UpdateGateways method due to improper validation of user-supplied strings. Authentication is required but can be bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25915</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-396: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic UpdateOpcSettings SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-396/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens TeleControl Server Basic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31353; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Siemens TeleControl Server Basic. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the UpdateOpcSettings method due to lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25916</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a New KimJongRAT Stealer Variant and Its PowerShell Implementation</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/kimjongrat-stealer-variant-powershell/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an in-depth analysis of a malware campaign, specifically focusing on a PowerShell-based stealer and its various components. The article describes the different stages of the malware's operation, including data extraction from browsers and file systems, as well as interactions with a command-and-control (C2) server.

Key findings include:

1. The malware is designed to extract sensitive information such as browser data, cryptocurrency wallet extensions, and system files.
2. The malware uses various techniques to evade detection, including anti-VM checks and obfuscation of its code.
3. The malware communicates with a C2 server to upload stolen data, download additional payloads, and execute commands.
4. The malware has persistence mechanisms in place, including registry entries and file creation.

The article provides detailed information on the malware's components, including VBScript code, PowerShell scripts, and Base64-encoded payloads. It also discusses the different stages of the malware's operation and its interactions with the C2 server.

Overall, this analysis provides valuable insights into the capabilities and behavior of this particular malware campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143320</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate List of Free and Open-source Threat Intelligence Feeds</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/the-ultimate-list-of-free-and-open-source-threat-intelligence-feeds/</link>
      <description>The article discusses free and open-source threat intelligence feeds that can help cybersecurity professionals improve their visibility across the threat landscape without relying solely on expensive commercial platforms. The article presents a collection of highly regarded and globally accessible threat intelligence feeds, including MISP, SANS Internet Storm Center (ISC), AlienVault OTX, InfraGard, Automated Indicator Sharing (AIS), Cisco Talos, GreyNoise, VirusTotal, OpenPhish, Spamhaus, and SOCRadar Labs. These feeds provide real-time or regularly updated data on malicious activity, such as phishing campaigns, malware infrastructure, scanning IPs, and malicious URLs, which can help automate alerts, enrich incident context, and enhance proactive defense capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100017473</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Flodrix Botnet Variant Exploits Langflow AI Server RCE Bug to Launch DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-flodrix-botnet-variant-exploits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Langflow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3248; Summary: Langflow's missing authentication vulnerability (CVE-2025-3248) allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted HTTP requests, potentially leading to remote code execution. Attackers are exploiting this flaw to deliver the Flodrixbotnet malware and conduct reconnaissance, installing a shell script downloader and eventually launching DDoS attacks over TCP or TOR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-flodrix-botnet-variant-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150K+ Users Affected by Malicious Loan Apps on iOS and Google Play</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/150k-users-affected-by-malicious-loan-apps/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RapiPlata app; CVE(s): None; Summary: The RapiPlata app, posing as a financial service, targeted Colombian users by gaining access to sensitive data such as SMS messages, call logs, calendar events, and installed applications. It exploited permissions under the guise of credit assessment to conduct keyword-based SMS scanning, behavioral data harvesting, and unauthorized exfiltration of personal information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142481</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 09:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploiting Chrome Zero‑Day Vulnerability in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploiting-chrome-zero%e2%80%91day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2783; Summary: The vulnerability arises from an incorrect handle being provided in unspecified circumstances, allowing remote attackers to escape Chrome's sandbox via a malicious file or website. This enables attackers to bypass one of Chrome's core security mechanisms, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution on the victim's machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 08:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TP-Link Router Flaw CVE-2023-33538 Under Active Exploit, CISA Issues Immediate Alert</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/tp-link-router-flaw-cve-2023-33538.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TP-Link; CVE(s): CVE-2023-33538; Summary: The vulnerability is a command injection bug (CVSS score: 8.8) in TP-Link wireless routers that could result in the execution of arbitrary system commands when processing the ssid1 parameter in a specially crafted HTTP GET request, with evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/tp-link-router-flaw-cve-2023-33538.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Devices Under Siege: How Threat Actors Abuse OEM Permissions for Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-threat-actors-abuse-oem-permissions-for-privilege-escalation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting legitimate channels, such as sideloading and OEM permissions, to achieve privilege escalation and gain control over devices. This can occur through malicious apps requesting excessive system access or inheriting elevated privileges. The vulnerability lies in the exploitation of trusted pathways, allowing attackers to bypass Android's standard security model and compromise user privacy settings.

(Note: Since this article is about a cybersecurity-relevant issue rather than a specific vulnerability with CVEs, I responded in the "FYSA" format.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142461</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts: iOS Zero‑Click Flaw Actively Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-ios-zero%e2%80%91click-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43200; Summary: The zero-click vulnerability in Apple's ecosystem allowed attackers to compromise iOS, iPadOS, macOS, watchOS, and visionOS devices without user interaction. The flaw was triggered by processing maliciously crafted photos or videos shared via iCloud Links, enabling remote code execution and full device compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142469</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCHQ Intern Sentenced to 7 Years for Illegally Copying Secret Files to Smartphone</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gchq-intern-sentenced-to-7-years/</link>
      <description>A former GCHQ intern, Hasaan Arshad, has been sentenced to 7 and a half years in prison for smuggling top secret data out of a secure facility using his mobile phone. The breach was described as a "flagrant violation" of national security protocols, posing a significant risk to the UK's national security efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142445</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
