<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:01:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>BreachForums hacking forum operators reportedly arrested in France</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breachforums-hacking-forum-operators-reportedly-arrested-in-france/</link>
      <description>The French police have arrested five operators of the BreachForum cybercrime forum, including ShinyHunters and IntelBroker, who were involved in multiple high-profile data breaches. The arrested threat actors allegedly operated BreachForums v2, a community for cybercriminals to trade, sell, and leak stolen data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/breachforums-hacking-forum-operators-reportedly-arrested-in-france/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktivist Groups Target U.S. Companies and Military Domains in Retaliation for Iran Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacktivist-groups-target-u-s-companies-and-military-domains/</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist groups have claimed responsibility for a series of Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks targeting US military domains, major aerospace and defense corporations, and key financial institutions, in retaliation to US involvement in the Israel-Iran conflict. The cyber warfare has escalated with claims of data breaches, website defacements, and electronic interference with commercial navigation systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144125</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 Flaw Enables Token Theft; SAP GUI Flaws Risk Sensitive Data Exposure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-enables-token-theft.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP Graphical User Interface (GUI) for Windows and Java; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0055, CVE-2025-0056; Summary: The vulnerabilities allow attackers with administrative privileges or access to the user directory to access sensitive information stored in input history files. In SAP GUI for Windows, the data is weakly encrypted using XOR-based encryption, making it easily decodable. In SAP GUI for Java, the data is stored as unencrypted Java serialized objects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/citrix-bleed-2-flaw-enables-token-theft.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox 140 Launches with Critical Code Execution Bug Fix – Update Now</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/firefox-140-launches-with-critical-code-execution-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: The critical use-after-free vulnerability in the FontFaceSet component allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on a victim's machine, posing a major risk to user security. Additionally, two high-severity memory safety issues were patched, including memory corruption defects that could be exploited for remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144123</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Configuration Bug Freezes Update Scanning Process</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-configuration-bug-freezes-update-scanning-process/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "Scan for Updates" feature in Windows 11 version 24H2 can freeze unexpectedly, preventing devices from detecting and installing critical updates. This issue can leave systems vulnerable to threats. A temporary fix is restarting the computer, but a permanent resolution requires installing the May Windows non-security preview update (KB5058499) or subsequent updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144118</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realtek Bluetooth Flaw Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks During Pairing</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/realtek-bluetooth-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Realtek RTL8762E BLE SDK v1.4.0; CVE(s): CVE-2024-48290; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Realtek's Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) implementation allows attackers to launch denial-of-service (DoS) attacks during device pairing, disrupting connections and blocking legitimate pairing attempts. The flaw occurs when attackers inject premature pairing data or send a crafted ll_terminate_ind packet, causing the target device's Bluetooth stack to crash and prevent subsequent connection attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144114</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Releases Security Patch for 11 Code Execution Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-releases-security-patch-for-11-code-execution-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): 11 (no specific CVEs listed); Summary: The Chrome team has released a critical security update addressing 11 code execution vulnerabilities that could put millions of users at risk. The update patches a range of vulnerabilities, including several discovered and reported by external security researchers, and is being distributed through the stable channel to reach users over the coming days and weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144106</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes Guide to Address Memory Safety Vulnerabilities in Modern Software Development</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-guide-to-address-memory-safety-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and National Security Agency (NSA) have released a comprehensive guide titled “Memory Safe Languages: Reducing Vulnerabilities in Modern Software Development.” The report highlights the importance of adopting Memory Safe Languages (MSLs) to combat memory safety vulnerabilities, which contribute to 66-75% of Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVEs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144065</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Manipulate Search Results, Exploit ChatGPT and Luma AI Popularity to Deliver Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-manipulate-search-results/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using AI-themed websites to distribute malware, such as Vidar Stealer, Lumma Stealer, and Legion Loader. The attack begins with a user clicking on a seemingly legitimate search result, leading to an AI-themed webpage embedded with malicious JavaScript that collects browser data and initiates a multi-layered redirection process to deliver the malware payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144058</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Iranian Hacktivist Group Leaks Personal Records from the 2024 Saudi Games</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pro-iranian-hacktivist-group-leaks.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a data breach allegedly carried out by the pro-Iranian hacktivist group Cyber Fattah, which published personal records of athletes and visitors of the Saudi Games online. The breach is believed to have originated from the official website of the Saudi Games 2024 and was shared on DarkForums, a cybercrime forum. The leaked data includes IT staff credentials, government official email addresses, and sensitive documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/pro-iranian-hacktivist-group-leaks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes NodeRestriction Flaw Lets Nodes Bypass Resource Authorization</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kubernetes-noderestriction-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kubernetes; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4563; Summary: A critical security vulnerability in Kubernetes allows nodes to bypass authorization checks for dynamic resource allocation, enabling privilege escalation in affected clusters. The flaw resides in the NodeRestriction admission controller and affects kube-apiserver versions 1.32.0-1.32.5 and 1.33.0-1.33.1, with a CVSS score of 2.7 (Low severity).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144103</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NetNerve: AI-Powered Tool for Deep PCAP Threat Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/netnerve-ai-powered-tool/</link>
      <description>The article discusses NetNerve, an AI-powered platform that automates packet capture analysis, providing real-time insights and actionable recommendations to detect threats hidden in packet capture files. This platform addresses the limitations of traditional packet capture solutions by leveraging machine learning to identify potential security threats, eliminating manual review requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144093</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akamai Reveals New Strategies for Defenders to Combat Cryptominer Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/akamai-reveals-new-strategies-for-defenders/</link>
      <description>Akamai has developed two proactive strategies to disrupt malicious cryptominer operations by exploiting the design of common mining topologies. The first strategy targets mining proxies by submitting invalid mining job results, while the second method temporarily bans wallet addresses by flooding login requests. These techniques can halt botnet-driven cryptomining campaigns and potentially impact other cryptocurrencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144029</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware the Hidden Risk in Your Entra Environment</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/beware-hidden-risk-in-your-entra.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: A gap in access control in Microsoft Entra's subscription handling allows guest users to create and transfer subscriptions into the tenant they are invited into, while maintaining full ownership rights. This privilege escalation tactic allows a guest user to gain a foothold in an environment where they should only have limited access.

FYSA: The article discusses a surprising risk in Microsoft Entra ID that can allow guest users to escalate their privileges by creating and controlling subscriptions. The vulnerability is due to the fact that Microsoft's billing permissions are scoped at the billing account level, rather than the Entra directory. This allows an attacker with the right billing role to spin up or transfer subscriptions from their home tenant to gain control inside a target tenant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/beware-hidden-risk-in-your-entra.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Attackers Leverage Microsoft ClickOnce to Run Malware as Trusted Applications</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-attackers-leverage-microsoft-clickonce/</link>
      <description>The article reports an Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) malware campaign dubbed “OneClik” targeting the energy, oil, and gas sectors. The campaign uses phishing attacks, exploits Microsoft ClickOnce, and employs "living off the land" tactics to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143998</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-418: Apple macOS CoreGraphics PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-418/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31196; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Apple macOS by parsing PDF files without proper validation, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required for exploitation, and the issue can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26498</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal abuse of large language models</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/cybercriminal-abuse-of-large-language-models/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are exploiting artificial intelligence (AI) technologies such as large language models (LLMs) to aid in their criminal hacking activities. They use uncensored LLMs or custom-built criminal LLMs for illicit purposes, including generating malicious code, creating undetectable malware, and sending phishing emails. Some enterprising cybercriminals have developed their own LLMs without restrictions, marketing them to other cybercriminals on the dark web.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685ac23e178bd70001283c68</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall NetExtender Trojan and ConnectWise Exploits Used in Remote Access Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sonicwall-netextender-trojan-and.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SSL VPN NetExtender; CVE(s): None; Summary: The trojanized version of SonicWall's SSL VPN NetExtender application steals credentials from unsuspecting users by impersonating the latest version (10.3.2.27) and modifying components "NeService.exe" and "NetExtender.exe" to exfiltrate configuration information to a remote server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/sonicwall-netextender-trojan-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Plans to Remove Chrome’s Tab Scrolling Feature</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-plans-to-remove-chromes-tab-scrolling-feature/</link>
      <description>The "Tab Scrolling" feature in Google's Chrome browser is being deprecated, which will allow tabs to compress into an unreadable strip again. Users who relied on this feature may need to explore alternative tab management solutions or adjust their browsing habits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144051</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Kibana Flaws Enable Heap Corruption and Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-kibana-flaws-enable-heap-corruption/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Elastic Kibana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2135; Summary: The critical vulnerability in Kibana's reporting engine, tracked as CVE-2025-2135, allows attackers to exploit heap memory corruption and potentially execute arbitrary code on the underlying system, posing a significant risk to data integrity and system security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144045</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CentOS Web Panel Vulnerability Allows Remote Code Execution – PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/centos-web-panel-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CentOS Web Panel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48703; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands, potentially leading to full server compromise. The flaw exploits two issues: improper enforcement of the authentication mechanism and a command injection vulnerability in the t_total parameter, which can be used to inject arbitrary commands and result in remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144040</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea-linked Supply Chain Attack Targets Developers with 35 Malicious npm Packages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/north-korea-linked-supply-chain-attack.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A total of 35 malicious npm packages have been discovered, linked to the Contagious Interview operation originating from North Korea. These packages contain a hex-encoded loader called HexEval, which collects host information and delivers a follow-on payload that downloads and executes a Python backdoor called InvisibleFerret, enabling remote control and data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/north-korea-linked-supply-chain-attack.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases New ICS Advisories Highlighting Ongoing Threats and Exploits</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-releases-new-ics-advisories/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Industrial Control Systems (ICS) products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2566, CVE-2025-5087, CVE-2025-47724, CVE-2025-47725, CVE-2025-47726, CVE-2025-47727, CVE-2025-3898, CVE-2025-3116, CVE-2025-3899, CVE-2025-3905, CVE-2025-3117, CVE-2025-3112, CVE-2025-5740, CVE-2025-5741, CVE-2025-5742, CVE-2025-5743, CVE-2025-49851, CVE-2025-49852, CVE-2025-49853, CVE-2025-5015, CVE-2025-49151, CVE-2025-49152, CVE-2025-49153; Summary: The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released eight new Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories addressing critical vulnerabilities and ongoing threats to essential infrastructure. The advisories detail technical information and mitigation guidance for various ICS products used worldwide, including vulnerabilities that allow remote code execution, extract sensitive credentials, or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144024</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamViewer for Windows Vulnerability Lets Hackers Delete Files with SYSTEM Rights</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/teamviewer-for-windows-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeamViewer Remote Management for Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-36537; Summary: A critical vulnerability (CVSS score 7.0) in TeamViewer's Remote Management features allows a local unprivileged attacker to delete arbitrary files with SYSTEM-level privileges, posing a risk of privilege escalation or system compromise. The flaw stems from an incorrect permission assignment for critical resources in the TeamViewer Client, affecting installations with Backup, Monitoring, or Patch Management enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144012</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Megatron LM Flaw Allows Attackers to Inject Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nvidia-megatron-lm-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Megatron-LM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23264, CVE-2025-23265; Summary: The Megatron-LM framework has two critical vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-23264 and CVE-2025-23265) that allow attackers to inject and execute malicious code on affected systems. Attackers can exploit these flaws by providing a specially crafted file, which could lead to remote code execution, privilege escalation, information disclosure, and data tampering with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=144001</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New FileFix Exploit Uses Windows File Explorer to Run Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-filefix-exploit-uses-windows-file-explorer/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a newly discovered exploit called "FileFix" that uses Windows File Explorer to execute malicious commands without leaving the web browser. It is a social engineering attack that relies on users following instructions to copy and paste file paths or commands, which can lead to execution of PowerShell commands, potentially delivering malware like infostealers, ransomware, or other types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143993</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 05:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Extends Windows 10 Security Updates for One Year with New Enrollment Options</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-extends-windows-10-security.html</link>
      <description>Microsoft is extending Windows 10 Extended Security Updates (ESU) for an extra year, allowing users to pay a small fee or sync their PC settings to the cloud. The enrollment wizard will be available in July and mid-August, enabling users to continue receiving critical and important security updates after support ends on October 14, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/microsoft-extends-windows-10-security.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google rolls out text-to-image model Imagen 4 for free</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-text-to-image-model-imagen-4-for-free/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's Imagen 4 text-to-image model, which is being rolled out for free on AI Studio. It also mentions two new Imagen models, Imagen 4 and Imagen 4 Ultra, which offer improvements in image generation quality. Additionally, the article touches on other cybersecurity-related topics such as patching automation and tech support scams detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-rolls-out-text-to-image-model-imagen-4-for-free/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Abuse Open-Source Tools To Target Africa’s Financial Sector</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/cybercriminals-attack-financial-sector-across-africa/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of attacks targeting financial organizations across Africa, attributed to an initial access broker. The threat actor uses a combination of open-source and publicly available tools, including PoshC2, Chisel, and Classroom Spy, to establish their attack framework and maintain persistence on compromised machines. The attackers create tunnels for network communication, perform remote administration, and disguise their tools to mask their malicious activities. Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected through various products and services, including Cortex XDR, XSIAM, Advanced WildFire, and the Unit 42 Deep and Dark Web Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=144003</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude catches up to ChatGPT with built-in memory support</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-catches-up-to-chatgpt-with-built-in-memory-support/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss any vulnerabilities, but rather mentions ChatGPT's memory feature and potential use by threat actors to write malware. 

(Note: Since the article is about ChatGPT's features and OpenAI's security measures, it does not fit into either of the other two formats)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-catches-up-to-chatgpt-with-built-in-memory-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud donates A2A AI protocol to the Linux Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-cloud-donates-a2a-ai-protocol-to-the-linux-foundation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the donation of Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol by Google Cloud to the Linux Foundation, creating a community-driven project for interoperability and collaboration between AI agents. This move aims to accelerate adoption and development of the A2A protocol while ensuring vendor-agnostic and open-source governance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/google-cloud-donates-a2a-ai-protocol-to-the-linux-foundation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall warns of trojanized NetExtender stealing VPN logins</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-trojanized-netextender-stealing-vpn-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall NetExtender; CVE(s): None; Summary: A trojanized version of the SonicWall NetExtender SSL VPN client is being distributed by threat actors to steal VPN credentials. The malicious installer mimics the legitimate software and is hosted on a spoofed website, bypassing elementary defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-trojanized-netextender-stealing-vpn-logins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 20:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New U.S. Visa Rule Requires Applicants to Set Social Media Account Privacy to Public</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-us-visa-rule-requires-applicants-to.html</link>
      <description>The US Embassy in India has announced that visa applicants must make their social media accounts public to facilitate vetting and verification of identity and admissibility. This move is part of a broader effort by the US government to expand social media screening of visa applicants, with similar directives issued by other US embassies worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-us-visa-rule-requires-applicants-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5061087 update released with 13 changes and fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5061087-update-released-with-13-changes-and-fixes/</link>
      <description>The article describes a non-security preview update (KB5061087) for Windows 10, version 22H2, which resolves various bugs and issues, including Start Menu launching problems, scanning feature failures on USB multi-function printers, and COM functionality errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5061087-update-released-with-13-changes-and-fixes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes known issue that breaks Windows 11 updates</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-known-issue-that-breaks-windows-11-updates/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft, Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A configuration update (KB5062324) is being rolled out to address an issue causing Windows Update to fail on some Windows 11 systems. The update is available for devices running Windows 11 version 24H2 and earlier updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-known-issue-that-breaks-windows-11-updates/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 17:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 users can get extended security updates using Microsoft points</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-extended-security-updates-available-using-reward-points/</link>
      <description>No vulnerabilities discussed in this article. The article is focused on Microsoft's Extended Security Updates (ESU) program for Windows 10 users and the end-of-support date for Windows 10, as well as statistics on Windows 10 and Windows 11 adoption rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-extended-security-updates-available-using-reward-points/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America, Netflix, and Microsoft Hacked to Inject Fake Phone Numbers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/america-netflix-and-microsoft-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Cybercriminals are exploiting reflected input vulnerabilities in the search functionality of major brands' websites (e.g., Apple, Bank of America, Facebook, HP, Microsoft, Netflix, and PayPal) to inject fake phone numbers into legitimate websites, deceiving users into contacting scammers under the guise of official customer support. The attackers manipulate search results by crafting URLs that exploit vulnerabilities in the search functionality, embedding fake phone numbers directly into the displayed search results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143965</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trezor’s support platform abused in crypto theft phishing attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trezors-support-platform-abused-in-crypto-theft-phishing-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trezor; CVE(s): None; Summary: The automated support system on Trezor's official platform is being abused by attackers to send phishing emails with deceptive subjects. These emails appear authentic, but contain fake alerts that link to a phishing page asking for wallet seed information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trezors-support-platform-abused-in-crypto-theft-phishing-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DRAT V2 Update Enhances C2 Protocol with Shell Command Execution Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-drat-v2-update-enhances-c2-protocol/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new variant of the DRAT remote access trojan (RAT), dubbed DRAT V2, used in a TAG-140 campaign targeting Indian government entities. The malware features updated command-and-control (C2) protocol and enhanced post-exploitation capabilities, including arbitrary shell command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143949</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FileFix attack weaponizes Windows File Explorer for stealthy commands</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/filefix-attack-weaponizes-windows-file-explorer-for-stealthy-powershell-commands/</link>
      <description>A new variant of the ClickFix social engineering attack called FileFix has been discovered, allowing threat actors to execute malicious commands via the File Explorer address bar in Windows. The attack works by tricking users into pasting a command into the File Explorer address bar, which can then be executed as an operating system command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/filefix-attack-weaponizes-windows-file-explorer-for-stealthy-powershell-commands/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gonjeshke Darande Hackers Pose as Activists to Infiltrate Iranian Crypto Exchange</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gonjeshke-darande-hackers-pose-as-activists/</link>
      <description>Gonjeshke Darande, a suspected Israeli state-sponsored group, launched a devastating attack on Nobitex, Iran's largest cryptocurrency exchange, resulting in the destruction of US$90 million in cryptocurrencies. The attack was motivated by political statements rather than financial gain and highlights the growing role of cyber operations in geopolitical conflicts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143938</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 2,000 Devices Compromised by Weaponized Social Security Statement Phishing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-2000-devices-compromised-by-weaponized-social-security/</link>
      <description>CyberArmor analysts have uncovered a sophisticated phishing campaign that has compromised over 2,000 devices by exploiting the trusted theme of Social Security Administration (SSA) statements. The campaign uses a convincing email lure and redirects victims to a counterfeit webpage hosted on Amazon Web Services (AWS), leading users to download malicious software and install malware on their systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143922</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Find Way to Shut Down Cryptominer Campaigns Using Bad Shares and XMRogue</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-find-way-to-shut-down.html</link>
      <description>Akamai researchers have identified two novel methods to disrupt cryptocurrency mining botnets by exploiting common mining topologies and pool policies. The methods involve submitting invalid mining job results ("bad shares") or initiating excessive login requests to ban the attacker's wallet, effectively shutting down the mining operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/researchers-find-way-to-shut-down.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit ConnectWise Configuration to Create Signed Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-connectwise-configuration/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ConnectWise; CVE(s): CVE-2024-1708, CVE-2024-1709; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting vulnerabilities in ConnectWise software to distribute signed malware, masquerading as legitimate applications. They use Authenticode stuffing to modify executables without invalidating signatures, enabling remote access malware that mimics trusted software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143907</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Today’s Pentest Models Compare and Why Continuous Wins</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-todays-pentest-models-compare-and-why-continuous-wins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the limitations of traditional pentesting approaches and introduces Continuous Penetration Testing (CPT) as a proactive security strategy that simulates real-world attackers operating against an organization's attack surface. CPT combines human-led testing with automation to provide continuous, contextual findings, and real-time alerts and remediation support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-todays-pentest-models-compare-and-why-continuous-wins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized DMV-Themed Phishing Scam Targets U.S. Citizens to Steal Personal and Financial Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-dmv-themed-phishing-scam-targets-u-s-citizens/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated phishing campaign targeting citizens across multiple US states has been detected, impersonating state Departments of Motor Vehicles (DMVs) to harvest personal and financial data. The campaign uses SMS phishing, fake DMV websites, and a centralized phishing kit named "Lighthouse" to execute its attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143897</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House bans WhatsApp on staff devices over security concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-house-bans-whatsapp-on-staff-devices-over-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>The U.S. House of Representatives has banned the installation and use of WhatsApp on government-issued devices due to concerns over data encryption and security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-house-bans-whatsapp-on-staff-devices-over-security-concerns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target Over 70 Microsoft Exchange Servers to Steal Credentials via Keyloggers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hackers-target-65-microsoft-exchange.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Exchange Server; CVE(s): CVE-2014-4078, CVE-2020-0796, CVE-2021-26855, CVE-2021-26857, CVE-2021-26858, CVE-2021-27065, CVE-2021-31206, CVE-2021-31207, CVE-2021-34473, CVE-2021-34523; Summary: Unidentified threat actors inject malicious code into Microsoft Exchange server login pages to harvest credentials. The code reads and processes authentication form data, then sends it via XHR request to a compromised server or uses Telegram bots as an exfiltration point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hackers-target-65-microsoft-exchange.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EagleSpy v5 RAT Promoted by Hacker for Stealthy Android Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/eaglespy-v5-rat-promoted-by-hacker-for-stealthy-android-access/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new version of the EagleSpy remote access Trojan (RAT), dubbed EagleSpy v5, which is being promoted by a threat actor known as "xperttechy" on a dark web forum. The malware has a wide range of features, including keylogging, screen streaming, and GPS tracking, and is designed to evade detection and maintain persistence on infected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143914</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zimbra Classic Web Client Vulnerability Allows Arbitrary JavaScript Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zimbra-classic-web-client-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zimbra Collaboration Suite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27915; Summary: The Zimbra Classic Web Client has a critical security flaw allowing arbitrary JavaScript execution through stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in ICS calendar invite files, affecting versions 9.0, 10.0, and 10.1 prior to patch releases. Attackers can execute embedded JavaScript, potentially leading to unauthorized actions like email redirection, data exfiltration, or session hijacking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143908</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Guidance Released for Reducing Memory-Related Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/24/new-guidance-released-reducing-memory-related-vulnerabilities</link>
      <description>The article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it highlights the importance of memory safety vulnerabilities in modern software development and promotes the adoption of memory safe languages (MSLs) as a mitigation measure to reduce exploitable flaws before products reach users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlID iDSecure On-Premises</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ControlID iDSecure On-premises; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49851, CVE-2025-49852, CVE-2025-49853; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to bypass authentication, retrieve information, leak arbitrary data, or perform SQL injections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23546</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSENS NMP Web+</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: MICROSENSE NMP Web+; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49151, CVE-2025-49152, CVE-2025-49153; Summary: The vulnerabilities in NMP Web+ allow an unauthenticated attacker to generate forged JSON Web Tokens (JWT) to bypass authentication, gain system access, overwrite files or execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23548</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EVLink WallBox</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EVLink WallBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5740, CVE-2025-5741, CVE-2025-5742, CVE-2025-5743; Summary: The Schneider Electric EVLink WallBox has multiple vulnerabilities, including path traversal, cross-site scripting, and OS command injection, which could allow an attacker to gain remote control of the charging station. Successful exploitation could cause arbitrary file writes, reads, or remote control of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23545</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Eight Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/06/24/cisa-releases-eight-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released eight Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on June 24, 2025. These advisories provide information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS products from various vendors, including Delta Electronics, Schneider Electric, and Mitsubishi Electric. CISA encourages users to review the advisories for technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23549</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Electronics CNCSoft</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47724, CVE-2025-47725, CVE-2025-47726, CVE-2025-47727; Summary: Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in Delta Electronics' CNCSoft human-machine interface software allow an attacker to execute code within the context of the current process if a user opens a maliciously crafted file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23543</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleris Navis N4 Terminal Operating System</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kaleris Navis N4; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2566, CVE-2025-5087; Summary: The Navis N4 terminal operating system contains two vulnerabilities: an unsafe Java deserialization vulnerability (CVE-2025-2566) that can allow remote code execution, and cleartext transmission of sensitive information (CVE-2025-5087). Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution or extraction of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23542</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric Modicon Controllers</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric Modicon Controllers M241, M251, M258, LMC058, and M262; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3898, CVE-2025-3117, CVE-2025-3905, CVE-2025-3116; Summary: Improper input validation, cross-site scripting, and uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerabilities exist in the Modicon Controllers, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code or cause a denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23544</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsons AccuWeather Widget</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-175-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Parsons AccuWeather and Custom RSS widget, AclaraONE Utility Portal; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5015; Summary: A cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in the AccuWeather and Custom RSS widget, allowing an unauthenticated user to replace the RSS feed URL with a malicious one. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to insert a malicious link that users might access through the RSS feed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23547</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Convoy Flaw Allows Remote Code Execution on Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-convoy-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Performave Convoy; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52562; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Performave Convoy allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code, steal sensitive data, and gain full server control. The flaw is due to improper input validation in the LocaleController component, enabling directory traversal attacks and remote code execution (RCE).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143880</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCSC Warns of SHOE RACK Malware Targeting Fortinet Firewalls via DOH &amp; SSH Protocols</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ncsc-warns-of-shoe-rack-malware-targeting-fortinet-firewalls/</link>
      <description>The National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) has identified a newly discovered malware called SHOE RACK that targets Fortinet firewalls and other perimeter devices. The malware uses DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) for command and control resolution, employs custom SSH extensions, and can enable lateral movement into local area networks (LANs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143848</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Donates A2A Protocol to Linux Foundation for Smarter, Secure Communication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-cloud-donates-a2a-protocol/</link>
      <description>Google Cloud has donated its Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol to the Linux Foundation to promote open, secure, and interoperable communication between AI agents. The A2A protocol is designed as an open standard for seamless collaboration between autonomous AI agents from different platforms and vendors. This move aims to foster innovation, reduce vendor lock-in, and accelerate the development of AI-driven applications across industries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143867</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between Buzz and Reality: The CTEM Conversation We All Need</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/between-buzz-and-reality-ctem.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the implementation of Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) in complex production environments. Three cybersecurity leaders share their insights and experiences in operationalizing CTEM, highlighting the importance of asset inventory, identity management, threat intelligence, and risk reporting. They also emphasize the need to move away from vulnerability-focused metrics and towards a business-risk-based approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/between-buzz-and-reality-ctem.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPPO Clone Phone Vulnerability Leaks Sensitive Data via Weak WiFi Hotspot</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oppo-clone-phone-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OPPO Clone Phone; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27387; Summary: The OPPO Clone Phone app has a high-severity vulnerability (CVSS 7.4) that allows attackers within WiFi range to intercept and retrieve files being transferred, exposing sensitive information such as photos, contacts, and messages. The vulnerability is due to the use of a weak password for the temporary WiFi hotspot, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143856</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Warns of Pro-Iranian Hacktivists Targeting U.S. Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dhs-warns-of-pro-iranian-hacktivists/</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist groups are expected to launch a wave of low-level cyberattacks targeting US networks in the next one to four weeks, with a focus on Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) campaigns and exploits targeting exposed operational technology (OT) devices. The attacks aim to disrupt entities supporting US efforts in the Israel-Iran conflict and may be backed by the Iranian government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143833</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-417: Clam AntiVirus UDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-417/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Clam AntiVirus; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20234; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Clam AntiVirus. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26010</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Misconfigured Docker APIs to Mine Cryptocurrency via Tor Network</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-docker.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Docker instances; CVE(s): None; Summary: Misconfigured Docker instances are being targeted by attackers who use the Tor anonymity network to stealthily mine cryptocurrency in susceptible environments. Attackers exploit misconfigured Docker APIs to gain access to containerized environments, then use Tor to mask their activities while deploying crypto miners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-docker.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Use Malicious Zoom Apps to Execute System-Takeover Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-use-malicious-zoom-apps/</link>
      <description>Suspected North Korean hackers have been reported to be behind a highly sophisticated scam, leveraging advanced social engineering techniques to trick professionals into compromising their systems. The campaign begins with a seemingly innocuous outreach on professional networking platforms like LinkedIn, and features a fraudulent account posing as a potential business collaborator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143824</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. House Bans WhatsApp on Official Devices Over Security and Data Protection Issues</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-house-bans-whatsapp-on-official.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WhatsApp; CVE(s): None; Summary: The U.S. House of Representatives has banned congressional staff from using WhatsApp on government-issued devices due to security concerns, citing lack of transparency in data protection, absence of stored data encryption, and potential security risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/us-house-bans-whatsapp-on-official.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LapDogs Hackers Compromise 1,000 SOHO Devices Using Custom Backdoor for Stealthy Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lapdogs-hackers-compromise-1000-soho-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): CVE-2015-1548, CVE-2017-17663; Summary: A custom backdoor named ShortLeash was used to infiltrate over 1,000 devices worldwide, primarily targeting SOHO routers and IoT devices, with a focus on critical regions. The malware exploits outdated vulnerabilities in lightweight web servers like ACME mini_httpd, using root privileges to survive reboots and employing dual-layer encryption and UCL-like compression to conceal its payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143783</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT28 Uses Signal Chat to Deploy BEARDSHELL Malware and COVENANT in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apt28-uses-signal-chat-to-deploy.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): BEARDSHELL, COVENANT; Summary: The article reports a cyber attack campaign by Russia-linked APT28 (UAC-0001) using Signal chat messages to deliver two new malware families, BEARDSHELL and COVENANT. BEARDSHELL offers the ability to download and execute PowerShell scripts, while COVENANT is a memory-resident framework that downloads intermediate payloads to launch the BEARDSHELL backdoor on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/apt28-uses-signal-chat-to-deploy.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Malware Campaign Targets WordPress and WooCommerce Sites with Hidden Skimmers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/advanced-malware-campaign-targets-wordpress-and-woocommerce-sites/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WordPress, WooCommerce; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign targeting WordPress and WooCommerce platforms was discovered by the Wordfence Threat Intelligence Team. The malware family features over 20 distinct samples, primarily focusing on credit card skimming and credential theft, with additional functionalities like malicious ad manipulation and payload distribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143799</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWASP Launches AI Testing Guide to Uncover Vulnerabilities in AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/owasp-launches-ai-testing-guide/</link>
      <description>The Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP) has released an AI Testing Guide to help organizations identify and mitigate vulnerabilities unique to AI systems. The guide emphasizes bias and fairness assessments, adversarial robustness, security and privacy evaluations, and continuous monitoring to ensure AI systems operate securely and privately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143813</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiaomi Interoperability App Flaw Allows Unauthorized Access to User Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xiaomi-interoperability-app-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Xiaomi Mi Connect Service App; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45347; Summary: The Mi Connect Service App has a critical vulnerability allowing attackers to bypass security checks and gain unauthorized access to user devices. This flaw can be exploited by an attacker on the same network segment, resulting in potential consequences such as unauthorized access to sensitive information, modification of device settings or stored data, disruption of normal device functionality, and complete compromise of device confidentiality and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143807</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinRAR Vulnerability Exploited with Malicious Archives to Execute Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/winrar-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RARLAB WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6218; Summary: A vulnerability in WinRAR allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by convincing a victim to open a specially crafted archive file. The flaw stems from insufficient validation during extraction, allowing directory traversal sequences to be embedded in archive entries. Exploitation requires user interaction and can lead to full system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143777</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aviatrix Cloud Controller Flaw Enables Remote Code Execution via Authentication Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/aviatrix-cloud-controller-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aviatrix Controller; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2171, CVE-2025-2172; Summary: The Aviatrix Controller has two critical vulnerabilities allowing for full system compromise through authentication bypass (CVE-2025-2171) and authenticated command injection (CVE-2025-2172). Attackers can brute-force a weak password reset mechanism to gain administrative access, then inject commands to execute code with root privileges, potentially compromising connected cloud gateways and APIs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143772</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Echo Chamber Attack Breaks AI Models Using Indirect Prompts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-echo-chamber-attack-breaks-ai-models/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Large Language Models (LLMs); CVE(s): None; Summary: The Echo Chamber Attack is a sophisticated vulnerability that exposes a critical flaw in the safety mechanisms of advanced LLMs. It leverages subtle, indirect cues and multi-turn reasoning to manipulate AI models into generating harmful or policy-violating content, bypassing token-level filters and safety guardrails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notepad++ Vulnerability Allows Full System Takeover — PoC Released</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/notepad-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Notepad++; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49144; Summary: A critical privilege escalation vulnerability (CVE-2025-49144) in Notepad++ v8.8.1 enables attackers to achieve full system control through a supply-chain attack, exploiting the installer's insecure search path behavior, allowing unprivileged users to escalate privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM with minimal user interaction. Successful exploitation can grant attackers SYSTEM-level access, enabling data theft, malware installation, and pivoting to other network systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143751</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-linked Salt Typhoon Exploits Critical Cisco Vulnerability to Target Canadian Telecom</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/china-linked-salt-typhoon-exploits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2023-20198; Summary: The vulnerability, CVE-2023-20198, is exploited by the China-linked Salt Typhoon actors to breach major global telecommunications providers. This allows the attackers to access configuration files and configure GRE tunnels for long-term access and data exfiltration.

FYSA: Chinese state-sponsored threat actors are targeting edge network devices, including those from Canadian and US-based telecommunications companies, as part of a cyber espionage campaign to breach and maintain persistent access to telecom service providers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/china-linked-salt-typhoon-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT28 hackers use Signal chats to launch new malware attacks on Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apt28-hackers-use-signal-chats-to-launch-new-malware-attacks-on-ukraine/</link>
      <description>APT28, a Russian state-sponsored threat group, is using Signal chats to target government targets in Ukraine with two previously undocumented malware families named BeardShell and SlimAgent. The attacks involve phishing, macros, and memory-resident backdoors to deliver malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/apt28-hackers-use-signal-chats-to-launch-new-malware-attacks-on-ukraine/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Integrates GenAI to Counter Indirect Prompt Injection Attack Vectors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-integrates-genai-to-counter/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Gemini 2.5; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in indirect prompt injection attacks, where malicious instructions are embedded within external data sources such as emails, documents, or calendar invites. The vulnerability is addressed by Google's layered security framework, which includes advanced model hardening, proprietary content classifiers, and user-centric safeguards to prevent data exfiltration and rogue actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143694</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAC-0001 Hackers Target ICS Devices Running Windows-Based Server Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uac-0001-hackers-target-ics-devices/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather a sophisticated cyberattack targeting the information and communication system (ICS) of a central executive body. The attackers used various tools, including BEARDSHELL, SLIMAGENT, COVENANT framework, and macros to compromise the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143685</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT36 Hackers Target Indian Defense Personnel with Sophisticated Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt36-hackers-target-indian-defense-personnel/</link>
      <description>APT36, a Pakistan-based cyber espionage group, has launched a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Indian defense personnel. The campaign uses malicious PDF attachments disguised as official government documents to infiltrate sensitive defense networks and steal credentials. The malware employs advanced anti-analysis techniques, keylogging, clipboard surveillance, and browser data theft to evade detection and exfiltrate sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143703</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1inch rolls out expanded bug bounties with rewards up to $500K</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/1inch-rolls-out-expanded-bug-bounties-with-rewards-up-to-500k/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a specific vulnerability but rather announces five dedicated bug bounty programs launched by 1inch, a leading DeFi aggregator. The programs aim to strengthen the platform's security and resilience across its smart contracts, wallet, dApp, developer tools, and infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143744</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian telecom hacked by suspected China state group</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/suspected-china-state-hackers-exploited-patched-flaw-to-breach-canadian-telecom/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco; CVE(s): CVE-2023-20198, CVE-2018-0171, CVE-2023-20273, CVE-2024-20399; Summary: Attackers exploited multiple previously patched vulnerabilities, including CVE-2023-20198, to compromise network devices operated by a Canadian telecom company. The hackers retrieved running configuration files and modified one file to create an aGRE tunnel for traffic collection from the internal network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/suspected-china-state-hackers-exploited-patched-flaw-to-breach-canadian-telecom/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RapperBot Targets DVRs to Hijack Surveillance Cameras and Record Video</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rapperbot-targets-dvrs-to-hijack-surveillance-cameras/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): RapperBot variant; Summary: A Mirai variant, RapperBot, targets Digital Video Recorders (DVRs) by exploiting inherent vulnerabilities such as weak default passwords, open ports, and infrequent firmware updates. It uses a multi-pronged approach to compromise DVRs, including brute force login attacks, exploiting known CVEs, and zero-day vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143679</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Vector Malware Uses SVG Images to Deliver AsyncRAT and RemcosRAT Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/shadow-vector-malware-uses-svg-images/</link>
      <description>A malicious campaign called "Shadow Vector" is targeting Colombian users by sending phishing emails with SVG attachments that mimic official legal documents. The attack vector uses embedded links to download a ZIP archive containing malicious DLLs and ultimately deploys remote access tools (RATs) such as AsyncRAT and RemcosRAT, enabling keylogging, credential theft, and full remote control of compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143671</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware on Google Play, Apple App Store stole your photos—and crypto</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malware-on-google-play-app-store-stole-your-photos-and-crypto/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various mobile apps on Google Play and Apple App Store; CVE(s): None; Summary: SparkKitty is a new mobile crypto-stealing malware that targets Android and iOS devices, stealing images from infected device's photo gallery to obtain cryptocurrency wallet recovery phrases. The malware spreads through official app stores and unofficial platforms, with identified malicious apps such as 币coin on Apple App Store and SOEX on Google Play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malware-on-google-play-app-store-stole-your-photos-and-crypto/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Homeland Security warns of escalating Iranian cyberattack risks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-homeland-security-warns-of-escalating-iranian-cyberattack-risks/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Homeland Security (DHS) issued a National Terrorism Advisory System bulletin warning about escalating cyberattack risks from Iran-backed hacking groups and pro-Iranian hacktivists, citing the ongoing conflict as a "heightened threat environment" with potential violent extremism and attacks on networks in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-homeland-security-warns-of-escalating-iranian-cyberattack-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo Chamber Jailbreak Tricks LLMs Like OpenAI and Google into Generating Harmful Content</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/echo-chamber-jailbreak-tricks-llms-like.html</link>
      <description>A new jailbreaking method called Echo Chamber can be used to trick large language models (LLMs) into generating undesirable responses. The attack uses indirect references and multi-step inference to manipulate the model's internal state, allowing for high success rates with little technical expertise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/echo-chamber-jailbreak-tricks-llms-like.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada says Salt Typhoon hacked telecom firm via Cisco flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canada-says-salt-typhoon-hacked-telecom-firm-via-cisco-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco IOS XE; CVE(s): CVE-2023-20198; Summary: The Chinese state-sponsored "Salt Typhoon" hacking group exploited a critical vulnerability (CVE-2023-20198) in February 2025, allowing remote attackers to create arbitrary accounts and gain admin-level privileges. This was the same vulnerability that had been previously exploited as a zero-day in October 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/canada-says-salt-typhoon-hacked-telecom-firm-via-cisco-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Warns Pro-Iranian Hackers Likely to Target U.S. Networks After Iranian Nuclear Strikes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/dhs-warns-pro-iranian-hackers-likely-to.html</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist groups are likely to target US networks after the US launched airstrikes on Iranian nuclear sites. The Department of Homeland Security warns of a "heightened threat environment" and notes that both hacktivists and Iranian government-affiliated actors may conduct attacks against US networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/dhs-warns-pro-iranian-hackers-likely-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revil ransomware members released after time served on carding charges</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/revil-hackers-released-after-time-served-on-carding-charges/</link>
      <description>Four REvil ransomware members arrested in January 2022 were released by Russia on time served after they pleaded guilty to carding and malware distribution charges. The defendants were part of a group of eight members of the REvil ransomware operation apprehended by Russian authorities more than three years ago, with some being sentenced to over 4 years in prison for illegal circulation of means of payment and distributing malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/revil-hackers-released-after-time-served-on-carding-charges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McLaren Health Care Data Breach Exposes Personal Information of 743,000 Individuals</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mclaren-health-care-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A data breach at McLaren Health Care compromised personal information of 743,131 individuals, including 25 residents of Maine. The breach occurred on July 17, 2024, and was discovered on August 5, 2024. The incident highlights the growing threat of cyberattacks targeting the healthcare sector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143655</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-414: Ruby WEBrick read_header HTTP Request Smuggling Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-414/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ruby WEBrick; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6442; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests on affected installations of Ruby WEBrick when deployed behind an HTTP proxy. The issue results from inconsistent parsing of terminators of HTTP headers in the read_headers method, which can be exploited to smuggle arbitrary HTTP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-21876</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-415: ServiceStack GetErrorResponse Improper Input Validation NTLM Relay Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-415/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6444; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to relay NTLM credentials on affected installations of ServiceStack. The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the GetErrorResponse method, resulting from improper input validation, which can lead to a type confusion condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25834</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-416: ServiceStack FindType Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-416/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceStack; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6445; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ServiceStack. It exists within the implementation of the FindType method, which lacks proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25837</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparkKitty Targets iOS and Android Devices via App Store and Google Play Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sparkkitty-targets-ios-and-android-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unknown; CVE(s): None; Summary: SparkKitty is a sophisticated spyware campaign that targets both iOS and Android users, infiltrating official app stores like Google Play and the App Store. The malware steals sensitive data, primarily images from device galleries, by exploiting user trust and using various technical strategies to compromise devices across platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143617</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McLaren Health Care says data breach impacts 743,000 patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mclaren-health-care-says-data-breach-impacts-743-000-patients/</link>
      <description>McLaren Health Care suffered a data breach caused by the INC ransomware gang, affecting 743,000 patients. The attack was discovered on August 5, 2024, but forensic investigations determining who was impacted were only completed on May 5, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mclaren-health-care-says-data-breach-impacts-743-000-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDoS Attack on Financial Sector Triggers Multi-Day Service Outages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ddos-attack-on-financial-sector/</link>
      <description>Financial institutions are increasingly targeted by sophisticated Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks, which exploit complex vulnerabilities in digital infrastructures and APIs. Threat actors employ advanced tactics to mimic legitimate user behavior, making detection and mitigation harder. The DDoS Maturity Model, introduced by FS-ISAC and Akamai, helps organizations assess their cyber maturity and prioritize investments in cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143576</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Weaponize GitHub Infrastructure to Distribute Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-weaponize-github-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated spearphishing campaign orchestrated by the North Korean threat group Kimsuky has been discovered, leveraging GitHub as a critical piece of attack infrastructure to distribute malware. The attackers use hardcoded GitHub Personal Access Tokens (PATs) with repository scope in the malware, granting read and write access to private repositories used as command and control (C&amp;C) infrastructure for storing malware, decoy files, and exfiltrated victim data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143594</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confucius Hackers Target Government and Military Entities Using WooperStealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/confucius-hackers-target-government-and-military-entities/</link>
      <description>Confucius hacking organization has been detected using a modular backdoor named "anondoor" paired with WooperStealer malware to target critical domestic units and industries in South and East Asia. The anondoor backdoor collects system information, downloads additional malicious components, and communicates with the command-and-control server using parameterized requests and custom delimiters, making tracing and defense challenging for security teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143569</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Teleport Vulnerability Allows Remote Authentication Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-teleport-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Teleport; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49825; Summary: The vulnerability in Teleport enables remote attackers to bypass authentication controls, potentially granting unauthorized access to sensitive systems. It affects versions up to 17.5.1 and earlier major releases, impacting self-hosted and cloud deployments, particularly those running Teleport SSH agents, OpenSSH-integrated deployments, and Teleport Git proxy setups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143653</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDigo Malware Exploits Windows LNK Flaw in Eastern European Government Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/xdigo-malware-exploits-windows-lnk-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): ZDI-CAN-25373; Summary: A remote code execution flaw in Microsoft Windows can be triggered when processing specially crafted LNK files. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the current user, and has been observed being used as part of a multi-stage procedure to deploy malware targeting government agencies in Eastern Europe and the Balkans.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/xdigo-malware-exploits-windows-lnk-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlueNoroff Hackers Exploit Zoom App to Deploy Infostealer Malware in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bluenoroff-hackers-exploit-zoom-app-to-deploy-infostealer-malware/</link>
      <description>The BlueNoroff threat actor group has launched a targeted social engineering campaign against a Canadian online gambling provider, using Zoom platform impersonation and spoofed domains to deploy infostealer malware, compromising sensitive data including user credentials and browser profiles. The attack chain involved technical finesse, psychological manipulation, and the use of anti-forensic techniques to minimize the attacker's footprint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143560</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel giant Nucor confirms hackers stole data in recent breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-confirms-hackers-stole-data-in-recent-breach/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation, North America's largest steel producer and recycler, has confirmed a recent cybersecurity incident where attackers stole data from the company's network. The incident led to the temporary shutdown of some systems and production operations at various facilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-confirms-hackers-stole-data-in-recent-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCSC Issues Alert on ‘UMBRELLA STAND’ Malware Targeting Fortinet FortiGate Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ncsc-issues-alert-on-umbrella-stand-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiGate 100D series firewalls; CVE(s): None; Summary: The UMBRELLA STAND malware targets internet-facing FortiGate 100D series firewalls to establish long-term access to compromised networks. It features advanced capabilities such as remote shell execution, configurable beacon frequencies, and AES-encrypted communications with its command-and-control server, posing a significant threat to organizations relying on these embedded devices for network security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143547</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux-Based Firewall IPFire 2.29 Rolls Out Update 194 with Improved VPN Features</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/linux-based-firewall-ipfire-2-29-194-with-improved-vpn-features/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of IPFire 2.29 – Core Update 194, which brings native support for WireGuard VPN protocol, security enhancements, and package updates. The update aims to improve the firewall's performance, security, and usability, making it more accessible to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143614</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Enhances Defender for Office 365 with Detailed Spam and Phishing Analysis</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-enhances-defender-for-office-365-with-detailed-spam-and-phishing-analysis/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a significant upgrade to Microsoft Defender for Office 365, introducing AI-powered capabilities to provide clear explanations for email submission results. The new feature aims to enhance transparency, improve incident response, and boost user trust by making threat detection reasoning more accessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143604</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI-Enabled Workflow Automation Can Help SOCs Reduce Burnout</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-ai-enabled-workflow-automation-can.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the challenges faced by Security Operations Center (SOC) analysts, including burnout, tooling fragmentation, and lack of growth opportunities. It highlights the potential benefits of artificial intelligence (AI) in alleviating these issues, such as streamlining workflows, providing real-time feedback, and enabling adaptive automation. The article also emphasizes the importance of targeted support for SOC leaders to reduce burnout and improve team culture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/how-ai-enabled-workflow-automation-can.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel Giant Nucor Suffers Cyberattack, IT Systems Breached</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/steel-giant-nucor-suffers-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation suffered a significant cybersecurity breach that disrupted operations across multiple facilities, leading to the theft of limited company data. The incident involved unauthorized access to its information technology (IT) systems, and the attacker exfiltrated "limited data" before being prevented from further accessing the systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143586</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Reduces Windows 11 24H2 Restore Point Retention from 90 to 60 Days</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-reduces-windows-11-24h2-restore-point-retention/</link>
      <description>The article discusses changes to System Restore in Windows 11 version 24H2, specifically reducing the retention period of restore points from 90 days to 60 days. This change aims to balance storage usage and system reliability while providing a clear and predictable window for recovery. The update also includes security improvements, feature updates, and resolves recurring issues with Windows Hello for Business and Noto fonts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143584</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Allegedly Selling Intelbras Router 0-Day Exploit on Dark Web Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-allegedly-selling-intelbras-router-0-day-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intelbras routers; CVE(s): None; Summary: A previously unknown exploit targeting Intelbras routers has been put up for sale on dark web forums, allowing attackers to gain remote access or control over affected devices. The exact vulnerability remains undisclosed, but the exploit can be used to compromise routers remotely, potentially impacting consumers and organizations relying on these devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143583</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Adds Multi-Layered Defenses to Secure GenAI from Prompt Injection Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-adds-multi-layered-defenses-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article discusses various safety measures implemented by Google to mitigate emerging attack vectors on its generative AI systems, specifically indirect prompt injections. The measures include model hardening, machine learning models, and system-level safeguards, as well as additional guardrails such as content classifiers, spotlighting, and user confirmation frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-adds-multi-layered-defenses-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Root Exploit, Oracle EBS Flaw, Crypto Logins, and Cisco Access Posted for Sale</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/android-root-oracle-ebs-flaws-crypto-logins-cisco-access-sale/</link>
      <description>The article reports on various listings found on underground forums offering high-value exploits, access credentials, and corporate network access. Specifically, it mentions alleged zero-day vulnerabilities targeting Android and Oracle E-Business Suite, as well as a massive cache of login credentials linked to cryptocurrency users and unauthorized Cisco system access for a German electronics company.

FYSA: The article highlights the continued interest of threat actors in targeting both infrastructure and user-level assets across industries, with listings offering high-value exploits and sensitive information for sale on underground forums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061172</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Chrome 0-Day, 7.3 Tbps DDoS, MFA Bypass Tricks, Banking Trojan and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-73-tbps-ddos.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article presents a collection of cybersecurity-related news and updates from various sources. It covers a range of topics, including data breaches, vulnerabilities, and security best practices.

Some notable points include:

* A breach at Viasat, a US satellite communications company, which was attributed to China-linked attackers.
* The discovery of over 46,000 internet-facing Grafana instances vulnerable to CVE-2025-4123.
* The use of legitimate platforms like Dropbox and Google Drive as "dead drop resolvers" by threat actors.
* A warning about the potential for AI agents to leak sensitive data without proper configuration.
* Guidance on securing Microsoft's System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM) to prevent silent domain takeover attacks.

Overall, the article provides a snapshot of current cybersecurity threats and vulnerabilities, along with practical advice on how to mitigate them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-73-tbps-ddos.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Family Safety Now Blocking All Versions of Google Chrome</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-family-safety-blocking-of-google-chrome/</link>
      <description>Microsoft's Family Safety feature is blocking all versions of Google Chrome from launching on Windows devices due to a bug in the feature. The issue affects only Chrome, while other browsers like Edge, Firefox, and Opera remain unaffected. The root cause is a bug in Microsoft's Family Safety feature, which prevents Chrome from running when enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143552</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former JBLM Soldier Admits Attempting to Leak U.S. Military Network Details to China</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/former-jblm-soldier-leak-u-s-military-network-details-to-china/</link>
      <description>A former US Army sergeant, Joseph Daniel Schmidt, has pleaded guilty to attempting to deliver sensitive military secrets to Chinese authorities. He held classified information while serving with the 109th Military Intelligence Battalion at Joint Base Lewis-McChord and later attempted to share this information with Chinese officials, including creating and offering documents containing "high-level secrets" during his time in Hong Kong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143545</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Snipping Tool Now Lets Users Export Captures as GIFs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-snipping-tool-export-captures-as-gifs/</link>
      <description>The article discusses an update to Microsoft's Snipping Tool that allows users to export screen recordings as animated GIFs. This feature aims to streamline the process of creating and sharing dynamic visual content, which can be particularly useful for remote work environments. The update is currently available in the Canary and Dev Channels for Windows 11 Insiders, with a broader rollout expected in the near future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143537</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Flaws Expose AWS Credentials and Enable Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/amazon-eks-flaws-expose-aws-credentials/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS); CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses vulnerabilities in Amazon EKS that could expose sensitive AWS credentials and enable privilege escalation. Misconfigurations and excessive container privileges allow attackers to intercept plaintext credentials, capture AWS credentials using standard tools like tcpdump, or spoof APIs to harvest authorization tokens and obtain valid AWS credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143530</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Meshtastic Flaw Allows Attackers to Decrypt Private Messages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-meshtastic-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Meshtastic; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52464; Summary: A severe cryptographic vulnerability in the Meshtastic project allows attackers to decrypt private messages and hijack nodes across LoRa mesh networks. The vulnerability stems from duplicated encryption keys and insufficient randomness during key generation, affecting multiple hardware platforms and posing significant risks to users relying on Meshtastic for secure off-grid communication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143527</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinMarketCap Doodle Image Vulnerability Lets Attackers Run Malicious Code via API Call</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coinmarketcap-doodle-image-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CoinMarketCap; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in a doodle image featured on CoinMarketCap's homepage allowed threat actors to inject malicious code, leading to a phishing campaign targeting user wallets. The exploit delivered a tampered JSON payload that embedded unauthorized JavaScript into the site's front end, prompting users to "Verify Wallet" and gain access to their crypto holdings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143523</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinMarketCap briefly hacked to drain crypto wallets via fake Web3 popup</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinmarketcap-briefly-hacked-to-drain-crypto-wallets-via-fake-web3-popup/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CoinMarketCap; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply chain attack was used to inject a malicious script into CoinMarketCap's website, which drained cryptocurrency from visitors' wallets when they connected them. The attack exploited a vulnerability in the site's "doodle" image and was executed through an API call, resulting in the execution of a wallet drainer script that stole assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinmarketcap-briefly-hacked-to-drain-crypto-wallets-via-fake-web3-popup/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 21:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford City Council suffers breach exposing two decades of data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oxford-city-council-suffers-breach-exposing-two-decades-of-data/</link>
      <description>Oxford City Council suffered a data breach where attackers accessed personally identifiable information from legacy systems, affecting former and current Council officers' data between 2001 and 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/oxford-city-council-suffers-breach-exposing-two-decades-of-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Snipping Tool now lets you create animated GIF recordings</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-snipping-tool-now-lets-you-create-animated-gif-recordings/</link>
      <description>The article discusses updates to Microsoft's Snipping Tool utility, including the addition of GIF export for screen recordings. It also mentions other recent features added to Snipping Tool, such as a Text Extractor and draw &amp; hold capabilities. There is no mention of vulnerabilities or cybersecurity-related threats in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-snipping-tool-now-lets-you-create-animated-gif-recordings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 14:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar Repair For Outlook: A Comprehensive Review Of The Ultimate PST Repair Tool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/stellar-repair-for-outlook/</link>
      <description>The article reviews Stellar Repair for Outlook, a software designed to repair and recover corrupted Outlook PST files. It highlights the causes of PST file corruption, such as oversized files, improper shutdowns, malware attacks, and storage device issues. The review provides an in-depth evaluation of the software's features, performance, and usability, including its ability to handle large PST files, selective recovery, and export options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=142783</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenVPN Driver Vulnerability Let Attackers Crash Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/openvpn-driver-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenVPN; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50054; Summary: The OpenVPN 2.7_alpha2 release addresses a critical vulnerability in the Windows driver (CVE-2025-50054) that could allow attackers to crash systems, emphasizing the importance of timely updates and rigorous testing before deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143447</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli Social Media Users Targeted in Covert Iranian Influence Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/israeli-social-media-users-targeted-in-covert/</link>
      <description>A covert Iranian social media operation has been uncovered, targeting Israeli users on platform X with a psychological campaign designed to sow discord and despair. The operation uses AI tools like ChatGPT for translation and recommends account naming conventions to enhance authenticity. The campaign's technical sophistication allows it to evade detection by moderation systems, making it difficult to detect using traditional automated detection methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143440</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattermost Vulnerabilities Let Attackers Execute Remote Code Via Path Traversal</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mattermost-vulnerabilities-let-attackers-execute-remote-code/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mattermost; CVE(s): None; Summary: Mattermost has disclosed critical path traversal vulnerabilities that could allow attackers to execute remote code. The flaws can be exploited to access restricted directories and files, potentially compromising sensitive data or disrupting operations. The company urges users to prioritize upgrading to the latest fixed versions to safeguard their environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143433</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac Cyber Attack – Hackers May Have Stolen Personal And Health Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-may-have-stolen-personal-and-health-information/</link>
      <description>Unauthorized access was detected in Aflac Incorporated's network infrastructure, potentially exposing sensitive personal and health information. The incident did not involve ransomware, but the company is conducting a comprehensive review to assess the full extent of the breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143418</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberWarfare on the Rise With Surge in Hacktivist Activity Following Israel-Iran</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberwarfare-on-the-rise-with-surge-in-hacktivist/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the escalation of cyber operations between Israel and Iran in the context of their military conflict. Israeli-linked group Gonjeshke Darande (Predatory Sparrow) executed high-impact strikes on Iranian infrastructure, while Iran has responded with psychological warfare, hacktivist activities, disinformation campaigns, and propaganda efforts. The article highlights the blurring of lines between state cyberattacks, hacktivist disruptions, and influence campaigns, posing risks to critical infrastructure and global businesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143465</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuckDuckGo Browser’s Scam Blocker to Guard Against Phishing and Malware Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/duckduckgo-browsers-scam-blocker-to-guard/</link>
      <description>DuckDuckGo has updated its browser's Scam Blocker feature to provide advanced protection against online threats, including phishing sites, malware, and sophisticated scams. The new feature is integrated into the browser for desktop and mobile platforms and offers real-time protection without compromising user privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143424</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Directories Exposes Publically Available tools Used by Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/open-directories-exposes-publically-available-tools/</link>
      <description>A series of misconfigured web servers have been uncovered, revealing a treasure trove of publicly accessible tools and tactics employed by malicious actors targeting critical infrastructure. The findings show the technical prowess and intent behind these operations, which extend beyond Taiwan to other regions and institutions. The use of open-source offensive software, such as Afrog, Brute Ratel C4, and OneForAll, suggests a reliance on readily available tools for reconnaissance and attack planning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143453</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in XSS Cyberattacks Targets Popular Webmail Platforms, ESET Reports</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surge-in-xss-cyberattacks-targets-popular-webmail-platforms/</link>
      <description>The Russia-aligned Sednit group has been conducting a sophisticated cyber espionage campaign, dubbed Operation RoundPress, targeting high-value webmail platforms through cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. The operation compromises popular webmail services, stealing credentials, exfiltrating email content, and bypassing two-factor authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143412</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Announces New Graph Powered Detection of Hybrid Attack Targeting Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-announces-new-graph-powered-detection/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has unveiled an innovative approach to detecting hybrid attacks that span on-premises and cloud environments. The Enterprise Exposure Graph provides contextual enrichment and enables Security Operations Center (SOC) teams to detect and respond to multi-faceted threats with unprecedented precision, addressing critical blind spots in traditional security frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143404</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hacktivist Attacking Israeli Military, Government, and Infrastructure Targets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hacktivist-attacking-israeli/</link>
      <description>Pro-Iranian hacktivist organizations launched a coordinated attack on Israeli military, government, and infrastructure targets, using tactics such as DDoS attacks, website defacements, and data breaches. The pro-Israeli groups responded with targeted infrastructure attacks against Iranian nuclear facilities and military assets, highlighting a significant imbalance in the ongoing digital conflict between the two nations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143396</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac Hit by Cyberattack: What You Need to Know About the Breach</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/aflac-cyberattack-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aflac; CVE(s): None; Summary: Aflac suffered a significant cybersecurity breach caused by social engineering tactics, resulting in unauthorized access to sensitive information on its network. The attackers accessed a range of Personally Identifiable Information (PII), including health insurance claims and medical-related data, Social Security numbers, and personal data associated with customers, beneficiaries, employees, agents, and potentially other individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061161</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 16:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian hackers bypass Gmail MFA using stolen app passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-bypass-gmail-mfa-using-stolen-app-passwords/</link>
      <description>Russian hackers bypassed multi-factor authentication and accessed Gmail accounts by leveraging app-specific passwords in advanced social engineering attacks that impersonated U.S. Department of State officials. The attackers used meticulously developed phishing messages, fake identities, and various materials to deceive victims into creating and sharing app-specific passwords, allowing the hackers full access to their Google accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-hackers-bypass-gmail-mfa-using-stolen-app-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Motors theme flaw mass-exploited to hijack admin accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-motors-theme-flaw-mass-exploited-to-hijack-admin-accounts/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The WordPress theme "Motors" contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to change administrator passwords, granting complete control of the targeted site. The flaw arises from improper user identity validation during password updating and affects all versions before and including 5.6.67.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-motors-theme-flaw-mass-exploited-to-hijack-admin-accounts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Behind Cyberattacks on M&amp;S and Co-op, Causing Up to $592M in Damages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/scattered-spider-behind-cyberattacks-on.html</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather a cyber attack on UK retailers Marks &amp; Spencer and Co-op. The attacks were classified as a single combined cyber event by the Cyber Monitoring Centre (CMC), with an estimated financial impact of £270-440 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/scattered-spider-behind-cyberattacks-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target 700+ ComfyUI AI Image Generation Servers to Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-700-comfyui-ai-image-generation-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ComfyUI; CVE(s): None; Summary: Critical vulnerabilities in ComfyUI have been exploited by hacker groups, compromising at least 695 servers worldwide. The flaws allow attackers to steal sensitive AI-related data, execute remote commands, and establish reverse shell access, posing a significant risk of network intrusions and data breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143372</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack Disrupts Russian Dairy Supply Chain by Targeting Animal Certification System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattack-disrupts-russian-dairy-supply-chain/</link>
      <description>A suspected cyberattack has targeted Russia's national veterinary certification system (Mercury), forcing it into emergency operation mode. The attack has halted normal operations, prompting authorities to implement contingency measures to maintain the flow of goods while restoration efforts are underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143317</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prometei Botnet Targets Linux Servers for Cryptocurrency Mining Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/prometei-botnet-targets-linux-servers/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a renewed wave of attacks by the Prometei botnet targeting Linux servers. The malware has advanced capabilities such as a backdoor for remote control, DGA for resilient C2 infrastructure, and self-updating mechanisms to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143326</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of Weaponized MSI Installer Masquerading as WhatsApp to Deliver XWorm RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-weaponized-msi-installer-masquerading-as-whatsapp/</link>
      <description>A China-based threat actor is targeting users across East and Southeast Asia with a trojanized MSI installer disguised as a legitimate WhatsApp setup file. The installer delivers a customized version of the XWorm Remote Access Trojan (RAT), which can steal sensitive data, maintain persistent access for attackers, and detect Telegram installations on compromised devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143293</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocha Manakin Uses Paste-and-Run Technique to Deceive Users into Downloading Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mocha-manakin-uses-paste-and-run-technique-to-deceive-users/</link>
      <description>Mocha Manakin is a malicious campaign using the "paste-and-run" technique to trick users into executing harmful scripts. The campaign employs sophisticated social engineering lures, exploiting digital conditioning to prompt users to copy and paste obfuscated PowerShell commands, which download malicious payloads from adversary-controlled infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143334</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Manipulate Google Search Results to Display Scammer’s Phone Number Instead of Real Number</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-manipulate-google-search-results/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are exploiting trust in sponsored search results to orchestrate scams, targeting popular brands and tech support services. They manipulate search engine results to display fake contact numbers and redirect users to malicious sites or fraudulent phone numbers, leading to financial losses, identity theft, and potential malware infections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143301</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record DDoS pummels site with once-unimaginable 7.3Tbps of junk traffic</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/record-ddos-pummels-site-with-once-unimaginable-7-3tbps-of-junk-traffic/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of reflection attacks in a record-breaking DDoS attack. Reflection attacks direct malicious traffic to third-party intermediaries, making it harder for targets to defend against the attack. The attack exploited various amplification vectors, including Network Time Protocol, Quote of the Day Protocol, Echo Protocol, and Portmapper services, as well as Mirai-based botnets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/06/record-ddos-pummels-site-with-once-unimaginable-7-3tbps-of-junk-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insomnia API Client Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary Code Execution via Template Injection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/insomnia-api-client-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Insomnia API Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1087; Summary: The Insomnia API Client has a severe security vulnerability allowing for arbitrary code execution through Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) due to its use of the Nunjucks templating engine. The flaw persists in version 11.2.0 and can be exploited via multiple vectors, including imported collection files, pasted data, server-provided cookies, and HTTP responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143308</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Vercel Hosting Platform to Distribute Remote Access Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-vercel-hosting-platform/</link>
      <description>CyberArmor has uncovered a sophisticated phishing campaign exploiting Vercel, a frontend hosting platform, to distribute a malicious variant of LogMeIn. The campaign targeted over 1,271 users with deceptive emails leading to fraudulent pages hosted on Vercel subdomains, tricking victims into downloading and installing the malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143286</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitoPro exchange links Lazarus hackers to $11 million crypto heist</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitopro-exchange-links-lazarus-hackers-to-11-million-crypto-heist/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cyberattack on Taiwanese cryptocurrency exchange BitoPro, allegedly carried out by the North Korean hacking group Lazarus. The attackers stole approximately $11 million worth of cryptocurrency and laundered it through decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and mixers. The incident involved social engineering, malware, and hijacked AWS session tokens to bypass multi-factor authentication (MFA).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitopro-exchange-links-lazarus-hackers-to-11-million-crypto-heist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TxTag Phishing Campaign Exploits .gov Domain to Deceive Employees</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/txtag-phishing-campaign-exploits-gov-domain/</link>
      <description>A new phishing campaign has emerged, using the credibility of a .gov domain to deceive employees into believing they owe unpaid tolls. The attack leverages the GovDelivery system and uses psychological manipulation, combined with technical deception, to maximize its impact. The campaign targets employees' personal data and corporate reputation, posing risks that traditional perimeter defenses often fail to detect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143269</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Loaders Use In-Memory Execution to Evade Disk-Based Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/powershell-loaders-use-in-memory-execution/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated PowerShell script named y1.ps1 has been discovered hosted in an open directory on a Chinese server. The script operates as a shellcode loader, employing advanced in-memory execution techniques to bypass traditional detection mechanisms. It uses various evasion techniques, including API hashing and forged User-Agent strings, to evade network monitoring and antivirus solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143261</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft investigates OneDrive bug that breaks file search</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft OneDrive; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some OneDrive users are experiencing blank search results or no results at all, even when searching for files they know exist. The issue affects a subset of users across most OneDrive platforms and there is currently no known workaround or estimated timeline for a fix.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-investigates-onedrive-bug-that-breaks-file-search/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Ransomware Adds "Call Lawyer" Feature to Pressure Victims for Larger Ransoms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/qilin-ransomware-adds-call-lawyer.html</link>
      <description>Qilin ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) scheme is intensifying its activity, offering legal counsel for affiliates to put pressure on victims to pay up. The group's affiliate panel now includes features like "Call Lawyer" and spam services, positioning itself as a full-service cybercrime platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/qilin-ransomware-adds-call-lawyer.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare blocks record 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack against hosting provider</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</link>
      <description>Cloudflare mitigated a record-breaking distributed denial of service (DDoS) attack in May 2025 that peaked at 7.3 Tbps, targeting a hosting provider. The attack used multiple vectors, including UDP floods, QOTD reflection, Echo reflection, NTP amplification, Mirai botnet UDP flood, Portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification, each exploiting legacy or poorly configured services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-blocks-record-73-tbps-ddos-attack-against-hosting-provider/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aflac discloses breach amidst Scattered Spider insurance attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aflac; CVE(s): None; Summary: The systems of American insurance giant Aflac were breached by a sophisticated cybercrime group, potentially stealing personal and health information. The attack shows signs of being carried out by Scattered Spider, a group known for their social engineering attacks against high-profile organizations worldwide.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, so no CVEs are listed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/aflac-discloses-breach-amidst-scattered-spider-insurance-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can users reset their own passwords without sacrificing security?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the benefits of self-service password reset (SSPR) solutions in reducing helpdesk load, costs, and improving productivity. It highlights the importance of proper security considerations when implementing an SSPR solution, including strong identity verification measures and multi-factor authentication (MFA). The article also emphasizes the need for a user-friendly experience to promote adoption and minimize abandonment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/can-users-reset-their-own-passwords-without-sacrificing-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive DDoS Attack Hits 7.3 Tbps Delivering 37.4 Terabytes in 45 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-ddos-attack-hits-7-3-tbps/</link>
      <description>A massive distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack peaked at 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps), overwhelming its target with 37.4 terabytes of data in just 45 seconds, targeting an unnamed hosting provider that relied on Cloudflare's Magic Transit service for network defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143273</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft to remove legacy drivers from Windows Update for security boost</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a specific vulnerability, but rather discusses Microsoft's plan to periodically remove legacy drivers from the Windows Update catalog to mitigate security and compatibility risks. The company aims to ensure the optimal set of drivers on Windows Update while maintaining its security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-to-remove-legacy-drivers-from-windows-update-for-security-boost/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Misconfiguration Lets Attackers Take Over Cloud Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/azure-misconfiguration-take-over-cloud-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): None; Summary: A chain of misconfigurations in Microsoft Azure allows attackers to gain complete control over an organization's cloud infrastructure, from initial access to full tenant takeover. The attack path involves unauthenticated reconnaissance, exploiting public storage accounts, and leveraging dynamic group membership rules to achieve privilege escalation and lateral movement, ultimately leading to total ownership of the Azure environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143248</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's State TV Hijacked Mid-Broadcast Amid Geopolitical Tensions; $90M Stolen in Crypto Heist</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</link>
      <description>Iran's state-owned TV broadcaster was hacked to air videos calling for street protests against the Iranian government, while Israel accused Iran of launching cyber attacks. The incident is part of a larger cyber war between Israel and Iran that has been ongoing for over a decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/irans-state-tv-hijacked-mid-broadcast.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AntiDot 3-in-1 Android Botnet Malware Grants Attackers Full Control Over Victim Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/antidot-3-in-1-android-botnet-malware-grants-attackers/</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a new Android botnet malware that grants cybercriminals control over infected devices. It has advanced capabilities such as screen recording, SMS interception, and credential theft through overlay attacks. The malware operates through at least 11 active command-and-control (C2) servers, managing over 3,775 infected devices across 273 distinct campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143233</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford City Council Hit by Cyberattack Exposing Employee Personal Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oxford-city-council-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Oxford City Council's network was targeted by a sophisticated cyberattack that exposed personal data of employees involved in council-administered elections over the past two decades. The attack allowed attackers to access historic data stored on legacy systems, affecting current and former council officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143245</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versa Director Flaws Let Attackers Execute Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/versa-director-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Versa Networks' SD-WAN orchestration platform, Versa Director; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23171, CVE-2025-23172; Summary: Authenticated attackers can upload malicious files and execute arbitrary commands on affected systems due to insecure file upload and webhook functionalities. The first flaw allows remote code execution (RCE) if a webshell is uploaded and accessed, while the second vulnerability enables authenticated users to execute commands as the "versa" user with sudo privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143238</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GodFather Android Malware Uses On-Device Virtualization to Hijack Legitimate Banking Apps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/godfather-android-malware-uses-on-device-virtualization/</link>
      <description>The GodFather Android banking malware creates a fully isolated virtual environment on the victim's device, enabling attackers to monitor and manipulate user interactions in real-time. It employs a malicious "host" application that downloads and runs a copy of the targeted app within a controlled sandbox, capturing credentials and sensitive information with precision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143210</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-411: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 DPAX File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-411/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47728; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPAX files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26167</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-412: Fuji Electric Smart Editor  X1 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-412/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor X1; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41413; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Smart Editor by writing past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26031</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-413: Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 File Parsing Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-413/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fuji Electric Smart Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41388; Summary: The Fuji Electric Smart Editor TL5 file parsing stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the processing of TL5 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26018</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgence of the Prometei Botnet</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/prometei-botnet-2025-activity/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Prometei Linux Botnet; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Prometei malware family, which includes both Linux and Windows variants, allows attackers to remotely control compromised systems for cryptocurrency mining (particularly Monero) and credential theft. The latest versions feature a backdoor that enables a variety of malicious activities, including brute-forcing administrator credentials, exploiting vulnerabilities, and self-updating features for stealth and evasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=143713</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps to 24/7 In-House SOC Success</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors often target businesses during off-hours when security personnel are fewer or not present. A 24/7 Security Operations Center (SOC) can provide real-time threat detection and resolution, but requires a perfect balance of proven processes, advanced tools, and skilled professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/6-steps-to-247-in-house-soc-success.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Billion Password Leak, Not New, Still Dangerous: What You Need to Know?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/16-billion-password-leak-not-new-still-dangerous/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the exposure of 16 billion login credentials collected by infostealer malware over several years. The data includes usernames, passwords, cookies, tokens, and other sensitive information from various services like Google, Facebook, Apple, Microsoft, Telegram, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061153</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 7.3 Tbps DDoS Attack Delivers 37.4 TB in 45 Seconds, Targeting Hosting Provider</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</link>
      <description>Cloudflare reported blocking a 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack, targeting an unnamed hosting provider, which used a combination of UDP flood, QOTD reflection attack, echo reflection attack, NTP reflection attack, Mirai UDP flood attack, portmap flood, and RIPv1 amplification attack. The attack originated from over 122,145 source IP addresses across 161 countries, with the largest portions coming from Brazil, Vietnam, Taiwan, China, Indonesia, Ukraine, Ecuador, Thailand, the United States, and Saudi Arabia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/massive-73-tbps-ddos-attack-delivers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Introduces Enhanced Security Defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-introduces-enhanced-security-defaults-for-windows-365/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing new secure-by-default capabilities for Windows 365 Cloud PCs to fortify virtual desktop environments against modern cyber threats. The update includes default disabling of device redirections (clipboard, drive, USB, and printer) and enabling advanced security controls such as virtualization-based security, Credential Guard, and hypervisor-protected code integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143202</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dover Fueling Solutions Flaw Lets Attackers Control Fueling Operations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dover-fueling-solutions-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dover Fueling Solutions' ProGauge MagLink LX consoles; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5310; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-5310, allows remote attackers to seize control of fueling operations, manipulate tank monitoring, and deploy malware, posing a severe risk to transportation systems worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143199</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 09:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 Billion Passwords Stolen From 320 Million+ Computers Leaked Online</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/16-billion-passwords-stolen-from-320-million-computers-leaked-online/</link>
      <description>A massive data breach has exposed approximately 16 billion login credentials, usernames, and passwords across various platforms, including Apple, Facebook, Google, Instagram, Telegram, GitHub, and government services. The compromised data can be used for account takeover, identity theft, targeted phishing attacks, and ransomware attacks.

FYSA: Cybercriminals have gained access to a massive dataset of login records, which can be exploited for account takeovers, identity theft, and targeted phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143181</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM QRadar SIEM Bug Lets Attackers Run Arbitrary Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-qradar-siem-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IBM Security QRadar SIEM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-33117, None (other CVEs mentioned are not explicitly linked to the vulnerability); Summary: A critical flaw in IBM's QRadar SIEM platform allows privileged users to execute arbitrary commands on affected systems, enabling attackers to compromise sensitive data or gain unauthorized access. The vulnerability has been addressed in the latest interim fix (UP12 IF02), and customers are urged to update their installations to protect against potential exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143190</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200+ Trojanized GitHub Repositories Found in Campaign Targeting Gamers and Developers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new campaign of 67 GitHub repositories claiming to offer Python-based hacking tools, but delivering trojanized payloads instead. The repositories were taken down by GitHub, and the campaign is believed to target users searching for software such as account cleaning tools and game cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache SeaTunnel Flaw Lets Unauthorized Users Launch Deserialization Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-seatunnel-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache SeaTunnel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32896; Summary: The Apache SeaTunnel vulnerability (CVE-2025-32896) allows unauthorized users to exploit insecure REST API endpoints, enabling arbitrary file read and potentially remote code execution through deserialization attacks. This affects versions 2.3.1-2.3.10 and has been classified as moderate to critical in severity, depending on deployment context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143186</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Wall Connector Hacked Through Charging Port in Just 18 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tesla-wall-connector-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tesla Wall Connector; CVE(s): None; Summary: Security researchers from Synacktiv successfully hacked the Tesla Wall Connector through its charging port in just 18 minutes, exposing critical vulnerabilities in the device's firmware and communication protocols. The attack involved downgrading the Wall Connector's firmware to an older version with exposed debug features, including a TCP debug shell accessible over Wi-Fi, and exploiting a global buffer overflow in the shell's command parsing logic for code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143172</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Support Tickets Let Hackers Exploit Atlassian’s Model Context Protocol</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-support-tickets-let-hackers-exploit-atlassians-model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian Jira Service Management (JSM); CVE(s): None; Summary: A new class of cyberattack targets organizations using Atlassian's Model Context Protocol (MCP), exploiting AI-powered workflows in JSM. Malicious support tickets can be used to gain privileged access and exfiltrate sensitive data without breaching internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143168</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 05:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No, the 16 billion credentials leak is not a new data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a massive compilation of previously stolen credentials, allegedly obtained through infostealers, data breaches, and credential-stuffing attacks. The compilation was briefly exposed online, containing over 64,000 credential pairs. The article warns users to adopt good cybersecurity habits, use unique and strong passwords, enable two-factor authentication (2FA), and monitor for known breaches using services like Have I Been Pwned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/no-the-16-billion-credentials-leak-is-not-a-new-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godfather Android malware now uses virtualization to hijack banking apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Godfather Android Malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Godfather Android malware creates isolated virtual environments on mobile devices to steal account data and transactions from legitimate banking apps, using tactics such as intent spoofing, StubActivity, and API hooking. The malware displays a fake lock screen overlay to trick users into entering their PIN/passwords and can record account credentials, passwords, PINs, touch events, and capture responses from the banking backend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/godfather-android-malware-now-uses-virtualization-to-hijack-banking-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100,000 WordPress Sites Exposed to Privilege Escalation via MCP AI Engine</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-100000-wordpress-sites-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Jordy Meow AI Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5071; Summary: The AI Engine plugin has a severe vulnerability allowing authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access or higher to gain full control over the Model Context Protocol (MCP) module, enabling privilege escalation and potentially complete site compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143132</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Deploy Malware Using Weaponized Calendly and Google Meet Links</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-deploy-malware-using-weaponized-calendly/</link>
      <description>TA444, a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor group, has launched a sophisticated malware campaign targeting cryptocurrency foundations. The attack leverages weaponized Calendly links, deceptive Google Meet invitations, and deepfakes to deliver malicious payloads designed for macOS systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143141</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver Fox APT Uses Weaponized Medical Software to Deploy Remote Access Tools and Disable AV</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silver-fox-apt-uses-weaponized-medical-software/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the China-based advanced persistent threat (APT) group Silver Fox's multi-stage campaign targeting healthcare delivery organizations (HDOs) and public sector entities. The campaign uses trojanized medical software, cloud infrastructure, and a custom remote access trojan (RAT) to deploy cyber espionage and data theft operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143124</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamers Targeted! Fake Minecraft Mods Enable Attackers to Take Control of Your System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fake-minecraft-mods-enable-attackers-to-take-control/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Minecraft; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious campaign targeting Minecraft users has been discovered, using a Distribution as a Service (DaaS) platform to distribute malware disguised as legitimate mods. The malware initiates a multi-stage attack chain designed to steal sensitive data and compromise systems, exploiting the trust of gamers seeking to enhance their gaming experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143113</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android Malware Surge Hits Devices via Overlays, Virtualization Fraud and NFC Theft</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</link>
      <description>AntiDot is a financially motivated Android malware sold as a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) on underground forums, compromising over 3,775 devices across 273 unique campaigns. It features capabilities to record device screens, intercept SMS messages, extract sensitive data, conduct overlay attacks, and remotely control infected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-android-malware-surge-hits-devices.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Stolen credentials are the new front door to your network</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</link>
      <description>Credential-based attacks are becoming increasingly common, with threat actors using stolen credentials to breach networks. Infostealer malware campaigns have exploded in recent years, stealing billions of credentials and feeding a booming cybercrime marketplace. The webinar will explore how attackers are shifting from exploiting vulnerabilities to simply logging in using large-scale credential abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/webinar-stolen-credentials-are-the-new-front-door-to-your-network/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-409: RARLAB WinRAR Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-409/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RARLAB WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6218; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of RARLAB WinRAR, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists in the handling of file paths within archive files, allowing an attacker to traverse to unintended directories and execute code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27198</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-410: Allegra calculateTokenExpDate Password Recovery Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-410/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Allegra; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6216; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Allegra, with no required user interaction. The issue stems from a predictable value used in generating a password reset token within the application's password recovery mechanism, allowing attackers to exploit it and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27104</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Sam Altman discusses GPT-5 release date</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be an update about OpenAI's next big upgrade to ChatGPT, including the potential release of GPT-5 and improvements to the Operator Agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-sam-altman-discusses-gpt-5-release-date/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-tied Predatory Sparrow hackers are waging cyberwar on Iran’s financial system</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: Predatory Sparrow, a group believed to be linked to Israel's military or intelligence agencies, has been carrying out cyberattacks against Iran's critical infrastructure, including railways and gas stations. The group's recent attack on the Khouzestan steel mill caused significant physical damage. It is unclear why they have turned their attention to Iran's financial sector, but experts warn that this development may lead to more serious consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/06/israel-tied-predatory-sparrow-hackers-are-waging-cyberwar-on-irans-financial-system/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US recovers $225 million of crypto stolen in investment scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice has seized over $225 million in cryptocurrency linked to investment fraud and money laundering operations, the largest crypto seizure in the history of the U.S. Secret Service. The funds were traced using blockchain analysis and were laundered through a complex network of cryptocurrency addresses to obscure their origin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/us-recovers-225-million-of-crypto-stolen-in-investment-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Webinar: Key Insights from Verizon’s 2025 DBIR</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report (DBIR) 2025, which highlights critical trends in cybersecurity, including rising GenAI-related risks, credential theft, and vulnerabilities from third-party partners. It also emphasizes the need for enterprises to adopt an updated, integrated approach to cybersecurity and provides insights on how to strengthen security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/special-webinar-key-insights-from-verizons-2025-dbir/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Cyber Attacks Targeting Manufacturing Industry in 2025</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/major-cyber-attacks-manufacturing-industry-in-2025/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article highlights the growing threat of cyberattacks in the manufacturing sector. In 2025, the global manufacturing industry faced a surge in cyberattacks, driven by ransomware gangs, espionage-motivated actors, and supply chain vulnerabilities. The cost of these attacks is increasing rapidly, with losses rising by 125% each year. The article also explores the tactics used by attackers and the key lessons for improving industrial cybersecurity.

Note: This summary does not fit into any specific format (vulnerability or threat actor-focused) as it does not specifically discuss a vulnerability or threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061085</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft unveils new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has announced new security defaults for Windows 365 Cloud PCs, including disabling clipboard, drive, USB, and printer redirections by default to reduce risks of data theft and block malware attacks. Additionally, the company will start blocking access to SharePoint, OneDrive, and Office files via legacy authentication protocols in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-unveils-new-security-defaults-for-windows-365-cloud-pcs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jQuery Migrate Library Compromised to Steal Logins via Parrot Traffic Direction System</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jquery-migrate-library-compromised-to-steal-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: jQuery Migrate; CVE(s): None; Summary: A weaponized version of the jQuery Migrate library was used in a sophisticated malware campaign that exploited the trust in the library. The attack delivered a malicious script through a compromised Middle Eastern business website, which stole sensitive data, logged keystrokes, and deployed additional threats such as cryptocurrency miners or click-fraud scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143096</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT will analyze Gmail emails, manage schedule on Google Calendar</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability, but rather mentions the testing of integration features between ChatGPT and Gmail/Google Calendar. The feature will allow users to summarize emails and create events, and may be tied to the ChatGPT Search feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-analyze-gmail-emails-manage-schedule-on-google-calendar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Amatera Stealer Using Advanced Web Injection and Anti-Analysis Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-deploy-amatera-stealer-using-advanced-web-injection/</link>
      <description>Amatera Stealer is a rebranded information stealer malware that exhibits advanced features and stealth mechanisms. It is distributed through web injection campaigns, software cracks, and fake downloads, and can steal sensitive data from browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, email clients, and messaging apps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143084</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krispy Kreme Data Breach Exposes Customer Personal Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/krispy-kreme-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A ransomware attack on Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corporation's information technology systems exposed the personal information of over 160,000 individuals. The attackers claimed to have stolen 184 GB of sensitive data, including personal and financial information, client documents, payroll, and accounting records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=143073</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
