<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:02:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker sneaks infostealer malware into early access Steam game</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-sneaks-infostealer-malware-into-early-access-steam-game/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aether Forge Studios, Chemia; CVE(s): None; Summary: EncryptHub compromised the Chemia game files on Steam to distribute info-stealing malware, specifically HijackLoader and Fickle Stealer. The malware was distributed through a DLL file and PowerShell script, which harvested data stored in web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-sneaks-infostealer-malware-into-early-access-steam-game/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitel warns of critical MiVoice MX-ONE authentication bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitel-warns-of-critical-mivoice-mx-one-authentication-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitel Networks MiVoice MX-ONE; CVE(s): None; Summary: The MiVoice MX-ONE Provisioning Manager component contains an improper access control weakness that allows unauthenticated attackers to gain unauthorized access to administrator accounts on unpatched systems, which can be exploited in low-complexity attacks without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitel-warns-of-critical-mivoice-mx-one-authentication-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CastleLoader Malware Infects 469 Devices Using Fake GitHub Repos and ClickFix Phishing</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/castleloader-malware-infects-469.html</link>
      <description>CastleLoader is a versatile malware loader used to distribute various information stealers and remote access trojans (RATs). It employs dead code injection, packing techniques, and anti-analysis measures to hinder analysis. The loader connects to a C2 server, downloads target modules, and executes them, making it a primary distribution mechanism in the current threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/castleloader-malware-infects-469.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant APT Group Exploits VLC Player and Encrypted Shellcode in Attacks on Defense Sector</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/elephant-apt-group-exploits-vlc-player/</link>
      <description>The article reports a sophisticated cyber-espionage operation attributed to the Dropping Elephant APT group, targeting Turkish defense contractors specializing in precision-guided missile systems. The campaign involves spear-phishing emails with malicious LNK files, DLL side-loading techniques, and shellcode injection using QueueUserAPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151150</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Using .hwp Files to Distribute RokRAT Malware and Evade Detection Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-using-hwp-files/</link>
      <description>The AhnLab Security Intelligence Center (ASEC) discovered a sophisticated campaign using Hangul Word Processor (.hwp) documents to spread the RokRAT remote access trojan (RAT). The malware uses Object Linking and Embedding (OLE) objects, DLL side-loading, and steganographic analysis to evade security detections and execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151140</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophos and SonicWall Patch Critical RCE Flaws Affecting Firewalls and SMA 100 Devices</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/sophos-and-sonicwall-patch-critical-rce.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos Firewall; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6704 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-7624 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-7382 (CVSS score: 8.8); Summary: Two vulnerabilities in Sophos Firewall, including arbitrary file writing and SQL injection flaws, can lead to remote code execution. Additionally, a high-severity command injection vulnerability in the WebAdmin component can result in pre-auth code execution on High Availability auxiliary devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/sophos-and-sonicwall-patch-critical-rce.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Comdb2 null pointer dereference and denial-of-service vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/bloomberg-comdb2-null-pointer-dereference-and-denial-of-service-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Bloomberg Comdb2; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2197 (CVE-2025-36520), TALOS-2025-2201 (CVE-2025-35966), TALOS-2025-2199 (CVE-2025-48498), TALOS-2025-2198 (CVE-2025-46354), TALOS-2025-2200 (CVE-2025-36512); Summary: Three null pointer dereference vulnerabilities exist in Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1, which can lead to denial of service by sending crafted messages over TCP. Additionally, there are two denial-of-service vulnerabilities in the Distributed Transaction Commit/Abort Operation and database handling a distributed transaction heartbeat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687ff9ac2e0cc100010c346e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-646: Amazon AWS Client VPN Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-646/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon AWS Client VPN; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8069; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Amazon AWS Client VPN by exploiting an uncontrolled search path element in the OpenSSL configuration. The attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26780</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoName057(16) Hackers Target 3,700 Unique Devices Over the Last 13 Months</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/noname05716-hackers-target-3700-unique-devices/</link>
      <description>This article is about the NoName057(16) hacktivist collective, which has been executing distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks against government and public-sector entities in European nations. The group uses a volunteer-driven platform called DDoSia to orchestrate large-scale application-layer DDoS campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151131</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers breach Toptal GitHub account, publish malicious npm packages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-breach-toptal-github-account-publish-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Toptal's GitHub organization account; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers compromised Toptal's GitHub organization account and used their access to publish ten malicious packages on the Node Package Manager (NPM) index. The packages included data-stealing code that collected GitHub authentication tokens and then wiped the victims' systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-breach-toptal-github-account-publish-malicious-npm-packages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC3944 Exploits VMware vSphere to Deploy Ransomware and Steal Data from Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/unc3944-exploits-vmware-vsphere-to-deploy-ransomware/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a highly advanced cyber operation orchestrated by the threat actor UNC3944, which uses social engineering tactics to infiltrate organizations and conduct reconnaissance on internal resources. The group exploits VMware vSphere environments, using a "living-off-the-land" methodology to minimize detectable indicators of compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151122</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splunk Guide to Detect, Mitigate, and Respond to the CitrixBleed 2 Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/splunk-guide-to-detect-mitigate-and-respond/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: An out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) affects Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway devices, enabling unauthenticated attackers to leak sensitive memory contents via malformed HTTP POST requests. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.3 and is exploited through simple payloads like an incomplete "login" parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151095</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-205-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor 24950 and 24952; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4393, CVE-2025-4394, CVE-2025-4395; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could lead to system compromise, unauthorized access to sensitive data, and manipulation of the monitor's functionality. The vulnerabilities are due to cleartext storage of sensitive information, an empty password in a configuration file, and deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23675</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Six Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/24/cisa-releases-six-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released six Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 24, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories are intended for users and administrators to review technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series; CVE(s): CVE-2016-2542; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious code by getting setup-launcher to load a malicious DLL due to Uncontrolled Search Path Element (CWE-427). Successful exploitation could lead to the execution of malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23674</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Thermostat X-Series WiFi Thermostats</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Network Thermostat X-Series WiFi thermostats; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6260; Summary: The vulnerable embedded web server allows unauthenticated attackers to gain direct access, reset user credentials, and potentially gain full administrative access. This vulnerability can be exploited remotely with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23676</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG Innotek Camera Model LNV5110R</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LG Innotek Camera Model LNV5110R; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7742; Summary: An authentication vulnerability exists in the camera model's firmware, allowing a malicious actor to upload an HTTP POST request to the device's non-volatile storage and potentially gain administrative access. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution at the administrator privilege level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23678</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeywell Experion PKS</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Honeywell Experion PKS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2520, CVE-2025-2521, CVE-2025-2522, CVE-2025-3946, CVE-2025-3947; Summary: The Honeywell Experion PKS contains multiple vulnerabilities including uninitialized variables, memory buffer issues, sensitive information reuse, integer underflows, and wrong handler deployments. Successful exploitation could lead to information exposure, denial of service, or remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23677</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch This Webinar to Uncover Hidden Flaws in Login, AI, and Digital Trust — and Fix Them</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/watch-this-webinar-to-uncover-hidden.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of managing customer logins and data privacy in the era of AI. It highlights the need for organizations to adapt their identity strategies to keep pace with changing user expectations and emerging threats. The webinar "Navigating Customer Identity in the AI Era" offers insights from Auth0's 2025 CIAM Trends Report, providing attendees with practical advice on navigating these challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/watch-this-webinar-to-uncover-hidden.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall urges admins to patch critical RCE flaw in SMA 100 devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-critical-rce-flaw-in-sma-100-VPN-appliances/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40599; Summary: The SMA 100 series appliances contain a critical authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability that can allow remote threat actors to gain code execution. Attackers need admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability, but SonicWall has not found evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-critical-rce-flaw-in-sma-100-VPN-appliances/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentests once a year? Nope. It’s time to build an offensive SOC</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/pentests-once-year-nope-its-time-to.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of having an ongoing and dynamic approach to offensive security, rather than relying on periodic pentests or audits. It argues that traditional approaches are insufficient in today's rapidly changing threat landscape and introduces the concept of an "Offensive Security Operations Center" (OSOC) as a solution. The OSOC would continuously validate exposures across prevention, detection, and response layers, using tools such as Breach and Attack Simulation (BAS) and Automated Penetration Testing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/pentests-once-year-nope-its-time-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Based APTs Deploy Fake Dalai Lama Apps to Spy on Tibetan Community</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-based-apts-deploy-fake-dalai-lama.html</link>
      <description>A China-nexus cyber espionage group has been targeting the Tibetan community with two campaigns (Operation GhostChat and Operation PhantomPrayers) ahead of the Dalai Lama's 90th birthday. The attacks use watering hole techniques, compromising legitimate websites and installing backdoors on victim systems to gather sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-based-apts-deploy-fake-dalai-lama.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Exploit Cursor Background Agents to Take Over Amazon EC2 Instance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-exploit-cursor-background-agents/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cursor's Background Agents; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability in Cursor's Background Agents that allows unauthorized access to an Amazon EC2 instance. The vulnerability is exploited through the "Show Terminal" button, which provides direct command-line access to the remote infrastructure. The researchers gain root access and can execute commands on the compromised machine, highlighting potential risks for privilege escalation and malicious activities such as cryptocurrency mining or data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151112</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm-2603 Exploits SharePoint Flaws to Deploy Warlock Ransomware on Unpatched Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/storm-2603-exploits-sharepoint-flaws-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability in on-premises Microsoft SharePoint Server that allows attackers to deploy Warlock ransomware. The attack chain involves exploiting two vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-49706 and CVE-2025-49704) to gain initial access, conduct lateral movement, and ultimately deploy the ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/storm-2603-exploits-sharepoint-flaws-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the new Chaos RaaS group attacks</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/new-chaos-ransomware/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an analysis of the Chaos ransomware group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The article highlights the similarities between the Chaos ransomware and other notable groups such as BlackSuit (Royal) ransomware. It also provides details on how the malware works, including its encryption methods and cleanup procedures.

Some key points from the article include:

1. The Chaos ransomware uses hybrid cryptographic techniques, combining Elliptic Curve Diffie-Hellman (ECDH) with Curve25519 for asymmetric operations and AES-256 for symmetric file encryption.
2. The ransomware performs selective encryption based on command-line configuration parameters, allowing operators to customize the attack.
3. The malware targets local and network resources, using SMB connections to encrypt shared drives and distributed file systems.
4. The article provides details on how the Chaos ransomware can be detected and blocked by various Cisco products, including Secure Endpoint, Secure Email, Secure Firewall, and others.

Overall, this article appears to be a comprehensive analysis of the Chaos ransomware group's TTPs, highlighting their similarities with other notable groups and providing insights into how they operate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68812cd32e0cc100010c34d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven Wi-Fi Biometrics WhoFi Tracks Humans Behind Walls with 95.5% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-driven-wi-fi-biometrics-whofi-tracks-humans-behind-walls/</link>
      <description>This article introduces WhoFi, an AI-powered deep learning pipeline that uses Wi-Fi Channel State Information (CSI) for person re-identification (Re-ID), achieving high accuracy on the NTU-Fi dataset. The system's robustness and privacy features make it suitable for applications in smart environments, such as security systems and healthcare monitoring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: SharePoint servers also targeted in ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-servers-also-targeted-in-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-53770; Summary: A China-based hacking group is exploiting a zero-day exploit chain on Microsoft SharePoint servers, leading to widespread attacks. The attackers use Mimikatz to extract plaintext credentials, move laterally with PsExec and Impacket, and deliver Warlock ransomware across compromised systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-servers-also-targeted-in-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Launch Targeted Campaign to Infect Windows Systems with Ghost RAT and PhantomNet Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-launch-targeted-campaign/</link>
      <description>A China-nexus advanced persistent threat (APT) group attributed to Operation GhostChat and Operation PhantomPrayers targeted the Tibetan community by compromising legitimate websites and distributing trojanized software. The attacks employed advanced evasion techniques, including DLL sideloading, shellcode injection, and encrypted payloads to bypass endpoint detection and response solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151056</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Introduces OSS Rebuild to Boost Security in Open-Source Package Ecosystems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-introduces-oss-rebuild-to-boost-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is about Google's OSS Rebuild project, which aims to enhance trust in package registries by independently reproducing upstream artifacts and generating SLSA Provenance attestations that meet Build Level 3 requirements. The project targets supply chain attacks on widely-used dependencies across Python's PyPI, JavaScript/TypeScript's npm, and Rust's Crates.io.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151041</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Module Released to Exploit SharePoint 0-Day Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/metasploit-module-exploit-sharepoint-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: The Metasploit module exploits a chain of unauthenticated remote code execution flaws in Microsoft SharePoint Server, allowing attackers to achieve complete system compromise without requiring authentication. The vulnerabilities represent sophisticated patch bypasses and can be exploited through the _/layouts/15/ToolPane.aspx endpoint, potentially leading to data theft, ransomware deployment, and lateral movement within corporate networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151069</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TP-Link Network Video Recorder Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tp-link-network-video-recorder-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TP-Link VIGI Network Video Recorder models (VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1 and VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2); CVE(s): CVE-2025-7723, CVE-2025-7724; Summary: The two TP-Link VIGI network video recorder models have critical security vulnerabilities that allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system. The flaws are characterized as authenticated and unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerabilities with high CVSS scores of 8.5 and 8.7, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151068</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Arrests XSS Forum Admin in Kyiv After 12-Year Run Operating Cybercrime Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-arrests-xss-forum-admin-in-kyiv.html</link>
      <description>Europol has arrested the suspected administrator of XSS.is, a Russian-speaking cybercrime platform, in collaboration with Ukrainian authorities and French Police. The platform, which had over 50,000 registered users, served as a marketplace for stolen data, hacking tools, and illicit services. The suspect is estimated to have made €7 million in profits from advertising and facilitation fees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-arrests-xss-forum-admin-in-kyiv.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weidmueller Industrial Routers Exposed to Remote Code Execution Flaws</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weidmueller-industrial-routers-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Weidmueller Industrial Routers (IE-SR-2TX); CVE(s): VDE-2025-052, None; Summary: Five high-severity security vulnerabilities in Weidmueller's IE-SR-2TX router series allow attackers to execute arbitrary code with root privileges, potentially compromising industrial networks and critical infrastructure. The flaws impact several models of wireless security routers commonly deployed in these environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151035</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Client VPN for Windows Vulnerability Could Allow Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/aws-client-vpn-for-windows-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Web Services (AWS) Client VPN; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8069; Summary: The AWS Client VPN software for Windows contains a critical vulnerability that allows non-administrative users to escalate their privileges to root-level access during the installation process. The flaw is due to a design error in the installation process, which can be exploited by placing arbitrary code within the OpenSSL configuration file. An attacker with elevated privileges could then use this code to gain unauthorized access to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151031</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Publishes Security Update Addressing Several Vulnerabilities in Community and Enterprise Edition</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gitlab-publishes-security-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GitLab; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4700, CVE-2025-4439, CVE-2025-7001, CVE-2025-4976; Summary: GitLab has released critical security patches addressing six vulnerabilities across its Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE) platforms. The most severe issues are two high-severity cross-site scripting (XSS) flaws that could allow unauthorized access to sensitive information and enable malicious script execution in specific deployment scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151025</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall SMA 100 Vulnerabilities Allow Remote Execution of Arbitrary JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sonicwall-sma-100-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40596, CVE-2025-40597, and CVE-2025-40598; Summary: The vulnerabilities allow unauthenticated remote attackers to trigger denial-of-service conditions or execute arbitrary code and JavaScript. Two buffer overflow issues can crash the appliance or execute arbitrary code, while a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript into unsuspecting user sessions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151021</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Google Chromium Input Validation Flaw Actively Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-google-chromium-input-validation-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chromium; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6558; Summary: A severe input validation vulnerability in Google Chromium's ANGLE and GPU components allows remote attackers to execute sandbox escape attacks through specially crafted HTML pages, affecting millions of users across multiple web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Deploy Stealth Backdoor in WordPress Mu-Plugins to Maintain Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-deploy-stealth-backdoor-in.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WordPress; CVE(s): None; Summary: A stealthy backdoor has been discovered in WordPress's "mu-plugins" directory, allowing threat actors to gain persistent access and perform arbitrary actions. The backdoor injects a file manager into the theme directory, creates an administrator user, downloads a malicious plugin, and changes passwords to lock out other administrators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-deploy-stealth-backdoor-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brave blocks Windows Recall from screenshotting your browsing activity</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brave-blocks-windows-recall-from-screenshotting-your-browsing-activity/</link>
      <description>Brave Browser has blocked Microsoft's Windows Recall feature from capturing screenshots of its windows by default, to protect users' privacy. This was done by utilizing Microsoft's SetInputScope API and setting the input scope to IS_PRIVATE for all browser windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/brave-blocks-windows-recall-from-screenshotting-your-browsing-activity/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about ToolShell, the SharePoint threat under mass exploitation</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/what-to-know-about-toolshell-the-sharepoint-threat-under-mass-exploitation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to infect systems with a webshell-based backdoor that gains access to sensitive parts of the SharePoint Server. Attackers can then extract tokens and credentials, gain administrative privileges, and exfiltrate sensitive data and deploy additional backdoors for future use.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/what-to-know-about-toolshell-the-sharepoint-threat-under-mass-exploitation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After $380M hack, Clorox sues its “service desk” vendor for simply giving out passwords</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/how-do-hackers-get-passwords-sometimes-they-just-ask/</link>
      <description>Clorox's internal password reset tool, MyID, and Okta passwords were compromised by a cybercriminal posing as an employee. The attacker successfully reset passwords and obtained MFA resets from Cognizant agents without proper verification procedures being followed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/how-do-hackers-get-passwords-sometimes-they-just-ask/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton launches privacy-respecting encrypted AI assistant Lumo</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/proton-launches-privacy-respecting-encrypted-ai-assistant-lumo/</link>
      <description>Proton has launched Lumo, a privacy-first AI assistant that does not log user conversations and doesn't use their prompts for training. The tool uses open-source large language models and encryption scheme, with complete source code available. It supports file uploads with full encryption support and is available on Android and iOS devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/proton-launches-privacy-respecting-encrypted-ai-assistant-lumo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers fooled Cognizant help desk, says Clorox in $380M cyberattack lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-fooled-cognizant-help-desk-says-clorox-in-380m-cyberattack-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>Clorox is suing Cognizant for gross negligence after a massive August 2023 cyberattack, allegedly enabled by Cognizant's failure to verify the identity of an employee whose password was reset by hackers without proper authentication. The incident gave attackers privileged access to Clorox's IT network, resulting in business disruption and losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-fooled-cognizant-help-desk-says-clorox-in-380m-cyberattack-lawsuit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actor Mimo Targets Magento and Docker to Deploy Crypto Miners and Proxyware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/threat-actor-mimo-targets-magento-and.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Magento CMS; CVE(s): None; Summary: Mimo, a threat actor, exploits undetermined PHP-FPM vulnerabilities in Magento e-commerce installations to obtain initial access and then uses GSocket to establish persistent access. The vulnerability allows command injection via a Magento CMS plugin.

FYSA: A threat actor known as Mimo has shifted its tactics from targeting vulnerable Craft CMS instances to exploiting Magento CMS and misconfigured Docker instances, ultimately deploying cryptocurrency miners and proxyware to monetize compromised machines' CPU resources and unused internet bandwidth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/threat-actor-mimo-targets-magento-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is rolling out 'personality' toggles to become your assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-rolling-out-personality-toggles-to-become-your-assistant/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the rollout of a new "personality" feature on OpenAI's ChatGPT web app, allowing users to personalize how ChatGPT interacts with them. The feature includes multiple personalities such as "Robot," "Cynic," "Listener," and "Sage."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-rolling-out-personality-toggles-to-become-your-assistant/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Backdoor in WordPress Plugins Grants Attackers Ongoing Access to Websites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hidden-backdoor-in-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WordPress; CVE(s): None; Summary: A highly skilled malware campaign targets WordPress websites by inserting a covert backdoor in the mu-plugins directory, allowing for persistent threats and unrestricted administrator privileges. The malware loads remote payloads, executes arbitrary PHP code, and creates hidden administrator accounts, making it resilient to standard remediation efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150988</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation CargoTalon Targets Russian Aerospace &amp; Defense to Deploy EAGLET Implant</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/operation-cargotalon-targets-russian-aerospace-defense/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Operation CargoTalon, a sophisticated spear-phishing campaign targeting employees at Russia's Voronezh Aircraft Production Association (VASO). The campaign uses malicious attachments and DLL files to deliver an EAGLET payload with espionage-focused features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150997</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPM package ‘is’ with 2.8M weekly downloads infected devs with malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-package-is-with-28m-weekly-downloads-infected-devs-with-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: John Harband 'is'; CVE(s): None; Summary: The 'is' NPM package was compromised in a supply chain attack that injected backdoor malware, allowing attackers to gain full access to compromised devices. Maintainer accounts were hijacked via phishing, and unauthorized owner changes went unnoticed for several hours, potentially compromising many developers who downloaded the new releases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-package-is-with-28m-weekly-downloads-infected-devs-with-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US nuclear weapons agency hacked in Microsoft SharePoint attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-nuclear-weapons-agency-hacked-in-microsoft-sharepoint-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None (zero-day vulnerability); Summary: Unknown threat actors exploited a recently patched Microsoft SharePoint zero-day vulnerability chain, breaching the National Nuclear Security Administration's network and potentially compromising 148 organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-nuclear-weapons-agency-hacked-in-microsoft-sharepoint-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US nuclear weapons agency reportedly hacked in SharePoint attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-nuclear-weapons-agency-reportedly-hacked-in-sharepoint-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, "None"; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability chain (ToolShell) in Microsoft SharePoint was exploited to breach the National Nuclear Security Administration's network and compromise at least 148 organizations worldwide. The vulnerability is being used by Chinese state-sponsored hacking groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-nuclear-weapons-agency-reportedly-hacked-in-sharepoint-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clorox Files Lawsuit Against Cognizant Over Employee Password Leak to Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clorox-files-lawsuit-against-cognizant/</link>
      <description>Clorox is suing Cognizant for $380 million over a cyberattack that allegedly occurred when Cognizant employees handed over network credentials to a criminal pretending to be a Clorox employee. The lawsuit claims Cognizant's security failures enabled the attack, which resulted in significant damages and disruptions to Clorox's operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150964</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ACRStealer Exploits Google Docs and Steam for C2 Server Using DDR Technique</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-acrstealer-exploits-google-docs-and-steam/</link>
      <description>ACRStealer is an infostealer malware that continues to evolve and evade detection by introducing new features such as bypassing traditional monitoring tools, maintaining core information theft capabilities, and facilitating the installation of supplementary malware strains. The threat actors behind ACRStealer have incorporated techniques like Heaven's Gate and manual HTTP structure assembly to disrupt dynamic analysis and signature-based detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150961</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI confirms ChatGPT's new study feature, helps with exams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-chatgpts-new-study-feature-helps-with-exams/</link>
      <description>OpenAI is testing a new feature, "Study Together", within the ChatGPT web app, allowing users to get homework help or break down complex problems with step-by-step guides. The feature will roll out to everyone in the coming hours or days. Additionally, OpenAI's Codex and Sora 2 projects are also mentioned, along with plans for a ChatGPT product by 2026 and a price drop for the ChatGPT o3 API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-chatgpts-new-study-feature-helps-with-exams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to harden your Active Directory against Kerberoasting</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-harden-your-active-directory-against-kerberoasting/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Active Directory; CVE(s): None; Summary: Kerberoasting is a privilege escalation attack that targets service accounts with Service Principle Names (SPNs) in Active Directory, allowing attackers to compromise service accounts with low risk of detection. The attack involves exploiting an existing Windows user account, requesting a service ticket from the Ticket Granting Service, and then cracking the SPN password hash using brute force techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/how-to-harden-your-active-directory-against-kerberoasting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimo Targets Magento CMS to Steal Card Details and Monetize Bandwidth</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mimo-targets-magento-cms-to-steal-card-details/</link>
      <description>The Mimo threat actor has been observed expanding its operations from Craft CMS to Magento CMS, exploiting undetermined PHP-FPM flaws to gain initial access. This evolution includes sophisticated persistence and evasion mechanisms, suggesting preparation for more advanced financial crimes beyond mere resource exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150949</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI prepares Sora 2 to take on Google's Veo 3</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-prepares-sora-2-to-take-on-googles-veo-3/</link>
      <description>OpenAI is working on Sora 2, a successor to their generative video model Sora, while Google has announced Veo 3 is free for college students with the Gemini AI Pro plan. The article also mentions ChatGPT's GPT-5-reasoning-alpha and o3-alpha models, which may have implications for education and coding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-prepares-sora-2-to-take-on-googles-veo-3/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine arrests suspected admin of XSS Russian hacking forum</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-arrests-suspected-admin-of-xss-russian-hacking-forum/</link>
      <description>The suspected administrator of a Russian-speaking hacking forum XSS.is was arrested by Ukrainian authorities at the request of the Paris public prosecutor's office, amid an investigation into ransomware and cybercrimes. This development is likely to have a chilling effect on the activity at XSS, as users fearing exposure to law enforcement may turn to other sites. The arrest comes shortly after French police arrested five operators of another major cybercrime platform, BreachForum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ukraine-arrests-suspected-admin-of-xss-russian-hacking-forum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA warns of hackers exploiting SysAid vulnerabilities in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-sysaid-vulnerabilities-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SysAid IT service management (ITSM) software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2775, CVE-2025-2776; Summary: Two unauthenticated XML External Entity (XXE) flaws allow attackers to hijack administrator accounts and retrieve local files containing sensitive information. The vulnerabilities were patched in March 2024 with the release of SysAid On-Prem version 24.4.60, but attacks are still ongoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-sysaid-vulnerabilities-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Engineer Pleads Guilty in U.S. Missile Detection Data Theft Case</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/silicon-valley-engineer-pleads-guilty/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather an instance of economic espionage and technology theft. A Silicon Valley engineer, Chenguang Gong, pleaded guilty to stealing critical defense technologies worth hundreds of millions of dollars from a Los Angeles-area research and development company. The stolen data included blueprints for sophisticated sensors and countermeasure technologies designed for military applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150951</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>npm 'accidentally' removes Stylus package, breaks builds and pipelines</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-accidentally-removes-stylus-package-breaks-builds-and-pipelines/</link>
      <description>The article reports that npm mistakenly took down the Stylus library, a legitimate package receiving 3 million weekly downloads, and replaced it with a security holding page. This was due to an administrative error involving one of the maintainers, who had published malicious packages in the past.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/npm-accidentally-removes-stylus-package-breaks-builds-and-pipelines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack on Germany’s AMEOS Hospital Network Exposes Patient Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattack-on-germanys-ameos-hospital-network/</link>
      <description>The article reports a cyberattack on Germany's AMEOS Hospital Network, which resulted in unauthorized access and potential exposure of sensitive data. Despite robust defenses, attackers managed to infiltrate the network using advanced persistent threat (APT) tactics, potentially exfiltrating personal health information, employee records, and partner data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150928</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Coyote Malware Variant Exploits Windows UI Automation to Steal Banking Credentials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-coyote-malware-variant-exploits.html</link>
      <description>The Windows banking trojan Coyote exploits the Windows accessibility framework UI Automation (UIA) to harvest sensitive information, targeting Brazilian users by extracting credentials linked to 75 banking institutes' web addresses and cryptocurrency exchanges. The malware uses UIA to parse through UI child elements of windows in an attempt to identify browser tabs or address bars and cross-reference with a list of targeted addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-coyote-malware-variant-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Nuclear Weapons Data Compromised via SharePoint Zero-Day Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/us-nuclear-weapons-data-compromised/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None; Summary: A zero-day exploit in Microsoft SharePoint was linked to Chinese government-affiliated hacking groups, compromising critical US government infrastructure, including the National Nuclear Security Administration. The vulnerability allowed hackers to remotely access SharePoint servers, enabling data theft and potential movement across connected services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150946</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious LNK File Posing as Credit Card Security Email Steals User Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-lnk-file-posing-as-credit-card/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have deployed a malicious LNK file masquerading as a credit card company's security email authentication pop-up to pilfer sensitive user information. The LNK file executes alongside a decoy file, fetching an additional HTA and bait HTML document from the attacker's server, storing and running them in the system's temporary folder. The malware exhibits specialized infostealer and backdoor capabilities, targeting browser data from multiple browsers and services, as well as executing remote shell commands and exfiltrating documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150905</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma Stealer Masquerades as Pirated Apps to Steal Logins and Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lumma-stealer-masquerades-as-pirated-apps/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability. It discusses the resurgence of Lumma Stealer, an information-stealing malware-as-a-service platform, after a global law enforcement operation in May 2025. The malware has evolved and adapted to evade detection, using various tactics such as domain obfuscation, cloud-based providers, and social engineering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150863</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synology BeeDrive for Desktop on Windows Vulnerabilities Let Hackers Run Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/synology-beedrive-for-desktop-on-windows-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Synology BeeDrive desktop application for Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54158, CVE-2025-54159, CVE-2025-54160; Summary: The BeeDrive desktop application for Windows contains three critical vulnerabilities that allow attackers to execute malicious code, delete arbitrary files, and gain elevated privileges. The flaws can be exploited using local or remote attack vectors, making them a significant risk to system integrity and data security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150911</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ZuRu Malware Variant Targets macOS via Termius SSH Exploit</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-zuru-malware-variant-targets-macos/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a variant of the macOS.ZuRu malware that has resurfaced, employing advanced evasion techniques to deploy a modified Khepri command-and-control beacon. The malware uses trojanized versions of SSH client Termius and other backend tools like SecureCRT and Navicat to infiltrate professional workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150846</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Introduces Powerful New AI Features – What’s New!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-introduces-powerful-new-ai-features/</link>
      <description>This article is about the new AI-powered features and enhancements in Windows 11, including a conversational agent in the Settings app, improved search, productivity tools, and features like Relight and object select tool in Paint. The update aims to make PCs smarter, more responsive, and better tailored to individual needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150893</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brave Browser Block Microsoft Recall Over Privacy Issues</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/brave-browser-block-microsoft-recall/</link>
      <description>Microsoft's Recall feature, which periodically captures full-screen snapshots of user activity, was criticized for its potential to expose sensitive browsing habits through an unencrypted, local database. Brave Software has proactively disabled Recall by default in its browser starting with version 1.81 for Windows 11 and newer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150883</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operator of Jetflix illegal streaming service gets 7 years in prison</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/operator-of-jetflix-illegal-streaming-service-gets-7-years-in-prison/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the conviction of Kristopher Lee Dallmann, the ringleader of the illegal paid streaming operation Jetflicks, which operated for 12 years and had tens of thousands of subscribers. The scheme generated millions of dollars in criminal profits by pirating content from platforms like Netflix, Hulu, Vudu, and Amazon Prime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/operator-of-jetflix-illegal-streaming-service-gets-7-years-in-prison/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical JavaScript Library Vulnerability Exposes Apps to Remote Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-javascript-library-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: form-data JavaScript package; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7783; Summary: The form-data JavaScript package contains a critical vulnerability that allows attackers to predict and manipulate boundary values in multipart form-encoded data. This can lead to parameter injection attacks, compromising internal systems and exposing sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150873</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerberoasting Detections: A New Approach to a Decade-Old Challenge</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/kerberoasting-detections-new-approach.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses the challenges of detecting Kerberoasting attacks, which exploit weaknesses in Kerberos authentication protocol. It highlights the limitations of traditional heuristic-based detection methods and proposes a statistical framework for improving anomaly detection accuracy and reducing false positives. The article presents a model that groups similar ticket-request patterns into distinct clusters and uses histogram bins to track frequency over time, allowing for more accurate identification of anomalies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/kerberoasting-detections-new-approach.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes bug behind incorrect Windows Firewall errors</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-bug-behind-incorrect-windows-firewall-errors/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: A known issue in Windows 11 24H2 systems with the June 2025 preview update installed triggers invalid Windows Firewall errors after rebooting. The bug has been fixed in the KB5062660preview cumulative update for Windows 11 24H2, released on Tuesday, and will be generally available to all users who install the August Patch Tuesday updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-bug-behind-incorrect-windows-firewall-errors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Hazel Burton</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/humans-of-talos-meet-hazel-burton/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability or cybersecurity-relevant content. It appears to be an employee spotlight or "Humans of Talos" series featuring Hazel Burton, a team member at Talos. The conversation touches on her career journey and what drew her to join the organization, as well as her advice for someone looking to join Talos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687e75c82e0cc100010c33bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Launches OSS Rebuild to Expose Malicious Code in Widely Used Open-Source Packages</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-launches-oss-rebuild-to-expose.html</link>
      <description>Google's OSS Rebuild initiative aims to bolster the security of open-source package ecosystems by providing build provenance for packages across various registries. It leverages automation, heuristics, and network monitoring capabilities to produce trustworthy security metadata, enabling users to verify a package's origin and detect supply chain compromises.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-launches-oss-rebuild-to-expose.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyote Malware Targets WILS, Abusing Microsoft UI Automation to Exfiltrate Logins</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coyote-malware-targets-wils/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft UI Automation (UIA) framework; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel variant of the Coyote banking trojan exploits Microsoft's UI Automation (UIA) framework to manipulate user interface elements and steal login credentials. The malware uses UIA's Component Object Model (COM) interfaces to evade traditional endpoint detection and response (EDR) tools, allowing it to extract sensitive data without direct process injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150817</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Groups Weaponize RMM Tools to Infiltrate Networks and Exfiltrate Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-groups-weaponize-rmm-tools/</link>
      <description>Ransomware gangs have co-opted Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) tools to orchestrate sophisticated network intrusions, persistence, lateral movement, and data exfiltration. The tools were exploited by groups such as Hunters International and Medusa to evade traditional security controls due to their legitimate status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150808</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Chinese Hackers Actively Exploiting SharePoint 0-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-chinese-hackers-actively-exploiting-sharepoint-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A vulnerability chain dubbed "ToolShell" is actively exploited by Chinese hackers to gain unauthorized access to on-premises SharePoint servers. The vulnerabilities allow for network spoofing and remote code execution, enabling attackers to achieve unauthenticated system access, authenticated access, and execute arbitrary code across networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150832</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Introduces Black Screen of Death and Auto Recovery</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-introduces-black-screen-of-death-and-auto-recovery/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced significant updates to Windows 11's system recovery capabilities, including a redesigned "Black Screen of Death" interface and automated recovery features like Quick Machine Recovery (QMR) aimed at minimizing downtime and improving user experience during system failures. The new features promise to reduce system downtime and automate recovery processes, addressing critical pain points in enterprise environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150803</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Expose Russia’s Most Secretive FSB Spy Network</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-expose-russias-most-secretive-fsb/</link>
      <description>Researchers analyzed open-source intelligence (OSINT) and phaleristics to reveal the structure and operations of the Russian Federal Security Service's (FSB) 16th Center, a unit responsible for signals intelligence (SIGINT), cryptanalysis, and computer network operations (CNO). The study mapped the center's internal architecture, including at least ten departments, and geolocated ten SIGINT facilities across Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150792</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kali Linux Introduces Two New Tools for Raspberry Pi to Boost Wi-Fi Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kali-linux-introduces-tools-raspberry-pi-wi-fi-performance/</link>
      <description>The article is about the integration of Nexmon firmware-patching framework into Kali Linux, enabling native monitor-mode and packet-injection capabilities on Raspberry Pi boards. This update streamlines wireless security assessments on popular ARM-based Pi boards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150802</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome High-Severity Vulnerabilities Allow Hackers to Gain Full Control</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-high-severity-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): None; Summary: The latest Chrome update addresses three significant security vulnerabilities, including two high-severity issues involving type confusion errors in V8, Chrome's JavaScript engine. These flaws can allow attackers to manipulate data types, leading to memory corruption and arbitrary code execution, enabling cybercriminals to bypass security measures, steal sensitive information, or install malicious software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150790</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Orders Urgent Patching After Chinese Hackers Exploit SharePoint Flaws in Live Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-orders-urgent-patching-after.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: Two Microsoft SharePoint flaws, CVE-2025-49704 and CVE-2025-49706, have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The vulnerabilities, tracked as ToolShell, enable unauthorized access to on-premise SharePoint servers and are being exploited by Chinese hacking groups like Linen Typhoon and Violet Typhoon since July 7, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-orders-urgent-patching-after.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Warns: SysAid Flaws Under Active Attack Enable Remote File Access and SSRF</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-warns-sysaid-flaws-under-active.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SysAid IT support software; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2775, CVE-2025-2776; Summary: Two XXE vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-2775 and CVE-2025-2776, allow for administrator account takeover, file read primitives, and potential remote code execution when chained with other flaws. The vulnerabilities were disclosed by watchTowr Labs researchers in May and addressed in SysAid's on-premise version 24.4.60 build 16 released in early March 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-warns-sysaid-flaws-under-active.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Launches Firefox 141 With Critical Security Fixes – Update Immediately</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mozilla-launches-firefox-141/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8027, CVE-2025-8028, CVE-2025-8034, CVE-2025-8035, CVE-2025-8040; Summary: The vulnerability summary states that Firefox 141 addresses 18 distinct CVEs, including high-impact memory safety bugs and moderate issues in URL handling and sandboxing. The most critical defects fixed include two high-severity flaws in the JavaScript engine, which could lead to arbitrary code execution, cross-origin data leaks, and privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150786</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Injected Malicious Firefox Packages in Arch Linux Repo</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-injected-malicious-firefox-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Arch Linux; CVE(s): None; Summary: Three compromised packages containing Remote Access Trojan (RAT) malware were uploaded to the Arch User Repository (AUR), targeting users seeking alternative Firefox configurations and browsers. The malware was designed to establish persistent remote access capabilities on infected systems, potentially granting attackers comprehensive system access without user knowledge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150781</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Active Exploitation of Microsoft SharePoint Code Injection and Authentication Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-of-microsoft-sharepoint-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint allow attackers to gain unauthorized access and execute code, posing significant risks to enterprise deployments. The vulnerabilities can be chained together to create devastating attack scenarios, enabling malicious actors to view sensitive information and make unauthorized modifications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150776</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma infostealer malware returns after law enforcement disruption</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-returns-after-law-enforcement-disruption/</link>
      <description>The Lumma infostealer malware operation has resumed activities after a massive law enforcement operation in May, which resulted in the seizure of 2,300 domains and parts of its infrastructure. Despite significant disruption, the operators claimed their central server had not been seized and restoration efforts were underway, eventually regaining trust within the cybercrime community.

(Note: Since there is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, I have formatted my response as a summary for a malware operation.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lumma-infostealer-malware-returns-after-law-enforcement-disruption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Logging for Security and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/cloud-logging-for-security/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of cloud logging and monitoring in enterprise environments. It provides an overview of the different log categories for enterprise environments, including Audit, Compute, Network, Secrets, Cloud-Native Storage, and Kubernetes. The article also highlights the complexities of cloud logging across different cloud service providers (CSPs) such as AWS, Azure, and GCP.

The article emphasizes the need for a holistic approach to cloud logging that balances security, regulatory, and business needs while optimizing costs. It provides best practices for organizations to effectively monitor, secure, and manage their cloud environments.

Overall, this article aims to educate readers on the importance of cloud logging and monitoring in today's digital landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147360</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EFF moves to stop power utility reporting suspected pot growers to cops</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/07/eff-moves-to-stop-power-utility-reporting-suspected-pot-growers-to-cops/</link>
      <description>The article discusses how SMUD's smart meter data analysis program has been used to monitor and potentially identify individuals growing cannabis in their homes. Law enforcement agencies, including the Sacramento Police Department, have requested lists of customers using above a certain threshold of electricity, with disproportionately high penalties levied against Asian property owners who were found to be growing cannabis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/07/eff-moves-to-stop-power-utility-reporting-suspected-pot-growers-to-cops/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5062660 update brings new 'Windows Resilience' features</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062660-update-brings-new-windows-resilience-features/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article discusses various updates and changes to Windows 11, including new features, fixes, and improvements. The main updates are:

1. Quick machine recovery: This feature enables automatic detection and fixing of widespread issues on Windows 11 devices using the Windows Recovery Environment (WinRE).
2. Streamlined interface during unexpected restarts: The updated design aligns with Windows 11's visual style and helps users return to work faster.
3. Boolean option for configuring Start menu pins: Administrators can apply Start menu pins once, allowing users to make changes to their pinned layout and have those changes safeguarded.
4. Improvements to Snap in Windows 11, including inline messages and keyboard shortcuts.
5. Fixes for various issues, such as authentication problems, file explorer bugs, graphics recognition, input method editor issues, stability problems, and Windows Firewall errors.

Overall, this article highlights the importance of keeping software up-to-date and secure, as well as the value of auto-recovery tools in mitigating downtime caused by widespread issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062660-update-brings-new-windows-resilience-features/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 gets new Black Screen of Death, auto recovery tool</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-gets-new-black-screen-of-death-auto-recovery-tool/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Microsoft's Windows Resiliency Initiative, which aims to make Windows more stable and self-healing. The initiative includes the replacement of the Blue Screen of Death (BSOD) with a new Black Screen of Death, as well as the introduction of the Quick Machine Recovery feature, which can automatically resolve boot failures without requiring manual intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-gets-new-black-screen-of-death-auto-recovery-tool/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-634: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-634/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7981; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an uninitialized variable in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25475</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-638: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-638/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7990; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the file parsing functionality. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25944</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-639: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-639/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7986; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by parsing VC6 files. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25755</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-640: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-640/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7989; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by parsing out-of-bounds read remote code execution. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of AR files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25943</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-641: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-641/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7987; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required, and the attack can be executed by visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-642: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-642/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7992; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of AR files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25972</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-643: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-643/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7991; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by reading past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25945</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-644: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-644/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7988; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of VC6 files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25862</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-645: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-645/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by parsing out-of-bounds RFA files. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27254</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-629: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-629/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7977; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an out-of-bounds read in the LI file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25354</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-630: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-630/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7982; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an integer overflow before allocating a buffer during LI file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25476</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-631: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-631/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7980; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the VC6 file parsing. User interaction is required, and the flaw results from improper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25465</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-632: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-632/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7978; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to an uninitialized variable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25459</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-633: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-633/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7979; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of VC6 files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25463</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-635: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-635/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Graphite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7983; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25477</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-636: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-636/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7984; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs when parsing AR files due to uninitialized variables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25700</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-637: (0Day) Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-637/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7985; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt by exploiting an integer overflow in the parsing of VC6 files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25704</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coyote malware abuses Windows accessibility framework for data theft</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coyote-malware-abuses-windows-accessibility-framework-for-data-theft/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new variant of the banking trojan "Coyote" that abuses Microsoft's UI Automation framework (UIA) to identify which banking and cryptocurrency exchange sites are accessed on a device for potential credential theft. The malware, which targets 75 apps primarily in Brazil, uses UIA to extract web addresses from browser tabs or address bars and cross-referenced with a hardcoded list of targeted services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coyote-malware-abuses-windows-accessibility-framework-for-data-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and FBI warn of escalating Interlock ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-and-fbi-warn-of-escalating-interlock-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>CISA and the FBI have warned of increased Interlock ransomware activity targeting businesses and critical infrastructure organizations in double extortion attacks. The advisory provides indicators of compromise (IOCs) collected during investigations, as well as mitigation measures to protect networks against this ransomware gang's attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-and-fbi-warn-of-escalating-interlock-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major European healthcare network discloses security breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-european-healthcare-network-discloses-security-breach/</link>
      <description>AMEOS Group suffered a security breach that may have exposed customer, employee, and partner information. External actors gained unauthorized access to its IT systems and accessed sensitive information.

Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, but rather a security breach at AMEOS Group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/major-european-healthcare-network-discloses-security-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scavenger Malware Compromises Popular npm Packages to Target Developers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scavenger-malware-compromises-popular-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Npm package eslint-config-prettier; CVE(s): None; Summary: The npm package eslint-config-prettier was compromised through a phishing email and used to distribute a novel malware dubbed "Scavenger" that targets Windows systems. The malware uses various evasion techniques, including anti-VM checks, anti-antivirus measures, and dynamic resolution of functions using CRC32 hashing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hackers Target Global Airlines to Steal Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-hackers-target-global-airlines/</link>
      <description>APT39, a state-sponsored hacker collective connected to Iran's Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS), was exposed as operating through the compromised internal systems of Amnban, a cybersecurity company. The breach reveals a sophisticated campaign involving cyber network exploitation (CNE) and preparation for cyber network attacks (CNA), with millions of airline passengers' sensitive personal identifiable information (PII) harvested worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150730</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Links Ongoing SharePoint Exploits to Three Chinese Hacker Groups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-links-ongoing-sharepoint.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53771, CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The exploitation of security flaws in internet-facing SharePoint Server instances has been linked to two Chinese hacking groups, Linen Typhoon and Violet Typhoon, as well as a third China-based threat actor, Storm-2603. The vulnerabilities allow for authentication bypass and remote code execution, leading to the deployment of a web shell and potential data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-links-ongoing-sharepoint.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETQ Reliance RCE Flaw Grants Full SYSTEM Access with a Single Space</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/etq-reliance-rce-flaw-grants-full-system-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hexagon ETQ's ETQ Reliance; CVE(s): 2025-34140, 2025-34141, 2025-34142, 2025-34143; Summary: The Java-based quality management system, ETQ Reliance, has several serious flaws including reflected cross-site scripting (XSS), XML External Entity (XXE) injection, authentication bypass, and remote code execution (RCE). These vulnerabilities were responsibly disclosed, leading to patches in NXG Release 2025.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150713</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-628: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 OCPP Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-628/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25271, ZDI-CAN-26346, ZDI-25-628; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and an attacker can leverage it to bypass authentication on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26346</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Target Linux SSH Servers to Deploy SVF Botnet</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-target-linux-ssh-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux servers; CVE(s): None; Summary: Weak SSH credentials on Linux servers are being exploited by threat actors to launch DDoS attacks and cryptocurrency mining. The SVF Botnet malware is used to achieve this, which also incorporates proxy servers for enhanced evasion and has a modular design with customizable attack parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150698</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco: Maximum-severity ISE RCE flaws now exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-maximum-severity-ise-rce-flaws-now-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282, CVE-2025-20337; Summary: Three critical remote code execution vulnerabilities in Cisco ISE are being actively exploited. The flaws allow attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root without authentication and can lead to gaining a foothold on corporate networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisco-maximum-severity-ise-rce-flaws-now-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is the Deep Web?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-is-the-deep-web/</link>
      <description>The article explains the concept of the "deep web", which refers to parts of the internet that search engines cannot index. It includes private databases, login-restricted content, and subscription-based pages. The deep web is legal, secure, and essential for daily online activity, supporting research, and powering secure access to sensitive systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062009</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Web3 Phishing Scam Uses Fake AI Platforms to Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-web3-phishing-scam-uses-fake-ai-platforms/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a phishing campaign by the LARVA-208 threat actor group targeting Web3 developers. The attackers use spearphishing links to lure victims into downloading malware disguised as a Realtek HD Audio Driver, which executes PowerShell commands and exfiltrates sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150688</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFake Interview Attack Leverages ClickFix Technique to Deploy GolangGhost Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/clickfake-interview-attack-leverages-clickfix-technique/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the "ClickFake Interview" campaign by Lazarus Group, a North Korean state-sponsored hacker outfit. This operation targets job seekers in the cryptocurrency and technology sectors with fake job interviews that lead to malware deployment. The campaign uses the "ClickFix" technique, which exploits human vulnerabilities and bypasses traditional security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150659</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Bans Public Sector from Paying Ransomware Gangs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uk-bans-public-sector-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</link>
      <description>The UK government has announced a comprehensive ban preventing public sector organizations from paying ransom demands to cybercriminals in an effort to disrupt the business model that makes ransomware attacks profitable. The ban aims to protect critical national infrastructure operators, including NHS trusts and schools, by prohibiting ransom payments to criminal groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150696</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Confirms Active Exploits Targeting ISE Flaws Enabling Unauthenticated Root Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-confirms-active-exploits.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20337, CVE-2025-20282; Summary: A set of critical-rated vulnerabilities (CVSS scores: 10.0) in Cisco's Identity Services Engine (ISE) and ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to issue commands, execute arbitrary code, or upload and execute files as the root user. The flaws stem from insufficient validation of user-supplied input and lack of file validation checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-confirms-active-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban public sector orgs from paying ransomware gangs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-to-ban-public-sector-orgs-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</link>
      <description>The UK government is planning to ban public sector and critical infrastructure organizations from paying ransoms after ransomware attacks. The proposed legislation aims to target the business model that fuels cybercriminals' activities and makes vital services less attractive targets for ransomware groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-to-ban-public-sector-orgs-from-paying-ransomware-gangs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credential Theft and Remote Access Surge as AllaKore, PureRAT, and Hijack Loader Proliferate</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/credential-theft-and-remote-access.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a long-running campaign targeting Mexican organizations with modified versions of AllaKore RAT and SystemBC. The attacks use phishing or drive-by compromises to distribute booby-trapped ZIP archives, which facilitate the deployment of AllaKore RAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/credential-theft-and-remote-access.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Alerts on ISE RCE Vulnerability Actively Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-alerts-on-ise-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282, CVE-2025-20337; Summary: A set of critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities affecting Cisco's Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) products are being actively exploited in the wild. The flaws allow unauthenticated attackers to gain root-level access to vulnerable systems with a CVSS base score of 10.0, and no viable workarounds exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150681</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-adds-four-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various (CrushFTP, Google Chromium ANGLE and GPU, SysAid On-Prem); CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2025-2776, CVE-2025-2775; Summary: Four new vulnerabilities have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to active exploitation. These vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and other organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23659</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert (PME) and EcoStruxure Power Operation (EPO); CVE(s): CVE-2025-6788; Summary: A resource exposure vulnerability exists that exposes TGML diagram resources to unauthorized control, allowing other authenticated users unauthorized access to TGML diagrams. Successful exploitation could provide potentially inappropriate access to TGML diagrams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23666</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxture IT Data Center Expert</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure IT Data Center Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50121, CVE-2025-50122, CVE-2025-50123, CVE-2025-50124, CVE-2025-6438; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities exist in Schneider Electric's EcoStruxure IT Data Center Expert, including OS command injection, insufficient entropy, code injection, server-side request forgery, improper privilege management, and XML external entity reference. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to disrupt operations, access system data, or gain unauthorized file access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23668</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Operation</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Operation; CVE(s): CVE-2023-50447, CVE-2022-45198, CVE-2024-28219, CVE-2023-35945, CVE-2023-44487; Summary: The EcoStruxure Power Operation (EPO) has multiple vulnerabilities including improper neutralization of directives in dynamically evaluated code ('Eval Injection'), integer overflow to buffer overflow, improper handling of highly compressed data (data amplification), out-of-bounds write, and uncontrolled resource consumption. Successful exploitation could result in the loss of system functionality or unauthorized access to system functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23663</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Two Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-adds-two-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: The two vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. These types of vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23670</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric System Monitor Application</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric System Monitor Application, Harmony Industrial PC series and Pro-face Industrial PC series; CVE(s): CVE-2020-11023; Summary: The vulnerability is a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) issue in the System Monitor Application. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute untrusted code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23667</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuraComm DP-10iN-100-MU</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: DuraComm Corporation SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41425, CVE-2025-48733, CVE-2025-53703; Summary: The SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU power distribution panel contains vulnerabilities that could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information or cause a denial-of-service condition. The vulnerabilities include cleartext transmission of sensitive information, missing authentication for a critical function, and improper neutralization of input during web page generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23664</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Nine Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/cisa-releases-nine-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released nine Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 22, 2025. These advisories provide information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits affecting ICS products from various vendors, including DuraComm, Lantronix, Schneider Electric, and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23669</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lantronix Provisioning Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-203-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lantronix Provisioning Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7766; Summary: The Lantronix Provisioning Manager contains an improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) Reference vulnerability, which can be exploited to perform cross-site scripting attacks and achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23665</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Advisory Issued on Protecting Against Interlock Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/22/joint-advisory-issued-protecting-against-interlock-ransomware</link>
      <description>The US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Agency (CISA) has issued a joint advisory with the FBI, Department of Health and Human Services, and Multi-State Information Sharing and Analysis Center to help protect businesses and critical infrastructure organizations against Interlock ransomware. The advisory provides indicators of compromise, tactics, techniques, and procedures identified through recent FBI investigations, along with recommended mitigations for reducing the risk of Interlock ransomware threat activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23656</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#StopRansomware: Interlock</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-203a</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an advisory on emerging ransomware threats, specifically the Interlock Ransomware gang. The report provides an in-depth analysis of the group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), as well as recommended mitigations and best practices for organizations to prevent and respond to such attacks.

As a cybersecurity analyst, I would categorize this article under "FYSA" since it is not discussing a specific vulnerability or product issue. Instead, it offers valuable insights into the tactics used by the Interlock Ransomware gang and provides guidance on how to improve defenses against these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23643</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Selling macOS 0-Day LPE Exploit on Dark Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-selling-macos-0-day-lpe-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: A threat actor claims to possess a zero-day Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) exploit targeting Apple's macOS operating system, offering the vulnerability for sale at $130,000. The alleged exploit could allow attackers to gain complete administrative control over compromised systems, bypassing Apple's built-in security mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Jena Vulnerability Allows Arbitrary File Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-jena-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Jena; CVEs: CVE-2025-49656, CVE-2025-50151; Summary: Two vulnerabilities in Apache Jena enable administrators to access and create files outside designated server directories, potentially compromising system security. The first vulnerability allows administrative users to create database files outside the intended directory boundaries, while the second vulnerability enables improper file access path validation, allowing administrators to reference and potentially access files anywhere on the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150670</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DCHSpy Android Malware Targets WhatsApp, Call Logs, Audio, and Photos</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-dchspy-android-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the discovery of four novel samples of DCHSpy, an advanced Android surveillanceware attributed to the Iranian threat actor group MuddyWater. The malware harvests sensitive information from infected devices and enables attackers to intercept WhatsApp communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150621</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Scanner Launched to Detect CVE-2025-53770 in SharePoint Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-scanner-to-detect-cve-2025-53770-in-sharepoint-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The vulnerability is an unauthenticated Remote Code Execution flaw affecting on-premise SharePoint deployments that have not been updated with Microsoft's security patches. The scanner, developed by Niels Hofmans, targets the vulnerability and allows administrators to detect exposure without causing damage to the target system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150655</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Sharepoint ToolShell attacks linked to Chinese hackers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-toolshell-attacks-linked-to-chinese-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Hackers with ties to the Chinese government exploited a zero-day vulnerability chain in Microsoft SharePoint, allowing them to breach dozens of organizations worldwide. The exploit chain, dubbed "ToolShell," provides unauthenticated access to systems and enables malicious actors to execute code over the network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-sharepoint-toolshell-attacks-linked-to-chinese-hackers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Sophos Firewall Flaws Allow Pre-Auth RCE</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sophos-firewall-flaws-allow-pre-auth-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6704, CVE-2025-7624, CVE-2025-7382, CVE-2024-13974, CVE-2024-13973; Summary: Multiple critical vulnerabilities were discovered in Sophos Firewall products, including remote code execution flaws and SQL injection vulnerabilities. The most severe flaw allows pre-authentication remote code execution through the Secure PDF eXchange (SPX) feature, while another vulnerability enables remote code execution when a quarantining policy is active for email.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150645</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Advance from SOC Manager to CISO?</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-advance-from-soc-manager-to-ciso.html</link>
      <description>This article provides guidance on the practical steps and skills needed to transition from managing a security operations center (SOC) to becoming a chief information security officer (CISO). It highlights the importance of developing strategic and leadership skills beyond technical expertise, as well as effective communication and risk management. The article also emphasizes the need for CISOs to understand the nuances of their role and adapt to different reporting structures and expectations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-advance-from-soc-manager-to-ciso.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft: Windows Server KB5062557 causes cluster, VM issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-kb5062557-causes-cluster-vm-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2019; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Cluster service on Windows Server 2019 may fail to function correctly after installing the July Windows security update, causing nodes to fail to rejoin the cluster or enter quarantine states, virtual machines to experience multiple restarts, and frequent Event ID 7031 errors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-windows-server-kb5062557-causes-cluster-vm-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Travel Agencies Exploit Cheap Deals to Steal Credit Card Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dark-web-travel-agencies-exploit-cheap-deals/</link>
      <description>Dark web travel agencies have developed into sophisticated organizations using hacked credit card information, compromised loyalty accounts, and fake identities to provide reduced travel services. They exploit popular booking aggregators, adapting quickly to blocked channels through advanced credential harvesting techniques. The article highlights the need for proactive, multi-layered defenses in the hospitality industry to combat these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150595</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Merge Android Malware with Click Fraud Apps to Harvest Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-merge-android-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article describes a campaign of active Android malware that combines brand impersonation with traffic monetization tactics. The malware exploits social engineering and off-market distribution channels to evade traditional security measures, preying on user trust to exfiltrate sensitive data such as login credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150557</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>wolfSSL Security Update Addresses Apple Trust Store Bypass</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wolfssl-security-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: wolfSSL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7394, CVE-2025-7395, CVE-2025-7396; Summary: The vulnerabilities affect users of wolfSSL versions after 5.7.6 and before 5.8.2 who utilize WOLFSSL_SYS_CA_CERTS and WOLFSSL_APPLE_NATIVE_CERT_VALIDATION features on Apple platforms. The most serious vulnerability allows malicious actors to bypass certificate verification processes, while the other two vulnerabilities relate to predictable random number generation and side-channel attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150591</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals from GLOBAL GROUP Target All Platforms with Golang Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-from-global-group-target/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation called GLOBAL GROUP, which is actually a rebranded version of the Mamona RIP and Black Lock ransomware families. The RaaS offers features such as automated negotiations, cross-platform payloads, and lucrative affiliate splits, but it leverages familiar foundations and shared code artifacts from previous ransomware operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150506</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Institutions Under Siege by Greedy Sponge Hackers’ Modified AllaKore RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/financial-institutions-under-siege-by-greedy-sponge-hackers/</link>
      <description>This article is about a threat actor group called Greedy Sponge that has been targeting Mexican organizations with a customized version of the AllaKore Remote Access Trojan (RAT) to steal banking credentials and authentication data. The malware, which can perform keylogging, screenshots, file uploads/downloads, and remote control capabilities, is delivered through spear-phishing and drive-by downloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit SharePoint Zero-Day Since July 7 to Steal Keys, Maintain Persistent Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-sharepoint-zero-day.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint is being actively exploited in the wild, putting thousands of global organizations at risk. The attack chain leverages a remote code execution flaw (CVE-2025-53770) and a spoofing vulnerability (CVE-2025-49706) to gain initial access and escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-sharepoint-zero-day.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Image Builder Vulnerability Grants Root Access to Windows Nodes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kubernetes-image-builder-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kubernetes Image Builder; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7342; Summary: A critical vulnerability in the Kubernetes Image Builder allows attackers to gain root access on Windows nodes by exploiting default credentials embedded in virtual machine images. The flaw affects images built with the Nutanix or OVA providers and can be exploited by logging in as the Administrator account, escalating privileges, and potentially compromising the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150543</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Reveals Just 10% Of Employees Drive 73% Of Cyber Risk</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-reveals-just-10-of-employees-drive-73-of-cyber-risk/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a report by Living Security and Cyentia Institute, titled "2025 State of Human Cyber Risk Report", which reveals that human risk in the workforce is concentrated among 10% of employees who account for 73% of risky behavior. The report highlights the importance of managing behavioral risk rather than just systems, and provides insights on how to reduce organizational risk exposure through strategic HRM programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150529</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak Password Enables Ransomware Attack on 158-Year-Old Firm</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weak-password-enables-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a specific vulnerability but highlights the devastating impact of cybersecurity vulnerabilities on British businesses. The case study of KNP, a logistics firm, demonstrates how a single compromised password can lead to catastrophic consequences, including ransomware attacks and data breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150501</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell Data Breach – World Leaks Group Hacks Test Lab Platform</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dell-data-breach/</link>
      <description>The World Leaks extortion group successfully infiltrated Dell Technologies' Customer Solution Centers platform, compromising a demonstration environment used to showcase products to commercial clients. The stolen information consists mainly of synthetic test data, publicly available datasets, and system data, with only an outdated contact list containing minimal operational significance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150496</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN Windows Client Flaw Could Expose User Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/expressvpn-windows-client-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ExpressVPN Windows Desktop Client; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows desktop client (versions 12.97 to 12.101.0.2-beta) had a vulnerability that could leak user connection details, specifically revealing their true IP address and RDP connections to on-network observers or internet service providers, although encryption remained intact. The issue was caused by debug code intended for internal testing but mistakenly shipped in production builds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150492</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Exploitation of Microsoft SharePoint Vulnerabilities: Threat Brief</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/microsoft-sharepoint-cve-2025-49704-cve-2025-49706-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: A set of high-impact vulnerabilities in on-premises Microsoft SharePoint servers allows unauthenticated threat actors to access restricted functionality and run arbitrary commands. The vulnerabilities have been actively exploited, and attackers are bypassing identity controls to gain privileged access and exfiltrate sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147463</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-626: (Pwn2Own) NVIDIA Container Toolkit Environment Variable Handling Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-626/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NVIDIA Container Toolkit by exploiting the handling of environment variables and lack of restrictions on spawning a hook process. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of the host system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27193</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-627: rocket.chat Incorrect Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-627/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: rocket.chat; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7974; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of rocket.chat, without requiring authentication. The issue is due to incorrect authorization within the web service listening on TCP port 3000 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel announces end of Clear Linux OS project, archives GitHub repos</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/intel-announces-end-of-clear-linux-os-project-archives-github-repos/</link>
      <description>Clear Linux OS has shut down after 10 years, and its user base is recommended to migrate to another distribution for security reasons, as it will no longer receive security patches or updates. The shutdown may be due to low user adoption and high maintenance burden, allowing Intel to focus on other projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/intel-announces-end-of-clear-linux-os-project-archives-github-repos/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Deploys Weaponized LNK Files with Cobalt Strike and Metasploit to Target Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ung0002-deploys-weaponized-lnk-files/</link>
      <description>A persistent threat entity, UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002), has been uncovered by Seqrite Labs, targeting critical sectors in Asia with sophisticated multi-stage attacks and evasive intrusion techniques. The group demonstrates adaptability, technical prowess, and a focus on intelligence gathering through espionage-driven operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150443</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolShell: Details of CVEs Affecting SharePoint Servers</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/toolshell-affecting-sharepoint-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Two path traversal vulnerabilities affecting SharePoint Server Subscription Edition, SharePoint Server 2016, and SharePoint Server 2019 allow for unauthenticated remote code execution. Patches have been provided for most versions, but SharePoint Server 2016 remains unpatched, and users are recommended to rotate their machine keys and enable Antimalware Scan Interface (AMSI) as an alternative mitigation measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687e91ad2e0cc100010c33cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeerStealer Malware Spread Through Weaponized .LNK and LOLBin Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/deerstealer-malware-spread-through-weaponized-lnk/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new wave of cyber-attacks that exploit Windows shortcut files (.LNK) and legitimate system utilities (LOLBin/S) to deliver the DeerStealer infostealer. The attacks use highly obfuscated multi-stage chains, leveraging MITRE ATT&amp;CK technique T1218.005, and employ anti-sandbox and anti-VM checks to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150434</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Compromise Popular npm Packages to Steal Maintainers’ Tokens</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-compromise-popular-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm; CVE(s): None; Summary: Phishing campaign targeting npm package maintainers resulted in the compromise of widely used JavaScript tooling libraries. Attackers utilized a typosquatted domain to trick developers into surrendering their authentication tokens, which were then used to publish malicious package versions directly to the npm registry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150429</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beware of npm Phishing Emails Targeting Developer Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beware-of-npm-phishing-emails/</link>
      <description>A highly advanced phishing email targeted npm package maintainers by spoofing the support@npmjs.org address and redirecting users to a malicious site that stole developer credentials. The campaign used unique tokens, semi-targeted approach, and infrastructure abuse to evade detection, highlighting the need for vigilance and proactive reporting to prevent supply chain attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150412</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ring denies breach after users report suspicious logins</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ring-denies-breach-after-users-report-suspicious-logins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ring; CVE(s): None; Summary: A backend update bug is causing unauthorized devices to be displayed as logged into customers' accounts, leading to concerns of a security incident. Customers are reporting unknown devices and countries listed in their Authorized Client Devices list, which cannot be previous logins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ring-denies-breach-after-users-report-suspicious-logins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint vulnerability with 9.8 severity rating under exploit across globe</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/sharepoint-vulnerability-with-9-8-severity-rating-is-under-exploit-across-the-globe/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: Attackers extract the ValidationKey directly from memory or configuration, allowing them to craft fully valid, signed __VIEWSTATE payloads and execute remote commands (RCE) without requiring credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/sharepoint-vulnerability-with-9-8-severity-rating-is-under-exploit-across-the-globe/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Use Zoho WorkDrive Folders to Spread Obfuscated PureRAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-use-zoho-workdrive-folders/</link>
      <description>A targeted attack was discovered against a U.S.-based certified public accounting firm using a novel crypter named "Ghost Crypt" to deliver PureRAT, a Remote Access Trojan (RAT). The attackers employed social engineering tactics and leveraged Zoho WorkDrive, a cloud-based file-sharing platform, to distribute malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150406</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT41 Hackers Exploiting Atexec and WmiExec Windows Modules for Malware Deployment</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt41-hackers-exploiting-atexec-and-wmiexec-windows-modules/</link>
      <description>This article reports a sophisticated targeted attack by APT41 against government IT services in the African region. The attackers used various tools and techniques to gain access to systems, including Impacket/WMI usage, DLL sideloading, and C2 domains. The attack was detected through suspicious activity on multiple workstations, and retrospective analysis revealed an IIS web server as the initial entry point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150375</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-625: Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager JobManagmentService Improper Access Control Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-625/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24286; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager, requiring authentication. The issue results from improper access control in the JobManagmentService component, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26062</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers Can Exploit Lighthouse Studio RCE Bug to Gain Server Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-can-exploit-lighthouse-studio-rce-bug/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sawtooth Software Lighthouse Studio; CVE(s): CVE-2025-34300; Summary: The Lighthouse Studio survey software contains a critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in its Perl CGI scripts, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on hosting servers. This flaw enables attackers to inject Perl code via specially crafted URL parameters, leveraging an eval sink that interprets content enclosed in [% … %] as executable code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150260</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran-Linked DCHSpy Android Malware Masquerades as VPN Apps to Spy on Dissidents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iran-linked-dchspy-android-malware.html</link>
      <description>Android spyware known as DCHSpy has been discovered by cybersecurity researchers at Lookout, which collects sensitive data such as WhatsApp information, accounts, contacts, SMS messages, call logs, files, location, and audio recordings. The malware is believed to be affiliated with the Iranian Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS) and has been distributed via masquerading VPN apps and Starlink-related lures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iran-linked-dchspy-android-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAWA4096 Ransomware Employs WMI Techniques to Delete Backup Snapshots</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kawa4096-ransomware-employs-wmi-techniques/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the KAWA4096 ransomware, a new strain detected in June 2025. It targets entities in the United States and Japan, using multithreaded encryption, network share targeting, and evasion tactics to amplify disruption. The ransomware embeds its configuration within the binary, terminates antivirus processes, and erases Volume Shadow Copies to hinder data recovery efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150351</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-621: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 DHCP Configuration Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-621/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25269, ZDI-CAN-26350, ZDI-25-621; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices without authentication. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call, which can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26350</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-622: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 Configuration Service Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-622/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25268; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the configuration service that listens on TCP port 5001 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26331</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-623: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 Origin Validation Error Firewall Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-623/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25270; Summary: The Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3150 device has an origin validation error that allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass firewall rules and access another interface without authentication. The vulnerability exists in the configuration of firewall rules and can be exploited by leveraging other vulnerabilities to execute code with root privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26332</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-624: (Pwn2Own) Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-624/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100; CVE(s): CVE-2024-25995; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Phoenix Contact CHARX SEC-3100 devices without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the default routemetric parameter to the config service, resulting from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-23328</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Cloaking Tools Help Threat Actors Hide Malicious Domains from Security Scans</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-powered-cloaking-tools-help-threat-actors/</link>
      <description>Threat actors are increasingly using AI-powered cloaking services to evade automated security scanners and prolong the operational lifespan of their infrastructure. These services analyze visitor attributes such as IP geolocation, user-agent strings, and browser entropy to classify and reroute requests, ensuring only targeted human users encounter the payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150320</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked Hackers Launch Targeted Espionage Campaign on African IT Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-linked-hackers-launch-targeted.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on a Chinese nation-state hacking group, tracked as APT41, which has launched a new campaign targeting government IT services in the African region. The attackers used hardcoded names of internal services, IP addresses, and proxy servers embedded within their malware to communicate with command-and-control (C2) servers, including a hacked SharePoint server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-linked-hackers-launch-targeted.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpressVPN bug leaked user IPs in Remote Desktop sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/expressvpn-bug-leaked-user-ips-in-remote-desktop-sessions/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ExpressVPN; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows client of ExpressVPN had a flaw that caused Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) traffic to bypass the virtual private network (VPN) tunnel, exposing users' real IP addresses. The issue was caused by remnants of debug code used for internal testing being mistakenly included in production builds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/expressvpn-bug-leaked-user-ips-in-remote-desktop-sessions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Recovery Orchestrator users locked out after MFA rollout</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/veeam-recovery-orchestrator-users-locked-out-after-mfa-rollout/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam Recovery Orchestrator; CVE(s): None; Summary: The recently released version of Recovery Orchestrator (build 7.2.1.286) blocks Web UI logins after enabling multi-factor authentication (MFA). This issue has been fixed with the release of version 7.2.1.290, and customers who installed the buggy version are advised to contact technical support for assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/technology/veeam-recovery-orchestrator-users-locked-out-after-mfa-rollout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Fix Targets Attacks on SharePoint Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/microsoft-fix-targets-attacks-on-sharepoint-zero-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint Server is actively being exploited to compromise vulnerable organizations, allowing attackers to execute code over the network and steal ASP.NET machine keys. The patch comes amid reports of breaches in U.S. federal and state agencies, universities, and energy companies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71737</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dior begins sending data breach notifications to U.S. customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dior-begins-sending-data-breach-notifications-to-us-customers/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a data breach incident at House of Dior, a French luxury fashion house, which affected U.S. customers' personal information. The breach occurred on January 26, 2025, and was only discovered on May 7, 2025. The compromised database contained full names, contact details, physical addresses, date of birth, passport or government ID number (in some cases), and Social Security Number (in some cases).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dior-begins-sending-data-breach-notifications-to-us-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Keylogger Uses Persistence via Scheduled Tasks to Steal Login Data Undetected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/snake-keylogger-uses-persistence-via-scheduled-tasks/</link>
      <description>Researchers have identified a sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Turkish enterprises, particularly defense and aerospace industries. The campaign involves emails masquerading as legitimate contractual documents from Turkish Aerospace Industries (TUSAŞ), which contain malware that steals sensitive data such as credentials, cookies, and financial details without detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150310</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Release PoC Exploit for High-Severity NVIDIA AI Toolkit Bug</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-release-poc-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit (NCT); CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: A severe vulnerability in NCT allows malicious containers to escape isolation and gain root access on host systems. The flaw stems from a misconfiguration in OCI hook handling, affecting NCT versions up to 1.17.7 and NVIDIA GPU Operator up to 25.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150208</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal Listings Target Fujitsu, Baxter Kelly, AGX Financeira, and a Belgian IT Platform</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cybercriminal-listings-target-fujitsu-baxter-kelly-agx-financeira-and-a-belgian-it-platform/</link>
      <description>This article reports on several new listings for unauthorized access sales and data breaches affecting companies across Japan, the U.K., Brazil, and Belgium. The listings include sensitive internal files, Citrix access, customer data, and administrative control over a monitoring system, with prices ranging from $1,500 to $20,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061978</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolShell Campaign: New SharePoint Zero-Day (CVE-2025-53770) Triggers Widespread Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/toolshell-sharepoint-zero-day-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint, identified as CVE-2025-53770, is actively being exploited in targeted attacks. The vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication, gain remote code execution capabilities, and establish persistent access using stolen cryptographic keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061964</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHP PDO Flaw Allows Attackers to Inject Malicious SQL Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/php-pdo-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PHP PDO; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious SQL commands by exploiting weaknesses in PDO's SQL parser. This affects millions of web applications worldwide, even when developers implement prepared statements correctly. Attackers can manipulate PDO's parsing logic through carefully constructed payloads, leading to SQL injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150385</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: SharePoint 0-Day, Chrome Exploit, macOS Spyware, NVIDIA Toolkit RCE and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a summary of various cyber-related incidents, attacks, and trends from around the world. The article discusses malware families like Rainbow Hyena, DiskStation Security, and Katz Stealer; phishing campaigns targeting specific industries or organizations; and large-scale cyber thefts affecting financial institutions and other entities.

There are no explicit discussions about vulnerabilities in software, hardware, or firmware within this article. However, the article does touch upon various cybersecurity concerns and threats that could potentially impact different systems and organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 CrushFTP servers exposed to ongoing hijack attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: All CrushFTP versions below 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23 are vulnerable to hijack attacks that exploit a critical security bug due to mishandled AS2 validation, allowing admin access to the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Role of AI in Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in Zero Trust architecture, highlighting its capabilities in adaptive trust, continuous risk evaluation, and automation. It also emphasizes the importance of human-machine teaming, where AI amplifies human decision-making rather than replacing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Firm Exploits SS7 Flaw to Track User Locations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surveillance-firm-exploits-ss7-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SS7 (Signaling System No. 7) protocol; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated surveillance operation has been discovered exploiting critical vulnerabilities in the global telecommunications infrastructure to track mobile phone users' locations without authorization. The attack leverages weaknesses in the decades-old SS7 protocol that underpins international cellular networks, manipulating the TCAP layer and using an obscure encoding technique called "extended tag encoding" to disguise malicious location tracking requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn 14 Languages from Babbel with this exclusive StackSocial deal</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</link>
      <description>The article is promoting language learning platforms Babbel, uTalk, and Rosetta Stone, offering lifetime subscriptions and discounts. It highlights the features of each platform, such as AI conversation partners and personalized review sessions. The article also includes a free board report deck for CISOs to present cloud security risks and priorities in business terms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell confirms breach of test lab platform by World Leaks extortion group</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</link>
      <description>World Leaks, a rebranded extortion gang, has breached Dell's product demonstration platform and is trying to extort the company into paying a ransom. The stolen data is believed to be synthetic test data used in product demonstrations and trials, with only a very outdated contact list being legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinDCX Hack Leads to $44.2 Million Loss</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coindcx-hack-leads-to-44-2-million-loss/</link>
      <description>CoinDCX, an Indian cryptocurrency exchange, suffered a significant security breach that resulted in approximately $44 million in losses. Despite the incident, customer funds remain secure and unaffected, thanks to the company's segregated account architecture. The investigation is ongoing to identify vulnerabilities, implement additional safety measures, and trace the movement of compromised funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150352</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE‑2025‑37103: Remote Access Risk in Aruba Instant On Access Points Due to Hardcoded Passwords</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve202537103-aruba-instant-on-hardcoded-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, CVE-2025-37102; Summary: The Aruba Instant On access points contain a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-37103) that allows remote access to the device's web interface without authentication due to a hardcoded admin password. This flaw can be exploited to gain administrative access and launch lateral attacks across the internal network, and when combined with CVE-2025-37102, it enables command injection and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061953</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-54309: New CrushFTP Zero-Day Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-54309-new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in CrushFTP allows attackers to gain administrator-level access through the HTTPS interface on unpatched servers, enabling file theft, privilege escalation, and deeper network compromise. The flaw affects versions prior to 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23, and building released after July 1, 2025, contain the fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061943</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AppLocker Flaw Lets Malicious Apps Bypass Security Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-applocker-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft AppLocker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft's AppLocker security feature allows malicious applications to bypass established security restrictions by exploiting a seemingly minor error in the MaximumFileVersion field. Attackers could potentially modify a blocked executable's version number to exceed the configured maximum version, but this would simultaneously break the file's digital signature, making it detectable by systems configured with "signed executables only" policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150306</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Livewire Flaw Puts Millions of Laravel Apps at Risk of RCE Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/livewire-flaw-of-rce-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Livewire; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54068; Summary: A critical remote command execution vulnerability exists in Livewire versions from 3.0.0-beta.1 to 3.6.3, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the server by injecting malicious code through property updates. Exploitation requires only a vulnerable component with default configuration, and no user authentication or interaction is necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
