<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Four arrested in UK over M&amp;S, Co-op, Harrod cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrod-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>The UK's National Crime Agency (NCA) arrested four individuals suspected of involvement in cyberattacks on major retailers, including Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, and Harrods. The attacks were attributed to threat actors classified as Scattered Spider, with a history of breaches over the past few years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrod-cyberattacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Arrested in £440M Cyber Attack on Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, and Harrods</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/four-arrested-in-440m-cyber-attack-on.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on the arrest of four individuals suspected of being involved in cyber attacks targeting major retailers in the UK. The attacks are believed to be perpetrated by a decentralized cybercrime group called Scattered Spider, which is notorious for its advanced social engineering tactics and willingness to be persistent in gaining initial access to targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/four-arrested-in-440m-cyber-attack-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Dark Web Monitoring Work? A Step-by-Step Overview</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/how-does-dark-web-monitoring-work-overview/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the process of dark web monitoring, which involves scanning hidden forums, leak sites, and underground marketplaces to detect stolen data, compromised credentials, and brand misuse. The article explains how this process works, from data collection to alert generation and integration with broader security systems. It also highlights the importance of accuracy, real-time delivery, and integration with existing security infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061742</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Security Leaders Need to Know About AI Governance for SaaS</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/what-security-leaders-need-to-know.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the increasing adoption of generative AI in software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications and the need for AI governance to ensure responsible use and minimize risks. It highlights concerns around data exposure, compliance violations, and operational issues that can arise from uncontrolled AI usage. The article emphasizes the importance of visibility, centralized strategy, and regular monitoring to prevent shadow AI instances and potential security breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/what-security-leaders-need-to-know.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ZuRu Malware Variant Targeting Developers via Trojanized Termius macOS App</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-macos-malware-zuru-targeting.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The ZuRu malware has been observed propagating via trojanized versions of legitimate software, including Termius, a cross-platform SSH client and server-management tool. The malware uses Khepri, an open-source post-exploitation toolkit, to gain remote control of infected hosts, and employs a modified loader and C2 techniques to backdoor its targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-macos-malware-zuru-targeting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD Warns of New Transient Scheduler Attacks Impacting a Wide Range of CPUs</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/amd-warns-of-new-transient-scheduler.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AMD; CVE(s): CVE-2024-36350, CVE-2024-36357, CVE-2024-36348, CVE-2024-36349; Summary: A set of vulnerabilities, collectively called Transient Scheduler Attacks (TSA), affects a broad range of AMD chipsets, allowing an attacker to infer data from previous stores and potentially leading to information leakage. The flaws manifest as speculative side channels in CPUs that leverage execution timing of instructions under specific microarchitectural conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/amd-warns-of-new-transient-scheduler.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix the Click: Preventing the ClickFix Attack Vector</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/preventing-clickfix-attack-vector/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This article appears to be an analysis of various cyber threats and tactics used by malicious actors. The article discusses different types of malware, including AutoIT, Lumma Stealer, and NetSupport RAT, as well as other techniques such as social engineering, typosquatting, and malvertising.

The article also highlights the use of legitimate software and tools, such as PowerShell, FileZilla, and Microsoft Windows, in malicious campaigns. Additionally, it discusses the role of cloud-based services and Linux systems in these attacks.

Overall, this article provides an overview of various cyber threats and tactics used by malicious actors, highlighting the importance of staying vigilant and proactive in protecting against these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=145728</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow Flaw CVE-2025-3648 Could Lead to Data Exposure via Misconfigured ACLs</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/servicenow-flaw-cve-2025-3648-could.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceNow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3648; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in ServiceNow's Now Platform allows unauthenticated users to infer and expose confidential data from various tables. The flaw is due to conditional access control list (ACL) rules, which can be exploited by malicious actors to obtain unauthorized access to sensitive information, including personally identifiable information (PII) and credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/servicenow-flaw-cve-2025-3648-could.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Violent Extremists Likely Shifting Focus to Targeted Physical Threats in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/us-violent-extremists-shifting-focus-targeted-physical-threats-2025</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I analyzed the provided article and found it to be a strategic threat assessment report from a credible source. The report provides an in-depth analysis of various terrorist organizations, their capabilities, and potential threats to the United States and its interests.

The report covers several key topics, including:

1. IS and Al-Qaeda: The report highlights the ongoing threat posed by these two terrorist organizations, which continue to inspire attacks and recruit supporters worldwide.
2. Hamas: The report notes that while mass-casualty attacks are unlikely, small-scale violence and sporadic incidents cannot be ruled out.
3. Iran and its proxies: The report suggests that Iran's military and intelligence agencies may attempt to recruit or incite threat actors to conduct targeted attacks against US politicians and Iranian dissidents on US soil.
4. Hezbollah and the Houthis: The report notes that these groups have not demonstrated an interest in conducting attacks in the United States, with Hezbollah being particularly weakened by leadership losses.

The report provides valuable insights into the current terrorist landscape and potential threats to national security. It is essential for policymakers, law enforcement agencies, and intelligence communities to stay informed about these developments to ensure effective counterterrorism strategies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/us-violent-extremists-shifting-focus-targeted-physical-threats-2025</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Authenticator on iOS moves backups fully to iCloud</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-authenticator-on-ios-moves-backups-fully-to-icloud/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is rolling out a new backup system for its Authenticator app on iOS, removing the requirement to use a Microsoft personal account. The new system will store backups in iCloud and restore them automatically on new devices using the same Apple account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-authenticator-on-ios-moves-backups-fully-to-icloud/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 22:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) sync is broken</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-windows-server-update-services-wsus-sync-is-broken/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft WSUS; CVE(s): None; Summary: A widespread issue in Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) prevents organizations from syncing with Microsoft Update and deploying the latest Windows updates. The problem is caused by a "problematic update revision in the storage layer" that affects devices trying to synchronize updates from Microsoft Updates using WSUS or Configuration Manager.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-windows-server-update-services-wsus-sync-is-broken/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 20:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qantas confirms data breach impacts 5.7 million customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-confirms-data-breach-impacts-57-million-customers/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a data breach at Qantas airline, where threat actors stole personal data from approximately 5.7 million customers. The stolen data includes names, email addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information. The attackers are believed to be Scattered Spider, a group known for targeting the aviation industry with social engineering attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-confirms-data-breach-impacts-57-million-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 20:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browser extensions turn nearly 1 million browsers into website-scraping bots</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/browser-extensions-turn-nearly-1-million-browsers-into-website-scraping-bots/</link>
      <description>The article discusses security concerns related to MellowTel and its ability to open unknown sites, which can compromise end users' trust in the vetting process. This raises risks for enterprise networks that restrict code and site access. Additionally, the article highlights a previous analysis of browser extensions that collected sensitive user data without consent, including proprietary information from various companies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/browser-extensions-turn-nearly-1-million-browsers-into-website-scraping-bots/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 20:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google reveals details on Android’s Advanced Protection for Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-reveals-details-on-androids-advanced-protection-for-chrome/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the security improvements brought by Google's Advanced Protection program for Android mobile users. With the release of Android 16, Advanced Protection can be activated from the settings, enhancing security measures across Google apps like Chrome, Messages, and Phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-reveals-details-on-androids-advanced-protection-for-chrome/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 19:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Depot breach exposes data of nearly 27,000 crypto users</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitcoin-depot-breach-exposes-data-of-nearly-27-000-crypto-users/</link>
      <description>Bitcoin Depot's data breach has exposed sensitive information of nearly 27,000 customers, including names, phone numbers, driver's license numbers, addresses, dates of birth, and email addresses. The incident occurred on June 23, 2024, but public disclosure was delayed due to an ongoing investigation by federal agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bitcoin-depot-breach-exposes-data-of-nearly-27-000-crypto-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 17:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Melody IAB Exploits Exposed ASP.NET Machine Keys for Unauthorized Access to Targets</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/gold-melody-iab-exploits-exposed-aspnet.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on an Initial Access Broker (IAB) called Gold Melody, which exploits leaked ASP.NET machine keys to obtain unauthorized access to organizations. The IAB uses the exploited keys to sign malicious payloads that provide access to targeted servers through ASP.NET ViewState deserialization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/gold-melody-iab-exploits-exposed-aspnet.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruckus Networks leaves severe flaws unpatched in management devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ruckus-networks-leaves-severe-flaws-unpatched-in-management-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ruckus Wireless; CVE(s): CVE-2025-44957, CVE-2025-44962, CVE-2025-44954, CVE-2025-44960, CVE-2025-44961, CVE-2025-44963, CVE-2025-44955, CVE-2025-6243, CVE-2025-44958; Summary: Multiple unpatched vulnerabilities in Ruckus Wireless management products, including remote code execution, hardcoded passwords, and hardcoded SSH public and private keys, could allow an attacker to fully compromise the network environment they serve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ruckus-networks-leaves-severe-flaws-unpatched-in-management-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingram Micro starts restoring systems after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-starts-restoring-systems-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>Ingram Micro suffered a SafePay ransomware attack, resulting in a global outage and forced employees to work from home. The company is currently restoring systems and business services, but it's unclear if data was stolen during the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-starts-restoring-systems-after-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury sanctions North Korean over IT worker malware scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/treasury-sanctions-north-korean-over-it-worker-malware-scheme/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury has sanctioned Song Kum Hyok, a cyber actor associated with North Korea's Andariel hacking group, for facilitating IT worker schemes that generated revenue for the Pyongyang regime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/treasury-sanctions-north-korean-over-it-worker-malware-scheme/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 14:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MFA You Trust Is Lying to You – and Here's How Attackers Exploit It</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-mfa-you-trust-is-lying-to-you-and-heres-how-attackers-exploit-it/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the vulnerabilities of using one-time passwords (OTP) sent via SMS or authenticator apps for multi-factor authentication (MFA). It highlights how these methods can be easily phished, relayed, or intercepted by attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-mfa-you-trust-is-lying-to-you-and-heres-how-attackers-exploit-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 2025 Patch Tuesday Overview: 130 Vulnerabilities &amp; One Disclosed Zero-Day (CVE-2025-49719)</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/july-2025-patch-tuesday-130-flaws-cve-2025-49719/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49719; Summary: An information disclosure vulnerability in Microsoft SQL Server allows an unauthenticated attacker to potentially access uninitialized memory, exposing sensitive information. The risk of exploitation is low, but users should update SQL Server to the latest version and applications built on SQL Server should update to Microsoft OLE DB Driver version 18 or 19.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061729</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 13:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoNot APT Expands Operations, Targets European Foreign Ministries with LoptikMod Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/donot-apt-expands-operations-targets.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on a targeted attack by an Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) group called DoNot Team against a European foreign affairs ministry. The attack uses custom-built Windows malware, including backdoors like YTY and GEdit, delivered through spear-phishing emails or malicious documents. The malware can harvest sensitive data from compromised hosts and establish persistence on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/donot-apt-expands-operations-targets.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ServiceNow flaw lets attackers enumerate restricted data</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-servicenow-flaw-lets-attackers-enumerate-restricted-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ServiceNow; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3648; Summary: A vulnerability in ServiceNow allows low-privileged users to extract sensitive data from tables to which they should not have access. The issue is due to permissive ACLs that grant access if a user satisfies just one ACL, even if other ACLs would block them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-servicenow-flaw-lets-attackers-enumerate-restricted-data/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Sanctions North Korean Andariel Hacker Behind Fraudulent IT Worker Scheme</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-sanctions-north-korean-andariel.html</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned a member of a North Korean hacking group called Andariel for their role in an IT worker scheme. The scheme involved using foreign-hired IT workers to seek remote employment with US companies, and the sanctions are part of efforts to disrupt North Korea's ability to generate revenue through illicit means.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/us-sanctions-north-korean-andariel.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical CitrixBleed 2 vulnerability has been under active exploit for weeks</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/critical-citrixbleed-2-vulnerability-has-been-under-active-exploit-for-weeks/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of providing detailed security advisories and indicators to help defenders detect and respond to critical vulnerabilities. It highlights how Citrix's decision to withhold technical details about a recent vulnerability has allowed attackers to gain an advantage, making it harder for customers to identify compromised devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/critical-citrixbleed-2-vulnerability-has-been-under-active-exploit-for-weeks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Automate Ticket Creation, Device Identification and Threat Triage With Tines</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-automate-ticket-creation-device.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a pre-built workflow in Tines, a workflow orchestration and AI platform, that automates the process of responding to malware security alerts from CrowdStrike. The workflow involves integrating with various platforms such as Oomnitza, GitHub, PagerDuty, and Slack to streamline the response to malware threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-to-automate-ticket-creation-device.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hacker Xu Zewei Arrested for Ties to Silk Typhoon Group and U.S. Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hacker-xu-zewei-arrested-for.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on the alleged involvement of Chinese national Xu Zewei and state-sponsored hacking group Silk Typhoon (also known as UNC5221) in cyber attacks against American organizations and government agencies, including exploiting zero-day flaws in Microsoft Exchange Server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hacker-xu-zewei-arrested-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patches 130 Vulnerabilities, Including Critical Flaws in SPNEGO and SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-patches-130-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SQL Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49719; Summary: The vulnerability is an information disclosure flaw that could permit an unauthorized attacker to leak uninitialized memory. This could allow attackers to retrieve remnants of sensitive data, such as credentials or connection strings. The flaw likely results from improper input validation in SQL Server's memory management, allowing access to uninitialized memory.

FYSA: An 11-month streak of patching at least one zero-day that was exploited in the wild ended this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-patches-130-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday, July 2025 Edition</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/microsoft-patch-tuesday-july-2025-edition/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SQL Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49719, None; Summary: A publicly disclosed information disclosure vulnerability (CVE-2025-49719) affects all versions of SQL Server as far back as 2016, allowing sensitive information to be exposed without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71624</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-555: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-555/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7308; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26389</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-556: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-556/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7310; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data during DWG file parsing. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26393</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-557: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-557/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7309; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26391</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-558: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-558/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7311; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26395</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-559: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-559/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7312; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains an out-of-bounds read remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26398</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-560: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-560/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7313; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing DWG files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26399</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-561: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-561/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7314; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains a memory corruption remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26400</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-562: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-562/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7315; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, and the attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26408</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-563: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-563/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7316; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin suffers from a remote code execution vulnerability due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data during DWG file parsing, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code with user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26410</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-564: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-564/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7317; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin is vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data during DWG file parsing. An attacker can exploit this by requiring user interaction, such as visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, resulting in memory corruption and arbitrary code execution in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26411</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-565: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-565/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7318; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files and results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26412</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-566: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-566/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7319; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains an out-of-bounds read remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, and the issue exists in the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26413</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-567: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-567/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7320; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DXF files, requiring user interaction. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26418</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-568: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-568/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7321; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin is vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability due to memory corruption in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26421</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-569: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-569/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7322; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26423</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-570: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-570/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7323; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files and can result in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26428</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-571: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-571/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7324; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists in the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26430</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-572: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-572/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7325; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction to exploit. The issue exists in the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26434</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-573: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-573/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7299; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files, requiring user interaction. The issue stems from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26376</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-574: Siemens SINEC NMS reqToChangePassword Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-574/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SINEC NMS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40736; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Siemens SINEC NMS, with no prior authentication required. The flaw exists within the implementation of the reqToChangePassword method and results in access to password change functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26569</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-575: Siemens SINEC NMS unZipJarFilestoLocation Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-575/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SINEC NMS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40737; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens SINEC NMS. Authentication is required, but the existing mechanism can be bypassed due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26571</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-576: Siemens SINEC NMS uploadFWBinary Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-576/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens SINEC NMS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40738; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Siemens SINEC NMS, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The flaw exists in the implementation of the uploadFWBinary method due to improper validation of a user-supplied path prior to file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-577: Microsoft Windows AppX Deployment Service Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-577/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48820; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26358</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-578: Microsoft Windows win32kfull Integer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-578/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49742; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which results from an integer overflow before writing to memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26768</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-579: Microsoft PC Manager Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-579/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft PC Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47993; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft PC Manager. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26249</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-580: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft SharePoint ToolPane Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-580/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint, with no required authentication needed for exploitation. The flaw exists in the handling of the Referer HTTP header provided to the ToolPane endpoint, allowing an attacker to access a protected API and bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27162</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-581: (Pwn2Own) Microsoft SharePoint DataSetSurrogateSelector Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-581/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Microsoft SharePoint Server by deserializing untrusted data, bypassing existing authentication mechanisms. The flaw exists within the DataSetSurrogateSelector class due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27247</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-582: Microsoft Windows Startup Folder SmartScreen Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-582/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49740; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the SmartScreen security feature on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by exploiting the handling of executables in the user's Startup folder. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27246</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-583: Microsoft Windows win32kfull Out-Of-Bounds Write Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-583/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows win32kfull; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49732; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows by writing before the start of an allocated array. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can result in executing arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26791</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-584: Microsoft Windows win32kfull Out-Of-Bounds Write Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-584/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49727; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data and can be used to write past the end of an allocated buffer, allowing for privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27167</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-585: Trend Micro Maximum Security Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-585/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Maximum Security; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52521, ZDI-CAN-26887; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Maximum Security by creating a junction and abusing the Platinum Host Service to delete arbitrary files. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability, which can then be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26887</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-586: Trend Micro Password Manager Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-586/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Password Manager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52837; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Password Manager by exploiting a flaw within the Trend Micro Password Manager Service. The attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system and can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25729</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung announces major security enhancements coming to One UI 8</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/samsung-announces-major-security-enhancements-coming-to-one-ui-8/</link>
      <description>Samsung has announced multiple data security and privacy enhancements for its upcoming Galaxy smartphones running One UI 8, including the introduction of Knox Enhanced Encrypted Protection (KEEP), upgrades to Knox Matrix, and the addition of quantum resistance to WiFi connectivity. The updates aim to protect user inputs, sensitive data, and cloud-connected services from unauthorized access and manipulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/samsung-announces-major-security-enhancements-coming-to-one-ui-8/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;S confirms social engineering led to massive ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-confirms-social-engineering-led-to-massive-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>M&amp;S experienced a sophisticated impersonation attack that led to a DragonForce ransomware attack, with the threat actors impersonating an employee's details to trick a third-party entity into resetting their password. The attackers used social engineering tactics and exploited a third-party help desk support system to breach the company's network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-confirms-social-engineering-led-to-massive-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday for July 2025 — Snort rules and prominent vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-july-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49735, CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49695, CVE-2025-49696, CVE-2025-49697, CVE-2025-49698, CVE-2025-49702, CVE-2025-49703, CVE-2025-48822, CVE-2025-47981, CVE-2025-49717; Summary: Microsoft released 132 vulnerabilities in July 2025, including 14 critical ones. The vulnerable products include Windows services and applications, SharePoint server, Office, and SQL Server. The vulnerabilities are remote code execution (RCE) vulnerabilities, out-of-bounds read, use after free, heap-based buffer overflow, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">686d5fdf5df3de0001555dcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-483: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-483/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7251; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26108</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-484: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-484/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7252; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds read remote code execution vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this by persuading the target to visit a malicious page or open a malicious file, allowing them to execute arbitrary code on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26109</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-485: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-485/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7235; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by writing past the end of an allocated buffer due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26075</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-486: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-486/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7250; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains an out-of-bounds read remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The vulnerability exists in the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26107</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-487: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-487/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7236; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26080</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-488: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-488/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7240; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting memory corruption through the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26086</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-489: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-489/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7241; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26087</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-490: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-490/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7242; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data that can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26088</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-491: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-491/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7243; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists in the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26091</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-492: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-492/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7249; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26100</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-493: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-493/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7253; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26112</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-494: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-494/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7233; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information by parsing out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26072</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-495: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-495/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7234; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CGM files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26074</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-496: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-496/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7254; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing DXF files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition. User interaction is required for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26113</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-497: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-497/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7244; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26093</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-498: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-498/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7246; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing malicious DWG files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26095</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-499: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-499/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7247; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting an out-of-bounds read in the parsing of DXF files. User interaction is required, and the attack vector involves visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26096</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-500: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-500/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7255; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26118</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-501: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-501/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7248; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26098</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-502: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-502/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7256; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DXF files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26119</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-503: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-503/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7257; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF file parsing memory corruption remote code execution vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of the plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26126</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-504: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-504/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7237; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting memory corruption in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26083</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-505: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-505/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7238; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and it occurs when the plugin parses DXF files without proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26084</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-506: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-506/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7239; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26085</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-507: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-507/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7258; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains an out-of-bounds write remote code execution vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue occurs due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26127</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-508: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-508/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7260; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26129</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-509: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-509/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7261; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists in the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26130</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-510: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-510/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7262; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26132</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-511: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-511/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7263; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing CGM files. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26170</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-512: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-512/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7264; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by reading past the end of an allocated buffer during CGM file parsing. User interaction is required, and the attack can occur when a user visits a malicious page or opens a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26171</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-513: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-513/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7265; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of CGM files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26173</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-514: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-514/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7266; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26174</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-515: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-515/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7267; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26179</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-516: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-516/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7268; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26182</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-517: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-517/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7269; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists within the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26188</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-518: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-518/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7270; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26189</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-519: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-519/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7273; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26202</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-520: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-520/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7271; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin is vulnerable to a remote code execution vulnerability due to improper validation of user-supplied data during DXF file parsing. User interaction is required for exploitation, which involves visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26193</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-521: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-521/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7272; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the DXF file parsing. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26198</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-522: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-522/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7275; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of the plugin. User interaction is required, and the issue exists within the parsing of CGM files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in an out-of-bounds read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26204</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-523: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-523/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7276; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26208</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-524: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-524/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7277; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists within the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26209</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-525: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-525/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7274; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26203</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-526: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-526/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7278; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The flaw exists in the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26211</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-527: IrfanView CADImage Plugin CGM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-527/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7279; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CGM files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26213</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-528: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-528/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7280; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26214</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-529: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-529/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7281; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26215</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-530: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-530/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7282; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DXF files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26216</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-531: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-531/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7283; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing DWG files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26219</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-532: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-532/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7286; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26222</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-533: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-533/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7287; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26223</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-534: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-534/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7288; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26224</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-535: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-535/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7289; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26225</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-536: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-536/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7284; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26220</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-537: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-537/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7285; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DXF files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26221</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-538: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-538/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7290; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26226</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-539: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-539/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7291; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing DXF files without proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26227</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-540: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-540/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7292; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26228</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-541: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-541/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7293; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin, requiring user interaction. The issue exists within the parsing of DXF files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26229</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-542: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-542/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7298; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26246</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-543: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-543/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7294; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing DXF files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26230</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-544: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-544/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7295; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26242</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-545: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-545/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7297; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin contains a remote code execution vulnerability due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing DWG files. An attacker can exploit this by visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, requiring user interaction, and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26244</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-546: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DXF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-546/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7296; Summary: The IrfanView CADImage Plugin has a remote code execution vulnerability due to memory corruption caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing DXF files. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by tricking a target into visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, allowing for arbitrary code execution in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26243</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-547: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-547/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7300; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by parsing malicious DWG files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26377</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-548: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-548/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7301; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26380</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-549: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-549/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7302; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting a memory corruption condition in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26381</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-550: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-550/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7303; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by parsing malicious DWG files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26384</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-551: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-551/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7304; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26385</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-552: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-552/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7305; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin by exploiting memory corruption in the parsing of DWG files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26386</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-553: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-553/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7306; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a memory corruption condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26387</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-554: IrfanView CADImage Plugin DWG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-554/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: IrfanView CADImage Plugin; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7307; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of IrfanView CADImage Plugin. User interaction is required, and the flaw exists within the parsing of DWG files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26388</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Android TapTrap attack fools users with invisible UI trick</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-android-taptrap-attack-fools-users-with-invisible-ui-trick/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel tapjacking technique called TapTrap can exploit user interface animations to bypass Android's permission system and allow access to sensitive data or trick users into performing destructive actions, such as wiping the device. This vulnerability affects Android 15 and 16 and allows malicious apps to launch a harmless transparent activity on top of a malicious one, remaining unmitigated in these versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-android-taptrap-attack-fools-users-with-invisible-ui-trick/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5062554 cumulative update released with 13 changes, fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5062554-cumulative-update-released-with-13-changes-fixes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): One zero-day vulnerability and 136 other flaws; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5062554 cumulative update contains fixes for one zero-day vulnerability and 136 other flaws. It is mandatory and will automatically start installing once checked for updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5062554-cumulative-update-released-with-13-changes-fixes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use Leaked Shellter Tool License to Spread Lumma Stealer and SectopRAT Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-use-leaked-shellter-tool.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Shellter; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers are exploiting a popular red teaming tool called Shellter to distribute stealer malware. The tool allows offensive security teams to bypass antivirus and endpoint detection and response (EDR) software installed on endpoints, making it a powerful tool in the wrong hands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-use-leaked-shellter-tool.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5062553 &amp; KB5062552  cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062553-and-kb5062552-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>There are no specific cybersecurity-related vulnerabilities or threats mentioned in this article. The article is focused on describing the new features and updates included in the latest Windows 11 cumulative updates, such as changes to the taskbar, Narrator, and Voice Access. Additionally, the article includes a brief mention of cloud attacks growing more sophisticated but does not provide any specific details or recommendations for mitigating these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5062553-and-kb5062552-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft July 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes one zero-day, 137 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-july-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-one-zero-day-137-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SQL Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49719; Summary: A publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SQL Server allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to access data from uninitialized memory. The flaw can be fixed by installing the latest version of Microsoft SQL Server and by installing the Microsoft OLE DB Driver 18 or 19.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-july-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-one-zero-day-137-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatsa Android Banking Trojan Hits 90,000 Users with Fake PDF App on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/anatsa-android-banking-trojan-hits.html</link>
      <description>An Android banking malware campaign, known as Anatsa, has targeted users in North America by distributing a trojan disguised as a "PDF Update" to a document viewer app. The malware can steal credentials through overlay and keylogging attacks, conduct Device-Takeover Fraud (DTO), and receive a dynamic list of targeted financial institutions from an external server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/anatsa-android-banking-trojan-hits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android malware Anatsa infiltrates Google Play to target US banks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-anatsa-infiltrates-google-play-to-target-us-banks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hybrid Cars Simulator, Drift &amp; Racing; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Anatsa banking trojan was found in Google Play as an app posing as a PDF viewer that had over 50,000 downloads. The malware becomes active immediately after installation and tracks users launching North American banking apps, serving overlays, keylogging, or automating transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-anatsa-infiltrates-google-play-to-target-us-banks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Technical Barriers in Desktop and Application Virtualization</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/overcoming-technical-barriers-in-desktop-and-application-virtualization/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges and risks associated with desktop and application virtualization, including security risks from exposed firewall ports, lateral movement threats, and network performance issues. It highlights the importance of implementing a Zero Trust architecture and Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) to mitigate these risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/overcoming-technical-barriers-in-desktop-and-application-virtualization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Chrome extensions with 1.7M installs found on Web Store</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-chrome-extensions-with-17m-installs-found-on-web-store/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome Web Store; CVE(s): None; Summary: Malicious extensions with over 1.7 million downloads in the Google Chrome Web Store can track users, steal browser activity, and redirect to potentially unsafe web addresses. The extensions, posing as legitimate tools, were discovered by researchers at Koi Security and reported to Google.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-chrome-extensions-with-17m-installs-found-on-web-store/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Servers: Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/mcp-servers-everything-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the concept of Malicious Command Pattern (MCP) servers and their potential to be used as attack vectors in cybersecurity attacks. It highlights several concerns, including command injection vulnerabilities, lack of authentication standards, and absence of integrity controls, which can lead to unauthorized actions or data leaks.

The article also explores the possibility of malicious actors deploying MCP servers that masquerade as legitimate tools, performing actual network scans, exfiltrating scan results, using the MCP protocol to communicate with other compromised systems, and establishing persistent backdoors. It emphasizes the need for security teams to be aware of these potential attack patterns and take steps to prevent them.

In addition, the article discusses common mistakes that security teams make when deploying MCP servers, including running them as root/administrator, not using network segmentation, and blindly trusting "verified" servers. It highlights the importance of implementing proper monitoring and security measures to prevent attacks.

Overall, the article provides a comprehensive overview of the potential risks associated with Malicious Command Pattern (MCP) servers and emphasizes the need for security teams to be proactive in preventing these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061708</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Pull Request Targets 6,000+ Developers via Vulnerable Ethcode VS Code Extension</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malicious-pull-request-infects-6000.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Visual Studio Code (VS Code) extension Ethcode; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply chain attack compromised the Ethcode VS Code extension, which has been installed over 6,000 times. The attacker added a malicious dependency called "keythereum-utils" that downloads an unknown second-stage payload, potentially capable of stealing cryptocurrency assets or poisoning smart contracts.

FYSA: This is an example of a broader trend of software supply chain attacks, where attackers weaponize public repositories like GitHub and npm to deliver malware directly into developer environments. The attack highlights the importance of secure development practices and the need for continuous monitoring and auditing of open-source dependencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malicious-pull-request-infects-6000.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerson ValveLink Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-189-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Emerson ValveLink Products; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52579, CVE-2025-50109, CVE-2025-46358, CVE-2025-48496, CVE-2025-53471; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker with access to the system to read sensitive information stored in cleartext, tamper with parameters, and run un-authorized code. The affected products are ValveLink SOLO, ValveLink DTM, ValveLink PRM, and ValveLink SNAP-ON, all versions prior to ValveLink 14.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23602</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases One Industrial Control Systems Advisory</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/08/cisa-releases-one-industrial-control-systems-advisory</link>
      <description>CISA released an Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisory on July 8, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisory is for Emerson ValveLink Products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23603</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways Identity-based Attacks Are Breaching Retail</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/5-ways-identity-based-attacks-are.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses recent high-profile data breaches in retail, where attackers exploited overprivileged access and unmonitored service accounts using social engineering tactics. The attacks targeted third-party customer service providers, resulting in the exposure of customer data, including names, email addresses, and order details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/5-ways-identity-based-attacks-are.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RondoDox Botnet Exploits Flaws in TBK DVRs and Four-Faith Routers to Launch DDoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/rondodox-botnet-exploits-flaws-in-tbk.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TBK Digital Video Recorders (DVRs) - DVR-4104 and DVR-4216; Four-Faith routers - F3x24 and F3x36; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3721, CVE-2024-12856; Summary: Medium-severity command injection vulnerabilities in TBK DVRs and Four-Faith routers allow attackers to deploy different Mirai botnet variants. The flaws have been publicly disclosed and are actively being targeted, posing serious risks to device security and overall network integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/rondodox-botnet-exploits-flaws-in-tbk.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaitTrap: Over 17,000 Fake News Websites Caught Fueling Investment Fraud Globally</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/baittrap-over-17000-fake-news-websites.html</link>
      <description>A large-scale scam operation utilizing fake news websites (Baiting News Sites) has been discovered, targeting users across 50 countries with online investment fraud. The scammers use sponsored ads and fake articles to lure victims into fraudulent trading platforms, followed by a two-phase structure of building trust and extracting maximum value before the victim realizes it's a trap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/baittrap-over-17000-fake-news-websites.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoldMelody’s Hidden Chords: Initial Access Broker In-Memory IIS Modules Revealed</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/initial-access-broker-exploits-leaked-machine-keys/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a threat brief on an Initial Access Broker (IAB) group known as TGR-CRI-0045, which is leveraging in-memory IIS techniques for persistent access. The article discusses the group's use of ASP.NET View State deserialization vulnerabilities and its exploitation of exposed Machine Keys.

The article provides details on the group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including the use of reflective .NET assemblies, TxPortMap tooling, and GodPotato privilege escalation technique. It also discusses the group's post-exploitation activities, such as code injection attacks using publicly disclosed ASP.NET machine keys.

The article concludes by highlighting the need for organizations to prioritize identifying and remediating compromised Machine Keys, as outlined by Microsoft. It also mentions that Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected from these threats through various products and features.

Overall, this article is not discussing a specific vulnerability (software, hardware, or firmware), but rather providing insights on an IAB group's TTPs and the need for organizations to be aware of these types of attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=145084</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover Batavia Windows Spyware Stealing Documents from Russian Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/researchers-uncover-batavia-windows.html</link>
      <description>The article describes two separate cyberattacks, one delivering Batavia Windows spyware and another delivering NordDragonScan Windows stealer malware. Both attacks use phishing emails to deliver malicious payloads that steal sensitive data from compromised hosts.

FYSA: Russian organizations have been targeted by a campaign delivering the previously undocumented Windows spyware called Batavia. The attack uses bait emails containing malicious links, which download an archive file containing a Visual Basic Encoded script (.VBE) file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/researchers-uncover-batavia-windows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Critical Vulnerabilities to KEV Catalog Due to Active Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-four-critical-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): CVE-2014-3931, CVE-2016-10033, CVE-2019-5418, CVE-2019-9621; Summary: Four security flaws have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The vulnerabilities include a buffer overflow in MRLG, command injection in PHPMailer, path traversal in Ruby on Rails' Action View, and SSRF in Zimbra Collaboration Suite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-four-critical-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Chinese hacker tied to Silk Typhoon arrested for cyberespionage</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/alleged-chinese-hacker-tied-to-silk-typhoon-arrested-for-cyberespionage/</link>
      <description>A Chinese national, Xu Zewei, was arrested in Italy for allegedly being linked to the state-sponsored Silk Typhoon hacking group, responsible for cyberattacks against American organizations and government agencies. The group is accused of targeting infectious disease researchers and healthcare organizations, as well as the U.S. Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control and the Committee on Foreign Investment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/alleged-chinese-hacker-tied-to-silk-typhoon-arrested-for-cyberespionage/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 01:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unless users take action, Android will let Gemini access third-party apps</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/unless-users-take-action-android-will-let-gemini-access-third-party-apps/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Google Gemini app's data collection capabilities and provides remedies for users who want to prevent data collection. Disabling app activity or uninstalling the app can be done through command-line terminal or using Android debug bridge, but some users may encounter errors like "DELETE_FAILED_INTERNAL_ERROR".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/unless-users-take-action-android-will-let-gemini-access-third-party-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 23:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public exploits released for Citrix Bleed 2 NetScaler flaw, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-exploits-released-for-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The CitrixBleed2 vulnerability allows attackers to retrieve memory contents by sending malformed POST requests during login attempts. This can lead to the theft of user session tokens and potentially exploit sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/public-exploits-released-for-citrixbleed-2-netscaler-flaw-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 22:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employee gets $920 for credentials used in $140 million bank heist</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/employee-gets-920-for-credentials-used-in-140-million-bank-heist/</link>
      <description>The article reports a social engineering attack on an employee at C&amp;M, a company that offers financial connectivity solutions. The attackers bribed the employee to gain access to confidential systems and steal nearly $140 million from six banks in Brazil. The incident highlights the importance of employee awareness and training in preventing such attacks.

FYSA: The article discusses a sophisticated social engineering attack on an employee at C&amp;M, a company that offers financial connectivity solutions. The attackers bribed the employee to gain access to confidential systems and steal nearly $140 million from six banks in Brazil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/employee-gets-920-for-credentials-used-in-140-million-bank-heist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-474: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-474/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7223; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VPM files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25044</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-475: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-475/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7224; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VPM files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25045</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-476: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-476/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7225; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of VPM files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25047</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-477: (0Day) INVT HMITool VPM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-477/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT HMITool; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7226; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT HMITool by parsing VPM files with an out-of-bounds write. User interaction is required, and the issue stems from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in writing past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25048</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-478: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-478/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parser; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7227; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required, and the attack can be initiated through a malicious page or file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25550</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-479: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-479/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT, VT-Designer PM3 File Parser; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7228; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting an out-of-bounds write issue in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25571</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-480: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-480/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7229; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by parsing PM3 files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25722</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-481: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-481/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7230; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer by exploiting a type confusion condition in the parsing of PM3 files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25723</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-482: (0Day) INVT VT-Designer PM3 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-482/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: INVT VT-Designer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7231; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of INVT VT-Designer. It requires user interaction, such as visiting a malicious page or opening a malicious file, and is caused by the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the parsing of PM3 files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25724</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic macOS infostealer adds backdoor for persistent attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atomic-macos-infostealer-adds-backdoor-for-persistent-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atomic macOS Stealer; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Atomic macOS info-stealer (AMOS) has been updated with a backdoor, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary remote commands, survive reboots, and maintain control over infected hosts indefinitely. The malware can log keystrokes, introduce additional payloads, or perform lateral movement. It also features string obfuscation and checks for sandbox or virtual machine environments to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/atomic-macos-infostealer-adds-backdoor-for-persistent-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“No honor among thieves”: M&amp;S hacking group starts turf war</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-honor-among-thieves-ms-hacking-group-starts-turf-war/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a potential conflict between two ransomware groups, DragonForce and RansomHub, which could lead to increased risk of cyberattacks and double extortions. The instability in the extortion ecosystem can have serious implications for ransomware and data theft extortion victims. Additionally, the global cost of cybercrime is estimated to reach $10 trillion by 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-honor-among-thieves-ms-hacking-group-starts-turf-war/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEO Poisoning Campaign Targets 8,500+ SMB Users with Malware Disguised as AI Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/seo-poisoning-campaign-targets-8500.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article does not describe a vulnerability in any specific product. Instead, it discusses various malicious campaigns and tactics used by threat actors to spread malware, steal sensitive information, and commit financial fraud. The article highlights the use of search engine optimization (SEO) poisoning techniques, malvertising, and social engineering tactics to deliver malware loaders like Oyster, Vidar, Lumma, and Legion Loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/seo-poisoning-campaign-targets-8500.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qantas is being extorted in recent data-theft cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-is-being-extorted-in-recent-data-theft-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Qantas has confirmed a cyberattack that potentially exposed 6 million customers' data, with threat actors demanding extortion. The attack did not expose financial information or sensitive details, but warned customers to be cautious of scams and phishing emails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/qantas-is-being-extorted-in-recent-data-theft-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Batavia' Windows spyware campaign targets dozens of Russian orgs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/batavia-windows-spyware-campaign-targets-dozens-of-russian-orgs/</link>
      <description>The article describes a previously undocumented spyware called "Batavia" that targets large industrial enterprises in Russia through phishing email campaigns. The malware has multiple stages, including profile gathering, data exfiltration, and additional payload downloads, indicating an espionage operation on Russia's industrial activity.

FYSA: The article highlights the effectiveness of simple techniques used by threat actors, even as cloud attacks become more sophisticated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/batavia-windows-spyware-campaign-targets-dozens-of-russian-orgs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 16:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers abuse leaked Shellter red team tool to deploy infostealers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-abuse-leaked-shellter-red-team-tool-to-deploy-infostealers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Shellter; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers used Shellter Elite, a commercial AV/EDR evasion loader for penetration testing, in attacks after a customer leaked a copy of the software. The misuse was discovered by security researchers and an update has been released to address the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-abuse-leaked-shellter-red-team-tool-to-deploy-infostealers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-473: Parallels Client Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-473/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Parallels Client; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6812; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Client by exploiting an uncontrolled search path element in the AppServer service, which loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability and execute arbitrary code in the context of a target user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25039</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Four Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/07/cisa-adds-four-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple products; CVE(s): CVE-2014-3931, CVE-2016-10033, CVE-2019-5418, CVE-2019-9621; Summary: The Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog has added four new vulnerabilities, including a Multi-Router Looking Glass Buffer Overflow, PHPMailer Command Injection, Rails Ruby on Rails Path Traversal, and Synacor Zimbra Collaboration Suite Server-Side Request Forgery. These vulnerabilities are frequently targeted by malicious actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and other organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23600</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Chrome 0-Day, Ivanti Exploits, MacOS Stealers, Crypto Heists and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-ivanti.html</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a collection of various cybersecurity-related news and developments, covering topics such as malware attacks, phishing campaigns, data breaches, and security updates from major technology companies. There are no specific vulnerabilities mentioned in the article.

However, it's worth noting that the article does discuss some common attack vectors and tactics used by malicious actors, including smishing campaigns, email bombing, and file system redirection attacks. It also highlights the importance of robust cybersecurity measures and the need for organizations to stay vigilant against emerging threats.

Overall, while this article is not focused on a specific vulnerability, it provides valuable insights into the current state of cybersecurity and the types of threats that organizations may face in today's digital landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-chrome-0-day-ivanti.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Security: Why Default Passwords Must Go</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/manufacturing-security-why-default.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the risks associated with using default passwords in various devices and software systems. It emphasizes that default passwords provide an easy entry point for attackers, allowing them to recruit botnets, launch ransomware attacks, and compromise entire networks or partner systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/manufacturing-security-why-default.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSO 0-Day &amp; Fortinet Exploits, Allianz Breach, Social Media Ban Service Listed on Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/sso-0-day-fortinet-exploits-allianz-breach-social-media-ban-service/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apereo CAS, Jasig, Keycloak with the CAS plugin; CVE(s): None; Summary: An alleged 0-day redirect vulnerability exists in major Single Sign-On (SSO) platforms, potentially allowing attackers to redirect users from trusted login portals to attacker-controlled domains, enabling phishing, session hijacking, or login bypass. The issue affects over 12,000 live systems across government, healthcare, finance, and international organizations.

FYSA: Threat actors are advertising exploits targeting known Fortinet CVEs (CVE-2024-55591) and a stolen database linked to Allianz Seguros Spain, potentially containing approximately 4.6 million records. Additionally, a social media ban service is being promoted, offering targeted takedowns across multiple platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061689</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 09:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAG-140 Deploys DRAT V2 RAT, Targeting Indian Government, Defense, and Rail Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/tag-140-deploys-drat-v2-rat-targeting.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of a modified variant of a remote access trojan (RAT) called DRAT V2, used by the threat actor TAG-140 to target Indian government organizations. The malware, which is part of an "interchangeable suite" of RATs, allows for harvesting sensitive data and complicates attribution, detection, and monitoring efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/tag-140-deploys-drat-v2-rat-targeting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI says GPT-5 will unify breakthroughs from different models</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-says-gpt-5-will-unify-breakthroughs-from-different-models/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it provides information on OpenAI's plans to unify multiple models into one, creating GPT-5, and improves the existing models.

FYSA: Threat actors are using simple techniques to succeed in cloud attacks, with 8 key techniques revealed by Wiz's detections across thousands of organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-says-gpt-5-will-unify-breakthroughs-from-different-models/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hands on with Windows 11 Notepad's new markdown support</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-windows-11-notepads-new-markdown-support/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the addition of markdown text formatting in Windows 11's Notepad app. The feature allows users to apply different formatting options such as headings, bold and italic styling, and hyperlinks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/hands-on-with-windows-11-notepads-new-markdown-support/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is testing disruptive Study Together feature</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-testing-disruptive-study-together-feature/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article does not contain information about a vulnerability. Instead, it discusses new features and updates related to OpenAI's ChatGPT, including the potential introduction of "Study together" mode, new connectors for GPT Search and Deep Research, and upcoming developments with GPT-5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-testing-disruptive-study-together-feature/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingram Micro outage caused by SafePay ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-outage-caused-by-safepay-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>The article reports on an ongoing outage at Ingram Micro caused by a SafePay ransomware attack. The attack led to the shutdown of internal systems and ransom notes were found on employee devices, although it's unclear if devices were actually encrypted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-outage-caused-by-safepay-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 15:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan NSB Alerts Public on Data Risks from TikTok, Weibo, and RedNote Over China Ties</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/taiwan-nsb-alerts-public-on-data-risks.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Taiwan's National Security Bureau (NSB) warned about various Chinese-developed applications; CVE(s): None; Summary: The NSB detected excessive data collection, privacy infringement, and unauthorized data transmission from apps like RedNote, Weibo, TikTok, WeChat, and Baidu Cloud to China. These apps breached security indicators, including personal data collection, permission usage, data transmission, system information extraction, and biometric data access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/taiwan-nsb-alerts-public-on-data-risks.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alert: Exposed JDWP Interfaces Lead to Crypto Mining, Hpingbot Targets SSH for DDoS</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/alert-exposed-jdwp-interfaces-lead-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple applications (TeamCity, Jenkins, Selenium Grid, Elasticsearch, Quarkus, Spring Boot, Apache Tomcat); CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting exposed Java Debug Wire Protocol (JDWP) interfaces to obtain code execution capabilities and deploy cryptocurrency miners on compromised hosts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/alert-exposed-jdwp-interfaces-lead-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Deep Research tests new connectors for more context</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-deep-research-tests-new-connectors-for-more-context/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article discusses the integration of Slack with ChatGPT, a research AI agent. It mentions potential use cases for the integration, such as allowing ChatGPT to access an organization's chat and use messages in the context of research.

(Note: Since there is no vulnerability mentioned in the article, I summarized it using the FYSA format)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-deep-research-tests-new-connectors-for-more-context/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 22:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingram Micro suffers global outage as internal systems inaccessible</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-suffers-global-outage-as-internal-systems-inaccessible/</link>
      <description>Ingram Micro's global outage impacting its websites and internal systems, with customers concerned it may be a cyberattack. The company remains silent on the cause of the issue. Some customers and employees claim the outage is due to a potential ransomware attack or breach, but this has not been confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ingram-micro-suffers-global-outage-as-internal-systems-inaccessible/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker leaks Telefónica data allegedly stolen in a new breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-leaks-telef-nica-data-allegedly-stolen-in-a-new-breach/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability but rather reports on a potential data breach at Telefónica, a Spanish telecommunications company. The hacker, known as "Rey," claims to have stolen 106GB of internal data and has released a 2.6GB archive to prove the breach occurred.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-leaks-telef-nica-data-allegedly-stolen-in-a-new-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NightEagle APT Exploits Microsoft Exchange Flaw to Target China's Military and Tech Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/nighteagle-apt-exploits-microsoft.html</link>
      <description>No vulnerability is mentioned in this article. Instead, it discusses a threat actor called NightEagle (APT-Q-95) that targets Microsoft Exchange servers as part of a zero-day exploit chain to gather intelligence from government, defense, and technology sectors in China. The attackers use a bespoke version of the Chisel utility and implant a Trojan into the Internet Information Server (IIS) service of the Microsoft Exchange Server to gain unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/nighteagle-apt-exploits-microsoft.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your AI Agents Might Be Leaking Data — Watch this Webinar to Learn How to Stop It</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/your-ai-agents-might-be-leaking-data.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article is not about a specific vulnerability, but rather highlights the potential risks of using generative AI (GenAI) systems without proper access controls, governance policies, and oversight. It discusses how well-meaning AI agents can unintentionally leak sensitive data to the wrong users or the internet, and emphasizes the importance of securing AI agents to prevent data exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/your-ai-agents-might-be-leaking-data.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Sudo Vulnerabilities Let Local Users Gain Root Access on Linux, Impacting Major Distros</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-sudo-vulnerabilities-let-local.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sudo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32462, CVE-2025-32463; Summary: Two security flaws were discovered in Sudo, a command-line utility for Linux and Unix-like operating systems. The vulnerabilities allow local attackers to escalate their privileges to root on susceptible machines. CVE-2025-32462 enables listed users to execute commands on unintended machines, while CVE-2025-32463 allows local users to obtain root access by using the --chroot option with a user-controlled directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-sudo-vulnerabilities-let-local.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Ordered to Pay $314M for Misusing Android Users' Cellular Data Without Permission</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ordered-to-pay-314m-for-misusing.html</link>
      <description>Google has been ordered by a California court to pay $314 million over allegations that it misused Android device users' cellular data when idle, sending information to the company without permission. The verdict marks an end to a legal class-action complaint filed in 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ordered-to-pay-314m-for-misusing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaks hint at Operator-like tool in ChatGPT ahead of GPT-5 launch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leaks-hint-at-operator-like-tool-in-chatgpt-ahead-of-gpt-5-launch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: There are no cybersecurity-relevant vulnerabilities or threats discussed in this article. Instead, it appears to be a collection of unrelated news and updates about OpenAI's ChatGPT and cloud security. The article mentions the possibility of an "Operator-like tool" being developed by OpenAI, but does not provide any information about potential vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leaks-hint-at-operator-like-tool-in-chatgpt-ahead-of-gpt-5-launch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 23:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-469: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-469/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47724; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26718</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-470: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-470/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47725; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26719</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-471: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-471/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47727; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft by parsing DPB files without proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, requiring the target to visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26842</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-472: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor DPB File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-472/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics CNCSoft Screen Editor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47726; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics CNCSoft, requiring user interaction. It exists within the parsing of DPB files by the Screen Editor module due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated data structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26720</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-467: GStreamer H266 Codec Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-467/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GStreamer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6663; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GStreamer. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of H266 sei messages, resulting from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27381</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-468: GFI Archiver Telerik Web UI Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-468/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GFI, Archiver; CVE(s): CVE-2019-18935, CVE-2017-11317, CVE-2014-2217; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GFI Archiver. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from the use of a vulnerable version of Telerik Web UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26061</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
