<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:05:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Update Adds Erlang/OTP SSH Exploit and OPNSense Scanner</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/metasploit-update-erlang-opnsense-scanner/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP SSH servers; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: The Erlang/OTP SSH Pre-Auth Root RCE exploit targets a critical pre-authentication vulnerability in Erlang-based SSH servers, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root by sending crafted SSH packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134862</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 09:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Researchers Use Mach IPC to Uncover Sandbox Escape Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mach-ipc-to-uncover-sandbox-escape-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Project Zero researchers, macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The researchers discovered new sandbox escape vulnerabilities in macOS using Mach Interprocess Communication (IPC) mechanisms-core components of Apple's operating system. The vulnerabilities allow crafted messages to cause out-of-bounds memory access, potentially enabling privilege escalation and sandbox escapes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134804</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Hide Undetectable Ransomware Inside JPG Images</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/undetectable-ransomware-inside-jpg-images/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new ransomware attack method that exploits JPEG image files to deliver fully undetectable (FUD) ransomware. The attack involves embedding malicious code within standard JPG images, which activates a multi-stage attack when the victim opens the image, including downloading the ransomware executable and encrypting the victim's files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134792</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Legacy Protocols in Microsoft Entra ID to Bypass MFA and Conditional Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-legacy-protocols-in-microsoft-entra-id/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra ID; CVE(s): None; Summary: The campaign exploited outdated legacy authentication protocols, including BAV2ROPC, SMTP AUTH, POP3, and IMAP4, to bypass modern security measures like MFA and Conditional Access. Attackers targeted legacy endpoints like Exchange Online and the Microsoft Authentication Library, exploiting OAuth legacy flows, password authentication, basic authentication, and legacy Exchange protocols.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134763</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Abuse Copilot AI in SharePoint to Steal Passwords and Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-abuse-copilot-ai-in-sharepoint/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a vulnerability where attackers can exploit AI agents embedded in SharePoint sites to bypass traditional security controls, extract passwords, and access restricted files. Attackers can manipulate these agents by framing malicious queries as legitimate security audits, allowing them to evade detection and gain unauthorized access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134731</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defendnot: A Tool That Disables Windows Defender by Registering as Antivirus</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/defendnot-a-tool-that-disables-windows-defender/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "defendnot" tool uses undocumented Windows Security Center APIs to disable Windows Defender by registering itself as a third-party antivirus solution. It achieves this by utilizing the Windows Security Center (WSC) service and performing signature verification, DLL characteristic checks, and other security checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134710</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitel SIP Phone Flaws Allow Attackers to Inject Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitel-sip-phone-flaws-allow-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47188, CVE-2025-47187; Summary: A pair of vulnerabilities in Mitel's 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones could enable attackers to execute arbitrary commands or upload malicious files to compromised devices, posing significant risks to enterprise communication systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134738</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake AI Tools Used to Spread Noodlophile Malware, Targeting 62,000+ via Facebook Lures</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-ai-tools-used-to-spread.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using fake AI-powered tools as lures to entice users into downloading an information stealer malware dubbed Noodlophile. The malware harvests browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallet information, and other sensitive data, and in some cases, bundles with a remote access trojan for persistent access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-ai-tools-used-to-spread.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams to Safeguard Meetings by Blocking Screen Snaps</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-blocking-screen-snaps/</link>
      <description>Microsoft is introducing a "Prevent Screen Capture" feature for Teams, which will block unauthorized screenshots and recordings during virtual meetings. When activated, any attempt to take a screenshot will result in the meeting window going completely black, leaving only system notifications visible in the captured image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134749</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Exploit Method Extracts Microsoft Entra Tokens Through Beacon</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-exploit-method-extracts-microsoft-entra-tokens/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Entra; CVE(s): None; Summary: A novel exploit method uses Beacon Object Files (BOFs) to extract Microsoft Entra tokens from compromised endpoints, including non-domain-joined or BYOD devices. The technique bypasses traditional detection mechanisms and expands access to high-value targets, posing significant risks to enterprise cloud environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134720</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Code Published for Linux nftables Security Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poc-code-for-linux-nftables-security-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux; CVE(s): CVE-2024-26809; Summary: The Linux nftables firewall subsystem contains a high-severity double-free vulnerability that allows local attackers to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code. The flaw resides in the pipapo set implementation, which can be exploited by deleting a set marked as "dirty" while it's still dirty, leading to repeated deallocations of memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134711</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth 6.1 enhances privacy with randomized RPA timing</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-61-enhances-privacy-with-randomized-rpa-timing/</link>
      <description>The Bluetooth Special Interest Group (SIG) has announced Bluetooth Core Specification 6.1, which improves device privacy by randomizing Resolvable Private Address (RPA) updates between 8 and 15 minutes (default), allowing custom values between 1 second to 1 hour. This makes tracking harder due to the lack of pattern in value selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/bluetooth-61-enhances-privacy-with-randomized-rpa-timing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is finally adding Download as PDF for Deep Research</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-finally-adding-download-as-pdf-for-deep-research/</link>
      <description>The article discusses upcoming features for ChatGPT, including the ability to save reports as PDFs and a new GitHub connector for Teams subscribers. Additionally, it mentions various benchmarks and releases related to OpenAI's GPT-4.1 models. No cybersecurity-specific information is provided in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-is-finally-adding-download-as-pdf-for-deep-research/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iClicker site hack targeted students with malware via fake CAPTCHA</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iclicker-hack-targeted-students-with-malware-via-fake-captcha/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: iClicker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The iClicker website was compromised by a ClickFix attack that displayed a fake CAPTCHA prompt to trick students and instructors into installing malware on their devices. The attack used social engineering tactics to execute PowerShell scripts, which could have installed malware or stolen sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/iclicker-hack-targeted-students-with-malware-via-fake-captcha/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 14:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated PhaaS Phish Toolkits are Now Genetrating Realistic Fake Phishing Pages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/phishing-scams-on-the-rise-with-sophisticated-phaas/</link>
      <description>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) toolkits are being used to generate convincing replicas of legitimate websites in real-time, enhancing the effectiveness of credential-harvesting campaigns. These toolkits allow attackers to tailor phishing pages instantly for any target organization and evade detection by human users and automated security systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134535</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Azure and Power Apps Vulnerabilities Allow Attackers to Exploit RCE</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-azure-and-power-apps-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure cloud services and Power Apps platform; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29813, CVE-2025-29827, CVE-2025-29972, CVE-2025-47733; Summary: Four critical security vulnerabilities were patched in Microsoft's Azure cloud services and Power Apps platform. The most severe vulnerability (CVE-2025-29813) could allow attackers to escalate privileges or access sensitive information by exploiting improper handling of pipeline job tokens within Visual Studio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134283</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Detecting Backdoors in Enterprise Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/detecting-backdoors-enterprise-networks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware vCenter Server; CVE(s): CVE-2024-38812; Summary: A critical remote code execution flaw (CVE-2024-38812) was exploited in a backdoor attack, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to systems and potentially remain undetected for months while exfiltrating sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134680</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Windows Endpoints Using Group Policy Objects (GPOs): A Configuration Guide</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/securing-windows-endpoints-using-group-policy-objects-gpos-a-configuration-guide/</link>
      <description>This article is a guide on how to effectively use Group Policy Objects (GPOs) for endpoint security in Windows environments. It provides best practices for designing and implementing GPOs to manage and enforce security settings, including structuring Active Directory, configuring password policies, application control, and firewall settings, and maintaining audit logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134295</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth Core 6.1 Released – What’s New!</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bluetooth-6-1-unveiled/</link>
      <description>The Bluetooth SIG has transitioned to a bi-annual release cadence, focusing on rapid iteration and market responsiveness. This shift aims to empower developers with more efficient integration of enhancements, reducing the gap between standardization and real-world implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134458</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams will soon block screen capture during meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-teams-will-soon-block-screen-capture-during-meetings/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new feature in Microsoft Teams that prevents users from capturing screenshots of sensitive information shared during meetings. The feature will turn the meeting window black if someone tries to take a screenshot, protecting the sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-teams-will-soon-block-screen-capture-during-meetings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome 137 Integrates Gemini Nano AI to Combat Tech Support Scams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-137-integrates-gemini-nano-ai/</link>
      <description>Google has integrated its Gemini Nano large language model (LLM) into Chrome 137 to detect and block tech support scams in real-time. The on-device AI analysis evaluates webpage content for deceptive patterns, generating security signals for Google's Safe Browsing service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134423</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Employee Computer Infected with Malware and Leaked Data Found Info-Stealer Logs</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/doge-employee-credentials-exposed-in-multiple-info-stealer-leaks/</link>
      <description>This article reports on the unauthorized access to sensitive government systems, including the Federal Emergency Management Agency's core financial management platform, by Kyle Schutt, a 37-year-old DOGE employee. The article highlights systemic cybersecurity challenges within federal agencies, specifically the reliance on password-based authentication and the need for multi-factor authentication (MFA) and layered defense approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134393</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CISOs Must Prioritize Cybersecurity Culture in Remote Work</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybersecurity-culture-in-remote-work/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of building a strong cybersecurity culture in remote work environments. It highlights that Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs) must go beyond traditional technical responsibilities and foster a security-first mindset among remote employees. The article provides five practical steps for CISOs to build this culture, including developing remote-specific security policies, delivering ongoing training, encouraging open communication, recognizing good security behavior, and turning mistakes into learning opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=132248</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake AI video generators drop new Noodlophile infostealer malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-ai-video-generators-drop-new-noodlophile-infostealer-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a new information-stealing malware family called 'Noodlophile,' which uses fake AI-powered video generation tools to distribute the malware. The malware targets data stored on web browsers, steals account credentials, session cookies, tokens, and cryptocurrency wallet files, and exfiltrates stolen data via a Telegram bot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-ai-video-generators-drop-new-noodlophile-infostealer-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Uses Advanced AI to Combat Sophisticated Online Scams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-chrome-uses-ai/</link>
      <description>Google has integrated artificial intelligence into its cybersecurity toolkit to shield users from financial and data theft scams. The company has unveiled AI-driven initiatives across Search, Chrome, and Android, aimed at counteracting increasingly sophisticated scams. The advancements include AI classifiers capable of analyzing vast web content datasets, identifying emerging scam patterns, and neutralizing coordinated campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea’s OtterCookie Malware Added a New Feature to Attack Windows, Linux, and macOS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-koreas-ottercookie-malware/</link>
      <description>WaterPlum, a North Korea-linked attack group, has been targeting financial institutions, cryptocurrency operators, and FinTech companies globally since 2023. They have utilized various malware tools, including BeaverTailand InvisibleFerret, Contagious Interview, and their latest tool, OtterCookie, which has undergone rapid updates and evolved through multiple versions (v1 to v4) with enhanced capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134226</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Pays $1.375 Billion to Texas Over Unauthorized Tracking and Biometric Data Collection</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-pays-1375-billion-to-texas-over.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses two lawsuits against Google related to unauthorized tracking and collection of user data, including geolocation, incognito searches, and biometric data. The company has agreed to pay Texas $1.4 billion to settle the suits, which marks one of the largest privacy-related settlements in history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-pays-1375-billion-to-texas-over.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Shuts Down eXch Over $1.9B Laundering, Seizes €34M in Crypto and 8TB of Data</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/germany-shuts-down-exch-over-19b.html</link>
      <description>The German Federal Criminal Police Office (BKA) seized the online infrastructure and shut down eXch, a cryptocurrency exchange accused of money laundering and operating a criminal trading platform. The operation allegedly allowed users to conceal financial flows without implementing anti-money laundering measures, with an estimated $1.9 billion worth of assets transferred since its launch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/germany-shuts-down-exch-over-19b.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Brief: CVE-2025-31324</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/threat-brief-sap-netweaver-cve-2025-31324/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A critical vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver's Visual Composer Framework (version 7.50) allows unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files, leading to remote code execution and system compromise. The vulnerability is exploited by sending specially crafted HTTP requests to the /developmentserver/metadatauploader endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=140450</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ascension says recent data breach affects over 430,000 patients</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ascension-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-430-000-patients/</link>
      <description>A data breach disclosed by Ascension, a private healthcare system in the US, affected over 430,000 patients, exposing personal and healthcare information. The breach was caused by a former business partner's vulnerability in third-party software used by the partner, which was exploited in a widespread Clop ransomware attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ascension-says-recent-data-breach-affects-over-430-000-patients/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome to use on-device AI to detect tech support scams</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-to-use-on-device-ai-to-detect-tech-support-scams/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's implementation of a new Chrome security feature that uses the Gemini Nano large-language model to detect and block tech support scams while browsing the web. This feature analyzes web pages in real-time to detect scam signals, and if malicious intent is confirmed, it displays a warning message informing the user of the risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-chrome-to-use-on-device-ai-to-detect-tech-support-scams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police dismantles botnet selling hacked routers as residential proxies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-dismantles-botnet-selling-hacked-routers-as-residential-proxies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various router models from Linksys and Cisco; CVE(s): None; Summary: A botnet infected thousands of routers worldwide, including older wireless internet routers, with malware since at least 2004. The compromised devices were used to build two networks of residential proxies (Anyproxy and 5socks) which were sold as proxy servers on the dark web, allowing unauthorized access to be sold for malicious activities such as ad fraud, DDoS attacks, brute forcing, or exploiting victim's data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-dismantles-botnet-selling-hacked-routers-as-residential-proxies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattackers Targeting IT Help Desks for Initial Breach</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattackers-targeting-it-help-desks/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a trend of cybercriminals impersonating IT support personnel, tax officials, or banking representatives to manipulate victims into granting access to critical systems. The attackers exploit psychological vulnerabilities and human tendencies to defer to authority figures, bypassing technical defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134268</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Stealthy .NET Malware Hiding Malicious Payloads Within Bitmap Resources</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-stealthy-net-malware-hiding-malicious-payloads/</link>
      <description>Palo Alto Networks' Unit 42 researchers discovered a novel obfuscation method used by threat actors to conceal malware within bitmap resources of seemingly benign .NET applications. The method embeds malicious payloads in bitmap files, initiating a multi-stage infection chain that delivers destructive malware families such as Agent Tesla, Remcos RAT, and XLoader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134622</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Weaponizing Facebook Ads to Deploy Multi-Stage Malware Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-weaponizing-facebook-ads/</link>
      <description>A persistent malvertising campaign on Facebook has been uncovered, exploiting trust associated with major cryptocurrency exchanges to distribute multi-stage malware. The campaign uses advanced evasion techniques, mass brand impersonation, and user-tracking mechanisms to bypass conventional security defenses and target users with fake ads and accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134609</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Target Job Seekers with Three New Unique Adversaries</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-target-job-seekers/</link>
      <description>A sharp rise in recruitment scams has been detected by Netcraft, driven by three distinct threat actors employing unique and highly technical strategies to exploit vulnerabilities in the job market. These scams have resulted in over $500 million in losses in the U.S. alone in 2023 and are likely to continue growing as economic pressures create fertile ground for cybercriminals. The threats involve advance fee fraud, phishing websites, and identity theft tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134594</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: 7,000-Device Proxy Botnet Using IoT, EoL Systems Dismantled in U.S. - Dutch Operation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/breaking-7000-device-proxy-botnet-using.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a joint law enforcement operation that dismantled a criminal proxy network powered by thousands of infected IoT and end-of-life devices. The botnet was used to provide anonymity to malicious actors, with users paying a monthly subscription fee for access to the infected routers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/breaking-7000-device-proxy-botnet-using.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OtterCookie v4 Adds VM Detection and Chrome, MetaMask Credential Theft Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ottercookie-v4-adds-vm-detection-and.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Contagious Interview campaign, a North Korean threat actor group that uses updated versions of cross-platform malware called OtterCookie. The malware has capabilities to steal credentials from web browsers and other files, and has been found to incorporate new modules for stealing credentials from Google Chrome and MetaMask extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ottercookie-v4-adds-vm-detection-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers behind attacks targeting SAP NetWeaver servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-behind-attacks-targeting-sap-netweaver-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A maximum severity vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer allows unauthenticated attackers to upload malicious files, enabling remote code execution and potentially leading to complete system compromise. The vulnerability was exploited by a Chinese threat actor, with multiple customers' systems breached through unauthorized file uploads on SAP NetWeaver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-behind-attacks-targeting-sap-netweaver-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Spider Malware Targets Klaviyo, HubSpot, and Pure Storage Platforms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/scattered-spider-malware-targets-klaviyo/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a notorious hacker collective, continues to actively target prominent services in 2025, including Klaviyo, HubSpot, and Pure Storage. Their tactics, techniques, and procedures have evolved with updated phishing kits and a new variant of the Spectre RAT designed for persistent access to compromised systems. The group's infrastructure choices, such as using dynamic DNS vendors and privacy-focused providers like Njalla, Virtuo, and Cloudflare, indicate a deliberate move toward operational stealth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134559</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany takes down eXch cryptocurrency exchange, seizes servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-takes-down-exch-cryptocurrency-exchange-seizes-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVEs: None; Summary: The article reports on the seizure of a cryptocurrency exchange platform called eXch by German authorities due to alleged money laundering activities. The platform is suspected of facilitating transactions worth approximately $1.9 billion and is linked to the notorious North Korean hacking group "Lazarus".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/germany-takes-down-exch-cryptocurrency-exchange-seizes-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit SAP RCE Vulnerability to Deploy Supershell Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-exploit-sap-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer 7.x; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer 7.x allows attackers to upload malicious binaries, including web shells, granting full system takeover capabilities. The vulnerability is being actively exploited by a Chinese threat actor, tracked as Chaya_004, and can be used to disrupt operations, steal sensitive data, and violate regulatory requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134536</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target IT Admins by Poisoning SEO to Push Malware to Top Search Results</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-it-admins-by-poisoning-seo-to-push-malware/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are using Search Engine Optimization (SEO) poisoning techniques to trick IT administrators into downloading malicious software, which can lead to devastating consequences such as data exfiltration and ransomware. The attackers establish persistent access, evade detection by masquerading traffic over common ports, and systematically target mission-critical assets. To combat this, experts recommend a robust "Defense in Depth" approach, including hardening access to critical assets, deploying Endpoint Detection and Response solutions, and implementing application allow-listing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134509</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mamona Ransomware Targets Windows Systems Using Abused Ping Command</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-mamona-ransomware-targets-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>Mamona is a newly discovered commodity ransomware strain that rapidly spreads across Windows systems. It employs a unique set of tactics, including exploiting the Windows "ping" command as a timing mechanism and operating entirely offline, making detection and response more difficult. The ransomware operates in "mute mode," executing all encryption and logic locally, and does not attempt to steal files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134567</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Python Package Impersonates Discord Developers to Deploy Remote Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-python-package-impersonates-discord-developers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: discordpydebug; CVE(s): None; Summary: The 'discordpydebug' Python package was marketed as a debugging utility for Discord bot developers, but it actually contained a fully functional remote access trojan (RAT). Over 11,000 downloads were made before its malicious nature was exposed, putting thousands of systems at risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134447</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Supply Chain Attack Compromises Popular npm Package with 45,000 Weekly Downloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-supply-chain-attack-compromises-popular-npm-package/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WebScrapingAPI rand-user-agent; CVE(s): None; Summary: The npm package rand-user-agent has been targeted by an advanced supply chain attack, which embedded malicious code in several recent releases. The compromised package can be used to establish covert communication channels with command-and-control (C2) servers, upload files, and execute arbitrary shell commands, posing a severe risk of data theft and unauthorized control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134480</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage Multimedia Systems in Stealthy Vishing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-multimedia-systems/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have begun exploiting multimedia systems, such as VoIP and streaming services, to orchestrate advanced voice phishing (vishing) attacks that integrate compromised platforms with social engineering tactics. These attacks exploit vulnerabilities in protocols like SIP and RTSP, and use deepfake technology to deceive victims, posing a significant challenge to organizations and individuals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134421</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit PDF Invoices to Target Windows, Linux, and macOS Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-pdf-invoices-to-target-windows/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated email campaign targets organizations in Spain, Italy, and Portugal, distributing a Remote Access Trojan (RAT) known as RATty, primarily affecting Windows systems but also posing a threat to Linux and macOS environments where the Java Runtime Environment (JRE) is installed. The campaign uses legitimate Spanish email service provider, serviciodecorreo.es, and advanced evasion tactics to deliver malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134394</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indirect Prompt Injection Exploits LLMs’ Lack of Informational Context</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/indirect-prompt-injection-exploits-llms-lack/</link>
      <description>A new type of cyber threat, called "indirect prompt injection attacks," targets large language models (LLMs) by embedding malicious directives within external data sources. These attacks exploit LLMs' trust in uncurated content and can lead to data leaks, misinformation, and code injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134291</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeDrain Phishing Attack Targets Users to Steal Financial Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/freedrain-phishing-attack-targets-users/</link>
      <description>The article exposes an industrial-scale cryptocurrency phishing operation called FreeDrain, which has been active since 2022. It leverages search engine optimization manipulation, free-tier web services, and intricate redirection techniques to target unsuspecting users of cryptocurrency wallets. The operation is believed to be based in the UTC+05:30 timezone (likely India) and operates on a standard 9-to-5 weekday schedule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=134302</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
