<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 and Red Hat Linux hacked on first day of Pwn2Own</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-and-red-hat-linux-virtualbox-hacked-on-first-day-of-pwn2own/</link>
      <description>Security researchers were awarded over $260,000 after successfully demonstrating zero-day exploits for Windows 11, Red Hat Linux, and Oracle VirtualBox at Pwn2Own Berlin 2025. The competition will continue to target fully patched products in various categories, with a grand prize pool of over $1,000,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-and-red-hat-linux-virtualbox-hacked-on-first-day-of-pwn2own/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Tor Oniux tool anonymizes any Linux app's network traffic</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-tor-oniux-tool-anonymizes-any-linux-apps-network-traffic/</link>
      <description>Tor has announced Oniux, a command-line tool for routing any Linux application securely through the Tor network using Linux namespaces, providing kernel-enforced isolation and preventing data leaks. Unlike Torsocks, which relies on user-space tricks, Oniux achieves this by placing each app in its own network namespace with no access to the host's interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-tor-oniux-tool-anonymizes-any-linux-apps-network-traffic/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Steal Customers Banking Details in Nova Scotia Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-steal-customers-banking-details/</link>
      <description>A cyberattack was detected on March 19, 2025, which compromised Nova Scotia Power's IT infrastructure and exfiltrated sensitive customer data, including banking details from pre-authorized payment systems. The breach impacts an undisclosed number of customers and exposed personal identifiers, financial records, and operational data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136066</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New .NET Multi-Stage Loader Targets Windows Systems to Deploy Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-net-multi-stage-loader-targets-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>A .NET-based multi-stage loader has been discovered, capable of deploying commodity stealers, keyloggers, and Remote Access Trojans (RATs) such as AgentTesla, Formbook, Remcos, and 404Keylogger. The loader's complex architecture and ability to embed encrypted payloads make detection challenging for traditional security tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136075</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xerox Launches April 2025 Security Patch for FreeFlow Print Server v2</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xerox-launches-april-2025-security-patch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Xerox FreeFlow Print Server v2 running on Windows 10; CVE(s): CVE-2025-21191, CVE-2025-27732, CVE-2024-9143; Summary: The update addresses over 40 critical vulnerabilities in OpenJDK Java, Apache HTTP Server, and OpenSSL, while introducing stricter encryption protocols for secure file transfers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135907</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook Down – Millions of Business &amp; Personal Users Worldwide Impacted</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-outlook-down/</link>
      <description>A major outage hit Microsoft Outlook and other Microsoft 365 services, leaving millions of users unable to access their email, calendars, and productivity tools. The disruption affected various services, including Teams, Excel, PowerPoint, and the Microsoft Store, causing disruptions for businesses and individuals alike. The timing of the outage, coinciding with the end of the financial year in some regions, exacerbated its impact on business communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136101</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Agents Bribed, Data of ~1% Users Leaked; $20M Extortion Attempt Fails</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/coinbase-agents-bribed-data-of-1-users.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Coinbase; CVE(s): None; Summary: Unknown cyber actors stole account data for less than 1% of Coinbase's monthly transacting users by targeting customer support agents overseas. The goal was to gather a list of customers and deceive them into handing over their cryptocurrency assets, with the attackers attempting to extort $20 million from Coinbase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/coinbase-agents-bribed-data-of-1-users.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nucor Steel Manufacturer Halts Production After Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nucor-steel-manufacturer-halts-production/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Nucor Corporation (Operational Systems); CVE(s): None; Summary: Unauthorized access to Nucor's information technology systems compromised critical operational systems, disrupting production at multiple facilities. The breach highlights the escalating risks of cyber threats to industrial control systems and the delicate balance between maintaining operational continuity and mitigating cybersecurity risks in critical manufacturing sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135977</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Data Compromised in Dior Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/customer-data-compromised/</link>
      <description>Dior's customer database was breached by unauthorized external actors, exposing various categories of personal information. The breach did not expose financial details, but may have placed affected customers at risk of targeted attacks or identity theft attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135954</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enisa Launched New European Vulnerability Database to Strengthen Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/enisa-unveils-new-european-vulnerability-database/</link>
      <description>The European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA) has launched the European Vulnerability Database (EUVD), a platform designed to enhance digital security across the EU by aggregating and standardizing vulnerability information affecting Information and Communication Technology (ICT) products and services. The database is accessible to the public, aiming to raise cybersecurity standards and provide users with actionable details for mitigating vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135880</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xanthorox Emerging BlackHat AI Tool Empowering Hackers in Phishing and Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/xanthorox-emerging-blackhat-ai-tool-empowering-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Xanthorox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Xanthorox is an artificial intelligence platform that enables the automated generation of phishing campaigns, malware, and hyperrealistic deepfakes. Its accessibility and affordability make it a potent tool for cybercriminals, allowing them to launch personalized attacks with ease. The platform's capabilities include generating ransomware code, crafting phishing emails, and producing deepfake audio or video for impersonation scams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135860</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vulnerability Enables Attackers to Crash Processes and Disrupt Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/node-js-vulnerability-enables-attackers-to-crash-processes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Node.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23166, CVE-2025-23167, CVE-2025-23165; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities in Node.js could allow attackers to crash server processes and disrupt critical services. CVE-2025-23166 affects improper error handling in asynchronous cryptographic operations, while CVE-2025-23167 updates the llhttp HTTP parser library to version 9.2.0, addressing security and robustness issues. CVE-2025-23165 addresses a resource cleanup issue in uv_fs_req_cleanup, which could lead to resource leaks or process instability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious NPM package uses Unicode steganography to evade detection</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-package-uses-unicode-steganography-to-evade-detection/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: os-info-checker-es6; CVE(s): None; Summary: The malicious Node Package Manager (NPM) package, os-info-checker-es6, uses invisible Unicode characters to hide malicious code and a Google Calendar link to host the command-and-control location. It delivers a sophisticated C2 mechanism that drops a malware payload, which is executed using eval() and includes persistence mechanisms in the system's temporary directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-npm-package-uses-unicode-steganography-to-evade-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase data breach exposes customer info and government IDs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-discloses-breach-faces-up-to-400-million-in-losses/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Coinbase; CVE(s): None; Summary: Rogue support agents stole customer data and demanded a $20 million ransom, which Coinbase refused to pay. The attackers exfiltrated personally identifiable information of up to 1% of Coinbase's customer base (around 1 million individuals), but could not steal private keys or passwords, nor access Coinbase Prime accounts and hot or cold wallets.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-discloses-breach-faces-up-to-400-million-in-losses/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Hackers Exploit XSS Vulnerabilities to Inject Malicious Code into Email Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/russian-hackers-exploit-xss-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Roundcube, Horde, MDaemon, Zimbra; CVE(s): CVE-2020-35730, CVE-2024-11182; Summary: Sednit group exploited known and zero-day XSS vulnerabilities in webmail servers to steal sensitive data. The campaign, dubbed Operation RoundPress, targets governmental and defense entities worldwide using spearphishing emails that inject malicious JavaScript payloads into victims' webmail interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136009</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized Google Calendar Invites Deliver Malicious Payload Using a Single Character</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-google-calendar-invites-deliver-malicious-payload/</link>
      <description>Malware distribution method leverages Google Calendar invites to deliver malicious payloads through seemingly innocuous links. The attack uses obfuscation techniques, including base64 encoding and binary trickery, to fetch payloads from a Google-hosted calendar event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135863</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Defender Application Control Bypassed Through Browser Exploit Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-defender-application-control-bypassed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers from X-Force Red Adversary Simulation team discovered a novel method to bypass Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC) by exploiting vulnerabilities in trusted Electron applications using the V8 engine. This technique allows attackers to execute native shellcode, effectively sidestepping WDAC's stringent controls and introducing malicious payloads into tightly controlled systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135981</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Officials Probe Rogue Communication Devices in Solar Power Inverters</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/u-s-officials-probe-rogue-communication-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Chinese-manufactured power inverters; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports that Chinese-manufactured power inverters contain undocumented communication equipment, which could allow remote access to manipulate or disable the devices, potentially destabilizing power grids and causing widespread blackouts. Experts warn that these hidden channels could bypass firewall protections, allowing malicious actors to alter inverter settings or shut them down en masse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135847</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransferLoader Malware Enables Attackers to Execute Arbitrary Commands on Infected Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/transferloader-malware-enables-attackers/</link>
      <description>TransferLoader is a sophisticated malware loader that has been active since at least February 2025. It consists of multiple components, including a downloader, backdoor, and specialized loader for the backdoor module. The malware allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on compromised systems and has been linked to the deployment of Morpheus ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135960</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkCloud Stealer Employs AutoIt to Evade Detection and Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/darkcloud-stealer-employs-autoit-to-evade-detection/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a series of attacks involving the DarkCloud Stealer malware, which uses AutoIt scripting and multi-stage payloads to bypass traditional detection mechanisms. The malware targets sensitive data such as login credentials, credit card information, and browser data, and has impacted sectors like government, high tech, and finance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135881</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chihuahua Stealer Exploits Google Drive Document to Harvest Browser Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chihuahua-stealer-exploits-google-drive-document/</link>
      <description>Chihuahua Stealer is a .NET-based infostealer that uses sophisticated techniques to infiltrate systems and exfiltrate sensitive data. It targets browser data, including login credentials, cookies, autofill information, and browsing history, as well as crypto wallet extensions. The malware's approach utilizes Google Drive as an initial infection vector, multi-stage payload delivery, scheduled task persistence, and advanced encryption methods, making it a significant challenge for cybersecurity professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interlock Ransomware Targeting Defense Contractors and Supply Chain Networks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/interlock-ransomware-targeting-defense-contractors/</link>
      <description>The Interlock Ransomware group has emerged as a significant threat targeting defense contractors and their supply chain networks, exploiting geopolitical tensions and local conflicts for espionage or strategic disruption. The group's attacks have exposed sensitive information about global defense supply chains, including connections to major players like Raytheon, SpaceX, Thales, and Leonardo, posing a direct threat to national security by enabling adversaries to map military supply chains, redirect shipments, or gain strategic insights during ongoing geopolitical conflicts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135808</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies hack high-value mail servers using an exploit from yesteryear</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/spies-hack-high-value-mail-servers-using-an-exploit-from-yesteryear/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Operation RoundPress, a cyberespionage campaign that exploited cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in mail servers to steal email secrets. The malicious code was embedded in HTML portions of emails and only ran when the email was viewed from a vulnerable webmail instance, with no persistence but repeatable exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/spies-hack-high-value-mail-servers-using-an-exploit-from-yesteryear/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pen Testing for Compliance Only? It's Time to Change Your Approach</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/pen-testing-for-compliance-only-its.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of compliance-focused penetration testing and emphasizes the importance of continuous penetration testing to identify and remediate new vulnerabilities. It highlights how compliance-driven testing often misses complex security flaws, gives attackers an attack vector, and creates a false sense of security. The article also presents benefits of embracing continuous security testing, such as proactive identification of vulnerabilities, continuous improvement, and staying ahead of attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/pen-testing-for-compliance-only-its.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 BCDR Essentials for Effective Ransomware Defense</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-5-bcdr-capabilities-for-ransomware-defense.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolving nature of ransomware and its increased sophistication, making it a highly coordinated and dangerous threat capable of crippling organizations of any size. It highlights the importance of having a strong recovery strategy in place, including building a business continuity and disaster recovery (BCDR) plan that includes isolation, immutability, and verification of backups. The article also emphasizes the need for regular testing, automation, and monitoring to ensure that backups are reliable and can be used to recover from attacks quickly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-5-bcdr-capabilities-for-ransomware-defense.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Linked APT28 Exploited MDaemon Zero-Day to Hack Government Webmail Servers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russia-linked-apt28-exploited-mdaemon.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): CVE-2023-43770, CVE-2024-27443, CVE-2024-11182; Summary: A Russia-linked threat actor (APT28) has been attributed to a cyber espionage operation targeting webmail servers via cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. The operation exploits flaws in Horde, MDaemon, and Zimbra, including a zero-day in MDaemon, to steal confidential data from specific email accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/russia-linked-apt28-exploited-mdaemon.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Package Leverages Unicode Steganography, Google Calendar as C2 Dropper</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-npm-package-leverages-unicode.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm package "os-info-checker-es6"; CVE(s): None; Summary: The package disguises itself as an operating system information utility, using Unicode-based steganography to hide its initial malicious code. It utilizes Google Calendar event short links as a dynamic dropper for its final payload, making it a sophisticated and evolving threat within the npm ecosystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-npm-package-leverages-unicode.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google fixes high severity Chrome flaw with public exploit</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw-with-public-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4664; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability was discovered in the Chrome web browser's Loader component, allowing remote attackers to leak cross-origin data via maliciously crafted HTML pages, potentially leading to full account takeover. The vulnerability has a public exploit and users are advised to update their browsers as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw-with-public-exploit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical BitLocker Flaw Exploited in Minutes: Bitpixie Vulnerability Proof of Concept Unveiled</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bitlocker-encryption-bypassed-in-minutes/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft BitLocker; CVE(s): CVE-2023-21563; Summary: A vulnerability in Windows BitLocker encryption allows attackers to bypass encryption and extract keys with brief physical access without modifying the hardware. This can compromise sensitive data on devices that lack pre-boot authentication, which is the default configuration for many Windows devices. The vulnerability requires a network connection and no specialized hardware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135804</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Zero-Day Vulnerability (CVE-2025-4664) Actively Exploited in The Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve-2025-4664-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4664; Summary: The vulnerability involves insufficient policy enforcement in Chrome's Loader component, allowing remote attackers to leak cross-origin data via crafted HTML pages. Exploits for this zero-day flaw are actively being used in the wild, and users are advised to update Chrome at the earliest opportunity to safeguard their systems with these essential security patches.

Additional Unspecified Fix from Internal Efforts (ID: 417268830); FYSA: This fix is part of multiple fixes from Google's internal security audits, fuzzing, and other initiatives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135789</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Chrome Vulnerability Enables Cross-Origin Data Leak via Loader Referrer Policy</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-chrome-vulnerability-enables-cross.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4664; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-4664, is a high-severity issue in Google Chrome's Loader component due to insufficient policy enforcement. An attacker can leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page, potentially leading to full account takeover and theft of sensitive query parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-chrome-vulnerability-enables-cross.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome to block admin-level browser launches for better security</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-chrome-to-block-admin-level-browser-launches-for-better-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a change to Chromium that will "de-elevate" Google Chrome, preventing it from running as an administrator in Windows. This is done to increase security by warning users and automatically relaunching the browser without elevated permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/google/google-chrome-to-block-admin-level-browser-launches-for-better-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers behind UK retail attacks now targeting US companies</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-scattered-spider-switches-targets-to-us-retail-chains/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a collective of threat actors, is targeting retail chains in the United Kingdom and has now started targeting retailers in the United States with ransomware and extortion operations. The group's tactics include social engineering, phishing, SIM swapping, and multi-factor authentication (MFA) bombing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-scattered-spider-switches-targets-to-us-retail-chains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Patches CVE-2025-4632 Used to Deploy Mirai Botnet via MagicINFO 9 Exploit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/samsung-patches-cve-2025-4632-used-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4632; Summary: A critical path traversal flaw (CVE-2025-4632) in Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server, tracked as CVSS score 9.8, allows attackers to write arbitrary files with system authority, and has been actively exploited in the wild, including to deploy the Mirai botnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/samsung-patches-cve-2025-4632-used-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BianLian and RansomExx Exploit SAP NetWeaver Flaw to Deploy PipeMagic Trojan</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/bianlian-and-ransomexx-exploit-sap.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29824, CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: Multiple cybercrime groups, including BianLian and RansomExx, are exploiting a recently disclosed security flaw in SAP NetWeaver. The vulnerability allows for privilege escalation and has been used to deliver malware, including the PipeMagic trojan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/bianlian-and-ransomexx-exploit-sap.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs join ongoing SAP NetWeaver attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-join-ongoing-sap-netweaver-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A maximum-severity vulnerability allows threat actors to gain remote code execution on vulnerable servers. The vulnerability can be exploited without login credentials, potentially leading to complete system compromise. Ransomware gangs, including RansomEXX and BianLian, have joined attacks exploiting this flaw, with evidence of Chinese threat actor involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-join-ongoing-sap-netweaver-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An $8.4 billion money launderer has been operating for years on US soil</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/incorporated-in-us-8-4b-money-launderer-for-chinese-speaking-crypto-scammers/</link>
      <description>Tether, a cryptocurrency, has the ability to freeze payments when it identifies bad actors. Despite this capability, there is no clear evidence that Tether has taken measures to stop Chinese-language crypto scammers and others from using its currency. The article highlights the ongoing struggle against financial crime in the cryptocurrency space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/incorporated-in-us-8-4b-money-launderer-for-chinese-speaking-crypto-scammers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Human Rights Commission leaks docs to search engines</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/australian-human-rights-commission-leaks-docs-to-search-engines/</link>
      <description>The Australian Human Rights Commission (AHRC) disclosed a data breach incident where private documents containing sensitive information, such as names, contact information, health details, and photographs, were leaked online and indexed by major search engines. The breach impacted 670 submissions between specific dates, and AHRC has requested the removal of the files from search engines and disabled web forms to prevent further exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/australian-human-rights-commission-leaks-docs-to-search-engines/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xinbi Telegram Market Tied to $8.4B in Crypto Crime, Romance Scams, North Korea Laundering</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/xinbi-telegram-market-tied-to-84b-in.html</link>
      <description>Xinbi Guarantee, a Telegram-based marketplace, has facilitated $8.4 billion in transactions since 2022, offering various illicit services such as technology sales, personal data trading, and money laundering services. The platform's users include vendors selling fake IDs, databases of stolen information, and services for stalking and intimidating targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/xinbi-telegram-market-tied-to-84b-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Leverage Weaponized HTML Files to Deliver Horabot Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-leverage-weaponized-html-files/</link>
      <description>A phishing campaign targeting Spanish-speaking users in Latin America has been discovered by FortiGuard Labs. The attack uses malicious HTML files embedded in emails to steal sensitive information and propagate through networks. The campaign is highly sophisticated, using browser redirection tricks, custom string decoding, and PowerShell scripts to evade detection and exfiltrate data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135763</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TA406 Hackers Target Government Entities to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ta406-hackers-target-government-entities/</link>
      <description>TA406, a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor, has launched targeted phishing campaigns against Ukrainian government entities. The attacks aim to gather strategic intelligence on the Russian invasion of Ukraine and assess risks to North Korea's forces assisting Russia. The campaign involves credential harvesting through fake Microsoft security alerts and malware deployment via RAR archives and HTML attachments.

FYSA: TA406's dual-pronged offensive includes credential harvesting through fake Microsoft security alerts and malware deployment via RAR archives and HTML attachments, aiming to gather strategic intelligence on the Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Threat Intelligence Releases Actionable Threat Hunting Technique for Malicious .desktop Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-releases-actionable-threat-hunting-technique/</link>
      <description>Malicious .desktop files were discovered to be a novel attack vector used by threat actors to compromise systems. These files exploit legitimate system processes and use junk code to obfuscate their intent. The files, which typically include sections like [Desktop Entry] with keys such as Name, Comment, Exec, and Icon, can trigger commands that open seemingly innocuous PDFs via Google Drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135719</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Adobe Photoshop Vulnerability Enables Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-adobe-photoshop-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Photoshop; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30324, CVE-2025-30325, CVE-2025-30326; Summary: Three high-severity vulnerabilities in Photoshop 2024 and 2025 allow arbitrary code execution on Windows and macOS systems through memory corruption risks. The flaws involve improper memory management during image file processing and require user interaction via malicious file openings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135681</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe Adobe Illustrator Flaw Allows Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/severe-adobe-illustrator-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Adobe Illustrator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30330; Summary: The vulnerability allows arbitrary code execution on affected systems, impacting Windows and macOS versions of Illustrator 2024 and 2025. It could enable attackers to take control of a user's device by tricking them into opening a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135702</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft fixes Linux boot issues on dual-boot Windows systems</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-linux-boot-issues-on-dual-boot-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The August 2024 Windows security updates prevented Linux from booting on dual-boot systems with Secure Boot enabled, due to an SBAT update that blocks UEFI shim bootloaders vulnerable to the CVE-2022-2601 GRUB2 Secure Boot bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-fixes-linux-boot-issues-on-dual-boot-windows-systems/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel giant Nucor Corporation facing disruptions after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-corporation-facing-disruptions-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nucor Corporation, the largest steel producer in the US, experienced a cybersecurity incident that forced it to take parts of its network offline and suspend production at multiple locations. The incident has been reported to law enforcement authorities and external cybersecurity experts have been engaged to assist with the investigation. No details about the attack's date or type were provided, including whether data theft or encryption was involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/steel-giant-nucor-corporation-facing-disruptions-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Unveil New Mechanism to Track Compartmentalized Cyber Threats</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-mechanism-to-track-compartmentalized-cyber-threats/</link>
      <description>This article introduces the extended Diamond Model for cybersecurity professionals to tackle compartmentalized cyber threats. The model integrates a "Relationship Layer" to contextualize interactions between adversaries, capabilities, infrastructure, and victims, enabling accurate attribution and prevention of erroneous clustering of threat activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135703</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HTTPBot Botnet Rapidly Expands to Target Windows Machines</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-httpbot-botnet-rapidly-expands/</link>
      <description>The HTTPBot Botnet is a novel Trojan developed in the Go programming language that targets Windows machines and uses innovative HTTP-based Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attack methods to target high-value business interfaces. It deploys seven distinct HTTP attack techniques, including randomized User-Agent strings, dynamic URL paths, and cookie replenishment mechanisms to bypass conventional rule-based detection systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135680</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTM360 Identifies Surge in Phishing Attacks Targeting Meta Business Users</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ctm360-identifies-surge-in-phishing.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a global phishing threat called "Meta Mirage" that targets businesses using Meta's Business Suite. The attackers impersonate official Meta communications, tricking users into handing over sensitive details like passwords and security codes (OTP). The campaign uses fake alerts about policy violations, account suspensions, or urgent verification notices to deceive victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ctm360-identifies-surge-in-phishing.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Phishing: Attack Targets Victims With Trusted Sites and Live Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/focused-phishing-attack-targets-victims-with-trusted-sites-and-live-validation/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a real-world phishing incident that showcases advanced tactics used by attackers, including leveraging legitimate infrastructure, precision email validation, and evasive delivery techniques. The attack involved a server-side phishing page that dynamically handled email input and included anti-analysis mechanisms to obstruct analysis efforts. The article highlights the importance of browser-based, zero-day phishing protection and emphasizes the need for security stacks to detect and block phishing pages even on trusted domains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/focused-phishing-attack-targets-victims-with-trusted-sites-and-live-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
