<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:00:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>VMware ESXi, Firefox, Red Hat Linux &amp; SharePoint Hacked – Pwn2Own Day 2</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-esxi-firefox-red-hat-linux-sharepoint-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Viettel Cyber Security used an OOB Write for a Guest-to-Host escape on Oracle VirtualBox, earning $40,000 and 4 Master of Pwn points.

FYSA: The competition has awarded a cumulative total of $695,000 with participants revealing 20 unique zero-day vulnerabilities thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136532</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms May Windows 10 updates trigger BitLocker recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-may-windows-10-updates-trigger-bitlocker-recovery/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some Windows 10 and Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2021 systems will boot into BitLocker recovery after installing the May 2025 security updates. This issue may trigger an Automatic Repair, which requires input of a BitLocker recovery key to initiate the repair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-may-windows-10-updates-trigger-bitlocker-recovery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical WordPress Plugin Flaw Puts Over 10,000 Sites of Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-wordpress-plugin-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Eventin plugin for WordPress; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Eventin plugin allows unauthenticated users to gain administrative access to affected sites due to a lack of proper permission checks in the /wp-json/eventin/v2/speakers/import REST API endpoint. This vulnerability can be exploited by uploading a CSV file containing user details, including the desired role set to administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136486</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated NPM Attack Leverages Google Calendar2 for Advanced Communication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophisticated-npm-attack-leverages-google-calendar2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: os-info-checker-es6; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign was embedded within the npm package os-info-checker-es6, which evolved from gathering basic OS information to a complex threat using platform-specific compiled Node.js modules and obfuscation techniques. The malware employed steganography, Unicode-based hiding of malicious payloads, and a command-and-control mechanism utilizing Google Calendar short links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136460</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ransomware Attack Targets Elon Musk Supporters Using PowerShell to Deploy Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-ransomware-attack-targets-elon-musk-supporters/</link>
      <description>A newly identified ransomware campaign targets supporters of Elon Musk through a sophisticated phishing-based attack. The attack begins with a deceptive PDF document, which leads to the download of malicious ZIP files hosted on Netlify. The infection chain involves multi-stage PowerShell scripts and executables designed to compromise the target system, ultimately deploying a variant of the Fog ransomware for financial gain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136498</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printer Company Distributes Malicious Drivers Infected with XRed Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/printer-company-distributes-malicious-drivers-infected/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Procolored; CVE(s): None; Summary: Procolored's software drivers contained malicious code, including the XRed backdoor malware and SnipVex virus. The XRed backdoor facilitated keylogging, file downloads, screenshots, and remote command execution, while SnipVex posed a persistent threat by targeting .exe files and replacing Bitcoin addresses in the clipboard to divert transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Agent Impersonate as Stanford Student For Intelligence Gathering</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-agent-impersonate-as-stanford-student/</link>
      <description>A Chinese intelligence operative posing as a Stanford University student has been uncovered, targeting students conducting China-related research. The agent used the alias "Charles Chen" and employed a "crowdsourced approach" to gather sensitive information, including using civilians unaffiliated with intelligence agencies to collect data. This case highlights concerns about Chinese intelligence activities at American universities and the need for increased awareness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136455</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel arrests new suspect behind Nomad Bridge $190M crypto hack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/israel-arrests-new-suspect-behind-nomad-bridge-190m-crypto-hack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Nomad bridge smart-contract; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Nomad bridge smart-contract introduced a critical vulnerability in its Replica smart contract, allowing hackers to siphon over $190 million worth of assets. The flaw allowed any message with a correct root hash to be accepted, even if the underlying proof was invalid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/israel-arrests-new-suspect-behind-nomad-bridge-190m-crypto-hack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT rolls out Codex, an AI tool for software programming</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-rolls-out-codex-an-ai-tool-for-software-programming/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenAI's new AI agent, Codex, which automates and delegates programming tasks for software engineers. Codex can write new code, propose pull requests, and run each task in its own sandbox, making developers more productive with AI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-rolls-out-codex-an-ai-tool-for-software-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers exploit VMware ESXi, Microsoft SharePoint zero-days at Pwn2Own</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-vmware-esxi-microsoft-sharepoint-zero-days-at-pwn2own/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Competitors successfully exploited zero-day bugs in multiple products, including Microsoft SharePoint, VMware ESXi, Oracle VirtualBox, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, and Mozilla Firefox, earning a total of $695,000 over the first two days of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-vmware-esxi-microsoft-sharepoint-zero-days-at-pwn2own/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printer maker Procolored offered malware-laced drivers for months</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/printer-maker-procolored-offered-malware-laced-drivers-for-months/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Procolored printers; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official software supplied with Procolored printers included a remote access trojan (XRedRAT) and a cryptocurrency stealer (SnipVex) for at least six months. These malware were delivered through the companion software and drivers for Procolored UV printer models F8, F13, F13 Pro, V6, V11 Pro, and VF13 Pro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/printer-maker-procolored-offered-malware-laced-drivers-for-months/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs increasingly use Skitnet post-exploitation malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-increasingly-use-skitnet-post-exploitation-malware/</link>
      <description>Skitnet ("Bossnet") is a new malware used by ransomware gangs for post-exploitation activities. It uses a Rust-based loader to decrypt a Nim binary and establish a DNS-based reverse shell for communication with the command and control server. The malware supports various commands, including persistence, screenshot capture, remote access tool installation, and antivirus enumeration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-increasingly-use-skitnet-post-exploitation-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058379 Update Causes PCs to Enter Recovery Mode and Prompt for BitLocker Key</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-10-kb5058379-update-causes-pcs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5058379 security update causes technical issues for numerous systems, booting them into Windows Recovery mode and requiring BitLocker recovery keys. This issue affects enterprise environments, particularly those using SCCM or WSUS deployment mechanisms, and is caused by the update triggering BitLocker's hardware validation mechanisms inappropriately during installation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136448</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal Andrei Tarasov Escapes US Extradition, Returns to Russia</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminal-andrei-tarasov-escapes-us-extradition/</link>
      <description>Andrei Vladimirovich Tarasov, a Russian cybercrime figure known as "Aels," has returned to Russia after evading US extradition. He was released from German custody and used ride-sharing services and transportation routes without showing identification documents to make his escape. Tarasov remains active in cybercrime circles, participating in spamming channels on Telegram and sharing plans for hacking Zimbra servers at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136434</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HTTPBot Botnet Launches 200+ Precision DDoS Attacks on Gaming and Tech Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-httpbot-botnet-launches-200.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a botnet malware called HTTPBot that targets Windows systems in China's gaming industry, technology companies, and educational institutions. It uses various attack modules to launch distributed denial-of-service attacks with "scalpel-like" precision, bypassing traditional rule-based detection mechanisms by simulating HTTP protocols and mimicking legitimate browser behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-httpbot-botnet-launches-200.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Alerts Public to Malicious Campaign Impersonating US Government Officials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fbi-alerts-public-to-malicious-campaign/</link>
      <description>The Federal Bureau of Investigation has issued a warning about an ongoing malicious messaging campaign targeting current and former senior US government officials and their contacts. Threat actors are impersonating high-ranking US officials through text messages and AI-generated voice calls to gain access to personal accounts and potentially sensitive information, using "smishing" (SMS phishing) and "vishing" (voice phishing) tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136383</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigidstealer Malware Targets macOS Users to Harvest Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/frigidstealer-malware-targets-macos-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: FrigidStealer is an information-stealing malware that targets macOS users by masquerading as routine browser updates. It bypasses Gatekeeper protections and steals sensitive data such as browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and system information. The malware operates with sophistication, establishing persistence through launchservicesd and employing Apple Events for unauthorized inter-process communication to harvest data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136377</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Group 123 Targets Windows Systems in Ongoing Malicious Payload Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-group-123-targets-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is about Group123, a North Korean state-sponsored APT group that targets Windows-based systems across multiple regions. The group's primary motivation is information theft and espionage, often aligning with North Korea's strategic interests. They use various tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) to carry out their attacks, including spear phishing, exploiting software vulnerabilities, and using custom malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136321</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH Auth Key Reuse Uncovers Advanced Targeted Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ssh-auth-key-reuse-targeted-phishing-campaign/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Kuwait's fisheries, telecommunications, and insurance sectors has been exposed by Hunt.io researchers. The campaign uses 230 malicious domains, a network of servers, and advanced tradecraft to harvest credentials from unsuspecting users. It leverages reused SSH authentication keys, consistent Autonomous System Number (ASN) usage, and multi-tenant server usage for efficiency, underscoring the threat actors' focus on scalability and persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136349</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Endpoint Manager Vulnerabilities Allow Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-endpoint-manager-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: A critical vulnerability chain in Ivanti EPMM allows pre-authenticated remote code execution attacks without credentials. The chain consists of an authentication bypass (CVE-2025-4427) and a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVE-2025-4428), enabling attackers to compromise systems without credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136342</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best Practices for Effective Data Protection</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-10-best-practices-for-effective.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses data protection best practices to safeguard sensitive data from cyber threats. It covers topics such as understanding the outcome you want, identifying crown jewel data, defining a data protection program, using AI-powered classification, adopting a zero-trust architecture, and ensuring compliance with regulations. The article also touches on unmanaged devices, browser isolation, cloud posture management, and data security training.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-10-best-practices-for-effective.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenkins Released Security Updates – Multiple Vulnerabilities Fixed That Allow Attackers to Exploit CI/CD Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jenkins-released-security-updates-multiple-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Jenkins plugins; CVEs: CVE-2025-47884, CVE-2025-47889, CVE-2025-47885, CVE-2025-47886, CVE-2025-47887, CVE-2025-47888; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities were identified in various Jenkins plugins, including authentication bypasses, cross-site scripting, and missing permission checks. These flaws could allow attackers to compromise Jenkins environments, bypass authentication, or gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136288</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Expose New Intel CPU Flaws Enabling Memory Leaks and Spectre v2 Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-new-intel-cpu-flaws.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intel; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45332, CVE-2024-28956, CVE-2025-24495; Summary: All modern Intel CPUs are vulnerable to a flaw known as Branch Privilege Injection (BPI), which allows attackers to gain unauthorized access to information from other processor users. The vulnerability can be exploited to read the contents of the processor's cache and working memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-new-intel-cpu-flaws.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US charges 12 more suspects linked to $230 million crypto theft</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-charges-12-more-suspects-linked-to-230-million-crypto-theft/</link>
      <description>Twelve suspects were charged with a RICO conspiracy for allegedly stealing over $230 million in cryptocurrency and laundering the funds using crypto exchanges and mixing services. The scheme involved spoofed phone numbers, impersonating customer support at Google and Gemini, and exploiting 2FA and remote desktop applications to steal private keys and cryptocurrency funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-charges-12-more-suspects-linked-to-230-million-crypto-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pwn2Own Day 1 – Windows 11, Red Hat Linux, &amp; Oracle VirtualBox Hacked</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-red-hat-linux-oracle-virtualbox-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: Three separate successful attacks against Windows 11 highlighted significant security weaknesses in Microsoft's flagship operating system. The attacks exploited use-after-free (UAF) vulnerabilities with integer overflows and type confusion, successfully escalating privileges to SYSTEM level.

FYSA: The Pwn2Own Berlin competition showcased significant cybersecurity threats across multiple platforms, including Windows 11 and Red Hat Linux. Exploits targeted virtualization technologies and containerization, demonstrating serious security implications for these technologies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136239</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall SMA1000 Vulnerability Allow Attackers to Exploit Encoded URLs To Remotely Gain Internal Systems Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sonicwall-sma1000-vulnerability-allow-attackers-to-exploit-encoded-urls/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA1000 Appliance; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40595; Summary: The SonicWall SMA1000 Appliance has a high-severity Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to send unauthorized requests to unintended destinations, potentially compromising internal networks and sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136229</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Target Industrial Automation Systems Using Over 11,600 Malware Variants</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-target-industrial-automation-systems/</link>
      <description>Hackers are targeting Industrial Control Systems (ICS) with an arsenal of 11,679 different malware families, employing various tactics and using legitimate services like content delivery networks and cloud storage to evade defenses. The trend shows a surge in specific threat categories and regional disparities, highlighting the need for tailored defenses and bolstered cybersecurity frameworks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136266</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Group Assessment: Muddled Libra (Updated May 16, 2025)</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/muddled-libra/</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be an in-depth analysis of a threat actor known as "Muddled Libra." This group is described as being methodical and proficient in various security disciplines, making them a significant threat to enterprise organizations.

The article provides an overview of Muddled Libra's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including their use of social engineering, phishing, and remote access tools. It also highlights the group's ability to adapt and evolve, as seen in their transition from focusing primarily on data theft to incorporating ransomware and disruption of operations.

The article offers recommendations for defending against Muddled Libra, including implementing multi-factor authentication (MFA), conducting user awareness training, and monitoring and managing access to critical defenses and controls. It also suggests employing capabilities such as network security, endpoint security, and security automation to detect and respond to threats.

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the tactics and strategies employed by Muddled Libra, highlighting the importance of robust cybersecurity measures and threat intelligence in defending against advanced persistent threats (APTs) like this group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=128741</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leveraging PowerShell to Bypass Antivirus and EDR Defenses</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-leveraging-powershell/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft PowerShell; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting Microsoft PowerShell to bypass advanced antivirus and EDR defenses, using techniques such as "Living off the Land" (LotL) to leverage built-in system utilities and evade detection. This allows attackers to perform post-compromise activities like privilege escalation, credential dumping, and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136253</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA tags recently patched Chrome bug as actively exploited</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tags-recently-patched-chrome-bug-as-actively-exploited-zero-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4664; Summary: The vulnerability is due to insufficient policy enforcement in Google Chrome's Loader component, allowing remote attackers to leak cross-origin data via maliciously crafted HTML pages. Successful exploitation can lead to account takeover or stealing query parameters containing sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tags-recently-patched-chrome-bug-as-actively-exploited-zero-day/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Replicate Advanced Tactics and Tools of VanHelsing Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-replicate-advanced-tactics-and-tools/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the VanHelsing ransomware operation, which has been emulated by cybersecurity researchers at AttackIQ. The emulation replicates the ransomware's behavioral patterns to help organizations validate their security controls against this evolving threat. The article details the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) used by VanHelsing, including local system reconnaissance, Ingress Tool Transfer, and file encryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136240</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fileless Remcos RAT Delivered via LNK Files and MSHTA in PowerShell-Based Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fileless-remcos-rat-delivered-via-lnk.html</link>
      <description>A new malware campaign uses PowerShell-based shellcode loader to deploy Remcos RAT, a remote access trojan. The attack chain delivers malicious LNK files embedded within ZIP archives, often disguised as Office documents, and leverages mshta.exe for proxy execution during the initial stage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fileless-remcos-rat-delivered-via-lnk.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Webinar] From Code to Cloud to SOC: Learn a Smarter Way to Defend Modern Applications</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-code-to-cloud-to-soc-learn-smarter.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the challenges of security teams keeping up with modern app development in the cloud. It highlights how attackers quickly exploit vulnerabilities, while organizations often respond late to critical alerts. The article emphasizes the importance of unifying security tools and teams across silos (DevSecOps, CloudSec, SOC) to prevent 80% of cloud exposures from slipping through.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/from-code-to-cloud-to-soc-learn-smarter.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proofpoint Buys Hornetsecurity, A Microsoft 365 Security Specialist For $1 Billion</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/a-microsoft-365-security-specialist-for-1-billion/</link>
      <description>Proofpoint acquires Hornetsecurity Group to strengthen its position in delivering human-centric security solutions to small and mid-sized businesses worldwide. The deal brings over $160 million in annual recurring revenue and expands Proofpoint's presence in the SMB segment through managed service providers (MSPs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136213</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tor Oniux Tool Offers Anonymous Linux App Traffic</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tor-oniux-tool/</link>
      <description>Oniux is a new command-line utility from the Tor Project that provides comprehensive network isolation for Linux applications, ensuring all traffic routes exclusively through the Tor network. This tool eliminates the risk of accidental data leaks by leveraging Linux kernel namespaces to create complete network separation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136203</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak confirms OpenAI's ChatGPT will integrate MCP</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leak-confirms-openais-chatgpt-will-integrate-mcp/</link>
      <description>This article does not mention a vulnerability in any product or system. Instead, it discusses the development of Model Context Protocol (MCP) by OpenAI for its ChatGPT AI model to connect with third-party services and use them as context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/leak-confirms-openais-chatgpt-will-integrate-mcp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT will soon record, transcribe, and summarize your meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-soon-record-transcribe-and-summarize-your-meetings/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: This article does not contain information about a specific vulnerability. It discusses OpenAI's planned "Record" feature in their ChatGPT product, which will allow users to record live meetings and generate AI-powered transcripts. The article also mentions other cybersecurity-related topics such as the top 10 MITRE ATT&amp;CK techniques behind 93% of attacks, but does not provide specific details about vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-will-soon-record-transcribe-and-summarize-your-meetings/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058379 update triggers BitLocker recovery on some devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-triggering-bitlocker-recovery-after-install/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5058379 cumulative update is causing unexpected BitLocker recovery prompts on some devices after installation and restart, with reports of affected devices from Lenovo, Dell, and HP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-triggering-bitlocker-recovery-after-install/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI warns of ongoing scam that uses deepfake audio to impersonate government officials</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/fbi-warns-of-ongoing-scam-that-uses-deepfake-audio-to-impersonate-government-officials/</link>
      <description>The article provides guidance on how to detect malicious messaging campaigns, including verifying the identity of those contacting you, examining email addresses and URLs for subtle imperfections, and listening carefully to voice tone and word choice. It also acknowledges that AI-generated content has advanced making it difficult to identify, but emphasizes the importance of being cautious and seeking help when in doubt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/fbi-warns-of-ongoing-scam-that-uses-deepfake-audio-to-impersonate-government-officials/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After latest kidnap attempt, crypto types tell crime bosses: Transfers are traceable</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/fractured-skulls-and-ski-masks-more-crypto-kidnap-madness-on-the-streets-of-paris/</link>
      <description>Crypto robbery tactics have caught the attention of organized crime, with copycat attacks increasing in France, Belgium, and Spain. The misconception that crypto transfers are untraceable is believed to be driving these attacks, despite efforts by industry insiders like Chainalysis CEO Jonathan Levin to educate criminal organizations on the traceability of crypto transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/fractured-skulls-and-ski-masks-more-crypto-kidnap-madness-on-the-streets-of-paris/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breachforums Boss to Pay $700k in Healthcare Breach</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/breachforums-boss-to-pay-700k-in-healthcare-breach/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the novel legal outcome where a cybercriminal, Conor Brian Fitzpatrick (a.k.a. "Pompompurin"), will forfeit nearly $700,000 to settle a civil lawsuit from a health insurance company whose customer data was posted for sale on Breachforums in 2023. The article also touches on Fitzpatrick's criminal activity, including possession of child sexual abuse material and operating the cybercrime community Breachforums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71263</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government webmail hacked via XSS bugs in global spy campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/government-webmail-hacked-via-xss-bugs-in-global-spy-campaign/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various webmail servers (Roundcube, Horde, MDaemon, Zimbra); CVE(s): CVE-2020-35730, CVE-2023-43770, CVE-2024-11182, CVE-2024-27443; Summary: Hackers, attributed to Russian state-sponsored hackers APT28 (Fancy Bear), are exploiting zero-day and n-day flaws in webmail servers to steal email credentials from high-value government organizations. The campaign starts with spear-phishing emails containing malicious JavaScript payloads that execute when the email is opened, allowing credential theft and data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/government-webmail-hacked-via-xss-bugs-in-global-spy-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: US officials targeted in voice deepfake attacks since April</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-us-officials-targeted-in-voice-deepfake-attacks-since-april/</link>
      <description>The FBI warned that cybercriminals are using AI-generated audio deepfakes to target U.S. officials in voice phishing attacks, starting in April. The attackers impersonate senior US officials to establish rapport before gaining access to personal accounts and compromising other government officials' contact information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbi-us-officials-targeted-in-voice-deepfake-attacks-since-april/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xoxo to Prague</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/xoxo-to-prague/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a rare and unfiltered look into LockBit's operations after their dark web affiliate panels were defaced, exposing 20 tables including chats between affiliates and victims. The chats reveal tactics, ransom demands, and negotiation strategies, as well as instances of confusion and pressure from tight deadlines.

FYSA: The article highlights the complexity of cybercrime and the human stories behind the headlines, emphasizing the importance of understanding the intricate relationships and interactions between various threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6824fb08fed2140001359138</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Data Breach – Customers Personal Info, Government‑ID &amp; Transaction Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coinbase-data-breach/</link>
      <description>Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States, has been targeted by a sophisticated insider campaign that compromised sensitive customer account information and internal documentation. The breach occurred when several overseas contractors and employees were bribed to steal data from Coinbase's internal systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136196</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta to Train AI on E.U. User Data From May 27 Without Consent; Noyb Threatens Lawsuit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-to-train-ai-on-eu-user-data-from.html</link>
      <description>Meta's plan to train AI models using user data without explicit opt-in consent has been criticized by Austrian privacy non-profit noyb (none of your business), which sent a cease-and-desist letter threatening a class action lawsuit. The group argues that Meta is relying on an alleged "legitimate interest" instead of seeking consent, and that this approach violates the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Union.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/meta-to-train-ai-on-eu-user-data-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova Scotia Power confirms hackers stole customer data in cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nova-scotia-power-confirms-hackers-stole-customer-data-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Nova Scotia Power suffered a data breach after threat actors stole sensitive customer data, including full names, phone numbers, and bank account numbers. The company discovered the incident on April 28, 2025, but it's believed to have occurred earlier on March 19, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nova-scotia-power-confirms-hackers-stole-customer-data-in-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Turla’s Uroboros Infrastructure and Tactics Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/inside-turlas-uroboros-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Uroboros rootkit, attributed to the APT group Turla, which showcases sophisticated and mastery over Windows kernel internals. The malware embeds itself into the operating system with strategic intent and architectural ingenuity, enabling long-term control and covert communication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136103</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Alerts on Five Active Zero-Day Windows Vulnerabilities Being Exploited</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-alerts-on-five-active-zero-day-windows-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added five newly identified Windows 0-day vulnerabilities to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, presenting significant risks for organizations relying on Microsoft Windows environments. The article highlights the potential impact of these vulnerabilities, including privilege escalation attacks and system takeover or additional malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136155</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Google Services to Send Malicious Law Enforcement Requests</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-google-services/</link>
      <description>Sophisticated phishing campaign uses Google services to create convincing law enforcement requests; attackers exploit trust associated with Google infrastructure to deceive companies and individuals into disclosing sensitive information. The campaign leverages Google Forms and Drive to craft and distribute fraudulent requests, posing a severe threat to data privacy and security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136121</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
