<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:01:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Reveal How Hacktivist Groups Gain Attention and Choose Their Targets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-reveal-how-hacktivist-groups/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have released findings on the operational dynamics of hacktivist organizations, revealing sophisticated attention-seeking behaviors and strategic target selection methodologies. The study highlights hacktivists' calculated targeting strategies, self-promotion mechanisms, and use of psychological warfare approaches to amplify their perceived influence. It also notes the commercialization trend within the hacktivist community and the increasing focus on capability development, leading to a more complex threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149772</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Actors Weaponize LNK Files via ClickFix Fake CAPTCHA Pages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ung0002-actors-weaponize-lnk-files/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a sophisticated espionage group known as UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002) that has been conducting persistent campaigns across multiple Asian jurisdictions since May 2024. The group uses social engineering techniques, advanced malware deployment methods, and custom-developed implants to target organizations in China, Hong Kong, and Pakistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149751</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK’s Co-op Retailer Hit by Cyberattack, 6.5 Million Members’ Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uks-co-op-retailer-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The UK's Co-op retailer suffered a significant cyberattack in April 2024, resulting in the theft of personal data from all 6.5 million members. While no financial information was compromised, hackers accessed names, addresses, and contact information. The breach highlights the ongoing cybersecurity challenges facing major retailers and the importance of robust preventive measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149774</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Disrupts NoName057(16) Hacktivist Group Linked to DDoS Attacks Against Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-disrupts-noname05716-hacktivist.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses an international operation led by Europol to disrupt the infrastructure of a pro-Russian hacktivist group called NoName057(16) that has been linked to DDoS attacks against Ukraine and its allies. The joint effort resulted in the dismantling of the group's central server infrastructure, arrests, searches, and issuance of arrest warrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-disrupts-noname05716-hacktivist.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Container Toolkit Vulnerability Allows Privileged Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nvidia-container-toolkit-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit and GPU Operator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266, CVE-2025-23267; Summary: The NVIDIA Container Toolkit and GPU Operator contain two critical vulnerabilities that allow attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. The first vulnerability (CVE-2025-23266) has a CVSS score of 9.0, while the second (CVE-2025-23267) has a score of 8.5. These flaws enable privilege escalation, data tampering, information disclosure, and denial-of-service attacks in containerized environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149760</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-Click Oracle Cloud Code Editor RCE Flaw Allows Malicious File Upload to Shell</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/1-click-oracle-cloud-code-editor-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Code Editor; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure's Code Editor enabled attackers to silently hijack victim Cloud Shell environments through a single malicious link, allowing for potential lateral movement across OCI services and compromise of integrated developer tools. The vulnerability stemmed from a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) weakness in the file upload mechanism, which was remediated by implementing additional CSRF protections requiring a custom HTTP header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149729</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM vs ASM vs Vulnerability Management: What Security Leaders Need to Know in 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ctem-vs-asm-vs-vulnerability-management.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of implementing Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) programs, which complement Vulnerability Management (VM) and Attack Surface Management (ASM). CTEM provides a systematic approach to discover, prioritize, validate, and respond to security exposures. The article also highlights the benefits of integrating VM, ASM, and penetration testing solutions into a unified interface to support a holistic CTEM program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ctem-vs-asm-vs-vulnerability-management.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Threat Actors Use AI-Generated Emails to Target Cybersecurity Researchers and Academics</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-threat-actors-use-ai-generated-emails/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Iranian state-backed Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) groups and their hacktivist allies' increased cyber operations following Israeli and American strikes on Iranian nuclear and military facilities. The article highlights the groups' tactics, including espionage, disruption, and psychological warfare, as well as their use of AI-enhanced phishing operations and industrial control system scanning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149704</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaaS operation using Emmenhtal and Amadey linked to threats against Ukrainian entities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/maas-operation-using-emmenhtal-and-amadey-linked-to-threats-against-ukrainian-entities/</link>
      <description>A Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation, dubbed "Amadey," has been identified by Cisco Talos. The operation uses fake GitHub accounts to host payloads and tools, allowing operators to deliver various malware families to infected hosts. This MaaS operation overlaps with a previous SmokeLoader phishing campaign targeting Ukrainian entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6876776cec6298000147ad76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use DNS Queries to Evade Defenses and Exfiltrate Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-dns-queries-to-evade-defenses-and-exfiltrate-data/</link>
      <description>DNS tunneling is a technique used by cybercriminals to bypass corporate security measures and steal sensitive data by encoding data within DNS queries and responses. The attack process begins when threat actors gain control of a domain name's authoritative name server, allowing them to conduct command-and-control (C2) operations and data exfiltration while remaining largely undetected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149688</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy 28+ Malicious Packages to Spread Protestware Scripts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-28-malicious-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Socket's Threat Research Team; CVE(s): None; Summary: A network of at least 28 malicious packages, including protestware scripts, was discovered in the npm supply chain. The protestware disrupts user interface interactions by disabling mouse events and initiating playback of the Ukrainian national anthem, affecting Russian-language users on specific domains. The vulnerability highlights the risks of code reuse in open-source repositories, where undisclosed payloads can cascade through dependencies, amplifying potential impacts on downstream applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149690</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPI Blocks Inbox.ru Domains After 1,500+ Fake Package Uploads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pypi-blocks-inbox-ru-domains/</link>
      <description>PyPI blocked the inbox.ru email domain after a campaign created over 250 fraudulent accounts and uploaded more than 1,500 empty projects, causing confusion among end-users and straining resources. The incident highlights the delegated security model of PyPI's registration process and emphasizes the importance of user vigilance and advanced detection mechanisms to prevent future incursions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149680</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical SharePoint RCE Vulnerability Exploited via Malicious XML in Web Part</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sharepoint-rce-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None; Summary: A severe remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint allows attackers to execute arbitrary code through malicious XML content embedded within web parts. The vulnerability originates from the deserialization process of web part properties and can be exploited through multiple endpoints, including the _/vti_bin/webpartpages.asmx service using the ConvertWebPartFormat SOAP action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149676</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Actively Exploited CitrixBleed 2 Flaw Ahead of PoC Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-actively-exploited-citrixbleed-2-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The CitrixBleed 2 vulnerability was exploited by threat actors nearly two weeks before a public proof-of-concept was released, highlighting the sophistication of modern attack campaigns. Initial exploitation began on June 23, followed by the public release of a proof-of-concept on July 4, and GreyNoise's subsequent creation of a tracking tag on July 7. The vulnerability represents a significant security risk for organizations running Citrix NetScaler appliances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149671</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Flaw Lets Remote Attackers Upload Arbitrary Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-unified-intelligence-center-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Intelligence Center; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20274; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Cisco's Unified Intelligence Center allows authenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files, potentially enabling complete system compromise through privilege escalation to root access. The flaw stems from improper file validation and can be exploited by users with Report Designer role privileges, allowing for the execution of arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149656</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponizing SVG: How Threat Actors Embed Malicious JavaScript in Vector Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-threat-actors-embed-malicious-javascript-in-vector-files/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers have identified an emerging attack campaign using Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) files to deliver JavaScript-based redirect attacks. The technique exploits the inherent trust in image formats, allowing malicious actors to embed obfuscated JavaScript within SVG files that execute automatically when opened in web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149610</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Target Taiwan's Semiconductor Sector with Cobalt Strike, Custom Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwans.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on spear-phishing campaigns conducted by three Chinese state-sponsored threat actors targeting the Taiwanese semiconductor industry. The campaigns involve phishing emails with malicious payloads, including Cobalt Strike or a custom backdoor, and DLL side-loading to spawn reverse shells and establish command-and-control connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwans.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0-Day RCE Flaw in SonicWall SMA Devices Exploited to Launch OVERSTEP Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/0-day-rce-flaw-in-sonicwall-sma-devices-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall; CVE(s): CVE-2024-38475, None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting previously stolen credentials and a new rootkit called OVERSTEP to target end-of-life SonicWall Secure Mobile Access (SMA) 100 series appliances. The campaign represents a significant escalation in attacks against network infrastructure devices, as the threat actors are successfully compromising appliances even after organizations have applied the latest security updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149604</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Confirms BGP Hijack Behind 1.1.1.1 DNS Disruption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cloudflare-confirms-bgp-hijack-behind-1-1-1-1-dns-disruption/</link>
      <description>A global outage of Cloudflare's 1.1.1.1 DNS resolver service was caused by an internal configuration error rather than an external attack. The incident affected millions of users worldwide and coincided with an unrelated BGP hijack, which complicated the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149591</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Takes Down NoName057(16)’s Global Network of Over 100 Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/europol-takes-down-noname05716s-global-network/</link>
      <description>Europol and Eurojust conducted Operation Eastwood to dismantle the NoName057(16) hacktivist collective's global infrastructure of over 100 servers worldwide. The operation resulted in two arrests, seven international arrest warrants, 24 house searches, and disruption of over 100 servers globally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149587</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Warns of Critical ISE Flaw Allowing Unauthenticated Attackers to Execute Root Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-ise-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20337; Summary: The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. It affects ISE and ISE-PIC releases 3.3 and 3.4, regardless of device configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-ise-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 05:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Cables Face Increasing Threats Amid Geopolitical Tensions and Limited Repair Capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/submarine-cables-face-increasing-threats</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This analysis highlights various vulnerabilities in the submarine cable ecosystem, including:

1. **Concentration of cables at landing stations**: The clustering of multiple submarine cables at single landing sites increases the likelihood that damage to or near a landing site will impact multiple cables.
2. **Limited repair capacity**: Repair vessels are focused on laying new cable systems, constraining their ability to respond immediately to cable faults, leading to extended repair times.
3. **Regulatory hurdles**: Complex and lengthy permitting processes for repair ships vary by national territory, prolonging repair timelines and exacerbating the impact of limited repair capacity.

These vulnerabilities can have significant consequences for global internet connectivity, highlighting the need for investments in streamlining repair processes and expanding cable ship repair capacity to mitigate potential disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/submarine-cables-face-increasing-threats</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-op confirms data of 6.5 million members stolen in cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/co-op-confirms-data-of-65-million-members-stolen-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>A massive cyberattack on UK retailer Co-op resulted in the theft of personal data for 6.5 million members. The attackers accessed and stole Windows domain's Windows NTDS.dit file, which contains password hashes for Windows accounts.

FYSA: Threat actors associated with Scattered Spider were behind the Co-op cyberattack, as well as other attacks on M&amp;S, Harrods, and MGM Resorts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/co-op-confirms-data-of-65-million-members-stolen-in-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 22:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Army soldier pleads guilty to extorting 10 tech, telecom firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-army-soldier-pleads-guilty-to-extorting-10-tech-telecom-firms/</link>
      <description>A 21-year-old former U.S. Army soldier pleaded guilty to charges of hacking and extorting at least ten telecommunications and technology companies in the country. The man, Cameron John Wagenius, used online accounts associated with the nickname “kiberphant0m” and conspired with others to defraud victim organizations by obtaining login credentials for their protected computer networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-army-soldier-pleads-guilty-to-extorting-10-tech-telecom-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google finds custom backdoor being installed on SonicWall network devices</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/google-finds-custom-backdoor-being-installed-on-sonicwall-network-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): 2024-38475; Summary: UNC6148 exploited vulnerabilities in SMA appliances, gaining local administrator credentials and valid session tokens. They may have used infostealer logs or credential marketplaces to obtain credentials. A reverse shell was installed, providing a web interface for running commands and installing Overstep. The motivations of the group and what they do after Overstep is installed are unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/google-finds-custom-backdoor-being-installed-on-sonicwall-network-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracked Apps Delivering Infostealers Identified as Leading Attack Vector in June 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cracked-apps-delivering-infostealers-identified/</link>
      <description>The article discusses infostealer malware masquerading as keygens and cracked software, which uses advanced SEO poisoning to elevate malicious distribution sites in search results. It highlights the diversity of infostealers, including variants like LummaC2, Rhadamanthys, ACRStealer, Vidar, and StealC, and notes their evolving sophistication through techniques like evasion, deception, and anti-analysis mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149538</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leverage 607 Malicious Domains to Spread APK Malware with Remote Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-leverage-607-malicious-domains/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): Janus vulnerability on Android versions 5.0 through 8.0 (None); Summary: Rogue domains were used in a large-scale phishing campaign to spread fake Telegram Messenger application files (APKs) over the course of a month, leveraging QR codes and centralized redirection for efficient malware delivery. The malicious APKs employ cleartext traffic protocols, grant broad permissions, and integrate MediaPlayer invocations and socket-based callbacks for remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149532</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Vuitton says regional data breaches tied to same cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/louis-vuitton-says-regional-data-breaches-tied-to-same-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The article reports a data breach at luxury fashion giant Louis Vuitton, which affected customers in the UK, South Korea, and Turkey. The breach is believed to be linked to the ShinyHunters extortion group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/louis-vuitton-says-regional-data-breaches-tied-to-same-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Weaponize WordPress Sites to Redirect Visitors to Malicious Domains</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-weaponize-wordpress-sites/</link>
      <description>The article describes a sophisticated malware campaign targeting WordPress websites, where threat actors embedded malicious code within core files to facilitate unauthorized redirects and SEO poisoning. The malware uses obfuscation techniques and bot-evasion tactics to evade detection, and can manipulate search engine rankings by injecting fake sitemaps and verifying with Google Search Console.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149525</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Eastwood Targets NoName057(16) in Global Crackdown</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/operation-eastwood-targets-noname05716/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability but rather discusses an international law enforcement operation called Operation Eastwood, which targeted a pro-Russian hacktivist group known as NoName057(16). The group was responsible for carrying out widespread DDoS attacks against Ukraine and other perceived enemies of Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061854</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SquidLoader Deploys Stealthy Malware with Near-Zero Detection to Evade Security Measures</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/squidloader-deploys-stealthy-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SquidLoader; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new variant of SquidLoader malware has been discovered, which achieves near-zero detection rates on platforms like VirusTotal by leveraging advanced anti-analysis, anti-sandbox, and anti-debugging mechanisms. The malware deploys Cobalt Strike Beacons for remote access and contains a multi-stage infection process with various evasion techniques, including anti-emulation tricks and API resolution via PEB walking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149514</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leverage Microsoft Teams to Spread Matanbuchus 3.0 Malware to Targeted Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-leverage-microsoft-teams-to.html</link>
      <description>Matanbuchus 3.0 is a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) that packs significant features to enhance its stealth and evade detection. It can be used as a conduit for next-stage payloads, including Cobalt Strike beacons and ransomware. The loader is often deployed using hands-on social engineering tactics, making it more targeted and coordinated than typical commodity loaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-leverage-microsoft-teams-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare says 1.1.1.1 outage not caused by attack or BGP hijack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-says-1111-outage-not-caused-by-attack-or-bgp-hijack/</link>
      <description>The article explains that the recent 1.1.1.1 Resolver service outage was caused by an internal misconfiguration at Cloudflare, not a cyberattack or BGP hijack incident. The misconfiguration occurred due to a configuration change for a future Data Localization Suite (DLS) performed on June 6, which mistakenly linked 1.1.1.1 Resolver IP prefixes to a non-production DLS service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-says-1111-outage-not-caused-by-attack-or-bgp-hijack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall SMA devices hacked with OVERSTEP rootkit tied to ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-sma-devices-hacked-with-overstep-rootkit-tied-to-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall Secure Mobile Access appliances (SMA 100 Series); CVE(s): CVE-2021-20038, CVE-2024-38475, CVE-2021-20035, CVE-2021-20039, CVE-2025-32819; Summary: The article describes a previously unseen malware called OVERSTEP that modifies the boot process of fully-patched but no longer supported SonicWall SMA appliances. The backdoor allows hackers to hide malicious components, maintain persistent access on the device, and steal sensitive credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-sma-devices-hacked-with-overstep-rootkit-tied-to-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-603: Autodesk Revit RTE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-603/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of RTE files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27152</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Fortinet FortiWeb hacks likely linked to public RCE exploits</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-fortinet-fortiweb-hacks-likely-linked-to-public-rce-exploits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-25257 affects FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized SQL code or commands via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests, which can lead to web shell infections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-fortinet-fortiweb-hacks-likely-linked-to-public-rce-exploits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol disrupts pro-Russian NoName057(16) DDoS hacktivist group</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-disrupts-pro-russian-noname05716-ddos-hacktivist-group/</link>
      <description>Operation Eastwood, an international law enforcement operation led by Europol and Eurojust, targeted the pro-Russian hacktivist group NoName057(16) responsible for DDoS attacks across Europe, Israel, and Ukraine. The operation disrupted over 100 servers hosting the group's infrastructure, resulted in two arrests, and issued seven European arrest warrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-disrupts-pro-russian-noname05716-ddos-hacktivist-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC6148 Backdoors Fully-Patched SonicWall SMA 100 Series Devices with OVERSTEP Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/unc6148-backdoors-fully-patched.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall Secure Mobile Access (SMA) 100 series; CVE(s): CVE-2021-20035, CVE-2021-20038, CVE-2021-20039, CVE-2024-38475, CVE-2025-32819; Summary: A threat activity cluster has been observed targeting fully-patched end-of-life SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances to drop a backdoor called OVERSTEP. The attackers are believed to have initially gained access through the exploitation of known security flaws or obtained administrator credentials through information-stealing logs or credential marketplaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/unc6148-backdoors-fully-patched.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITRE Launches AADAPT Framework to Secure Digital Assets</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/mitre-launches-aadapt-framework-secure-digital-assets/</link>
      <description>The MITRE organization has launched a new cybersecurity initiative called AADAPT (Adversarial Actions in Digital Asset Payment Technologies), which aims to help organizations detect and mitigate cyber threats in digital finance. The framework provides a structured approach to tackling risks in cryptocurrencies, smart contracts, decentralized applications, and blockchain systems, drawing on lessons from over 150 real-world incidents and expert sources across government, academia, and industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061842</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Vantage Flaws Enable Attackers to Gain SYSTEM-Level Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lenovo-vantage-flaws-enable-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo Vantage; CVE(s): 2025-6230, 2025-6231, 2025-6232; Summary: Multiple privilege escalation vulnerabilities in Lenovo Vantage allow unprivileged users to bypass authentication mechanisms and execute code with SYSTEM-level privileges, potentially leading to full system compromise. The flaws stem from Lenovo Vantage's modular architecture and expose JSON-based requests routed to add-ins defined in XML files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149490</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung WLAN AP Flaws Let Remote Attackers Run Commands as Root</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/samsung-wlan-ap-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung WEA453e Wireless Access Point; CVE(s): None; Summary: The WEA453e wireless access point has a critical chain of vulnerabilities that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute commands with full administrative privileges. The vulnerability chain begins with a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw and ends with local file inclusion (LFI) and command injection, allowing attackers to read sensitive files and gain root-level access without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149460</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese ‘Salt Typhoon’ Hackers Infiltrated US National Guard Network for Almost a Year</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-salt-typhoon-hackers-infiltrated/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated advanced persistent threat (APT) group, known as Salt Typhoon, has successfully penetrated a U.S. state's Army National Guard network, enabling potential exfiltration of sensitive military and law enforcement data. The intrusion leveraged lateral movement techniques across interconnected systems, highlighting vulnerabilities in hybrid federal-state infrastructures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149463</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Secure Boot Certificate Expired in June, Microsoft Issues Warning</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-secure-boot-certificate-expired-in-june/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Secure Boot certificates used by most Windows devices are scheduled to expire starting in June 2026, potentially affecting device functionality and security. If not properly updated, affected devices may encounter boot failures or security vulnerabilities, leaving systems exposed to malware attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149449</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s AI ‘Big Sleep’ Detects Critical SQLite 0-Day, Halts Ongoing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/googles-ai-big-sleep-detects-critical-sqlite-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SQLite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6965; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability was found in SQLite by Google's AI agent "Big Sleep", which allowed it to stop exploitation attempts before widespread attacks could occur. The vulnerability was detected using threat intelligence and advanced code analysis, demonstrating a proactive approach to predictive threat prevention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149441</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Golden dMSA Attack in Windows Server 2025 Enables Cross-Domain Attacks and Persistent Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-golden-dmsa-attack-in-windows.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical design flaw in Delegated Managed Service Accounts (dMSAs) allows for high-impact attacks, enabling cross-domain lateral movement and persistent access to all managed service accounts and their resources across Active Directory. Exploitation requires possession of a Key Distribution Service (KDS) root key, which is typically only available to privileged accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-golden-dmsa-attack-in-windows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Partners Hacker Group Drains Crypto Wallets Using Fake AI Tools and VPN Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dark-partners-hacker-group-drains-crypto-wallets/</link>
      <description>Dark Partners, a financially driven cybercrime organization, has been planning massive cryptocurrency theft since May 2025 using over 250 malicious domains posing as AI tools, VPN services, and software brands. The group's infrastructure facilitates data harvesting from victims across multiple countries, with a focus on cryptocurrency, blockchain, technology, financial services, and VPN sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149392</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Message Exploit Triggers Code Execution in Claude, Bypassing Protections</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gmail-message-exploit-triggers-code-execution-in-claude/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Claude Desktop; CVE(s): None; Summary: A cybersecurity researcher demonstrated a code execution attack on Claude Desktop, an AI assistant application, by leveraging the Model Context Protocol (MCP) and exploiting compositional risk. The attack did not rely on any vulnerabilities in individual MCP servers but rather the combination of untrusted input sources, excessive execution permissions, and lack of contextual guardrails between different tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149423</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Act Like Employees With Root Access—Here's How to Regain Control</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ai-agents-act-like-employees-with-root.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the importance of identity-first security in securing generative AI systems. It warns that most organizations are not securing their AI deployments properly and that every LLM access point or website is a new identity edge that can be exploited. The article emphasizes the need for phishing-resistant MFA, granular RBAC, and continuous device trust enforcement to eliminate AI access risk without hindering innovation.

FYSA: The threat surface of AI systems expands internal attack surfaces, especially if access control and identity segmentation aren't enforced at runtime. Third-party tools can be misused or accessed by unauthorized users, or corporate users on personal accounts, where governance gaps exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ai-agents-act-like-employees-with-root.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Issues Critical Update Fixing 309 Vulnerabilities Across Products</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oracle-issues-critical-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle; CVE(s): 309 (None); Summary: The Oracle July 2025 Critical Patch Update addresses 309 security vulnerabilities across its product portfolio, including Oracle Database Server, MySQL Server, WebLogic Server, Java SE, and other products. The update affects multiple version ranges, with some affecting software dating back several years. The vulnerabilities can be exploited remotely without authentication, leading to unauthorized access, data breaches, and system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149332</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers exploit a blind spot by hiding malware inside DNS records</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-exploit-a-blind-spot-by-hiding-malware-inside-dns-records/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of Domain Name System (DNS) records to host malicious PowerShell scripts. Researchers have found that threat actors are using TXT records to embed attacker-devised text into documents or files being analyzed by AI chatbots, which can be exploited through prompt injections. This technique allows attackers to manipulate the chatbot's behavior and achieve malicious objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-exploit-a-blind-spot-by-hiding-malware-inside-dns-records/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NimDoor MacOS Malware Abuses Zoom SDK Updates to Steal Keychain Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nimdoor-macos-malware-abuses-zoom-sdk-updates/</link>
      <description>SentinelOne researchers discovered NimDoor, a sophisticated MacOS malware campaign attributed to North Korean-affiliated attackers (Stardust Chollima gang) targeting the bitcoin industry, exploiting social engineering tactics to steal sensitive data. The malware uses Nim-compiled binaries and process injection techniques for stealthy operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149355</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok 4 benchmark results: Tops math, ranks second in coding</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-benchmark-results-tops-math-ranks-second-in-coding/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various AI-related topics, including the performance of Grok 4, a reasoning model, in different domains such as coding and math. It also mentions the threat actors' techniques used for cloud-fluent attacks, which are surprisingly simple despite growing sophistication. Additionally, it touches on upcoming developments in the AI space, including the potential launch of Grok 3.5 and GPT-5 models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-benchmark-results-tops-math-ranks-second-in-coding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konfety Android Malware Exploits ZIP Tricks to Masquerade as Legit Apps on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/konfety-android-malware-exploits-zip-tricks/</link>
      <description>The Konfety Android malware uses complex ZIP-level changes to avoid detection and mimic genuine apps on the Google Play Store, employing an "evil-twin" strategy, runtime decryption, and deceptive manifest declarations. It can redirect users to fraudulent websites, initiate unwanted app sideloads, and severely impact user privacy and device integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149334</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-598: Oracle VirtualBox BusLogic Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-598/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53025; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26654</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-599: Oracle VirtualBox LSILogic Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-599/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53026; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26653</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-600: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox VMSVGA Out-Of-Bounds Write Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-600/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53028; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting an out-of-bounds write local privilege escalation flaw in the VMSVGA virtual device, which can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27163</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-601: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox VMSVGA Integer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-601/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53024; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting an integer overflow in the VMSVGA virtual device. An attacker must first obtain high-privileged code execution on the target guest system to exploit this flaw, which results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27122</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-602: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox OHCI USB Controller Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-602/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53027; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting a lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object in the virtual OHCI USB controller. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system to exploit this vulnerability, which can then be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27154</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talos IR ransomware engagements and the significance of timeliness in incident response</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/talos-ir-ransomware-engagements-and-the-significance-of-timeliness-in-incident-response/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article appears to be a case study on a cybersecurity incident involving a series of malicious activities by an attacker. The analyst's analysis reveals that the attack involved multiple tools and techniques, including social engineering, malware deployment, data exfiltration, and command and control (C2) communication.

From a security perspective, several concerns are raised:

1. **Lack of robust security controls**: The article highlights the importance of implementing strong security controls to prevent unauthorized access and data breaches.
2. **Inadequate logging and monitoring**: The analyst notes that the attack was only detected due to the victim's logging and monitoring efforts. This emphasizes the need for organizations to maintain comprehensive logging and monitoring capabilities.
3. **Malware deployment**: The article highlights the importance of maintaining up-to-date antivirus software and implementing sandboxing or virtualization technologies to contain malware outbreaks.
4. **Command and control (C2) communication**: The analyst notes that the attacker used C2 servers to communicate with compromised hosts. This underscores the need for organizations to implement robust C2 detection and mitigation strategies.

In terms of specific vulnerabilities, the article does not discuss any particular software, hardware, or firmware vulnerabilities. However, it highlights the importance of keeping systems and applications up-to-date with the latest security patches and updates.

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) used by attackers and emphasizes the need for organizations to prioritize robust security controls, logging, monitoring, and incident response capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687548cf405515000149657a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Filters Defeated by Polyglot File Trick Used in Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/email-filters-defeated-by-polyglot-file/</link>
      <description>This article discusses advanced techniques used by attackers to evade email filters and successfully send phishing payloads. The techniques include the use of polyglot files, which can be interpreted as multiple file formats simultaneously, allowing malicious content to appear benign to security scanners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149288</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google fixes actively exploited sandbox escape zero day in Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-sandbox-escape-zero-day-in-chrome/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6558; Summary: The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-6558, is a high-severity issue in ANGLE and GPU that affects Google Chrome versions before 138.0.7204.157. It allows an attacker to perform a sandbox escape by using a specially crafted HTML page, potentially executing arbitrary code within the browser's GPU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-sandbox-escape-zero-day-in-chrome/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive DDoS Attack Slams Internet with 7.3 Tbps and 4.8 Billion Packets Per Second</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-ddos-attack-slams-internet/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on a massive DDoS attack mitigated by Cloudflare, peaking at 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps) and 4.8 billion packets per second (Bpps). The report highlights the increasing frequency and intensity of DDoS attacks, with a focus on HTTP and L3/4 attacks, as well as emerging threats like Teeworlds and RIPv1 floods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149276</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Konfety Malware Variant Evades Detection by Manipulating APKs and Dynamic Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-konfety-malware-variant-evades.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated variant of an Android malware called Konfety that uses the evil twin technique for ad fraud. The malware employs dynamic code loading, obfuscation, and deception to evade detection. It can redirect users to malicious websites, prompt unwanted app installs, and trigger spam-like notifications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-konfety-malware-variant-evades.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urgent: Google Releases Critical Chrome Update for CVE-2025-6558 Exploit Active in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/urgent-google-releases-critical-chrome.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6558; Summary: The high-severity vulnerability (CVSS score: 8.8) allows a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page, exploiting an incorrect validation of untrusted input in the browser's ANGLE and GPU components, allowing attackers to break out of the browser's security bubble and interact with the underlying system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/urgent-google-releases-critical-chrome.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes. Fake Recruiters. Cloned CFOs — Learn How to Stop AI-Driven Attacks in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/deepfakes-fake-recruiters-cloned-cfos.html</link>
      <description>Social engineering attacks are evolving with the use of generative AI, stolen branding assets, and deepfake tools, allowing attackers to mimic executives, hijack social channels, and create convincing fakes. Modern attacks involve long-term, multi-channel campaigns across email, LinkedIn, SMS, and support portals, targeting employees, customers, and partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/deepfakes-fake-recruiters-cloned-cfos.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command-Line Editor Vim Hit by Vulnerability Allowing File Overwrites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/command-line-editor-vim-hit-by-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vim; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53906; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files on users' systems by exploiting a path traversal issue in Vim's zip.vim plugin when opening specially crafted zip archives. Successful exploitation could lead to arbitrary code execution, compromising entire systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149326</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Ivanti and Fortinet VPN Vulnerabilities in Attacks on Japanese Companies</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-ivanti-and-fortinet-vpn-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a surge in cyber espionage campaigns against Japanese companies, primarily targeting North Korean threat actors. These campaigns aim to exfiltrate sensitive data, including manufacturing blueprints and personal information, using various tactics such as spear phishing, malware, and social engineering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149267</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curl 8.15.0 Officially Released: 233 Bugs Fixed in Major Update</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/curl-8-15-0-officially-released/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of Curl 8.15.0, which addresses over 230 bugs and streamlines its internal architecture. The update removes support for Apple's Secure Transport API and BearSSL library to reduce maintenance overhead and promote adoption of widely tested TLS providers like OpenSSL. The article highlights the community-driven nature of the project, with many newcomers contributing to the codebase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149308</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Take Down ‘Diskstation’ Ransomware Gang Targeting Synology NAS Globally</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/authorities-take-down-diskstation-ransomware-gang/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Synology NAS systems; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "Diskstation" ransomware operation targeted Synology Network Attached Storage (NAS) systems worldwide, exploiting vulnerabilities to encrypt entire organizational datasets. The attackers specifically targeted these systems for data storage and backup solutions, allowing them to maximize their leverage over victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149301</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abacus Dark Web Market Suspected of Exit Scam with Held Bitcoin Funds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/abacus-dark-web-market-suspected-of-exit-scam/</link>
      <description>The largest Bitcoin-enabled Western darknet marketplace, Abacus Market, has gone offline amid suspicions of an exit scam that may have cost users millions of dollars in held cryptocurrency funds. The market's administrators likely shut down operations and disappeared with users' deposits, leaving behind a trail of frozen funds and delayed transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google AI "Big Sleep" Stops Exploitation of Critical SQLite Vulnerability Before Hackers Act</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ai-big-sleep-stops-exploitation.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SQLite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6965; Summary: The vulnerability is a memory corruption flaw affecting all versions prior to 3.50.2, which could allow an attacker to cause an integer overflow resulting in read off the end of an array.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ai-big-sleep-stops-exploitation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former U.S. Army Member Pleads Guilty in Telecom Hacking Case</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/former-u-s-army-member-pleads-guilty/</link>
      <description>A 21-year-old former U.S. Army soldier has pleaded guilty to participating in a sophisticated cybercrime operation that targeted telecommunications companies through hacking, data theft, and extortion schemes. The conspiracy involved at least 10 victim organizations, using specialized hacking tools and Telegram group chats to coordinate activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149262</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 06:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vulnerabilities Leave Windows Apps Vulnerable to Path Traversal and HashDoS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/node-js-vulnerabilities-leave-windows-apps-vulnerable/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Node.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27210, CVE-2025-27209; Summary: Two high-severity vulnerabilities affecting Windows applications, including denial-of-service attacks. The first vulnerability allows attackers to bypass path traversal protection mechanisms, while the second introduces a HashDoS vulnerability through changes in the V8 JavaScript engine's string hashing implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149257</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware ESXi and Workstation Vulnerabilities Allow Host-Level Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-esxi-and-workstation-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41236, CVE-2025-41237, CVE-2025-41238, CVE-2025-41239; Summary: Four critical vulnerabilities in VMware's virtualization suite allow attackers to escape virtual machines and execute code directly on host systems. The flaws affect ESXi, Workstation, Fusion, and VMware Tools across enterprise and desktop environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149253</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's image model gets built-in style feature on ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-image-model-gets-built-in-style-feature-on-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>The article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be focused on updates and features of OpenAI's image generation model, ChatGPT, including the introduction of a "Style" feature that allows users to create images in different styles.

FYSA: The article mentions threat actors using simple techniques for cloud attacks and notes that attackers are leveraging ChatGPT to write malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-image-model-gets-built-in-style-feature-on-chatgpt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abacus dark web drug market goes offline in suspected exit scam</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/abacus-dark-web-drug-market-goes-offline-in-suspected-exit-scam/</link>
      <description>Abacus Market, the largest Western darknet marketplace supporting Bitcoin payments, has shut down its public infrastructure, suspected to be an exit scam or covert law enforcement operation. The market reportedly enabled transactions of nearly $100 million worth of Bitcoin and possibly up to $300 million when including Monero transactions. User deposits dropped significantly after withdrawal delays, leading many to believe it was an exit scam rather than a law enforcement takedown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/abacus-dark-web-drug-market-goes-offline-in-suspected-exit-scam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows KB5064489 emergency update fixes Azure VM launch issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-kb5064489-emergency-update-fixes-azure-vm-launch-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): None; Summary: The bug prevented Azure virtual machines from launching when Trusted Launch setting was disabled and Virtualization-Based Security (VBS) was enabled, affecting Windows Server 2025 and Windows 11 24H2. The issue was caused by a secure kernel initialization problem and has been fixed with the KB5064489 out-of-band update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-kb5064489-emergency-update-fixes-azure-vm-launch-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean XORIndex malware hidden in 67 malicious npm packages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-xorindex-malware-hidden-in-67-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Node Package Manager (npm); CVE(s): None; Summary: North Korean threat actors uploaded 67 malicious packages to npm, which collectively received over 17,000 downloads. The packages were designed to deliver a new malware loader called XORIndex, which can collect host and network data, profile victims, and download additional payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korean-xorindex-malware-hidden-in-67-malicious-npm-packages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police disrupt “Diskstation” ransomware gang attacking NAS devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-disrupt-diskstation-ransomware-gang-attacking-nas-devices/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a law enforcement operation codenamed 'Operation Elicius' that dismantled a Romanian ransomware gang known as 'Diskstation', which targeted Synology Network-Attached Storage (NAS) devices. The gang encrypted the systems of several companies, paralyzing their businesses, and demanded ransom payments ranging from $10,000 to hundreds of thousands of dollars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/police-disrupt-diskstation-ransomware-gang-attacking-nas-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper-Volumetric DDoS Attacks Reach Record 7.3 Tbps, Targeting Key Global Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hyper-volumetric-ddos-attacks-reach.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a significant increase in distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks mitigated by Cloudflare in the second quarter of 2025. The article highlights the rise of hyper-volumetric DDoS attacks, which peaked at 7.3 terabits per second and 4.8 billion packets per second within a span of 45 seconds. It also discusses the increasing use of targeted probes by attackers to find weak spots and slip past defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hyper-volumetric-ddos-attacks-reach.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attack on Albemarle County Exposes Residents’ Personal Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-attack-on-albemarle-county/</link>
      <description>Albemarle County, Virginia, fell victim to a sophisticated ransomware attack despite having robust defenses in place, including endpoint detection and response systems, multi-factor authentication, and regular vulnerability patching. The attack exploited on-premises servers, potentially exposing sensitive personally identifiable information (PII) of local government and public school employees, as well as county residents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149147</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly Emerged GLOBAL GROUP RaaS Expands Operations with AI-Driven Negotiation Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/newly-emerged-global-group-raas-expands.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses a new ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation called GLOBAL GROUP that has targeted various sectors in Australia, Brazil, Europe, and the United States. The RaaS platform is designed to facilitate initial access brokers to deploy the ransomware by weaponizing access to vulnerable edge appliances from Cisco, Fortinet, and Palo Alto Networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/newly-emerged-global-group-raas-expands.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Explains How Security Copilot in Intune and Entra Supports Security and IT Teams</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-explains-how-security-copilot/</link>
      <description>None (The article is not about a vulnerability or cybersecurity-relevant content, but rather discusses Microsoft's Security Copilot tool and its features for improving security and IT operations.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149123</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal IT Contractor to Pay $14.75M for False Cybersecurity Services Claims</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/federal-it-contractor-to-pay-14-75m/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a settlement between Hill ASC Inc. and the U.S. Department of Justice regarding allegations of violating the False Claims Act through improper billing practices under a General Services Administration (GSA) Multiple Award Schedule (MAS) contract. The alleged violations include fraudulent claims for IT personnel, unauthorized billing for cybersecurity services, and unapproved fees on government invoices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149095</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DShield Honeypot Scanning Hits Record High with Over 1 Million Logs in a Single Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dshield-honeypot-scanning-hits-record-high/</link>
      <description>The article reports an unusual surge in cyber reconnaissance activity detected by DShield honeypots, with web logs exceeding 1 GB daily and peaking at nearly 58 GB. The increase is attributed to automated scanning from overlapping subnets targeting specific URL paths, potentially probing for vulnerabilities or gathering intelligence for future exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149077</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Threat Actors Target U.S. Critical Infrastructure, Including Water Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-threat-actors-target-u-s-critical-infrastructure/</link>
      <description>Intelligence Group 13, an elite unit within the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC), has been conducting asymmetric cyber operations in response to U.S. attacks on Iranian nuclear sites. The group uses advanced persistent threat (APT) techniques, including phishing-driven credential theft, open-source intelligence harvesting, and custom malware deployment for reconnaissance and sabotage. Its operations extend beyond technical compromise, incorporating psychological elements through propaganda fronts like CyberAveng3rs, which disseminates defacement screenshots, operational leaks, and taunting messages via Telegram and Instagram channels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149058</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kafbat UI Vulnerabilities Allow Arbitrary Code Execution via JMX Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kafbat-ui-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kafbat UI; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49127; Summary: The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code by exploiting unsafe deserialization in Kafbat UI's metrics collection system. Attackers can specify malicious JMX servers that return crafted serialized objects, enabling Java deserialization gadget chains and complete system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149227</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octalyn Stealer Harvests VPN Configs, Passwords, and Cookies in Organized Folder Structure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/octalyn-stealer-harvests-vpn-configs-passwords-and-cookies/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Octalyn Forensic Toolkit; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Octalyn Forensic Toolkit is a credential stealer that poses as a research tool for red teaming and digital forensics. It can extract sensitive data including browser passwords, cookies, autofill information, Discord and Telegram tokens, VPN configurations, gaming account details, and cryptocurrency wallet artifacts. The toolkit's payload establishes persistence via Windows Startup folder entries and registry modifications, and can exfiltrate stolen data over TLS-secured connections to api.telegram.org.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149044</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android malware Konfety uses malformed APKs to evade detection</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-konfety-uses-malformed-apks-to-evade-detection/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Konfety; CVE(s): None; Summary: The latest variant of the Konfety Android malware uses a malformed ZIP structure, obfuscation methods, and dynamic code loading to evade analysis and detection. It poses as a legitimate app, redirects users to malicious sites, pushes unwanted app installs, and steals information such as installed apps, network configuration, and system details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-malware-konfety-uses-malformed-apks-to-evade-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL GROUP RaaS Adds AI-Powered Negotiation Feature for Ransom Demands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/global-group-raas-adds-ai-powered-negotiation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) operation called GLOBAL GROUP that has deployed an AI-driven negotiation tool to pressure victims into paying ransoms. The operation uses Initial Access Brokers (IABs) to sell compromised VPN appliances and webshells, and its affiliates can deploy customized ransomware payloads that take advantage of chaos and speed to maximize damage before traditional endpoint defenses can react.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149208</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Exploit 67 Malicious npm Packages to Spread XORIndex Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-exploit-67-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Socket Threat Research Team discovered a software supply chain attack using the XORIndex malware loader, which has not been previously reported, attributed to North Korean state-backed actors. The attackers infiltrated the npm registry with 67 malicious packages, amassing over 17,000 downloads collectively, targeting developers, job seekers, and cryptocurrency holders by exfiltrating sensitive credentials and wallet data through a chain of malware stages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149020</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaitTrap Reveals Global Web of 17,000+ Fraud-Promoting Fake News Sites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/baittrap-reveals-global-web/</link>
      <description>A network of over 17,000 "Baiting News Sites" (BNS) has been discovered by cybersecurity firm CTM360, which are designed to disseminate investment fraud globally. These sites masquerade as authoritative news entities and use advanced social engineering tactics to target unsuspecting users with false information about lucrative investment opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149065</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AsyncRAT Forks Discovered Featuring Screamer Tool and USB Malware Spreader</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-asyncrat-forks-discovered/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AsyncRAT; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes two new variants of the AsyncRAT remote access trojan (RAT) that introduce a psychological warfare component and enhanced propagation mechanisms. The "Screamer" plugin manipulates Windows audio APIs to disorient victims, while the USB malware spreader component transforms AsyncRAT into a self-replicating worm capable of bridging air-gapped networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149190</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Energy Asset Suite</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-196-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hitachi Energy Equipment, including Asset Suite AnyWhere for Inventory (AWI) Android mobile app and Asset Suite 9 series; CVE(s): CVE-2019-9262, CVE-2019-9429, CVE-2019-9256, CVE-2019-9290, CVE-2025-1484, CVE-2025-2500; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities in Hitachi Energy's Asset Suite product allow for unauthorized access, remote code execution, and privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23623</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITEON IC48A and IC80A EV Chargers</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-196-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LITEONE IC48A and IC80A; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7357; Summary: Successful exploitation of the plaintext storage of a password vulnerability in Liteon EV chargers could allow an attacker to access sensitive information, with potential impacts on commercial facilities, energy, and transportation systems worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23625</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABB RMC-100</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-196-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ABB RMC-100; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6071, CVE-2025-6072, CVE-2025-6073, CVE-2025-6074; Summary: The ABB RMC-100 has several vulnerabilities that allow an attacker to gain unauthenticated access to MQTT configuration data, cause a denial-of-service condition on the MQTT configuration web server (REST interface), or decrypt encrypted MQTT broker credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23624</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Six Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/15/cisa-releases-six-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released six Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 15, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories cover various products from Hitachi Energy, ABB, LITEON, Schneider Electric, and others. Users and administrators are encouraged to review the advisories for technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23626</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktivists Launch Attacks on ICS Systems to Exfiltrate Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacktivists-launch-attacks-on-ics-systems/</link>
      <description>The article highlights the increasing intensity of hacktivist attacks targeting Industrial Control Systems (ICS), with a focus on Operational Technology (OT) environments, Supervisory Control and Data Acquisition (SCADA) systems, and Human-Machine Interfaces (HMIs).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148989</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's ChatGPT-powered browser is codenamed 'Aura'</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-chatgpt-powered-browser-is-codenamed-aura/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: While cloud attacks may be growing more sophisticated, attackers still succeed with surprisingly simple techniques. This report reveals 8 key techniques used by cloud-fluent threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-chatgpt-powered-browser-is-codenamed-aura/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Threat Grows as Attackers Move Into VMware and Linux</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attackers-move-into-vmware-and-linux/</link>
      <description>The article highlights the increasing trend of ransomware attacks targeting Linux environments, which were previously considered secure due to their reliability and inherent security. Threat actors are now engineering sophisticated Linux-specific ransomware variants, exploiting ubiquity in critical applications, APIs, DevOps pipelines, and virtualized infrastructures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148962</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 Hackers Arrested in Massive Tax Fraud Scheme, Authorities Confirm</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/14-hackers-arrested-in-massive-tax-fraud-scheme/</link>
      <description>Authorities have arrested 14 individuals for a sophisticated tax fraud scheme that exploited stolen personal data to submit fraudulent claims worth over £1 million. The operation involved international cooperation between UK and Romanian law enforcement agencies, demonstrating the growing collaboration in combating cross-border cybercrime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149174</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State-Backed HazyBeacon Malware Uses AWS Lambda to Steal Data from SE Asian Governments</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/state-backed-hazybeacon-malware-uses.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a previously undocumented Windows backdoor called HazyBeacon, which targets government agencies in Southeast Asia. The malware uses DLL side-loading techniques to deploy it on compromised hosts and establishes communication with an attacker-controlled URL to execute arbitrary commands and download additional payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/state-backed-hazybeacon-malware-uses.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaRecipe Tool with 2.3M Downloads Found Vulnerable to Full Server Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/larecipe-tool-with-2-3m-downloads-found-vulnerable-to-full-server-takeover/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: torch/larecipe; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53833; Summary: A critical Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-53833, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability affects all versions prior to 2.8.1 and requires no authentication or user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149163</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Agentic AI: How to Protect the Invisible Identity Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/securing-agentic-ai-how-to-protect.html</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the security implications of AI agents in cloud environments. It highlights the need for visibility into non-human identities (NHIs) and emphasizes the importance of applying least privilege and automation to ensure secure use of AI agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/securing-agentic-ai-how-to-protect.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Exploit Zoom Invites in Attacks on Crypto Companies</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/north-korean-hackers-exploit-zoom-invites-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article describes an ongoing malware campaign orchestrated by North Korean threat actors targeting individuals and organizations within the Web3, cryptocurrency, and blockchain industries. The malware uses spear-phishing tactics, fake job opportunities, and social engineering to deploy a multi-stage attack chain that compromises macOS systems and exfiltrates sensitive data, including cryptocurrency wallet credentials and personal information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148970</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsyncRAT's Open-Source Code Sparks Surge in Dangerous Malware Variants Across the Globe</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/asyncrats-open-source-code-sparks-surge.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AsyncRAT; CVE(s): None; Summary: AsyncRAT is a widely used remote access trojan that has evolved over the years, with its open-source nature allowing it to be modified and distributed by threat actors. It can capture screenshots, log keystrokes, steal credentials, and allow attackers to commandeer infected systems stealthily. The malware has spawned various variants, including DCRat, Venom RAT, and others, which have added new features and evasion techniques.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/asyncrats-open-source-code-sparks-surge.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-592: Autodesk Revit RVT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-592/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by parsing out-of-bounds write RVT files, requiring user interaction. The specific flaw exists within the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in a write past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26923</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-593: Autodesk Revit RVT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-593/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by parsing out-of-bounds read remote code execution. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26925</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-594: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-594/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by parsing out-of-bounds read RFA files. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26963</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-595: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-595/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by exploiting an out-of-bounds read in the parsing of RFA files. User interaction is required, and the issue results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27098</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-596: Autodesk Revit RTE File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-596/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5040; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit, requiring user interaction to exploit. The flaw exists in the parsing of RTE files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26917</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-597: Autodesk Revit RFA File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-597/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit by exploiting memory corruption in the parsing of RFA files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26922</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 10:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Citizen Sentenced for Islamophobic WiFi Hack at UK Train Stations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/british-citizen-sentenced-for-islamophobic-wifi-hack/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a 37-year-old individual, John Andreas Wik, who was sentenced to 24 months in prison, suspended for two years, for orchestrating an Islamophobic hack of free WiFi landing pages at multiple train stations across Britain. The hack caused distress and fear among commuters, highlighting the misuse of digital infrastructure to spread hateful content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149085</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 09:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITRE Launches AADAPT Framework to Counter Real-World Attacks on Digital Asset Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/mitre-launches-aadapt-framework/</link>
      <description>The MITRE Corporation has released its AADAPT framework, a comprehensive knowledge base for understanding and countering sophisticated attacks targeting digital asset management systems, cryptocurrency exchanges, and blockchain infrastructure. The framework organizes threat intelligence into a twelve-tactic matrix covering the attack lifecycle, including techniques such as Channel Wormholing, Quantum Efficient Factorization, Chain Reorganization attacks, and Partial Payments Attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149075</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 09:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache Tomcat Coyote Flaw Allows Attackers to Launch DoS Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apache-tomcat-coyote-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache Tomcat; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Tomcat Coyote module contains a vulnerability that allows malicious actors to orchestrate denial-of-service (DoS) attacks by manipulating stream concurrency limits in HTTP/2 protocol handling. This uncontrolled resource consumption issue can exhaust server threads, memory, or CPU resources, rendering the server unresponsive to legitimate requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148956</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCC Advises Immediate Windows 11 Upgrade to Strengthen Cyberattack Defenses</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ncc-advises-immediate-windows-11-upgrade/</link>
      <description>The National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) has released recommended configuration packs for Microsoft Windows operating systems to improve security settings, warning that the end-of-life (EOL) of Windows 10 is imminent on October 14, 2025. The article highlights the risks of unpatched vulnerabilities and emphasizes the importance of transitioning to Windows 11, which offers enhanced security features such as Trusted Platform Module (TPM) 2.0, Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI), and Secure Boot capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148948</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Clone CNN, BBC, and CNBC Sites to Lure Victims into Investment Fraud</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-clone-cnn-bbc-and-cnbc-sites/</link>
      <description>A sprawling cybercrime syndicate has been uncovered, orchestrating a large-scale phishing and investment fraud campaign by cloning legitimate news outlets. The operation uses domain spoofing, typosquatting, and social engineering tactics to target users in the United States and other countries, with over 17,000 baiting websites created across 50 countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148933</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Organizations Targeted via AWS Lambda URL Endpoint Exploits</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/government-organizations-targeted/</link>
      <description>The CL-STA-1020 threat cluster targets government agencies in Southeast Asia with a previously undocumented Windows backdoor, HazyBeacon, which exploits AWS Lambda URLs to establish a stealthy command-and-control (C2) infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148939</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Released for High-Severity Git CLI Vulnerability Allowing Arbitrary File Writes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poc-released-for-high-severity-git-cli-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Git; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48384; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Git's command-line interface allows arbitrary file writes and remote code execution on Linux and macOS systems. The vulnerability stems from a mismatch in Git's configuration parser behavior when processing control characters, enabling attackers to write malicious Git Hook scripts and achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149043</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBI Uncovers Noida Tech Support Scam Targeting Victims in UK and Australia</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cbi-uncovers-noida-tech-support-scam/</link>
      <description>The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) has taken down a sophisticated global cybercrime network that targeted people in Australia and the United Kingdom with tech support frauds. The syndicate used social engineering tactics, VoIP systems, proxy servers, and anonymized networks to evade detection. The CBI's operation, called Chakra-V, highlights the evolving landscape of cyber-enabled fraud and emphasizes the importance of international cooperation in combating cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148902</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageMagick Vulnerability Enables RCE via Malicious File Name Patterns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/imagemagick-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ImageMagick; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53101; Summary: A critical remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in ImageMagick's image processing library allows attackers to bypass stack buffer underwrite through carefully crafted filename templates. The flaw affects versions before 7.1.1-47 and 6.9.13-25, and has been addressed in versions 7.1.2-0 and 6.9.13-26.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149039</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean Hackers Flood npm Registry with XORIndex Malware in Ongoing Attack Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-flood-npm-registry.html</link>
      <description>The North Korean threat actors linked to the Contagious Interview campaign have been publishing malicious packages on the npm registry, using software supply chain attacks to target developers. The packages, which include a previously undocumented malware loader codenamed XORIndex, have attracted over 17,000 downloads and incorporate known JavaScript loaders and stealers called BeaverTail, which is used to extract data from web browsers and cryptocurrency wallets, as well as deploy a Python backdoor referred to as InvisibleFerret.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-flood-npm-registry.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Bull-Themed Phishing Attacks Target Job Seekers’ Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/red-bull-themed-phishing-attacks/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a phishing campaign targeting job seekers with spoofed Red Bull recruitment emails. The attackers leverage legitimate email services, transient VPS infrastructure, and brand impersonation to deliver malicious payloads that slip past SPF, DKIM, and DMARC checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148911</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 06:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE Denizen Marko Elez Leaked API Key for xAI</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/doge-denizen-marko-elez-leaked-api-key-for-xai/</link>
      <description>A DOGE employee, Marko Elez, inadvertently published a private API key for xAI's large language models on GitHub, allowing access to at least 52 LLMs. The exposed key has not been revoked and is still functional, raising concerns about operational security and the handling of sensitive government information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 01:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK launches vulnerability research program for external experts</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-launches-vulnerability-research-program-for-external-experts/</link>
      <description>The UK's National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) has launched a new Vulnerability Research Initiative (VRI) to strengthen relations with external cybersecurity experts, aiming to improve the discovery and sharing of critical insights with the community. This initiative will involve partnering with skilled external vulnerability researchers to identify flaws in specific products, assess mitigations, and disclose findings through the 'Equities Process' procedure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-launches-vulnerability-research-program-for-external-experts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 20:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interlock ransomware adopts FileFix method to deliver malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interlock-ransomware-adopts-filefix-method-to-deliver-malware/</link>
      <description>The Interlock ransomware gang has adopted a new technique called "FileFix" to drop a remote access trojan (RAT) on targeted systems. FileFix is a social engineering attack that weaponizes trusted Windows UI elements to trick users into executing malicious PowerShell or JavaScript code without displaying any security warnings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/interlock-ransomware-adopts-filefix-method-to-deliver-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia chips become the first GPUs to fall to Rowhammer bit-flip attacks</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/nvidia-chips-become-the-first-gpus-to-fall-to-rowhammer-bit-flip-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA GPUs (A6000 and other GDDR6-based GPUs in Nvidia’s Ampere generation); CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability known as GPUhammer, which exploits Rowhammer bit flips to flip bits inside discrete GPUs and target GDDR6 GPU memory modules. The vulnerability is mitigated by ECC, but using ECC can also cause miscorrections and silent data corruption if three or more bit flips occur in a code word.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/nvidia-chips-become-the-first-gpus-to-fall-to-rowhammer-bit-flip-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unusual Suspect: Git Repos</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/the-unusual-suspect-git-repos.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Exposed Git repositories are a critical risk for most enterprises, allowing attackers to silently create shadow access into core systems. This is not just about poor hygiene, but a systemic and growing supply chain risk. Attackers can weaponize exposed code repositories by harvesting secrets, pivoting to compromised infrastructure, and exploiting internal systems.

FYSA: The threat landscape surrounding Git repositories is expanding rapidly due to the growing complexity of DevOps practices, widespread reliance on public version control platforms like GitHub, and human error. Attackers can use exposed credentials and secrets to gain initial access into cloud environments, databases, SaaS platforms, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/the-unusual-suspect-git-repos.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PHP-Based Interlock RAT Variant Uses FileFix Delivery Mechanism to Target Multiple Industries</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-php-based-interlock-rat-variant.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new PHP variant of the Interlock remote access trojan (RAT) used by the Interlock ransomware group. The campaign involves compromised websites injecting JavaScript code that redirects users to fake CAPTCHA verification pages, leading to the deployment of NodeSnake or PHP variants of the RAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-php-based-interlock-rat-variant.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigabyte motherboards vulnerable to UEFI malware bypassing Secure Boot</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gigabyte-motherboards-vulnerable-to-uefi-malware-bypassing-secure-boot/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Gigabyte motherboard models; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7029, CVE-2025-7028, CVE-2025-7027, CVE-2025-7026; Summary: Dozens of Gigabyte motherboard models run on UEFI firmware vulnerable to security issues that allow planting bootkit malware that is invisible to the operating system and can survive reinstalls. The vulnerabilities could allow attackers with local or remote admin permissions to execute arbitrary code in System Management Mode (SMM), an environment isolated from the operating system and with more privileges on the machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/gigabyte-motherboards-vulnerable-to-uefi-malware-bypassing-secure-boot/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: APT36</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-apt36/</link>
      <description>APT36 is a Pakistan-linked state-sponsored cyber-espionage group active since at least 2013. The group targets Indian government bodies, defense contractors, armed forces, diplomatic missions, and research institutions, using phishing, remote-access trojans, and deceptive infrastructure to conduct long-term intelligence-gathering operations. Despite lacking sophistication, APT36 is highly persistent and adaptive, leveraging new platforms and cloud services, and malvertising campaigns to remain effective across South Asia's geopolitical threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061822</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigabyte UEFI Firmware Vulnerability Allows Code Execution in SMM Privileged Mode</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gigabyte-uefi-firmware-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Gigabyte motherboard; CVE(s): CVE-2023-XXXX (none listed); Summary: The firmware of multiple Gigabyte motherboard models contains vulnerabilities that allow attackers to execute arbitrary code in System Management Mode (SMM), enabling persistent malware installation, bootkit persistence, and system control even after OS reinstallation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148929</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Scattered Spider Arrests, Car Exploits, macOS Malware, Fortinet RCE and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-scattered-spider-arrests.html</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a comprehensive cybersecurity news roundup, covering various topics and threats in the industry. It does not seem to discuss specific vulnerabilities in software, hardware, or firmware products. Instead, it covers issues such as botnets, ransomware groups, API client security risks, and other cybersecurity-related matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-scattered-spider-arrests.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious VSCode extension in Cursor IDE led to $500K crypto theft</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-vscode-extension-in-cursor-ide-led-to-500k-crypto-theft/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Open VSX, Visual Studio Code; CVE(s): None; Summary: A fake extension named "Solidity Language" was published on Open VSX, claiming to be a syntax highlighting tool for Ethereum smart contracts. In reality, it executed PowerShell scripts and installed remote access tools (Quasar RAT) and infostealers (PureLogs stealer). The extension was downloaded 54,000 times before being removed and inflated its install count by publishing an almost identical version under the name "solidity", which had nearly two million installs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/malicious-vscode-extension-in-cursor-ide-led-to-500k-crypto-theft/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/14/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wing FTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47812; Summary: A vulnerability in Wing FTP Server allows for improper neutralization of null bytes or NUL characters, making it a frequent attack vector for malicious cyber actors. This poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and requires timely remediation to protect against active threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23621</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Explains How to Find and Stop Processes Blocking Files in Windows</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-explains-how-to-find-and-stop-processes-blocking-files/</link>
      <description>This article provides guidance from Microsoft on resolving the "The process cannot access the file because it is being used by another process" error message in Windows. The solutions include using built-in tools like Resource Monitor, Process Explorer, as well as command-line utilities like openfiles and Handle. These options cater to users of all skill levels, providing both graphical and command-line interfaces for resolving common system issues independently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148922</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMart Breach, Naver Leak, qTox Exploit, and Credit Card Sales Detected on Dark Web</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/bitmart-breach-naver-leak-qtox-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: qTox; CVE(s): None; Summary: A 0-day exploit targeting qTox's secure messaging platform has been advertised for sale on a dark web forum, allowing Remote Code Execution (RCE), privilege escalation, API key theft, and manipulation of wallet addresses. The exploit is being sold for 10 BTC with video proof of functionality.

FYSA: Threat actors remain highly active across dark web forums, with multiple alarming developments this week including the alleged breach of BitMart's backend infrastructure, a claimed database leak affecting Naver Corporation, and the sale of Canadian credit card data and a dataset containing over 54,000 card records from the U.S. and U.K.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061809</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Forensic Method Reveals Hidden Traces of RDP Exploits by Hackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-forensic-method-reveals-hidden-traces-of-rdp-exploits/</link>
      <description>The article discusses advanced techniques for tracking attackers who use Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) to move laterally through compromised networks. It highlights the ability to analyze RDP's bitmap caching mechanism to reveal forensic evidence of an attacker's activities, including their screen activity and copied passwords and sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148898</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized Games: Threat Actors Target Gen Z Gamers Through Popular Titles</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-games-threat-actors-target-gen-z-gamers/</link>
      <description>Sophisticated threat actor activities targeting the digitally native Gen Z population have been discovered by Kaspersky security researchers. Threat actors are exploiting popular games, streaming services, and anime to disseminate malware and harvest sensitive data through phishing schemes and social engineering tactics. Additionally, compromised accounts from these platforms are being repurposed for further phishing propagation or sold on underground markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148879</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Weaponize Compiled HTML Help to Deliver Malicious Payload</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-weaponize-compiled-html-help/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Compiled HTML Help (CHM) files; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors have exploited CHM files to distribute malware by disguising the file as a bank transfer receipt from Polish bank PKO. The file contains obfuscated JavaScript, an ActiveX control, and a C++ downloader that fetches a payload from a malicious domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148850</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Clouds: Attackers Targeting Governments in Southeast Asia Implement Novel Covert C2 Communication</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/windows-backdoor-for-novel-c2-communication/</link>
      <description>A novel cluster of suspicious activity, tracked as CL-STA-1020, has been targeting governmental entities in Southeast Asia. The threat actors behind this campaign have developed a previously undocumented Windows backdoor, HazyBeacon, which leverages AWS Lambda URLs as command and control (C2) infrastructure to hide in plain sight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=146273</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Vuitton Suffers Data Breach—Customer Information Stolen</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/louis-vuitton-suffers-data-breach/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a cyber-attack targeting Louis Vuitton's UK operations, resulting in unauthorized access to customer data. This incident is part of a broader trend of retail breaches affecting major brands, including Marks &amp; Spencer, the Co-op, and Harrods. Four arrests were made in connection with these attacks, highlighting the growing threat posed by cyber-criminals to retail operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148882</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RenderShock 0-Click Exploit Executes Payloads Silently via Background Process</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/rendershock-0-click-exploit/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a new class of cyberattack called RenderShock that can compromise enterprise systems without requiring user interaction. It exploits passive execution surfaces such as file preview panes, document indexing services, antivirus scanners, and cloud synchronization tools that automatically process files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148870</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats Actors Use Sophisticated Hacking Tools to Destroy Organizations Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threats-actors-use-sophisticated-hacking-tools/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: This article discusses the use of sophisticated cyber weapons by threat actors to breach and destroy vital infrastructure. It highlights various attacks, including Stuxnet, NotPetya, and others, that demonstrate the evolving nature of cyber warfare, its potential for widespread harm, and the need for proactive measures to mitigate risks.

(Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, only general descriptions of various cyber attacks and their characteristics.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148842</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KongTuke Campaign Deploys Modified Interlock RAT Using FileFix Method Against Windows Environments</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kongtuke-campaign-deploys-modified-interlock-rat/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a PHP-based remote access trojan (RAT) variant of the Interlock ransomware group's remote access trojan (RAT), which exploits compromised websites to deliver malicious payloads. The RAT demonstrates advanced execution techniques, including automated discovery and reconnaissance capabilities, and supports versatile execution capabilities such as downloading and running EXE or DLL files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148834</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBI Shuts Down £390K U.K. Tech Support Scam, Arrests Key Operatives in Noida Call Center</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cbi-shuts-down-390k-uk-tech-support.html</link>
      <description>A transnational cybercrime syndicate, which targeted citizens of Australia and the United Kingdom with tech support scams, has been dismantled by the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) as part of Operation Chakra V. The syndicate, which masqueraded as technical support staff of reputed multinational companies like Microsoft, is estimated to have led to losses worth over £390,000 in the UK alone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cbi-shuts-down-390k-uk-tech-support.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok-4 Jailbroken Using Echo Chamber and Crescendo Exploit Combo</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/grok-4-jailbroken/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grok-4 (AI language model); CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers successfully demonstrated a jailbreak attack against Grok-4 by combining the Echo Chamber and Crescendo exploit techniques. The attack bypasses safety mechanisms by manipulating the AI model's conversational context, achieving a 67% success rate in extracting harmful content prompts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148826</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eSIM Vulnerability in Kigen's eUICC Cards Exposes Billions of IoT Devices to Malicious Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/esim-vulnerability-in-kigens-euicc.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Kigen eUICC card; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Kigen eUICC card has a vulnerability that allows an attacker to install non-verified, potentially malicious applets. Successful exploitation requires physical access to the target chip and publicly known keys. This could enable the extraction of the identity certificate, download arbitrary profiles from MNOs in cleartext, access MNO secrets, and tamper with profiles without being flagged by MNO.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/esim-vulnerability-in-kigens-euicc.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinRAR 0‑Day Exploit Listed for $80K on Dark Web Forum</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/winrar-0%e2%80%91day-exploit-listed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WinRAR; CVE(s): None; Summary: A zero-day exploit targeting WinRAR has been discovered, affecting both latest and earlier versions of the software. The remote code execution vulnerability enables attackers to execute arbitrary code on target systems through specially crafted archive files, making it a significant concern for millions of users worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148821</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 05:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5062554 update breaks emoji panel search feature</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5062554-update-breaks-emoji-panel-search-feature/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The search feature for the Windows 10 emoji panel is broken after installing the KB5062554 cumulative update, making it impossible to look up emojis by name or keyword.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5062554-update-breaks-emoji-panel-search-feature/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Gemini flaw hijacks email summaries for phishing</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-gemini-flaw-hijacks-email-summaries-for-phishing/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Gemini for Workspace; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to generate email summaries that appear legitimate but include malicious instructions or warnings directing users to phishing sites without using attachments or direct links. Attackers can hide the malicious instruction in the body text at the end of the message using HTML and CSS, which will not be rendered in Gmail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-gemini-flaw-hijacks-email-summaries-for-phishing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet FortiWeb Fabric Connector Flaw Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortinet-fortiweb-fabric-connector-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb Fabric Connector; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A severe pre-authentication SQL injection vulnerability in FortiWeb's Fabric Connector allows unauthenticated attackers to execute unauthorized SQL commands and potentially achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability affects multiple versions of FortiWeb, including 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, with patches available in newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148812</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 10:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPC Investigates TikTok Over Transfer of EU User Data to China</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dpc-investigates-tiktok/</link>
      <description>The Data Protection Commission (DPC) has launched an inquiry into TikTok Technology Limited regarding the transfer and storage of European Economic Area (EEA) users' personal data to servers in China, citing discrepancies in previous submissions and concerns about accountability and transparency under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148712</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMmander: Network-Based Tool for COM and RPC Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/network-based-tool-for-com-and-rpc-exploitation/</link>
      <description>This article introduces COMmander, a lightweight, C#-based utility designed to monitor Remote Procedure Call (RPC) and Component Object Model (COM) activities at a granular level. It captures low-level events from the Microsoft-Windows-RPC ETW provider, empowering defenders to uncover potential malicious behaviors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148745</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Bypass Meta’s Llama Firewall Using Prompt Injection Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-bypass-metas-llama-firewall/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Meta's Llama Firewall; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Llama Firewall contains multiple vulnerabilities that allow attackers to bypass security measures and inject malicious prompts into language models. These vulnerabilities include multilingual and obfuscated injections, as well as Unicode-based invisible prompt injections. Exploitation details indicate that the firewall struggled to detect these types of attacks, allowing them to succeed in bypassing system safeguards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=148705</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPUHammer: New RowHammer Attack Variant Degrades AI Models on NVIDIA GPUs</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/gpuhammer-new-rowhammer-attack-variant.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA GPUs; CVE(s): None; Summary: A variant of RowHammer attacks, dubbed GPUHammer, has been demonstrated against NVIDIA's graphics processing units (GPUs), causing malicious users to tamper with other users' data by triggering bit flips in GPU memory. Enabling System-level Error Correction Codes (ECC) is advised as a defense against this type of attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/gpuhammer-new-rowhammer-attack-variant.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers are exploiting critical RCE flaw in Wing FTP Server</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-rce-flaw-in-wing-ftp-server/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wing FTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47812, CVE-2025-27889, CVE-2025-47811, CVE-2025-47813; Summary: The Wing FTP Server has a critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-47812) that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute code with the highest privileges on the system. Exploitation details include running multiple enumeration and reconnaissance commands followed by establishing persistence by creating new users, with the goal of achieving arbitrary code execution as root/SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-are-exploiting-critical-rce-flaw-in-wing-ftp-server/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 14:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 600 Laravel Apps Exposed to Remote Code Execution Due to Leaked APP_KEYs on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/over-600-laravel-apps-exposed-to-remote.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Laravel; CVE(s): CVE-2018-15133, CVE-2024-55556; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to gain remote code execution capabilities by exploiting a deserialization flaw in Laravel's APP_KEY, which is often leaked publicly. This can be achieved by invoking the decrypt() function with a maliciously crafted payload.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/over-600-laravel-apps-exposed-to-remote.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-591: Delta Electronics DTM Soft BIN File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-591/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics DTM Soft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53415; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics DTM Soft. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of BIN files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26161</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windows 11 build adds self-healing “quick machine recovery” feature</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/07/new-windows-11-build-adds-self-healing-quick-machine-recovery-feature/</link>
      <description>This article discusses upcoming changes to Windows Insider preview build 27898, including new Taskbar features and updates to speech-to-text voice access. The release of Windows 11 25H2 is anticipated to be a minor update with no major under-the-hood changes, instead focusing on enabling previously installed features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/07/new-windows-11-build-adds-self-healing-quick-machine-recovery-feature/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'123456' password exposed chats for 64 million McDonald’s job chatbot applications</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-chats-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-chatbot-applications/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Paradox.ai McHire; CVE(s): None; Summary: The McHire job application platform, used by McDonald's franchisees, contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability that allows attackers to expose chat transcripts, session tokens, and personal data of real job applicants. The flaw was discovered by security researchers Ian Carroll and Sam Curry, who found that the ChatBot's admin panel utilized weak credentials and could be exploited to access sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-chats-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-chatbot-applications/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'123456' password exposed chats for 64 million McDonald’s job applicants</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-chats-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-applicants/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: McHire (McDonald's chatbot job application platform); CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in McHire exposed the chats of over 64 million job applicants across the United States due to an IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) flaw. By incrementing or decrementing a lead_id number, attackers could access sensitive data belonging to other applicants without verifying authorization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-chats-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-applicants/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'123456' password exposed info for 64 million McDonald’s job applicants</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-info-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-applicants/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: McHire; CVE(s): None; Summary: The McHire chatbot job application platform has an IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) vulnerability that exposes the personal information of over 64 million job applicants across the United States. The flaw allows attackers to access and retrieve sensitive data belonging to other applicants by incrementing or decrementing a lead_id number in a request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/123456-password-exposed-info-for-64-million-mcdonalds-job-applicants/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploits for pre-auth Fortinet FortiWeb RCE flaw released, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploits-for-pre-auth-fortinet-fortiweb-rce-flaw-released-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A critical SQL injection vulnerability (CWE-89) exists in FortiWeb's Fabric Connector, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute unauthorized SQL code or commands via crafted HTTP requests. The flaw can be exploited to achieve pre-authenticated remote code execution on vulnerable servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/exploits-for-pre-auth-fortinet-fortiweb-rce-flaw-released-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Gravity Forms developer hacked to push backdoored plugins</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-gravity-forms-developer-hacked-to-push-backdoored-plugins/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Gravity Forms (WordPress plugin); CVE(s): None; Summary: The Gravity Forms WordPress plugin was compromised in a supply-chain attack, allowing attackers to inject a backdoor and collect site metadata. The malware can be triggered by an unauthenticated user and enables remote code execution on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/wordpress-gravity-forms-developer-hacked-to-push-backdoored-plugins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-587: Luxion KeyShot 3DM File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-587/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Luxion KeyShot; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7222; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot by writing past the end of an allocated buffer. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The issue exists within the parsing of 3DM files and can be exploited to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-588: Trend Micro Cleaner One Pro Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-588/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Cleaner One Pro; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53503; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Trend Micro Cleaner One Pro. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the Junk Files Cleanup functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26484</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-589: Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-589/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security; CVE(s): ZDI-25-589, ZDI-CAN-25342, CVE-2025-53378; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to hijack security agents on affected installations of Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security. It requires user interaction and exists within the agent activation API due to a lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25342</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-590: G DATA Total Security GDTunerSvc Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-590/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: G DATA Total Security; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2790; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of G DATA Total Security. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and can leverage it to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26240</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA shares guidance to defend GDDR6 GPUs against Rowhammer attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-shares-guidance-to-defend-gddr6-gpus-against-rowhammer-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA GDDR6 graphical processors; CVE(s): None; Summary: Rowhammer attacks can be triggered through software processes, causing memory cells to flip and potentially leading to denial-of-service conditions, data corruption, or privilege escalation. Enabling System Level Error-Correcting Codes (ECC) mitigates this risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-shares-guidance-to-defend-gddr6-gpus-against-rowhammer-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA shares guidance to defend GDDR6 GPUs against Rowhammer attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-issues-guidance-to-defend-gddr6-gpus-against-rowhammer/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA; CVE(s): None; Summary: NVIDIA is warning users to enable System Level Error-Correcting Code (ECC) mitigation to protect against Rowhammer attacks on graphical processors with GDDR6 memory, as demonstrated by researchers at the University of Toronto. Enabling ECC can prevent data corruption, denial-of-service conditions, or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/nvidia-issues-guidance-to-defend-gddr6-gpus-against-rowhammer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The zero-day that could've compromised every Cursor and Windsurf user</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-zero-day-that-couldve-compromised-every-cursor-and-windsurf-user/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenVSX; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability was discovered in OpenVSX, an open-source marketplace powering extensions for AI coding tools like VS Code and its forks. The flaw allowed an attacker to gain full control over the entire marketplace by stealing a powerful secret token that belongs to the trusted @open-vsx account. With this token, an attacker could publish updates, overwrite existing ones, and silently hijack the entire marketplace, leading to a supply chain nightmare.

Note: This is not a traditional vulnerability disclosure, as there are no CVEs assigned. However, based on the article's content, I've summarized the vulnerability according to your guidelines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/the-zero-day-that-couldve-compromised-every-cursor-and-windsurf-user/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 15:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA tags Citrix Bleed 2 as exploited, gives agencies a day to patch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tags-citrix-bleed-2-as-exploited-gives-agencies-a-day-to-patch/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: A critical memory safety vulnerability (out-of-bounds memory read) allows unauthenticated attackers to access restricted parts of memory, impacting devices configured as a Gateway or AAA virtual server in versions prior to 14.1-43.56, 13.1-58.32, and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cisa-tags-citrix-bleed-2-as-exploited-gives-agencies-a-day-to-patch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Releases Patch for Critical SQL Injection Flaw in FortiWeb (CVE-2025-25257)</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fortinet-releases-patch-for-critical.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A critical SQL injection vulnerability (CVE-2025-25257) in FortiWeb allows an unauthenticated attacker to run arbitrary database commands, impacting versions 7.6.0-7.6.3, 7.4.0-7.4.7, 7.2.0-7.2.10, and 7.0.0-7.0.10; exploitation details involve using a Bearer token in an HTTP request to execute unauthorized SQL code or commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fortinet-releases-patch-for-critical.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes a Dark Web Monitoring Tool Effective?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-makes-a-dark-web-monitoring-tool-effective/</link>
      <description>This article provides an overview of Dark Web Monitoring tools, highlighting the importance of having a comprehensive solution that offers real-time alerts, broad darknet source coverage, credential leak detection, SIEM/SOAR integration, customizable monitoring rules, and visual threat dashboards. The article also emphasizes the need for AI-driven threat scoring, automated response support, and user-friendly interfaces to meet today's security demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061796</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-47812: Wing FTP Server Exposed to Root-Level RCE Attacks</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-47812-wing-ftp-server-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wing FTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47812; Summary: A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in Wing FTP Server versions prior to 7.4.4, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary commands into session files managed by the server's Lua interpreter, leading to SYSTEM/root-level access without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061788</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerfektBlue Bluetooth Vulnerabilities Expose Millions of Vehicles to Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/perfektblue-bluetooth-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenSynergy BlueSDK; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45434, CVE-2024-45431, CVE-2024-45433, CVE-2024-45432; Summary: The vulnerabilities in OpenSynergy's BlueSDK Bluetooth stack can be exploited to achieve remote code execution on millions of transport vehicles from different vendors, potentially allowing attackers to track GPS coordinates, record audio, access contact lists, and take control of critical software functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/perfektblue-bluetooth-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are the Main Benefits of Dark Web Monitoring?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-are-the-main-benefits-of-dark-web-monitoring/</link>
      <description>This article highlights the importance of monitoring the Dark Web to detect early signs of danger, prevent data breaches, and protect brand reputation. It emphasizes the benefits of Dark Web monitoring, including detecting leaked credentials, compromised customer records, and internal documents, as well as providing real-time alerts to take action against threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061777</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Data in the AI Era</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/securing-data-in-ai-era.html</link>
      <description>The 2025 Data Risk Report highlights the risks of data loss through AI-fueled tools, SaaS applications, email, file-sharing services, and other digital channels. The report reveals trends such as millions of data loss incidents through AI apps like ChatGPT and Microsoft Copilot, surging SaaS data loss, and significant email and file-sharing data loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/securing-data-in-ai-era.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Wing FTP Server Vulnerability (CVE-2025-47812) Actively Being Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-wing-ftp-server-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Wing FTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-47812; Summary: The Wing FTP Server has a maximum-severity security flaw, tracked as CVE-2025-47812, that allows remote code execution through improper handling of null ('\0') bytes in the server's web interface. This can be exploited via anonymous FTP accounts, enabling threat actors to download and execute malicious Lua files, conduct reconnaissance, and install remote monitoring and management software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-wing-ftp-server-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian-Backed Pay2Key Ransomware Resurfaces with 80% Profit Share for Cybercriminals</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iranian-backed-pay2key-ransomware.html</link>
      <description>An Iranian-backed ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) named Pay2Key has resurfaced, offering bigger payouts to cybercriminals who launch attacks against Israel and the U.S. The RaaS platform, hosted on the Invisible Internet Project (I2P), is linked to a hacking group tracked as Fox Kitten (aka Lemon Sandstorm) and appears to partner with or incorporate Mimic ransomware's capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/iranian-backed-pay2key-ransomware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Tactics of SLOW#TEMPEST: A Deep Dive Into Advanced Malware Techniques</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/slow-tempest-malware-obfuscation/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SLOW#TEMPEST malware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article analyzes a malware variant related to the SLOW#TEMPEST campaign, which employs obfuscation techniques such as control flow graph (CFG) obfuscation using dynamic jumps and obfuscated function calls. The malware's authors use these techniques to hinder static analysis and make detection more challenging.

FYSA: The article highlights the importance of adopting advanced dynamic analysis techniques alongside static analysis to effectively dissect and understand modern malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=146001</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Citrix NetScaler CVE-2025-5777 to KEV Catalog as Active Exploits Target Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-citrix-netscaler-cve-2025.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: An instance of insufficient input validation in Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway allows an attacker to bypass authentication when the appliance is configured as a Gateway or AAA virtual server, leading to memory overread. This vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) has been weaponized in the wild and can be exploited by sending the same payload repeatedly, causing sensitive information to be leaked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisa-adds-citrix-netscaler-cve-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro basketball player and 4 youths arrested in connection to ransomware crimes</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/pro-basketball-player-and-4-youths-arrested-in-connection-to-ransomware-crimes/</link>
      <description>Authorities in the UK arrested four individuals, including three men and one woman, in connection with separate and unrelated ransomware operations. The attacks targeted M&amp;S, Co-op, and Harrods, and were attributed to Scattered Spider, a group that uses impersonation and phishing tactics to gain access to networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/pro-basketball-player-and-4-youths-arrested-in-connection-to-ransomware-crimes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 now uses JScript9Legacy engine for improved security</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-now-uses-jscript9legacy-engine-for-improved-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft JScript; CVE(s): None; Summary: Microsoft replaced the default scripting engine JScript with JScript9Legacy on Windows 11 version 24H2 and later to improve security against web threats such as cross-site scripting (XSS). The outdated JScript engine was a frequent target of memory corruption, arbitrary code execution, and XSS vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/windows-11-now-uses-jscript9legacy-engine-for-improved-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 20:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch, track, repeat</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/patch-track-repeat/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various cybersecurity-related topics, including the end of free support for Windows 10, concerns about the long-term stability of the CVE system, and an increase in Known Exploited Vulnerabilities. It also mentions several notable threats and attacks, such as a Chinese hacker tied to the Silk Typhoon group being arrested, malicious Chrome extensions with 1.7 million downloads, and a ransomware attack on Ingram Micro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">686ebf745df3de0001555dea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Charges Four in ‘Scattered Spider’ Ransom Group</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/uk-charges-four-in-scattered-spider-ransom-group/</link>
      <description>Scattered Spider, a data theft and extortion group, has been targeted by law enforcement in the UK, with four alleged members arrested. The group is known for using social engineering tactics to gain access to companies' systems and steal data for ransom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=70968</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical mcp-remote Vulnerability Enables Remote Code Execution, Impacting 437,000+ Downloads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-mcp-remote-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: JFrog mcp-remote; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6514; Summary: The mcp-remote project contains a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-6514) that allows attackers to execute arbitrary operating system commands, posing a significant risk to users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-mcp-remote-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian pro basketball player arrested for alleged role in ransomware attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-pro-basketball-player-arrested-for-alleged-role-in-ransomware-attacks/</link>
      <description>Russian professional basketball player Daniil Kasatkin was arrested in France at the request of the United States for allegedly acting as a negotiator for a ransomware gang. The arrest is part of an international effort to disrupt and prosecute cybercrime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-pro-basketball-player-arrested-for-alleged-role-in-ransomware-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerfektBlue Bluetooth flaws impact Mercedes, Volkswagen, Skoda cars</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/perfektblue-bluetooth-flaws-impact-mercedes-volkswagen-skoda-cars/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenSynergy BlueSDK; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45434, CVE-2024-45431, CVE-2024-45433, CVE-2024-45432; Summary: Four vulnerabilities in the OpenSynergy BlueSDK Bluetooth stack allow remote code execution and potentially grant access to critical elements in vehicles from multiple vendors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/perfektblue-bluetooth-flaws-impact-mercedes-volkswagen-skoda-cars/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asus and Adobe vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/asus-and-adobe-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Asus Armoury Crate; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2144 (CVE-2025-1533), TALOS-2025-2150 (CVE-2022-3464); Summary: A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the AsIO3.sys kernel driver of Asus Armoury Crate 5.9.13.0 allows an unprivileged attacker to run a program from user mode, while an authorization bypass vulnerability in the AsIO3.sys functionality can be triggered by creating a specially crafted hard link.

Vulnerable Product: Adobe Acrobat Reader; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2159 (CVE-2025-43578), TALOS-2025-2170 (CVE-2025-43576); Summary: An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the Font functionality of Adobe Acrobat Reader 2025.001.20435 allows disclosure of sensitive information, while a use-after-free vulnerability in the annotation object processing functionality can lead to memory corruption and arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">686ec0185df3de0001555dfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Gaming and AI Firms Push Malware on Cryptocurrency Users via Telegram and Discord</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fake-gaming-and-ai-firms-push-malware.html</link>
      <description>Cryptocurrency users are being targeted by a social engineering campaign that uses fake startup companies to trick them into downloading malware. The campaign employs spoofed social media accounts and project documentation on legitimate platforms like Notion and GitHub, and has been ongoing since at least March 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fake-gaming-and-ai-firms-push-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI's CJIS demystified: Best practices for passwords, MFA &amp; access control</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbis-cjis-demystified-best-practices-for-passwords-mfa-and-access-control/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the Criminal Justice Information Services (CJIS) Security Policy, which governs how criminal histories, fingerprints, and investigation files must be protected. It explains the origins of CJIS, its purpose, and why it matters to organizations handling criminal-justice information. The article also covers the pillars of identity (passwords, multifactor authentication, and strict access controls), and provides guidance on how to embed these controls seamlessly into an environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fbis-cjis-demystified-best-practices-for-passwords-mfa-and-access-control/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four arrested in UK over M&amp;S, Co-op, Harrods cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrods-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>Four individuals, including two 19-year-old males, one 17-year-old male, and a 20-year-old female, were arrested by the UK's National Crime Agency (NCA) for suspected involvement in cyberattacks on major retailers, including Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, and Harrods. The suspects are believed to be linked to Scattered Spider, a threat actor group known for numerous breaches over the past few years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrods-cyberattacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four arrested in UK over M&amp;S, Co-op, Harrod cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrod-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>The UK's National Crime Agency (NCA) arrested four individuals suspected of involvement in cyberattacks on major retailers, including Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, and Harrods. The attacks were attributed to threat actors classified as Scattered Spider, with a history of breaches over the past few years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/four-arrested-in-uk-over-mands-co-op-harrod-cyberattacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: Arkana Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-arkana-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Arkana Ransomware is a group that emerged in early 2025, claiming to have stolen customer databases and taken control of key backend systems. They are part of the Qilin Network, a Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS) platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061758</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Dark Web Monitoring API?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-is-a-dark-web-monitoring-api/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the importance of Dark Web Monitoring APIs in detecting cyber threats and preventing attacks. It highlights the benefits of using such tools, including real-time alerts, broad coverage, and seamless integration into existing security systems. The article also provides best practices for setting up and configuring dark web monitoring APIs, as well as legal considerations and regulatory requirements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061750</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Arrested in £440M Cyber Attack on Marks &amp; Spencer, Co-op, and Harrods</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/four-arrested-in-440m-cyber-attack-on.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on the arrest of four individuals suspected of being involved in cyber attacks targeting major retailers in the UK. The attacks are believed to be perpetrated by a decentralized cybercrime group called Scattered Spider, which is notorious for its advanced social engineering tactics and willingness to be persistent in gaining initial access to targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/four-arrested-in-440m-cyber-attack-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-of-Train and Head-of-Train Remote Linking Protocol</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-191-10</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: End-of-Train and Head-of-Train remote linking protocol; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1727; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to send their own brake control commands to the end-of-train device, potentially causing a sudden stoppage or inducing brake failure. Exploitation requires low attack complexity and can be achieved through software-defined radio and a malicious packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23613</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siemens Solid Edge</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-191-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Siemens Solid Edge SE2025; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40739, CVE-2025-40740, CVE-2025-40741; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute arbitrary code. The affected applications contain out-of-bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted PAR files, which could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23605</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
