<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack on Serviceaide Compromises Data of 480,000 Catholic Health Patients</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cyberattack-on-serviceaide-compromises-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Serviceaide; CVE(s): None; Summary: An improperly secured Elasticsearch database left sensitive information of approximately 480,000 patients exposed for nearly seven weeks. The incident was caused by a misconfigured database managed by Serviceaide, which became publicly accessible on September 19, 2024, and was only discovered on November 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137162</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy Bumblebee Malware via Poisoned Bing SEO Results</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-bumblebee-malware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a cyberattack campaign that uses SEO poisoning to distribute the Bumblebee malware. The attackers create fake download websites mimicking legitimate software packages and optimize their malicious sites to rank at the top of Bing search results. The malware is used as a downloader for additional payloads, making it particularly dangerous in developer environments where privileged access could be leveraged for broader attacks or data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137150</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Flaw in WordPress Plugin Puts 22,000 Websites at Risk of Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/security-flaw-in-wordpress-plugin-puts-22000-websites/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The Motors WordPress theme has an unauthenticated privilege escalation vulnerability that allows attackers to change passwords of any user, including administrators, without requiring prior authentication. This vulnerability, with a critical CVSS rating of 9.8, can be exploited by unauthenticated threat actors to gain complete control over compromised websites, enabling attacks such as uploading malicious files, injecting malware, or redirecting users to phishing sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137137</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical VMware Cloud Foundation Vulnerability Exposes Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vmware-cloud-foundation-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Broadcom VMware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41229, CVE-2025-41230, CVE-2025-41231; Summary: Three significant security vulnerabilities in VMware Cloud Foundation platform allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information and internal services. The flaws affect versions 4.5.x and 5.x and require immediate patching as no workarounds are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137120</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qilin Exploits SAP Zero-Day Vulnerability Weeks Ahead of Public Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/qilin-exploits-sap-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer was actively exploited nearly three weeks before its public disclosure. The flaw lacks proper authentication and authorization controls, enabling unauthenticated attackers to upload malicious files like web shells, leading to potential remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137125</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Plugin Flaw Puts 22,000 Websites at Risk of Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/wordpress-plugin-flaw-puts-22000-websites/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors WordPress Theme; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The Motors WordPress theme contains a critical Privilege Escalation vulnerability (CVE-2025-4322) that allows unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of any user, including administrators, thereby gaining full control over affected websites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137099</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crowded Battle: Key Insights from the 2025 State of Pentesting Report</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/the-crowded-battle-key-insights-from.html</link>
      <description>The article presents findings from the 2025 State of Pentesting Report, highlighting the strategies, tactics, and tools used by CISOs to cope with security alerts, breaches, and growing cyber risks. Key takeaways include the growth of software-based pentesting, increasing trust in automated tools, and the influence of cyber insurance providers on enterprise security priorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/the-crowded-battle-key-insights-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPRK IT Workers Impersonate Polish and US Nationals to Secure Full-Stack Developer Positions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dprk-it-workers-impersonate-polish-and-us-nationals/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated employment scam network potentially affiliated with the Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK) targets remote engineering and full-stack blockchain developer roles by impersonating Polish and US nationals. The threat actors employ deceptive tactics, including the use of GitHub accounts, portfolio websites, and freelancer profiles to deceive companies into hiring them for full-time or project-based freelance gigs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137070</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Multer Vulnerability Puts Millions of Node.js Apps at Risk</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-multer-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm Multer; CVE(s): None; Summary: All versions of Multer from 1.4.4-lts.1 to but not including 2.0.0 are vulnerable to denial-of-service attacks through maliciously crafted multi-part upload requests, potentially crashing Node.js processes and taking down entire web services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137064</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duping Cloud Functions: An emerging serverless attack vector</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/duping-cloud-functions-an-emerging-serverless-attack-vector/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Cloud Platform (GCP) Cloud Functions; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability was discovered in GCP's Cloud Functions serverless compute service and its Cloud Build continuous integration and continuous delivery pipeline service. An attacker could create or update a cloud function to escalate privileges to the default Cloud Build service account. The vulnerability has since been partially addressed by Google.

FYSA: Cisco Talos' research demonstrated that the technique used to exploit the GCP Cloud Functions vulnerability could be adapted to perform other malicious activities in other cloud-based environments, such as AWS Lambda and Azure Functions. Threat actors can use this method to gather valuable enumeration information about network devices, CPU scheduling, control group container IDs, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682b779afed2140001359170</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Privilege Escalation Vulnerability Let Attackers Gain Admin Access in Under 300 Milliseconds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-privilege-escalation-flaw-allows-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24076; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Windows 11 allowed attackers to escalate privileges from a standard user to system-level administrator in just 300 milliseconds through DLL hijacking. The flaw leveraged a Dynamic-link Library (DLL) hijacking technique within Windows 11's "Mobile devices" feature, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137032</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Deploy MarsSnake Backdoor in Multi-Year Attack on Saudi Organization</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-deploy-marssnake.html</link>
      <description>No vulnerabilities mentioned in the article; instead, it discusses threat actors and their tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) used to target organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/chinese-hackers-deploy-marssnake.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O2 VoLTE Flaw Allows Tracking of Customers’ Locations Through Phone Calls</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/o2-volte-flaw-allows-tracking-of-customers-locations/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: O2 UK; CVE(s): None; Summary: The VoLTE implementation in O2 UK's network contained a significant privacy vulnerability that exposed precise location data of call recipients. The vulnerability allowed any caller to access the recipient's IMSI and IMEI numbers, as well as cell tower identification data, which could be used to geolocate the recipient with minimal technical expertise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136985</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Issues Urgent Patch to Resolve BitLocker Recovery Problem</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-issues-urgent-patch-to-resolve-bitlocker/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical issue affecting Windows 10 devices with specific Intel processors causes unexpected system failures and forces users to enter BitLocker recovery keys. The issue was introduced in the May 13, 2025 security update and is fixed by the emergency update KB5061768, which addresses a severe problem impacting devices with Intel Trusted Execution Technology (TXT) enabled on 10th generation or later Intel vPro processors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136969</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Package in Koishi Chatbots Steals Sensitive Data in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-npm-package-in-koishi-chatbots/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Koishi; CVE(s): None; Summary: The koishi-plugin-pinhaofa plugin for the Koishi chatbot framework contains a data-exfiltration backdoor that scans messages for eight-character hexadecimal strings and silently forwards sensitive data to a hardcoded QQ account, allowing real-time data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137002</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-Based Malware Deploys XMRig Miner on Linux Hosts via Redis Configuration Abuse</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/go-based-malware-deploys-xmrig-miner-on.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses two separate cybersecurity threats. The first is RedisRaider, a Linux cryptojacking campaign targeting publicly accessible Redis servers. The attackers use a bespoke scanner to identify vulnerable systems and inject malicious cron jobs using Redis's SET command. The end goal is to drop an XMRig miner on compromised systems. The second threat is a targeted campaign exploiting legacy authentication protocols in Microsoft Entra ID, bypassing defenses like MFA and Conditional Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/go-based-malware-deploys-xmrig-miner-on.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tor Browser 14.5.2 Released: Bug Fixes and Enhanced Features</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/tor-browser-14-5-2-released/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of Tor Browser 14.5.2, which addresses security vulnerabilities, resolves privacy-related bugs, and implements infrastructural improvements. The update rebases its underlying engine on Firefox 128.10.1esr, prioritizes security by closing a potential loophole allowing malicious actors to bypass privacy controls, and strengthens cryptographic integrity by expanding the list of authorized signers for Tor Browser and Mullvad Browser tags.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136933</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W3LL Phishing Kit Launches Active Campaign to Steal Outlook Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/w3ll-phishing-kit-launches-active-campaign/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: W3LL Phishing Kit; CVE(s): None; Summary: The W3LL phishing kit is a sophisticated tool that uses advanced adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) techniques to harvest Microsoft 365 Outlook login credentials. It allows threat actors to purchase functionalities and components needed to conduct tailored phishing campaigns, making it more accessible and adaptable than conventional off-the-shelf kits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136966</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Actively Exploited Ivanti EPMM Zero-Day to KEV Catalog</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-epmm-zero-day-to-kev-catalog/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The vulnerabilities enable authentication bypass and remote code execution, respectively, due to insecure implementations of open-source libraries. CVE-2025-4427 allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication mechanisms, while CVE-2025-4428 enables authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code. These flaws could permit access to sensitive data without credentials or escalate privileges for malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136915</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical pfSense Firewall Flaws Enable Attackers to Inject Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-pfsense-firewall-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Netgate pfSense; CVE(s): CVE-2024-57273, CVE-2024-54780, CVE-2024-54779; Summary: Three critical vulnerabilities were discovered in pfSense firewall software, allowing attackers to inject malicious code, corrupt configurations, and gain unauthorized access. The first vulnerability affects the Automatic Configuration Backup service, while the second involves authenticated command injection in the OpenVPN management interface. The third allows XML injection in dashboard widgets, enabling persistent XSS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136900</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Users Targeted by Tycoon2FA Linked Phishing Attack to Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-365-users-targeted-by-tycoon2fa-linked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft 365; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new wave of targeted phishing campaigns is targeting Microsoft 365 users. The attackers are leveraging malformed URLs with backslash characters (https:\\) to bypass conventional email security filters and evade URL-based detection mechanisms. Despite the apparent incorrect format, modern web browsers can still parse and resolve these links, landing victims on sophisticated credential harvesting sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136917</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI Packages Exploit Instagram and TikTok APIs to Validate User Accounts</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-packages-exploit.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Python Package Index (PyPI); CVE(s): None; Summary: Malicious packages "checker-SaGaF", "steinlurks", and "sinnercore" were uploaded to PyPI, allowing threat actors to validate stolen email addresses against TikTok and Instagram APIs. These packages can be used to threaten account holders, sell validated user lists on the dark web, or launch credential stuffing or password spraying exploits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-packages-exploit.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI plans to combine multiple models into GPT-5</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-plans-to-combine-multiple-models-into-gpt-5/</link>
      <description>OpenAI plans to combine multiple products into its next foundational model, GPT-5, aiming to make existing models better and more efficient. This move may reduce confusion caused by identical model names across different tasks. The company is also focusing on building the best coding model, Codex, which will be built upon the o3 reasoning model.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-plans-to-combine-multiple-models-into-gpt-5/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 22:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake KeePass password manager leads to ESXi ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-keepass-password-manager-leads-to-esxi-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>Threat actors have been distributing trojanized versions of KeePass password manager for at least eight months to install Cobalt Strike beacons, steal credentials, and deploy ransomware. The campaign started with malicious KeePass installer promoted through Bing advertisements that led to fake software sites. The attack ultimately led to the company's VMware ESXi servers being encrypted with ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-keepass-password-manager-leads-to-esxi-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Phishing Attack Poses as Zoom Meeting Invites to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-phishing-attack-poses-as-zoom-meeting/</link>
      <description>A newly identified phishing campaign targets users by masquerading as urgent Zoom meeting invitations from colleagues. The campaign leverages realism and psychological manipulation to steal login credentials, with a focus on customizing URLs using stolen data. Users are advised to verify authenticity and avoid interacting with suspicious links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136865</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Hannibal Stealer Uses Stealth and Obfuscation to Evade Detection</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-hannibal-stealer-uses-stealth-and-obfuscation/</link>
      <description>The Hannibal Stealer is a modular .NET info-stealer and credential harvester that demonstrates advanced stealth mechanisms and obfuscation techniques to bypass modern detection systems. It can extract sensitive data from browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, and popular applications, and features geofencing capabilities to avoid scrutiny in certain countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136874</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese APT Hackers Target Organizations Using Korplug Loaders and Malicious USB Drives</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-apt-hackers-target-organizations/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on advanced persistent threat (APT) groups with ties to China that have been targeting European governmental and industrial entities. These groups use sophisticated tactics and tools, including Korplug loaders, malicious USB drives, and backdoors, to infiltrate sensitive networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136854</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cache Timing Techniques Used to Bypass Windows 11 KASLR and Reveal Kernel Base</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cache-timing-techniques-used-to-bypass-windows-11/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a cache timing side-channel attack that can circumvent Kernel Address Space Layout Randomization (KASLR) on fully updated Windows 11 PCs, exploiting speculative execution and processor cache behavior to infer the base address of ntoskrnl.exe. This attack requires no elevated privileges and has been successfully tested on Windows 11 version 10.0.26100.3775.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136841</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O2 UK patches bug leaking mobile user location from call metadata</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/o2-uk-patches-bug-leaking-mobile-user-location-from-call-metadata/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: O2 UK (VoLTE and WiFi Calling technologies); CVE(s): None; Summary: A flaw in O2 UK's implementation of VoLTE and WiFi Calling technologies allows anyone to expose the general location of a person and other identifiers by calling the target, including IMSI, IMEI, and cell location data. The issue was resolved after being reported by security researcher Daniel Williams on March 26 and 27, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/o2-uk-patches-bug-leaking-mobile-user-location-from-call-metadata/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit AutoIT Scripts to Deploy Malware Targeting Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-autoit-scripts-to-deploy-malware/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated attack leveraging AutoIT scripting language was discovered, featuring a double-layered AutoIT script designed to deploy a potentially devastating payload. The attack involves the deployment of malicious DLLs, including AsyncRAT and PureHVNC, allowing attackers to maintain long-term access to infected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136828</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 emergency updates fix BitLocker recovery issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-emergency-updates-fix-bitlocker-recovery-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: Windows 10 systems with Intel vPro processors (10th gen or later) and Intel Trusted Execution Technology (TXT) enabled may boot into BitLocker recovery after installing the May 2025 security updates. Installing KB5061768 emergency update or disabling TXT from BIOS can fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-emergency-updates-fix-bitlocker-recovery-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arla Foods confirms cyberattack disrupts production, causes delays</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arla-foods-confirms-cyberattack-disrupts-production-causes-delays/</link>
      <description>Arla Foods has been targeted by a cyberattack that disrupted its production operations at a facility in Germany, leading to product delivery delays or cancellations. The attack did not appear to involve data theft or encryption, and the type of attack and perpetrators remain unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arla-foods-confirms-cyberattack-disrupts-production-causes-delays/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Report Finds 67% of Organizations Experienced Cyber Attacks in the Last Year</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-report-finds-67-of-organizations/</link>
      <description>A report by Hiscox Cyber Readiness Report 2024 shows a rising trend of cyberattacks across eight worldwide markets, with 67% of businesses experiencing attacks in the previous 12 months. The report highlights the impact of attacks on reputations, finances, and employee behavior, emphasizing the need for organizations to prioritize cybersecurity training and leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136820</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0-PHP Vulnerability Enables Unauthorized Access for Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/auth0-php-vulnerability-enables-unauthorized-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Auth0-PHP SDK; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Auth0-PHP SDK versions 8.0.0-BETA1 and newer have a critical security vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to applications through brute force attacks on session cookie authentication tags, potentially leading to session hijacking and exploitation of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136783</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Exploitation of Ivanti EPMM Zero-Day Vulnerability in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-epmm-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Enterprise Mobility Management (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The zero-day vulnerability in Ivanti's EPMM platform can be chained with another vulnerability to achieve remote code execution, posing a significant threat to unpatched systems. Attackers have already attempted to exploit these security flaws, and many vulnerable instances remain exposed despite public disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136770</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft unveils Windows AI Foundry for AI-powered PC apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-unveils-windows-ai-foundry-for-ai-powered-pc-apps/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses Microsoft's new Windows AI Foundry, a tool that helps developers build, experiment, and reach users with AI experiences in their apps. The feature allows for the integration of various AI models, including open-source ones from Nvidia, and provides ready-to-use APIs for tasks such as text intelligence and image description. Additionally, it includes features like Foundry Local, which automatically matches models to a device's hardware, and developer tools like a command-line tool and SDK.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-unveils-windows-ai-foundry-for-ai-powered-pc-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Arrested for Taking Over SEC Social Media to Spread False Bitcoin News</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacker-arrested-for-taking-over-sec-social-media/</link>
      <description>A 26-year-old man, Eric Council Jr., has been sentenced to 14 months in prison for orchestrating a sophisticated SIM swap attack that allowed him to hijack the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) social media account on X, formerly known as Twitter. The unauthorized access was used to post false information about Bitcoin ETF approvals, causing significant market volatility in cryptocurrency prices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136763</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Cobalt Strike Beacons Using Shodan: A Researcher’s Guide</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/investigating-cobalt-strike-beacons-using-shodan/</link>
      <description>A security researcher has published a method for gathering threat intelligence on Cobalt Strike beacons using Shodan and PowerShell. The technique allows security professionals to collect configuration data from active Cobalt Strike servers, including beacon SpawnTo values and watermarks, which are critical for detection and attribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136752</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Car Hack Exposes Owner’s Personal Data and Service Records</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/volkswagen-car-hack-exposes-owners-personal-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Volkswagen My Volkswagen app; CVE(s): None; Summary: The My Volkswagen app contains critical security flaws that allowed unauthorized access to vehicle information and personal data. A security researcher discovered the vulnerabilities by exploiting a fundamental authentication weakness and identified multiple API vulnerabilities, including the exposure of sensitive user information and internal system credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136714</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms new "Advanced" Settings for Windows 11</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-new-advanced-settings-for-windows-11/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the new "Advanced Settings" feature in Windows 11. The feature allows users and developers to personalize their OS experience by customizing File Explorer and Virtual Machines settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-new-advanced-settings-for-windows-11/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft open-sources Windows Subsystem for Linux at Build 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-open-sources-windows-subsystem-for-linux-at-build-2025/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has open-sourced the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), making its source code available on GitHub, except for a few components that are part of Windows. This move is expected to increase community involvement and contributions to the project, allowing developers to inspect the code, build it themselves, submit improvements, and understand how WSL works under the hood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-open-sources-windows-subsystem-for-linux-at-build-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RVTools Official Site Hacked to Deliver Bumblebee Malware via Trojanized Installer</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/rvtools-official-site-hacked-to-deliver.html</link>
      <description>The official site for RVTools has been hacked to serve a compromised installer for the popular VMware environment reporting utility. Additionally, Procolored printers have been found to include malicious software with features such as collecting system information, logging keystrokes, and propagating via connected USB drives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/rvtools-official-site-hacked-to-deliver.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Legal Aid Agency confirms applicant data stolen in data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-legal-aid-agency-confirms-applicant-data-stolen-in-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A data breach has occurred at the United Kingdom's Legal Aid Agency (LAA), where hackers stole a large amount of sensitive applicant data, including contact details, dates of birth, national ID numbers, criminal history, employment status, and financial information. The agency is advising all applicants to be vigilant for potential scam attempts targeting them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-legal-aid-agency-confirms-applicant-data-stolen-in-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Reveals Hackers Targeting US Following UK Retailer Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-reveals-hackers-targeting-us/</link>
      <description>UNC3944, a well-known hacker collective, has been identified by the Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) as a persistent and dynamic cyberthreat. The group has evolved from initial SIM swap operations to ransomware and data theft extortion tactics, with a focus on large enterprises in English-speaking countries. Their modus operandi relies heavily on sophisticated social engineering, and they have orchestrated sector-specific waves of attacks, including financial services, food services, and retail sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136669</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skitnet Malware Employs Stealth Techniques to Execute Payload and Maintain Persistence Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/skitnet-malware-employs-stealth-techniques/</link>
      <description>Skitnet (Bossnet) is a highly sophisticated multi-stage malware developed by the threat group LARVA-306. It features advanced stealth techniques and evasion methods to execute its malicious payload, maintain persistent access on infected systems, and evade detection by security defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136656</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Gangs Use Skitnet Malware for Stealthy Data Theft and Remote Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ransomware-gangs-use-skitnet-malware.html</link>
      <description>Skitnet is a multi-stage malware used by ransomware actors for post-exploitation efforts, stealing sensitive data and establishing remote control over compromised hosts. It uses programming languages like Rust and Nim to evade detection, and incorporates persistence mechanisms, remote access tools, commands for data exfiltration, and download of additional payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ransomware-gangs-use-skitnet-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla fixes Firefox zero-days exploited at hacking contest</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-zero-days-exploited-at-hacking-contest/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4918, CVE-2025-4919; Summary: Two Firefox zero-day vulnerabilities were demonstrated at the Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 hacking competition. The flaws, tracked under CVE-2025-4918 and CVE-2025-4919, are an out-of-bounds read/write issue in the JavaScript engine and a flaw allowing attackers to perform out-of-bounds reads/writes on a JavaScript object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-zero-days-exploited-at-hacking-contest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers earn $1,078,750 for 28 zero-days at Pwn2Own Berlin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-earn-1-078-750-for-28-zero-days-at-pwn2own-berlin/</link>
      <description>The article reports on the Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 hacking competition, where security researchers exploited 29 zero-day vulnerabilities and earned $1,078,750 in cash awards. No specific vulnerability details are provided.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-earn-1-078-750-for-28-zero-days-at-pwn2own-berlin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Six Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/19/cisa-adds-six-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM), MDaemon Email Server, Srimax Output Messenger, Synacor Zimbra Collaboration Suite (ZCS), ZKTeco BioTime; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428, CVE-2024-11182, CVE-2025-27920, CVE-2024-27443, CVE-2023-38950; Summary: Six new vulnerabilities have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. These vulnerabilities affect Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile, MDaemon Email Server, Srimax Output Messenger, Synacor Zimbra Collaboration Suite (ZCS), and ZKTeco BioTime, and are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors, posing significant risks to the federal enterprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23401</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CTEM is the Winning Bet for CISOs in 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/why-ctem-is-winning-bet-for-cisos-in.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the concept of Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM), which solidifies its role as a strategic enabler for Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs). CTEM integrates Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV) and Exposure Assessment Platforms (EAP) to empower CISOs to adopt a continuous, adaptive model that keeps pace with attacker techniques and the evolving threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/why-ctem-is-winning-bet-for-cisos-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
