<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>New Scan Uncovers 150K Industrial Systems Worldwide Vulnerable to Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-scan-uncovers-150k-industrial-systems/</link>
      <description>The article reports that approximately 150,000 industrial control systems (ICS) worldwide are directly accessible on the public internet, posing severe risks of catastrophic cyberattacks. The study utilized advanced application-layer scanning to identify ICS devices, revealing a large number of exposed systems globally, with many not designed with robust security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137582</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 Introduces Enhanced Administrator Protection to Strengthen Security Against Elevated Privilege Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-11-introduces-enhanced-administrator-protection/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 11; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the introduction of Administrator Protection, a security feature designed to safeguard systems against privilege escalation attacks. This feature creates a security boundary around administrative operations by implementing a hidden system-managed profile-separated local user account that generates isolated admin tokens, preventing user-level malware from compromising code running in elevated contexts and eliminating auto-elevation functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137592</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-stealing Chrome extensions impersonate Fortinet, YouTube, VPNs</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-stealing-chrome-extensions-impersonate-fortinet-youtube-vpns/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome Web Store; CVE(s): None; Summary: A malicious campaign has been discovered on the Google Chrome Web Store, featuring over 100 fake browser extensions that mimic legitimate tools to steal browser cookies and execute remote scripts. The extensions offer some functionality but also connect to threat actor infrastructure to steal user information or receive commands to execute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/data-stealing-chrome-extensions-impersonate-fortinet-youtube-vpns/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ThreatLocker Patch Management: A Security-First Approach to Closing Vulnerability Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threatlocker-patch-management-a-security-first-approach-to-closing-vulnerability-windows/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of patch management in cybersecurity, highlighting the challenges organizations face in executing consistent and secure patching at scale. It introduces ThreatLocker's Patch Management solution as a way to provide security teams with greater control, visibility, and confidence over patching workflows while minimizing risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threatlocker-patch-management-a-security-first-approach-to-closing-vulnerability-windows/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Union sanctions Stark Industries for enabling cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/european-union-sanctions-stark-industries-for-enabling-cyberattacks/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a specific vulnerability, but rather the imposition of sanctions by the European Union against web-hosting provider Stark Industries and its owners for enabling "destabilising activities" against the EU.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/european-union-sanctions-stark-industries-for-enabling-cyberattacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PureRAT Malware Spikes 4x in 2025, Deploying PureLogs to Target Russian Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/purerat-malware-spikes-4x-in-2025.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a phishing campaign targeting Russian organizations, distributing malware called PureRAT. The attack chain begins with a phishing email containing a RAR file attachment or link, which extracts an executable that unpacks and runs the main payload, PureRAT.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/purerat-malware-spikes-4x-in-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerDNS Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Trigger DoS Attacks Through Malicious TCP Connections</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/powerdns-vulnerability-let-attacker-trigger-dos-attack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PowerDNS DNSdist; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30193; Summary: The DNSdist load balancer has a vulnerability (CVE-2025-30193) that allows remote attackers to trigger denial of service attacks without authentication, affecting all versions prior to 1.9.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137557</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanHelsing Ransomware Builder Exposed on Hacker Forums</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-exposed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VanHelsing Ransomware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The source code for the VanHelsing ransomware operation has been leaked publicly due to an internal dispute with a former developer. The leak includes critical components of the ransomware infrastructure, but some elements remain missing, limiting immediate exploitation by opportunistic threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137537</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Warns: One-Third of Cyber Attacks Use Advanced Tactics to Steal Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ibm-warns-one-third-of-cyber-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a trend in cyber intrusions that rely on identity-based attacks, exploiting valid login credentials to breach systems. This trend is driven by the use of generative AI (gen AI) and other sophisticated tools to scale phishing campaigns and harvest credentials through infostealer malware and credential phishing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137563</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-Year-Old Hacker Admits Guilt in Major Cyberattack on PowerSchool</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacker-admits-guilt-in-major-cyberattack-on-powerschool/</link>
      <description>Matthew D. Lane, a 19-year-old Massachusetts college student, has been accused of orchestrating a cyberattack on PowerSchool, a widely used educational software provider, resulting in the theft of confidential data from millions of students and teachers. The attack involved unauthorized access to cloud storage providers and the threat of publishing sensitive information unless a ransom was paid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137511</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake Kling AI Facebook Ads Deliver RAT Malware to Over 22 Million Potential Victims</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-kling-ai-facebook-ads-deliver-rat.html</link>
      <description>Counterfeit Facebook pages and sponsored ads are being used to trick users into downloading malware. The fake websites offer AI-powered image and video generation, but actually download a malicious Windows executable that installs a remote access trojan (RAT) and stealer, which steals sensitive data and exfiltrates it to a command-and-control server.

FYSA: Vietnamese threat actors are using Facebook malvertising techniques to distribute stealer malware, leveraging the popularity of generative AI tools as lures. The campaign impersonated Kling AI through fake ads and deceptive websites, demonstrating social engineering tactics combined with advanced malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fake-kling-ai-facebook-ads-deliver-rat.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian GRU Cyber Actors Targeting Western Logistics Entities and Tech Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/05/21/russian-gru-cyber-actors-targeting-western-logistics-entities-and-tech-companies</link>
      <description>A joint cybersecurity advisory was released by CISA, NSA, FBI, and other U.S. and international partners regarding a Russian state-sponsored cyber espionage campaign targeting Western logistics entities and technology companies, including those involved in delivering foreign assistance to Ukraine. The campaign is attributed to the Russian General Staff Main Intelligence Directorate (GRU) 85th Main Special Service Center, military unit 26165, which has been previously linked to IP camera attacks in Ukraine and bordering NATO nations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian GRU Targeting Western Logistics Entities and Technology Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-141a</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I analyzed the article provided, which appears to be a threat report on GRU unit 26165's tactics and techniques used in malicious activities. The article highlights various indicators of compromise (IoCs), tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) employed by this actor group.

The report discusses multiple aspects of cybersecurity, including:

1. Identity and Access Management: It emphasizes the importance of strong access controls, multi-factor authentication, and account throttling or lockout to prevent credential theft.
2. Network Security: The article suggests disabling NTLM entirely and migrating to more robust authentication processes like PKI certificate authentication.
3. IP Camera Security: It provides guidelines for securing IP cameras by ensuring they are currently supported, applying security patches and firmware updates, disabling remote access if unnecessary, and using a VPN for remote connections.

The report also includes several mitigation techniques, such as:

1. Disable Universal Plug and Play (UPnP), Peer-to-Peer (P2P), and Anonymous Visit features on IP cameras and routers.
2. Turn off other ports/services not in use (e.g., FTP, web interface, etc.).
3. Configure, tune, and monitor logging if available on the IP camera.

In conclusion, this report is a valuable resource for cybersecurity professionals seeking to understand and mitigate GRU unit 26165's tactics and techniques. It provides actionable guidance on various aspects of network security, identity and access management, and IP camera security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23341</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SideWinder APT Hackers Exploits Legacy Office Vulnerabilities to Deploy Malware Undetected</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sidewinder-apt-hackers-exploits-legacy-office-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2017-0199, CVE-2017-11882; Summary: The SideWinder APT group exploits unpatched legacy Microsoft Office vulnerabilities to deploy credential-stealing malware, using spear-phishing emails with malicious Word or RTF attachments. The exploit chain begins with remote code execution and memory corruption bugs, and ultimately leads to the exfiltration of sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137533</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health hit by system-wide outage after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-hit-by-system-wide-outage-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>A healthcare network, Kettering Health, experienced a system-wide technology outage due to a cyberattack, which forced the cancellation of inpatient and outpatient procedures. The attack may have involved ransomware, as Interlock ransomware gang is suspected to be behind the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/kettering-health-hit-by-system-wide-outage-after-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing CI/CD workflows with Wazuh</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/securing-cicd-workflows-with-wazuh.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the risks associated with Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery/Deployment (CI/CD) workflows, including supply chain attacks, insecure dependencies, insider threats, lack of visibility, compliance requirements, code and dependency vulnerabilities, container vulnerabilities, and misconfiguration of CI/CD tools. It highlights the importance of integrating security measures into CI/CD pipelines to maintain confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/securing-cicd-workflows-with-wazuh.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellcom Confirms Cybersecurity Breach After Network Failure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cellcom-confirms-cybersecurity-breach/</link>
      <description>The article reports a cyberattack on Cellcom/Nsight's network infrastructure, causing a five-day service disruption. The company confirmed the incident and assured customers that sensitive personal information remains secure. The attack did not compromise customer data repositories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137500</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LockBit Internal Data Leak Reveals Payload Creation Methods and Ransom Demands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lockbit-internal-data-leak-reveals-payload/</link>
      <description>This article reveals a major data breach of the LockBit ransomware group's operations, exposing internal processes and sensitive data. The leak includes details on ransomware payload creation, negotiation tactics with victims, and configuration data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137506</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Detect Phishing Attacks Faster: Tycoon2FA Example</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-to-detect-phishing-attacks-faster.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of phishing detection in corporate environments and highlights the capabilities of ANY.RUN's Interactive Sandbox in detecting and analyzing evasive phishing attacks. It provides a real-world example of a suspicious email and walks through how the sandbox can be used to detonate every stage of an attack, from the first click to the final payload. The article emphasizes the benefits of using sandboxes like ANY.RUN in detecting and responding to phishing threats quickly and efficiently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/how-to-detect-phishing-attacks-faster.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks &amp; Spencer faces $402 million profit hit after cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marks-and-spencer-faces-402-million-profit-hit-after-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>Marks &amp; Spencer, a British retailer, is bracing for a potential profit hit of up to £300 million ($402 million) following a recent cyberattack that led to widespread operational and sales disruptions. The company's online retail systems are still disabled, and the disruptions are expected to last at least until July. The attack was linked to the Scattered Spider, a collective of cybercriminals known for breaching high-profile organizations worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/marks-and-spencer-faces-402-million-profit-hit-after-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100 Malicious Chrome Extensions Exploiting Users to Steal Login Credentials and Execute Remote Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-100-malicious-chrome-extensions-exploiting-users/</link>
      <description>A network of over 100 malicious Chrome extensions has been discovered, stealing login credentials and executing unauthorized remote code. The extensions inject harmful scripts into the browser environment, harvesting critical data and exploiting vulnerabilities to establish backdoor access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137460</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti EPMM 0-Day RCE Vulnerability Under Active Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-epmm-0-day-rce-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The EPMM contains a critical vulnerability chain that allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems. The vulnerability combines an authentication bypass (CVE-2025-4427) and a remote code execution flaw (CVE-2025-4428) to create a critical attack vector. Exploitation has been observed since May 16th following the publication of proof-of-concept exploits by multiple security firms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137448</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase says recent data breach impacts 69,461 customers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-says-recent-data-breach-impacts-69-461-customers/</link>
      <description>A data breach at Coinbase affected 69,461 individuals, exposing customer and corporate data. The breached information included personal identifiers such as name, date of birth, social security numbers, and account information, which could be used in social engineering attacks to convince victims to move their funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/coinbase-says-recent-data-breach-impacts-69-461-customers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Alerts Users to Multiple Critical Vulnerabilities Affecting Data Center Server</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/atlassian-alerts-users-to-multiple-critical-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31650, CVE-2024-47072, CVE-2024-57699, CVE-2025-24970, CVE-2025-22157; Summary: Eight high-severity vulnerabilities affecting multiple enterprise products in Atlassian's Data Center and Server offerings, including denial-of-service attacks and privilege escalation. The vulnerabilities were discovered through various means, including the Bug Bounty program, penetration testing, and third-party library scans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137415</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminals Could Leverage Google Cloud Platform for Malicious Activities</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminals-could-leverage-google-cloud-platform/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Cloud Platform's (GCP) Cloud Functions and Cloud Build services; CVE(s): None; Summary: The default Cloud Build Service Account (SA) previously granted excessive permissions during the deployment of Cloud Functions, allowing attackers to escalate privileges by exploiting the deployment process. This could have enabled malicious activities, including environment enumeration, across multiple cloud platforms, despite Google's partial remediation patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137427</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Hackers Create Fake AI Tool to Exploit Millions of Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-hackers-create-fake-ai-tool/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a sophisticated campaign by hostile actors posing as Kling AI, an AI-powered picture and video synthesis platform. The attackers use counterfeit Facebook pages and paid advertisements to lure users into downloading malicious Windows executables disguised with double extensions and Hangul Filler characters, which execute anti-analysis tricks and deploy a PureHVNC Remote Access Trojan (RAT) that steals credentials and session tokens from various browser extensions and standalone applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137358</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Expose PWA JavaScript Attack That Redirects Users to Adult Scam Apps</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-pwa-javascript.html</link>
      <description>A new campaign has been discovered that employs malicious JavaScript injections on mobile devices to redirect site visitors to a Chinese adult-content Progressive Web App (PWA) scam, aiming to bypass basic browser protections and retain users longer. The attack only triggers on mobile devices and is designed to evade detection mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/researchers-expose-pwa-javascript.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Phishing Attack Uses AES &amp; Malicious npm Packages to Office 365 Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-phishing-attack-uses-aes-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>A highly sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Microsoft Office 365 (O365) credentials was uncovered by Fortra's Suspicious Email Analysis team. The attack employed modern technologies and developer infrastructure, including AES encryption, malicious npm packages, and content delivery networks (CDNs), to deliver a counterfeit O365 login page designed to steal credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137312</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kettering Health Experiences System-Wide Outage Due to Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kettering-health-experiences-system-wide-outage/</link>
      <description>A ransomware attack has hit Kettering Health, a major healthcare provider, causing a system-wide technology outage that has severely limited access to critical patient care systems. The attack is part of a troubling trend of cyber attacks targeting healthcare institutions, which are particularly vulnerable due to their critical need for immediate access to patient information and the life-or-death nature of their services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137342</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Lexmark Printers Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-lexmark-printers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lexmark; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1127; Summary: The vulnerability is a critical security flaw affecting over 150 Lexmark printer and multifunction device models. It enables remote attackers to execute malicious code on unpatched systems through a combination of path traversal and concurrent execution flaws, with the potential for full system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137322</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attaxion Leads the Way as First EASM Platform to Integrate ENISA’s EU Vulnerability Database (EUVD)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/attaxion-becomes-the-first-easm-platform-to-integrate-enisas-eu-vulnerability-database-euvd/</link>
      <description>The article announces the integration of the European Vulnerability Database (EUVD) into Attaxion's external attack surface management platform. This integration provides broader coverage and context for vulnerability prioritization, including EUVD IDs, exploitation confirmation, affected products, and references.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137374</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Can Now Auto-Change Compromised Passwords Using Its Built-In Manager</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-chrome-can-now-auto-change.html</link>
      <description>Google has announced a new feature in its Chrome browser that enables automated password changes when compromised credentials are detected during sign-in. The feature aims to reduce friction and help users keep their accounts secure without requiring manual intervention. Website owners can support this feature by adopting specific methods, such as using well-known URLs for password change forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/google-chrome-can-now-auto-change.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in Palo Alto GlobalProtect Gateway &amp; Portal Enables Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-vulnerability-in-palo-alto-globalprotect-gateway-portal/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Palo Alto Networks; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0133; Summary: A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks' GlobalProtect gateway and portal features allows attackers to execute malicious JavaScript code in authenticated users' browsers, posing risks of phishing and credential theft, particularly for organizations using Clientless VPN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137308</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk Targets DNS Vulnerabilities to Hijack Cloud Resources and Spread Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hazy-hawk-targets-dns-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Sophisticated threat actor "Hazy Hawk" has been exploiting DNS misconfigurations since at least December 2023 to hijack abandoned cloud resources from high-profile organizations. The actor utilizes these hijacked subdomains to distribute scams and malware, leveraging the inherent trustworthiness of the compromised domains to evade security controls and achieve higher rankings in search results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerSchool hacker pleads guilty to student data extortion scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/powerschool-hacker-pleads-guilty-to-student-data-extortion-scheme/</link>
      <description>This article is about a cyberattack on PowerSchool that resulted in the theft of personal data for millions of students and teachers. The attacker, Matthew D. Lane, 19, has agreed to plead guilty to four federal charges related to the attack, including cyber extortion conspiracy, unauthorized access to protected computers, and aggravated identity theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/powerschool-hacker-pleads-guilty-to-student-data-extortion-scheme/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KrebsOnSecurity Hit With Near-Record 6.3 Tbps DDoS</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/krebsonsecurity-hit-with-near-record-6-3-tbps-ddos/</link>
      <description>A massive distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack of over 6.3 terabits per second was launched against KrebsOnSecurity, with the attacker believed to be testing a new Internet of Things (IoT) botnet capable of launching crippling digital assaults. The botnet, known as Aisuru, is reportedly controlled by a 21-year-old individual claiming to reside in Brazil who has been peddling access to their DDoS machine on public Telegram chat channels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71303</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile carrier Cellcom confirms cyberattack behind extended outages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-carrier-cellcom-confirms-cyberattack-behind-extended-outages/</link>
      <description>Cellcom, a Wisconsin wireless provider, has confirmed that a cyberattack is responsible for the widespread service outage and disruptions that began on May 14, 2025. The attack affected voice and SMS services, leaving customers unable to make phone calls or send text messages. Cellcom's CEO has assured that the company has protocols in place for such incidents and is working to restore full service by the end of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mobile-carrier-cellcom-confirms-cyberattack-behind-extended-outages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Premium WordPress 'Motors' theme vulnerable to admin takeover attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/premium-wordpress-motors-theme-vulnerable-to-admin-takeover-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: StylemixThemes Motors; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4322; Summary: The Motors WordPress theme contains a privilege escalation vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to hijack administrator accounts and take complete control of websites. This flaw affects all versions up to 5.6.67, and exploitation enables attackers to implant malware, exfiltrate sensitive data, or redirect visitors to dangerous sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/premium-wordpress-motors-theme-vulnerable-to-admin-takeover-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanHelsing ransomware builder leaked on hacking forum</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-leaked-on-hacking-forum/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VanHelsing RaaS; CVE(s): None; Summary: The source code for the VanHelsing ransomware-as-a-service operation's affiliate panel, data leak blog, and Windows encryptor builder was leaked after an old developer tried to sell it on the RAMP cybercrime forum. The leaked code includes the legitimate builder for the Windows encryptor and the source code for the affiliate panel and data leak site, but is incomplete as it does not include the Linux builder or any databases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vanhelsing-ransomware-builder-leaked-on-hacking-forum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s how Windows 11 aims to make the world safe in the post-quantum era</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/heres-how-windows-11-aims-to-make-the-world-safe-in-the-post-quantum-era/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the security concerns surrounding Post-Quantum Cryptography (PQC) algorithms, specifically the increased key sizes and potential errors introduced into software during the transition away from RSA and Elliptic Curve cryptography.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/heres-how-windows-11-aims-to-make-the-world-safe-in-the-post-quantum-era/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SK Telecom says malware breach lasted 3 years, impacted 27 million numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sk-telecom-says-malware-breach-lasted-3-years-impacted-27-million-numbers/</link>
      <description>SK Telecom suffered a malware attack that exposed USIM data of 27 million subscribers, including IMSI, USIM authentication keys, network usage data, and SMS/contacts stored in the SIM. The company detected the malware on April 19, 2025, and isolated equipment suspected of being hacked, but initially undetected for nearly three years from June 15, 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sk-telecom-says-malware-breach-lasted-3-years-impacted-27-million-numbers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk gang exploits DNS misconfigs to hijack trusted domains</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hazy-hawk-gang-exploits-dns-misconfigs-to-hijack-trusted-domains/</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as "Hazy Hawk" is hijacking forgotten DNS CNAME records pointing to abandoned cloud services, using the compromised domains to distribute scams, fake apps, and malicious ads. The attacker's technique involves registering a new cloud resource with the same name as the original one, causing the subdomain to resolve to their new site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hazy-hawk-gang-exploits-dns-misconfigs-to-hijack-trusted-domains/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazy Hawk Exploits DNS Records to Hijack CDC, Corporate Domains for Malware Delivery</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hazy-hawk-exploits-dns-records-to.html</link>
      <description>A threat actor known as Hazy Hawk has been observed hijacking abandoned cloud resources, including Amazon S3 buckets and Microsoft Azure endpoints, by leveraging misconfigurations in DNS records. The hijacked domains are used to host URLs that direct users to scams and malware via traffic distribution systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/hazy-hawk-exploits-dns-records-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimsuky APT Group Deploys PowerShell Payloads to Deliver XWorm RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/kimsuky-apt-group-deploys-powershell-payloads/</link>
      <description>This article describes a malware campaign orchestrated by the Kimsuky APT group, using PowerShell payloads to deliver the XWorm Remote Access Trojan (RAT). The campaign involves multi-stage attacks, fileless execution, and Living-off-the-Land Binaries and Scripts (LOLBAS) techniques to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137257</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100+ Fake Chrome Extensions Found Hijacking Sessions, Stealing Credentials, Injecting Ads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/100-fake-chrome-extensions-found.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Unknown threat actor; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes malicious Chrome Browser extensions created by an unknown threat actor since February 2024. These extensions masquerade as seemingly benign utilities but can exfiltrate data, receive commands, and execute arbitrary code. They also enable credential and cookie theft, session hijacking, ad injection, and phishing via DOM manipulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/100-fake-chrome-extensions-found.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More_Eggs Malware Uses Job Application Emails to Distribute Malicious Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/more_eggs-malware-uses-job-application-emails/</link>
      <description>The article describes the More_Eggs malware, a JavaScript backdoor that exploits human trust through social engineering. It targets HR departments by masquerading as job application emails and uses obfuscated scripts and legitimate system binaries to establish a foothold in targeted environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137245</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trojanized RVTools push Bumblebee malware in SEO poisoning campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trojanized-rvtools-push-bumblebee-malware-in-seo-poisoning-campaign/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RVTools; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official website for the RVTools VMware management tool was taken offline due to a supply chain attack that distributed trojanized installers disguising as Bumblebee malware loaders. The attackers used fake typo-squatted domains and SEO poisoning to promote the malicious installers, which attempted to execute a malicious version.dll that was detected as the Bumblebee malware loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/trojanized-rvtools-push-bumblebee-malware-in-seo-poisoning-campaign/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RVTools hit in supply chain attack to deliver Bumblebee malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rvtools-hit-in-supply-chain-attack-to-deliver-bumblebee-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Robware RVTools; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official website for the RVTools VMware management tool was taken offline due to a supply chain attack that distributed a trojanized installer, dropping the Bumblebee malware loader on users' machines. The malware is designed to download and execute additional payloads, including Cobalt Strike beacons, information stealers, and ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/rvtools-hit-in-supply-chain-attack-to-deliver-bumblebee-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedisRaider Campaign Targets Linux Servers by Exploiting Misconfigured Redis Instances</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/redisraider-campaign-targets-linux-servers/</link>
      <description>The RedisRaider campaign is a sophisticated Linux worm that targets publicly accessible Redis instances with misconfigured servers. It exploits vulnerabilities to deploy a customized XMRig miner and employs advanced obfuscation, anti-forensics measures, and manipulation of Redis configurations to evade detection. The malware also has a web-based mining component, revealing a broader monetization strategy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=137230</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service desks are under attack: What can you do about it?</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/service-desks-are-under-attack-what-can-you-do-about-it/</link>
      <description>The article discusses social engineering attacks on service desk agents, where attackers use tactics such as pretexting, vishing, and building urgency and trust to gain initial access. This is often followed by privilege escalation or deploying ransomware. The article highlights the importance of verifying identities and implementing rigorous identity checks to prevent these attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/service-desks-are-under-attack-what-can-you-do-about-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
