<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:05:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized PyPI Package Targets Developers to Steal Source Code</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/weaponized-pypi-package-targets-developers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI "solana-token" package; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "solana-token" Python package was discovered to be malicious, targeting developers working with the Solana blockchain. It exhibited characteristics of infostealer malware, including hardcoded URLs referencing command-and-control servers and file-reading behaviors. The primary objective is to steal hardcoded cryptographic secrets, such as private keys or access credentials to cryptocurrency wallets, making it a precursor to potentially devastating breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135544</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Alerts on AD CS Flaw Enabling Remote Denial-of-Service Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-alerts-on-ad-cs-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS); CVE(s): CVE-2025-29968; Summary: A newly identified vulnerability in AD CS allows authenticated attackers to disrupt critical certificate management operations over a network, enabling denial-of-service (DoS) attacks. The flaw stems from improper input validation and requires valid authentication credentials for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135539</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkCloud Stealer: Comprehensive Analysis of a New Attack Chain That Employs AutoIt</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/darkcloud-stealer-and-obfuscated-autoit-scripting/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the DarkCloud Stealer malware, which is a data-stealing malware that collects and exfiltrates sensitive information such as computer names, usernames, passwords, and credit card details. The malware uses multi-stage payloads and obfuscated AutoIt scripting to evade detection and establish command and control (C2) communications.

FYSA: Palo Alto Networks customers are better protected from DarkCloud Stealer through their Network Security solutions and Cortex line of products, including Advanced WildFire, Cortex XDR, and Cortex XSIAM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=140509</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Exploit SAP NetWeaver Zero-Day Vulnerability to Target Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-hackers-exploit-sap-netweaver-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324; Summary: The article describes a sophisticated cyber-espionage campaign targeting critical infrastructure worldwide, exploiting an unauthenticated file upload flaw in SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer. The vulnerability allows remote code execution (RCE), providing attackers with a gateway to compromise high-value networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135500</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Unveil New Threat-Hunting Techniques to Detect Azure Managed Identity Abuse</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-unveil-new-threat-hunting-techniques/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a research paper by Hunters' Team Axon that presents threat-hunting techniques to identify and prevent the misuse of Azure Managed Identities. The paper provides tools and strategies for detecting suspicious behaviors, tracing compromised identities, and assessing blast radii of permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135478</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows CLFS Zero-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-clfs-zero-day-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32701; Summary: The Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) Driver has two critical security vulnerabilities that allow local privilege escalation and have been confirmed to be actively exploited in the wild. The first vulnerability is due to improper input validation, while the second is a Use-After-Free condition. Both require local access, low attack complexity, and low privileges but can result in complete compromise of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135492</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Samsung MagicINFO 9 Server Flaw Allows Arbitrary File Writes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-samsung-magicinfo-9-server-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4632; Summary: The MagicINFO 9 Server platform has a critical path traversal vulnerability that allows unauthorized actors to write arbitrary files with system-level privileges. Attackers could exploit this flaw to bypass directory restrictions, create or overwrite critical system files, and potentially implant persistence mechanisms, manipulate firmware images, or disrupt entire digital signage networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135472</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Fixes 78 Flaws, 5 Zero-Days Exploited; CVSS 10 Bug Impacts Azure DevOps Server</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-fixes-78-flaws-5-zero-days.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709; Summary: Five zero-day vulnerabilities have been identified in Microsoft's software lineup, including the Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability (CVE-2025-30397), Microsoft Desktop Window Manager (DWM) Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-30400), Windows Common Log File System (CLFS) Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-32701 and CVE-2025-32706), and Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability (CVE-2025-32709). These vulnerabilities can lead to remote code execution, privilege escalation, and information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/microsoft-fixes-78-flaws-5-zero-days.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Ancillary for WinSock 0-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited to Gain Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-ancillary-for-winsock-0-day-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32709; Summary: The Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock contains a critical privilege escalation vulnerability that allows local attackers with basic user privileges to gain SYSTEM-level access. Attackers can exploit the use-after-free flaw by crafting specific IOCTL requests, enabling arbitrary code execution in kernel space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135423</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Ammit Hackers Deploy New Tools to Target Military Drones</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/earth-ammit-hackers-deploy-new-tools/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the threat actor group Earth Ammit, believed to be associated with Chinese-speaking APTs, which orchestrated two campaigns (VENOM and TIDRONE) targeting Taiwan and South Korea. The group exploited supply chain vulnerabilities, using open-source tools and custom-built malware to maintain persistence and evade attribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135447</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Microsoft Scripting Engine Vulnerability Exposes Systems to Remote Code Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-microsoft-scripting-engine-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Scripting Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397; Summary: A type confusion weakness (CWE-843) allows remote code execution (RCE) attacks over networks by manipulating the engine's memory processes. Attackers can craft malicious scripts that confuse the engine into interpreting memory addresses as executable code segments, enabling arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the current user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135408</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Microsoft Office Vulnerabilities Enable Malicious Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-microsoft-office-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Office; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30377, CVE-2025-30386, CVE-2025-26629; Summary: Three critical security flaws in Microsoft Office enable remote code execution via use-after-free memory corruption weaknesses. The most severe vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-30377 and CVE-2025-30386, can be exploited without user interaction, while the third vulnerability, CVE-2025-26629, requires user interaction to execute malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135397</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Windows RDP Vulnerability Enables Network-Based Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-windows-rdp-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop services; CVE(s): CVE-2025-29966, CVE-2025-29967; Summary: Two critical heap-based buffer overflow flaws affect the Windows Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) and Remote Desktop Gateway (RD Gateway) service, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems over a network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135387</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical 0-Day in Windows DWM Enables Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-0-day-in-windows-dwm/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Desktop Window Manager (DWM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-30400; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers with local access to elevate their privileges on affected systems through a use-after-free memory condition in the DWM component. This zero-day threat has been actively exploited despite no prior public disclosure, and its exploitation grants attackers full control over affected systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135379</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Patches CVE-2025-32756 Zero-Day RCE Flaw Exploited in FortiVoice Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fortinet-patches-cve-2025-32756-zero.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A critical security flaw (CVE-2025-32756) in FortiVoice, FortiMail, FortiNDR, FortiRecorder, and FortiCamera allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands via crafted HTTP requests. The vulnerability has been exploited in the wild, with threat actors performing device network scans, erasing system crash logs, and enabling fcgi debugging to log credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/fortinet-patches-cve-2025-32756-zero.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Patches EPMM Vulnerabilities Exploited for Remote Code Execution in Limited Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ivanti-patches-epmm-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Ivanti EPMM software contains two security flaws that can be chained together to gain remote code execution. The vulnerabilities allow attackers to access protected resources without proper credentials and execute arbitrary code on the target system. Affected versions include 11.12.0.4 and prior, 12.3.0.1 and prior, 12.4.0.1 and prior, and 12.5.0.0 and prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ivanti-patches-epmm-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-288: Fortinet FortiWeb cgi_httpcontentrouting_post Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-288/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25254; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fortinet FortiWeb, requiring authentication to exploit. It occurs in the cgi_httpcontentrouting_post function due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied paths prior to file operations, enabling an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25181</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-289: Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-289/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation ThinManager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3618; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Rockwell Automation ThinManager. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the ThinServer component due to a null pointer dereference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25872</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-290: Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-290/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation ThinManager; CVE(s): CVE-2025-3617; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Rockwell Automation ThinManager by creating a symbolic link within the ThinServer component. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to delete arbitrary files and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25727</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAP patches second zero-day flaw exploited in recent attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sap-patches-second-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-recent-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: The article discusses a zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-42999) exploited in recent attacks targeting SAP NetWeaver servers. The flaw was discovered while investigating another unauthenticated file upload vulnerability (CVE-2025-31324) fixed in April. Threat actors were chaining both vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary commands remotely without privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sap-patches-second-zero-day-flaw-exploited-in-recent-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday for May 2025 — Snort rules and prominent vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-for-may-2025-snort-rules-and-prominent-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397, CVE-2025-32709, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706; Summary: A remote code execution vulnerability in the Microsoft Scripting Engine (CVE-2025-30397) and four elevation of privilege vulnerabilities affecting various Microsoft products have been observed to be exploited in the wild. The 11 "critical" entries include RCE, elevation of privilege, information disclosure, and spoofing vulnerabilities with varying levels of exploit likelihood.

FYSA: Talos has released a new Snort rule set to detect attempts to exploit some of these vulnerabilities, and Cisco Security Firewall customers should update their ruleset accordingly. Open-source Snort Subscriber Rule Set customers can stay up-to-date by downloading the latest rule pack from Snort.org.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6823abc72858e80001b10def</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google introduces Advanced Protection mode for its most at-risk Android users</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/google-introduces-advanced-protection-mode-for-its-most-at-risk-android-users/</link>
      <description>Android's Advanced Protection features aim to enhance phone security by disabling or restricting features that can be exploited by hackers, such as connecting to insecure Wi-Fi networks, using JavaScript protections, and automatically locking or powering down devices. This defense-in-depth approach reduces the "surface area" of potential attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/google-introduces-advanced-protection-mode-for-its-most-at-risk-android-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea ramps up cyberspying in Ukraine to assess war risk</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korea-ramps-up-cyberspying-in-ukraine-to-assess-war-risk/</link>
      <description>North Korean state-backed threat group Konni (Opal Sleet, TA406) targets Ukrainian government entities with phishing emails impersonating think tanks, likely to gather intelligence and support the DPRK's military involvement alongside Russia in Ukraine. The attackers use freemail services and embedded PowerShell to capture reconnaissance info and establish persistence, with a believed-to-be malware/backdoor payload facilitating espionage operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/north-korea-ramps-up-cyberspying-in-ukraine-to-assess-war-risk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-287: JetBrains TeamCity Diagnostics Data Directory Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-287/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: JetBrains TeamCity; CVE(s): CVE-2025-46618; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary script on affected installations of JetBrains TeamCity. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which exists in the handling of filenames in the diagnostics functionality due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25977</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio denies breach following leak of alleged Steam 2FA codes</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/twilio-denies-breach-following-leak-of-alleged-steam-2fa-codes/</link>
      <description>A threat actor claims to have accessed over 89 million Steam user records with one-time access codes, allegedly obtained from Twilio's SMS system. The authenticity of the data and the source of the breach are unclear, but experts suggest a possible supply-chain compromise involving Twilio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/twilio-denies-breach-following-leak-of-alleged-steam-2fa-codes/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-285: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer SLDPRT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-285/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1884; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer by parsing SLDPRT files. User interaction is required, and the attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26029</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-286: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer OBJ File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-286/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-1883; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations by exploiting an out-of-bounds write in the parsing of OBJ files. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26017</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday May 2025 Released With the Fixes for 72 Flaws With 5 Actively Exploited 0-Day</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30397, CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709; Summary: Microsoft has released May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates addressing 72 security vulnerabilities, including 5 zero-day vulnerabilities actively exploited in the wild. The flaws include Remote Code Execution, Elevation of Privilege, Information Disclosure, Denial of Service, and Security Feature Bypass, with Windows components being heavily targeted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135368</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti fixes EPMM zero-days chained in code execution attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-fixes-epmm-zero-days-chained-in-code-execution-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: Ivanti EPMM has two security vulnerabilities chained together to gain remote code execution. The first is an authentication bypass in the API component, allowing attackers to access protected resources on vulnerable devices. The second is a remote code execution vulnerability that allows threat actors to execute arbitrary code on targeted systems via maliciously crafted API requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-fixes-epmm-zero-days-chained-in-code-execution-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft May 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes 5 exploited zero-days, 72 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-5-exploited-zero-days-72-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30400, CVE-2025-32701, CVE-2025-32706, CVE-2025-32709, CVE-2025-30397; Summary: Microsoft fixed five actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities and 67 other flaws in its May 2025 Patch Tuesday updates. The vulnerable products include Windows DWM Core Library, Windows Common Log File System Driver, Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock, and Microsoft Scripting Engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-may-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-5-exploited-zero-days-72-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Released Security Updates to Fix for the Mutiple RCE Vulnerabilities – Patch Now</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-released-security-updates-for-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428, CVE-2025-22462, CVE-2025-22460 (None); Summary: Ivanti released critical security updates to address vulnerabilities in Endpoint Manager Mobile, Neurons for ITSM, Cloud Services Application, and Neurons for MDM. The vulnerabilities could allow attackers to execute remote code, gain administrative access, escalate privileges, or edit unauthorized resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135337</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5058411 and KB5058405 cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058411-and-kb5058405-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various updates and features in Windows 11, including improved search functionality, new widgets on Lock experience, and pivot-based curated views on File Explorer Home. It also mentions the availability of Windows 11 24H2 for everyone and resolves issues with Roblox on ARM PCs, but does not discuss any specific vulnerabilities or cybersecurity threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5058411-and-kb5058405-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android 16 expands 'Advanced Protection' with device-level security</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-16-expands-advanced-protection-with-device-level-security/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Android; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the improvements to the Advanced Protection feature in Android 16, which strengthens defenses against sophisticated spyware attacks. This includes device-level security hardening, verified boot and runtime integrity checks, strong sandboxing, USB port lockdown, app isolation, and other features that prevent disabling or weakening of individual security settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/android-16-expands-advanced-protection-with-device-level-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058379 update fixes SgrmBroker errors in Event Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-fixes-sgrmbroker-errors-in-event-viewer/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5058379 cumulative update includes four changes and fixes, including one for an SGRMBroker bug, seven zero-day vulnerabilities, and updates to the Windows Kernel Vulnerable Driver Blocklist. One known issue is fixed, which may cause Windows updates to fail if Citrix Session Recording Agent (SRA) version 2411 is installed on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5058379-update-fixes-sgrmbroker-errors-in-event-viewer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet FortiVoice Zero-day Vulnerability Actively Exploited in The Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortinet-fortivoice-o-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CWE-121; Summary: A critical stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability (CWE-121) was discovered in multiple Fortinet products, including FortiVoice, FortiMail, FortiNDR, FortiRecorder, and FortiCamera. The vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands remotely through specially crafted HTTP requests, posing a significant threat to affected organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135352</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet fixes critical zero-day exploited in FortiVoice attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fortinet-fixes-critical-zero-day-exploited-in-fortivoice-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32756; Summary: A critical remote code execution vulnerability (CVE-2025-32756) was exploited as a zero-day in attacks targeting FortiVoice enterprise phone systems, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code or commands via maliciously crafted HTTP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fortinet-fixes-critical-zero-day-exploited-in-fortivoice-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Attacks Surge by 123% Amid Evolving Tactics and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ransomware-attacks-surge-by-123-amid/</link>
      <description>The article reports a surge in ransomware attacks through third-party vendor ecosystems, driven by exploitation of weak links in vendor networks. The report highlights the importance of robust third-party risk management (TPRM) practices to mitigate risks and provide actionable strategies for organizations to fortify their defenses against these advanced persistent threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135327</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Introduce Mythic Framework Agent to Enhance Pentesting Tool Performance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-introduce-mythic-framework-agent/</link>
      <description>The article discusses advancements in penetration testing tools with the introduction of a new agent for the Mythic framework. The agent enhances detection evasion and operational efficiency by integrating sophisticated evasion techniques and modularity. It allows security experts to conduct operations with reduced risk of detection, making it a valuable tool for ethical hackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135308</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swan Vector APT Targets Organizations with Malicious LNK and DLL Implants</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/swan-vector-apt-targets-organizations/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a newly identified advanced persistent threat (APT) campaign called "Swan Vector" that targets educational institutions and mechanical engineering industries in East Asia. The campaign uses social engineering tactics, spearphishing attachments, and a multi-stage infection chain to evade detection and establish persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135275</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Weaponize KeePass Password Manager to Spread Malware and Steal Passwords</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-weaponize-keepass-password-manager-to-spread-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: KeePass; CVE(s): None; Summary: Threat actors successfully exploited KeePass to spread malware and facilitate large-scale password theft by modifying and re-signing installers with trusted certificates. The attack involved a custom malware loader dubbed KeeLoader, which modified executable files to incorporate malicious functionality, exfiltrate user credentials, and set up an autorun registry key for persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135295</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti warns of critical Neurons for ITSM auth bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Neurons for ITSM; CVE(s): CVE-2025-22462, CVE-2025-22460; Summary: The vulnerability (CVE-2025-22462) is a critical authentication bypass vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to gain administrative access to unpatched systems in low-complexity attacks. Ivanti also patched a default credentials security flaw (CVE-2025-22460) in its Cloud Services Appliance (CSA) that can let local authenticated attackers escalate privileges on vulnerable systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ivanti-warns-of-critical-neurons-for-itsm-auth-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Linked APTs Exploit SAP CVE-2025-31324 to Breach 581 Critical Systems Worldwide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SAP NetWeaver; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31324, CVE-2025-42999; Summary: A critical security flaw in SAP NetWeaver is being exploited by multiple China-nexus nation-state actors to target critical infrastructure networks. The vulnerability allows for remote code execution and has been used to deploy web shells, reverse shells, and backdoors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/china-linked-apts-exploit-sap-cve-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Intel CPU flaws leak sensitive data from privileged memory</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Intel CPUs; CVE(s): CVE-2024-45332; Summary: A "Branch Privilege Injection" flaw in modern Intel CPUs allows attackers to leak sensitive data from memory regions allocated to privileged software. The vulnerability, tracked under CVE-2024-45332, is a race condition on the branch predictor subsystem and affects all Intel CPUs from the 9th generation onward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-intel-cpu-flaws-leak-sensitive-data-from-privileged-memory/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious PyPI Package Posing as Solana Tool Stole Source Code in 761 Downloads</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PyPI; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Python Package Index (PyPI) repository had a malicious package named solana-token that was designed to steal source code and developer secrets. When installed, it attempts to exfiltrate data from the developer's machine to a hard-coded IP address, suggesting a target on developers creating their own blockchains.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/malicious-pypi-package-posing-as-solana.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft will update Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has extended its support for Office apps on Windows 10 until 2028, allowing users to continue receiving security updates and using the applications without having to upgrade to Windows 11 immediately. The decision comes as many users are reluctant to switch due to requirements such as TPM 2.0 support. The company will also provide updates beyond October 2025 for Long-Term Servicing Channel (LTSC) and Long-Term Servicing Branch (LTSB) releases, catering to specialized devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-will-update-office-apps-on-windows-10-until-2028/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increase Red Team Operations 10X with Adversarial Exposure Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the limitations of traditional red team engagements in identifying critical security gaps and proposes an alternative approach called Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV). AEV combines Breach and Attack Simulation (BAS) and Automated Penetration Testing to provide continuous, scalable, and automated offensive testing. This approach allows for repeatable and on-demand testing, enabling faster remediation, continuous benchmarking, and the agility to respond to new threats without waiting for the next audit or assessment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/increase-red-team-operations-10x-with-adversarial-exposure-validation/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks &amp; Spencer Confirms Customer Data Breach in Recent Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/marks-spencer-confirms-customer-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A cyber attack against Marks &amp; Spencer (M&amp;S) has compromised customer personal data, including names, dates of birth, telephone numbers, home addresses, and online order histories. The attackers used a "double extortion" method, exfiltrating sensitive data and encrypting company systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135277</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;S says customer data stolen in cyberattack, forces password resets</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</link>
      <description>Marks and Spencer (M&amp;S) confirmed a cyberattack occurred on April 22, 2025, involving DragonForce ransomware affiliates using the Scattered Spider social engineering tactic. The attackers stole sensitive customer information, including full names, email addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, dates of birth, online order history, household information, and "masked" payment card details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mands-says-customer-data-stolen-in-cyberattack-forces-password-resets/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Workplace Apps Flaws Allow Hackers to Gain Elevated Access</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/zoom-workplace-apps-flaws-allow-hackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Zoom Workplace Apps; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30663, CVE-2025-30664, CVE-2025-30665, CVE-2025-30666, CVE-2025-46785; Summary: The Zoom Workplace Apps contain seven newly discovered vulnerabilities, including a high-severity Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) vulnerability that could lead to privilege escalation when exploited successfully. The vulnerabilities include improper neutralization of special elements, NULL pointer dereference, and buffer over-read flaws, which could potentially allow attackers to execute arbitrary code, elevate privileges, or cause denial of service conditions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135248</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoC Exploit Published for macOS Sandbox Escape Vulnerability (CVE-2025-31258)</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/macos-sandbox-escape-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-31258; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-31258, is a sandbox escape flaw that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code outside application sandbox constraints. It affects macOS Ventura 13.4 through Sonoma 14.2 and can be exploited by launching a malicious app, which could grant read/write access to protected directories like ~/Library and limited command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=135083</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
