<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: What the Next Wave of AI Cyberattacks Will Look Like — And How to Survive</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-what-next-wave-of-ai.html</link>
      <description>Attackers are evolving with AI, gaining new tools such as deepfake scams, bots that bypass human review, and synthetic identities. The fight is no longer just at the network's edge, but also at the login screen. Legacy security models can't keep up with AI-powered threats, making identity the last line of defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-what-next-wave-of-ai.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft August 2025 Patch Tuesday Fixes Kerberos Zero-Day Among 111 Total New Flaws</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-august-2025-patch-tuesday.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53779 (CVSS score: 7.2), CVE-2025-53766 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-50165 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-53792 (CVSS score: 9.1), CVE-2025-53787 (CVSS score: 8.2), CVE-2025-50177 (CVSS score: 8.1), CVE-2025-50176 (CVSS score: 7.8); Summary: A publicly disclosed zero-day privilege escalation vulnerability in Windows Kerberos allows an attacker to compromise an Active Directory domain by misusing delegated Managed Service Account objects, requiring pre-existing control of two attributes of the dMSA; other vulnerabilities include remote code execution and information disclosure defects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-august-2025-patch-tuesday.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Charon Ransomware Uses DLL Sideloading and Anti-EDR Tactics in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-charon-ransomware-uses-dll-sideloading-and-anti-edr-tactics/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a novel ransomware family called Charon, deployed in a sophisticated campaign targeting the public sector and aviation industry in the Middle East. The malware employs advanced persistent threat (APT)-style techniques, including DLL sideloading, process injection, and multilayered payloads to evade endpoint security and encrypt files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156260</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious npm Package Lures Job Seekers and Exfiltrates Sensitive Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/malicious-npm-package-lures-job-seekers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: EvaCodes-Community/UltraX; CVE(s): None; Summary: The EvaCodes-Community/UltraX GitHub repository contains a malicious Trojanized npm package, rtk-logger@1.11.5, which steals sensitive data such as login credentials, encryption keys, and certificates from browsers like Chrome, Brave, Opera, and Firefox. The package also executes additional payloads, including remote command execution, environment detection, and logging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156248</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Security Update Fixes High-Severity Flaws Allowing Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chrome-security-update-fixes-high-severity-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8879, CVE-2025-8880, CVE-2025-8901; Summary: The update addresses six security vulnerabilities, including three high-severity flaws that could allow arbitrary code execution. The most critical vulnerability is a heap buffer overflow in the media codec library, while another vulnerability is a race condition in the V8 JavaScript engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156243</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charon Ransomware Hits Middle East Sectors Using APT-Level Evasion Tactics</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/charon-ransomware-hits-middle-east.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on a new ransomware family called Charon that targets the Middle East's public sector and aviation industry. The threat actor uses DLL side-loading, process injection, and evasion techniques to avoid detection by endpoint detection and response (EDR) software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/charon-ransomware-hits-middle-east.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FortiWeb Authentication Bypass Vulnerability Allows Logins as Any Existing User</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fortiweb-authentication-bypass-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52970; Summary: A critical vulnerability in FortiWeb's cookie parsing mechanism allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and impersonate any existing user, exploiting an out-of-bounds read access issue to force the server to use a predictable, all-zero secret key for session encryption and signing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156239</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical FortiSIEM Vulnerability Allows Attackers to Execute Malicious Commands, PoC Found in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-fortisiem-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25256; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Fortinet's FortiSIEM platform allows remote attackers to execute unauthorized commands without authentication, with a maximum CVSS score of 9.8 and practical exploit code circulating in the wild. The flaw enables OS command injection, granting attackers control over the SIEM infrastructure, potentially allowing manipulation of security logs or disabling monitoring capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156235</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zero-Click NTLM Credential Leak Exploit Bypasses Microsoft Patch for CVE-2025-24054</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-zero-click-ntlm-credential-leak-exploit/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50154; Summary: A zero-click NTLM credential leakage vulnerability allows attackers to extract NTLMv2-SSP hashes without user interaction on fully patched Windows systems. The exploit bypasses Microsoft's previous patch for CVE-2025-24054 by manipulating Windows shortcut files and exploiting how the explorer.exe process handles remote binary retrieval, posing risks for organizations relying solely on Microsoft's previous patch for protection against NTLM credential leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156229</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams RCE Flaw Allows Hackers to Read, Modify, and Delete Messages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Teams; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53783; Summary: A critical remote code execution vulnerability in Microsoft Teams allows attackers to execute malicious code and potentially access, modify, or delete user messages. The vulnerability requires no special privileges but necessitates user interaction, making exploitation less likely due to high attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156225</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday, August 2025 Edition</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/08/microsoft-patch-tuesday-august-2025-edition/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53786, CVE-2025-53779, CVE-2025-53766, CVE-2025-50165, CVE-2025-53733, CVE-2025-53778; Summary: Multiple critical vulnerabilities in Windows operating systems and software were fixed by Microsoft, including a vulnerability that allows an attacker to pivot from a compromised Exchange Server into an organization's cloud environment (CVE-2025-53786), a weakness in the Windows Kerberos authentication system that grants domain administrator privileges (CVE-2025-53779), and remote code execution bugs in the Windows GDI+ component and Microsoft Word.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71899</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude gets 1M tokens support via API to take on Gemini 2.5 Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-gets-1m-tokens-support-via-api-to-take-on-gemini-25-pro/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather an upgrade to the Claude Sonnet 4 API, which now supports remembering up to 1 million tokens of context. The increased limit enables users to build better apps and analyze more data at once.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/claude-gets-1m-tokens-support-via-api-to-take-on-gemini-25-pro/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers leak Allianz Life data stolen in Salesforce attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-leak-allianz-life-data-stolen-in-salesforce-attacks/</link>
      <description>The ShinyHunters extortion group has released stolen data belonging to US insurance giant Allianz Life, exposing 2.8 million records with sensitive information on business partners and customers. The attack is part of a wave of Salesforce-targeted thefts carried out by the group, which has also claimed responsibility for attacks on Internet Archive, Pearson, Coinbase, and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-leak-allianz-life-data-stolen-in-salesforce-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 22:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI rolls out Gmail, Calendar, and Contacts integration in ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-rolls-out-gmail-calendar-and-contacts-integration-in-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is not about a vulnerability. It discusses OpenAI's plans to integrate Google services (Gmail, Google Calendar, and Google Contacts) with ChatGPT, allowing users to access information from these tools in their conversations. The integration aims to enhance the chat experience by providing faster and easier access to relevant information.

Note: There is no mention of a vulnerability or a cybersecurity-related issue in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-rolls-out-gmail-calendar-and-contacts-integration-in-chatgpt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT's new subscription costs less than $5, but it's not for everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-new-subscription-costs-less-than-5-but-its-not-for-everyone/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article discusses OpenAI's introduction of a new pricing plan called "ChatGPT Go" aimed at developing countries, including India. It also mentions Google exploring a similar low-tier subscription for Gemini, likely limited to certain regions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-new-subscription-costs-less-than-5-but-its-not-for-everyone/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddled Libra’s Strike Teams: Amalgamated Evil</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/muddled-libras-strike-teams/</link>
      <description>Muddled Libra is a loose collaboration of cybercriminals with common interests, not an organized entity; the group's fluid nature makes it challenging to track and predict targets; defenders should focus on protecting valuable data and assets rather than predicting specific industries or tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=150936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 21:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malvertising campaign leads to PS1Bot, a multi-stage malware framework</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/ps1bot-malvertising-campaign/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article describes an in-depth analysis of a malware campaign that utilizes PowerShell modules to deliver malicious payloads to infected systems. The malware family, referred to as PS1Bot, demonstrates various techniques to evade detection and maintain persistence on the compromised system.

Key findings from the analysis include:

1. The use of PowerShell as a primary vector for delivering malicious payloads.
2. The implementation of multiple modules with distinct functionalities, such as screen capture, keylogging, clipboard capture, and system surveying.
3. The employment of runtime compilation to create and execute PowerShell scripts.
4. The use of mutex handling and sleep periods to evade detection by security products.
5. The similarity in design architecture and functionality between PS1Bot and another malware family, AHK Bot.

To detect and block this threat, the article recommends utilizing various Cisco Secure products, including:

* Cisco Secure Endpoint (formerly AMP for Endpoints)
* Cisco Secure Email (formerly Cisco Email Security)
* Cisco Secure Firewall (former Next-Generation Firewall and Firepower NGFW) appliances
* Cisco Secure Network/Cloud Analytics (Stealthwatch/Stealthwatch Cloud)
* Cisco Secure Malware Analytics (Threat Grid)
* Cisco Secure Access
* Umbrella, Cisco's secure internet gateway (SIG)

Additionally, the article provides Snort SIDs for the threats and ClamAV detections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689b3b59e2d85f00011b7e3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday for August 2025 — Snort rules and prominent vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-august-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50176, CVE-2025-50177, CVE-2025-53778, CVE-2025-53781, CVE-2025-53733, CVE-2025-53740, CVE-2025-53766, CVE-2025-50165, CVE-2025-49707, CVE-2025-48807, CVE-2025-53731, CVE-2025-53784, CVE-2025-53793; Summary: Microsoft has released a security update with 111 vulnerabilities affecting various products, including Windows services and applications. The vulnerabilities include remote code execution (RCE), elevation of privilege, and information disclosure vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689afbcbe2d85f00011b7e2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law Enforcement Seizes BlackSuit Ransomware Servers Targeting U.S. Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/law-enforcement-seizes-blacksuit-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The U.S. Department of Justice and international law enforcement agencies collaborated to seize critical infrastructure associated with the BlackSuit ransomware group, including command-and-control servers and domains used for deploying ransomware payloads, extorting victims, and laundering illicit proceeds. The operation targeted the group's backend infrastructure, which enabled initial access via phishing campaigns, RDP exploitation, and vulnerability chaining, as well as data exfiltration prior to encryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156170</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub still hosts dozens of Linux images with the XZ backdoor</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/docker-hub-still-hosts-dozens-of-linux-images-with-the-xz-backdoor/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Linux distributions (Debian, Fedora, OpenSUSE, and Red Hat); CVE(s): CVE-2024-3094; Summary: The XZ-Utils backdoor, discovered in March 2024, was malicious code hidden in the liblzma.so library of the xz-utils compression tool, versions 5.6.0 and 5.6.1. It allowed attackers to bypass authentication and remotely run commands as root via SSH. Despite being reported earlier, at least 35 Linux images on Docker Hub still contain the backdoor, making users and organizations vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/docker-hub-still-hosts-dozens-of-linux-images-with-the-xz-backdoor/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Spot XZ Utils Backdoor in Dozens of Docker Hub Images, Fueling Supply Chain Risks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-spot-xz-utils-backdoor-in.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: XZ Utils; CVE(s): CVE-2024-3094; Summary: The XZ Utils backdoor allows unauthorized remote access and execution of arbitrary payloads through SSH. It was discovered in versions 5.6.0 and 5.6.1, and can be triggered when a client interacts with the infected SSH server. The backdoor uses glibc's IFUNC mechanism to bypass authentication and execute root commands remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-spot-xz-utils-backdoor-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Arts Blocks 300,000 Cheating Attempts After Battlefield 6 Beta Launch</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/electronic-arts-blocks-300000-cheating-attempts/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the success of Electronic Arts' Javelin anti-cheat technology in preventing over 330,000 attempts to cheat or tamper with security controls during the Battlefield 6 Open Beta Early Access launch. The technology uses Secure Boot to ensure the integrity of the operating system and loaded drivers, detecting potential integrity breaches and enabling automated bans or further forensic analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156158</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Patch Tuesday August 2025: 107 Vulnerabilities Patched, Including 35 RCE Flaws</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-patch-tuesday-august-2025/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-50165, CVE-2025-53766, CVE-2025-53781, CVE-2025-48807, etc. (107 total); Summary: Microsoft has released August 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes addressing 107 vulnerabilities across its ecosystem, including 35 remote code execution bugs that could allow attackers to run malicious code on affected systems. The patches cover a range of products and services, including Windows, Office, Exchange Server, Azure, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=156211</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft August 2025 Patch Tuesday fixes one zero-day, 107 flaws</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-august-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-one-zero-day-107-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Kerberos; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5377; Summary: A publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerability in Windows Kerberos allows an authenticated attacker to gain domain administrator privileges by exploiting a relative path traversal flaw. The vulnerability requires elevated access to specific dMSA attributes, making it a complex attack vector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-august-2025-patch-tuesday-fixes-one-zero-day-107-flaws/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 KB5063878 &amp; KB5063875 cumulative updates released</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5063878-and-kb5063875-cumulative-updates-released/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather an announcement from Microsoft regarding cumulative updates and new features in Windows 11. It describes various improvements, including AI-powered features, a more streamlined interface for unexpected restarts, and bug fixes for File Explorer, Start menu, and Notifications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-kb5063878-and-kb5063875-cumulative-updates-released/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5063709 update fixes extended security updates enrollment</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5063709-update-fixes-extended-security-updates-enrollment/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the release of the KB5063709 cumulative update for Windows 10 22H2 and Windows 10 21H2, which includes seven fixes or changes, including a fix for a bug that prevented enrollment in extended security updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-10-kb5063709-update-fixes-extended-security-updates-enrollment/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet SSL VPNs Hit by Global Brute-Force Wave Before Attackers Shift to FortiManager</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fortinet-ssl-vpns-hit-by-global-brute.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet; CVE(s): None; Summary: Brute-force traffic aimed at Fortinet SSL VPN devices has been observed, with over 780 unique IP addresses participating in the effort. The targets include the United States, Hong Kong, Brazil, Spain, and Japan. The activity suggests deliberate and precise targeting of Fortinet's SSL VPNs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fortinet-ssl-vpns-hit-by-global-brute.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercrime Groups ShinyHunters, Scattered Spider Join Forces in Extortion Attacks on Businesses</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cybercrime-groups-shinyhunters.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses an ongoing data extortion campaign targeting Salesforce customers, attributed to ShinyHunters and Scattered Spider. The two groups appear to be working together, using tactics such as vishing and social engineering attacks. The campaign is targeting major corporations and financial services companies globally, with a focus on high-profile companies across various industry verticals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cybercrime-groups-shinyhunters.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US govt seizes $1 million in crypto from BlackSuit ransomware gang</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-seizes-1-million-in-crypto-from-blacksuit-ransomware-gang/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather reports on law enforcement efforts to combat ransomware attacks. The U.S. Department of Justice and other agencies seized cryptocurrency and digital assets worth $1,091,453 from the BlackSuit ransomware gang and $2.4 million from a Chaos ransomware group member, highlighting the importance of disrupting cybercriminals' financial infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-govt-seizes-1-million-in-crypto-from-blacksuit-ransomware-gang/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android's pKVM hypervisor earns SESIP Level 5 security certification</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/androids-pkvm-hypervisor-earns-sesip-level-5-security-certification/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Google's protected Kernel-based Virtual Machine (pKVM) for Android achieving SESIP Level 5 certification, the highest security assurance level for IoT and mobile platforms. The pKVM provides an isolated environment for executing critical workloads, including AI models and biometric authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/androids-pkvm-hypervisor-earns-sesip-level-5-security-certification/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curly COMrades cyberspies hit govt orgs with custom malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/curly-comrades-cyberspies-hit-govt-orgs-with-custom-malware/</link>
      <description>The article describes a new cyber-espionage threat group, tracked as Curly COMrades, which uses a custom backdoor malware called MucorAgent. The malware provides persistent access through seemingly inactive scheduled tasks and has been used to target government and judicial bodies in Georgia, energy firms in Moldova, and other organizations that support Russian interests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/curly-comrades-cyberspies-hit-govt-orgs-with-custom-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 3,000 NetScaler devices left unpatched against CitrixBleed 2 bug</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-3-000-netscaler-devices-left-unpatched-against-actively-exploited-citrixbleed-2-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777, CVE-2025-6543; Summary: Over 3,300 unpatched Citrix NetScaler devices remain vulnerable to a critical vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication and access sensitive data. The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-5777, can be exploited to steal session tokens, credentials, and other sensitive data. Additionally, the same devices are also vulnerable to another critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-6543, which has been actively exploited in denial-of-service attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-3-000-netscaler-devices-left-unpatched-against-actively-exploited-citrixbleed-2-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>275M patient records breached—How to meet HIPAA password manager requirements</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/275m-patient-records-breached-how-to-meet-hipaa-password-manager-requirements/</link>
      <description>The article highlights the importance of password management in healthcare, citing that over 700 data breach incidents occurred in the sector in 2024, exposing over 275 million patient records. It emphasizes that compromised credentials are a primary attack vector and notes that HIPAA violations can result in significant penalties, reputational damage, and permanent listing on OCR's "Wall of Shame" breach portal. The article also stresses the need for healthcare organizations to prioritize password management as a critical component of both compliance and patient safety.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/275m-patient-records-breached-how-to-meet-hipaa-password-manager-requirements/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 11 23H2 Home and Pro reach end of support in November</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-23h2-home-and-pro-reach-end-of-support-in-november/</link>
      <description>The article announces the end-of-service date for certain versions of Windows 11, including Home and Pro editions. It also notes the increasing adoption rate of Windows 11, surpassing Windows 10's install base. Additionally, it mentions a trend in password cracking, with nearly half of environments having passwords cracked in July 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-11-23h2-home-and-pro-reach-end-of-support-in-november/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ‘Curly COMrades’ APT Using NGEN COM Hijacking in Georgia, Moldova Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-curly-comrades-apt-using-ngen-com.html</link>
      <description>Curly COMrades is a previously undocumented threat actor that targets entities in Georgia and Moldova with a cyber espionage campaign to facilitate long-term access to target networks. The group uses legitimate tools, such as Resocks, SSH, and Stunnel, to create multiple conduits into internal networks and steal credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-curly-comrades-apt-using-ngen-com.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-224-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54923, CVE-2025-54924, CVE-2025-54925, CVE-2025-54926, and CVE-2025-54927; Summary: The Schneider Electric EcoStruxure Power Monitoring Expert contains multiple vulnerabilities including path traversal, deserialization of untrusted data, and server-side request forgery. Successful exploitation could allow a remote attacker to read arbitrary files, access internal services directly, or execute malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23754</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, Cobalt Share</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-224-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ashlar-Vellum (Cobalt, Xenon, Argon, Lithium, Cobalt Share); CVE(s): CVE-2025-53705, CVE-2025-41392, CVE-2025-52584, CVE-2025-46269; Summary: The affected applications lack proper validation of user-supplied data when parsing CO, AR, XE, and VC6 files, leading to out-of-bounds write, out-of-bounds read, and heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to disclose information and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23752</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Three Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/12/cisa-adds-three-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Internet Explorer, Microsoft Office Excel, RARLAB WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2013-3893, CVE-2007-0671, CVE-2025-8088; Summary: These three vulnerabilities have been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to evidence of active exploitation. The vulnerabilities are frequent attack vectors for malicious cyber actors and pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and other organizations that fail to remediate them in a timely manner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23758</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVEVA PI Integrator</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-224-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: AVEVA PI Integrator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54460, CVE-2025-41415; Summary: Unrestricted file upload and insertion of sensitive information into sent data vulnerabilities in PI Integrator for Business Analytics versions 2020 R2 SP1 and prior allow authenticated attackers to disclose sensitive information or execute files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23755</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santesoft Sante PACS Server</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-224-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Santesoft, Sante PACS Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0572, CVE-2025-53948, CVE-2025-54156, CVE-2025-54862, CVE-2025-54759; Summary: The Sante PACS Server is vulnerable to path traversal, double free, cleartext transmission of sensitive information, and cross-site scripting. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to create arbitrary files, cause a denial-of-service condition, obtain sensitive information, and steal a user's cookie information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23756</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson Controls iSTAR Ultra, iSTAR Ultra SE, iSTAR Ultra G2, iSTAR Ultra G2 SE, iSTAR Edge G2</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-224-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Johnson Controls iSTAR Ultra, iSTAR Ultra SE, iSTAR Ultra G2, iSTAR Ultra G2 SE, iSTAR Edge G2; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53695, CVE-2025-53696, CVE-2025-53697, CVE-2025-53698, CVE-2025-53699, CVE-2025-53700; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities were discovered in Johnson Controls iSTAR Ultra and Edge door controllers, including OS command injection, insufficient verification of data authenticity, use of default credentials, missing protection mechanism for alternate hardware interface, and insecure storage of sensitive information. Successful exploitation may allow an attacker to modify firmware and access protected space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23753</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Seven Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/12/cisa-releases-seven-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released seven Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 12, 2025. These advisories provide information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS products from various vendors, including Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt, Johnson Controls, Schneider Electric, AVEVA, MegaSys Computer Technologies, and Santesoft. The advisories aim to help users and administrators review technical details and mitigations for the identified issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23757</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Battle: Enterprise Browsers vs. Secure Browser Extensions</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/the-ultimate-battle-enterprise-browsers.html</link>
      <description>The article compares two approaches to addressing security gaps in browsers: Enterprise Browsers and Enterprise Browser Extensions. It highlights the pros and cons of each, including control, enforcement, integration, and operations. The guide is designed to help security teams make an informed decision about which approach best fits their environment and risk profile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/the-ultimate-battle-enterprise-browsers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch NCSC Confirms Active Exploitation of Citrix NetScaler CVE-2025-6543 in Critical Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/dutch-ncsc-confirms-active-exploitation.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6543; Summary: A critical security vulnerability (CVE-2025-6543) in Citrix NetScaler ADC products allows for unintended control flow and denial-of-service when devices are configured as a Gateway or AAA virtual server. The vulnerability was exploited as a zero-day since early May 2025, two months before its public disclosure, with malicious web shells found on compromised devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/dutch-ncsc-confirms-active-exploitation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-severity WinRAR 0-day exploited for weeks by 2 groups</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/high-severity-winrar-0-day-exploited-for-weeks-by-2-groups/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WinRAR; CVE(s): None; Summary: A vulnerability in WinRAR allowed attackers to install malware on infected systems. The vulnerability was exploited through archives attached to emails impersonating employees of the All-Russian Research Institute. Two execution chains were observed, one delivering a malicious DLL file and another running a Windows executable to deliver a final payload installing SnipBot, a known piece of RomCom malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/high-severity-winrar-0-day-exploited-for-weeks-by-2-groups/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TETRA Radio Encryption Flaws Expose Law Enforcement Communications</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-tetra-radio-encryption-flaws-expose.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Terrestrial Trunked Radio (TETRA); CVE(s): CVE-2025-52940, CVE-2025-52941, CVE-2025-52942, CVE-2025-52943, CVE-2025-52944; Summary: The TETRA protocol has several security issues, including replay and brute-force attacks on its end-to-end encryption (E2EE) mechanism. Additionally, packet injection attacks can be used to intercept radio communications and inject malicious data traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-tetra-radio-encryption-flaws-expose.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Spot Surge in Erlang/OTP SSH RCE Exploits, 70% Target OT Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-spot-surge-in-erlangotp-ssh.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/Open Telecom Platform (OTP); CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: A missing authentication issue allows attackers with network access to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable systems without requiring credentials, posing a severe risk. The flaw was patched in April 2025, and it has been observed being exploited since early May 2025, primarily targeting OT networks in industries such as healthcare, agriculture, media, and entertainment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-spot-surge-in-erlangotp-ssh.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce-Related Data Breach Affecting Multiple Companies</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/salesforce-data-breach-affecting-multiple-companies/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses a series of coordinated intrusions targeting multiple high-profile companies across various sectors, attributed to ShinyHunters. The attackers relied on social engineering, voice phishing, and abuse of Salesforce's Connected Apps feature to gain access to sensitive customer data. The breach did not exploit any vulnerability in Salesforce itself but rather manipulated end users and took advantage of misconfigured or overly permissive third-party app settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062589</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-8088: WinRAR Zero-Day Exploited in Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-8088-winrar-zero-day-exploited-targeted/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WinRAR; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8088; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-8088) in Windows versions of WinRAR, affecting UnRAR.dll and its portable source code, allows attackers to trick the tool into extracting files outside the user's intended directory. This can deposit malicious files in sensitive system locations, which execute automatically on login. The flaw has been actively exploited by Russia-aligned hacking group RomCom since July 18, 2025, and was fixed with the release of WinRAR 7.13 on July 30, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062579</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: BadCam Attack, WinRAR 0-Day, EDR Killer, NVIDIA Flaws, Ransomware Attacks &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-badcam-attack-winrar-0-day.html</link>
      <description>The article appears to be a collection of various cybersecurity-related news and updates, covering topics such as ransomware attacks, malware campaigns, phishing schemes, and security product releases. It does not specifically discuss a vulnerability in a software, hardware, or firmware product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-badcam-attack-winrar-0-day.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Agentic Threat Intelligence (ATI)?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-is-agentic-threat-intelligence-ati/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Agentic Threat Intelligence (ATI), which uses autonomous agents to analyze and respond to emerging threats. ATI systems can correlate Indicators of Compromise (IOCs), contextualize threat data, and recommend or initiate mitigation steps. The article highlights the advantages of ATI over traditional threat intelligence platforms, including its ability to adapt to novel attacks and ambiguous indicators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062560</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Lessons Learned: Focusing Security Where Business Value Lives</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/6-lessons-learned-focusing-security.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of aligning security efforts with business priorities to achieve better security outcomes and more efficient operations. It presents a 4-step methodology for identifying and securing business-critical assets, including identifying critical business processes, mapping those processes to technology, prioritizing based on business risk, and taking action to remediate exposures. The article highlights the need for CISOs to bridge the gap between technical findings and executive leadership, emphasizing the importance of framing security in terms of business risk management to gain support from financial leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/6-lessons-learned-focusing-security.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keys to the Kingdom: Erlang/OTP SSH Vulnerability Analysis and Exploits Observed in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/erlang-otp-cve-2025-32433/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Erlang/OTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-32433; Summary: This vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE) in the Secure Shell (SSH) daemon (sshd) from certain versions of the Erlang programming language's Open Telecom Platform (OTP). The failure to reject post-authentication messages before authentication completion creates a significant attack surface that is being exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=150857</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-Commerce Platforms Face Rising Dark Web Threats; Admin Access and Customer Data on Sale</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/e-commerce-platforms-dark-web-admin-access-data-sale/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on a growing trend of cybercriminal activity targeting global e-commerce businesses, including unauthorized admin access, leaked customer databases, and zero-day exploits. Threat actors are advertising these vulnerabilities and exploits for sale on the dark web, posing significant risks to online retailers and their customers.

(Note: There is no specific vulnerability mentioned in the article, but rather a trend of cybercriminal activity targeting e-commerce businesses.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062549</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WinRAR Zero-Day Under Active Exploitation – Update to Latest Version Immediately</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/winrar-zero-day-under-active.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ilya Korchun (WinRAR); CVE(s): CVE-2025-8088; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in WinRAR tracked as CVE-2025-8088 allows for arbitrary code execution by crafting malicious archive files. The issue affects Windows versions of WinRAR, RAR, UnRAR, portable UnRAR source code, and UnRAR.dll up to and including version 7.12, which has been addressed in version 7.13 released on July 30, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/winrar-zero-day-under-active.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Win-DDoS Flaws Let Attackers Turn Public Domain Controllers into DDoS Botnet via RPC, LDAP</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-win-ddos-flaws-let-attackers-turn.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-26673, CVE-2025-32724, CVE-2025-49716, CVE-2025-49722; Summary: A novel attack technique called Win-DDoS allows an attacker to manipulate public domain controllers (DCs) to create a malicious botnet for conducting powerful DDoS attacks. The attack can be triggered by sending RPC calls to DCs, which then send CLDAP requests to the attacker's server, leading to a referral response that refers the DCs to the attacker's LDAP server. This can cause a denial-of-service (DoS) attack on the target system without requiring code execution or credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/new-win-ddos-flaws-let-attackers-turn.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Detail Windows EPM Poisoning Exploit Chain Leading to Domain Privilege Escalation</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-detail-windows-epm.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49760; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft's Windows Remote Procedure Call (RPC) communication protocol allows an authorized attacker to perform spoofing attacks and impersonate a known server. The attack, called EPM poisoning, enables unprivileged users to pose as a legitimate service with the goal of coercing a protected process to authenticate against an arbitrary server chosen by the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-detail-windows-epm.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux-Based Lenovo Webcams’ Flaw Can Be Remotely Exploited for BadUSB Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/linux-based-lenovo-webcams-flaw-can-be.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4371; Summary: The vulnerabilities in select Lenovo webcams allow remote attackers to inject keystrokes covertly and launch attacks independent of the host operating system. This could turn the webcams into BadUSB attack devices, which can be used to compromise computers and re-infect them even after a wipe and reinstall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/linux-based-lenovo-webcams-flaw-can-be.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Reveal ReVault Attack Targeting Dell ControlVault3 Firmware in 100+ Laptop Models</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-reveal-revault-attack.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dell ControlVault3 firmware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25050, CVE-2025-25215, CVE-2025-24922, CVE-2025-24311, CVE-2025-24919; Summary: Multiple security flaws in Dell's ControlVault3 firmware and Windows APIs allow attackers to bypass Windows login, extract cryptographic keys, and maintain access after a fresh OS install by deploying malicious implants into the firmware. The vulnerabilities can be chained to escalate privileges, bypass authentication controls, and maintain persistence on compromised systems that survive operating system updates or reinstallations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-reveal-revault-attack.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover GPT-5 Jailbreak and Zero-Click AI Agent Attacks Exposing Cloud and IoT Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-uncover-gpt-5-jailbreak-and.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: OpenAI GPT-5; CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers have discovered a jailbreak technique to bypass ethical guardrails in OpenAI's latest large language model (LLM) GPT-5 and produce illicit instructions. The technique, called Echo Chamber, uses narrative-driven steering to trick the model into generating undesirable responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-uncover-gpt-5-jailbreak-and.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReVault! When your SoC turns against you… deep dive edition</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/revault-when-your-soc-turns-against-you-2/</link>
      <description>The article appears to be a comprehensive analysis of vulnerabilities and security risks in ControlVault devices, which are used for fingerprint recognition and authentication purposes. The analysis covers multiple vulnerabilities, including heap corruption, stack overflow, out-of-bound read, and out-of-bound write issues, as well as the potential consequences of exploiting these vulnerabilities.

The article also discusses how an attacker could leverage code execution in the firmware to compromise the device's host system. Specifically, it highlights how an attacker could modify the firmware to make Windows Hello accept any fingerprint, potentially leading to unauthorized access to devices and systems.

Furthermore, the analysis shows how an attacker could use the modified firmware to leak key material from the OTP memory of the Broadcom chip, allowing them to decrypt or forge SCD blobs. This could enable the creation of custom firmware that can be used to compromise device security.

In summary, this article provides a detailed analysis of vulnerabilities and potential attack vectors in ControlVault devices, highlighting the importance of robust security measures to prevent exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">689383955999ea0001bfbcc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encryption made for police and military radios may be easily cracked</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/encryption-made-for-police-and-military-radios-may-be-easily-cracked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sepura; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability in Sepura radios, specifically the use of reduced key lengths (128, 64, or 56 bit) for encryption, which may not be transparently communicated to end users. This could potentially weaken the encryption system and compromise government communications that rely on end-to-end encryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/encryption-made-for-police-and-military-radios-may-be-easily-cracked/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberArk and HashiCorp Flaws Enable Remote Vault Takeover Without Credentials</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cyberark-and-hashicorp-flaws-enable.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CyberArk Secrets Manager and Self-Hosted, HashiCorp Vault; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49827, CVE-2025-49831, CVE-2025-49828, CVE-2025-6000, CVE-2025-5999, CVE-2025-6037; Summary: The vulnerabilities in CyberArk Secrets Manager and Self-Hosted, and HashiCorp Vault allow remote attackers to bypass authentication, escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, steal enterprise secrets, and extract tokens. The most severe issues include remote code execution (CVE-2025-49828) and arbitrary remote code execution via plugin catalog abuse (CVE-2025-6000).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cyberark-and-hashicorp-flaws-enable.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KrebsOnSecurity in New ‘Most Wanted’ HBO Max Series</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/08/krebsonsecurity-in-new-most-wanted-hbo-max-series/</link>
      <description>The article features a documentary series about cybercrime on HBO Max, which includes interviews with a prolific Finnish hacker, Julius Kivimäki, who was convicted of leaking patient records from an online psychotherapy practice while attempting to extort the clinic and its patients. The documentary explores Kivimäki's criminal career, including his involvement in distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks, swatting, and extortion attempts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71873</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult sites are stashing exploit code inside racy .svg files</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/adult-sites-use-malicious-svg-files-to-rack-up-likes-on-facebook/</link>
      <description>Malicious actors are exploiting .svg format files on WordPress-based porn sites to hijack Facebook likes without user consent, inducing browsers to like specific posts. This attack requires the target's Facebook account to be open and logged in. The script downloads additional obfuscated JavaScript and ultimately loads Trojan.JS.Likejack, which silently clicks a "Like" button for a specified Facebook page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/adult-sites-use-malicious-svg-files-to-rack-up-likes-on-facebook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Tools Fuel Brazilian Phishing Scam While Efimer Trojan Steals Crypto from 5,000 Victims</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-tools-fuel-brazilian-phishing-scam.html</link>
      <description>A new phishing campaign is using legitimate generative AI-powered website building tools to create replica phishing pages mimicking Brazilian government agencies. The campaign targets unsuspecting users, tricking them into making unwarranted payments through the country's PIX payment system, and aims to collect sensitive personal information, including CPF numbers.

FYSA: Threat actors are using legitimate AI-powered website building tools to create phishing pages that mimic Brazilian government agencies, targeting unsuspecting users with financially motivated attacks. The campaign also employs staged data collection, API validation, and other tactics to increase the legitimacy of the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-tools-fuel-brazilian-phishing-scam.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: Interlock Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-interlock-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Interlock is a ransomware group that has been active since late 2024 and targets critical infrastructure, healthcare, education, manufacturing, government, finance, and technology sectors. The group uses advanced social engineering tactics, such as ClickFix and FileFix, to trick users into running malicious PowerShell commands. They also use double extortion, stealing data before encryption and threatening to leak it if the victim does not pay the ransom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062530</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes the Deep Web a Valuable Threat Intelligence Source</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-makes-the-deep-web-a-valuable-threat-intelligence-source/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the value of the deep web as a source of threat intelligence, highlighting its potential to provide early warnings, credential exposures, and covert threat actor activity that often go unnoticed by surface-level monitoring. It also emphasizes the importance of combining deep web insights with other intelligence sources and leveraging tools that provide real-time enrichment, while relying on skilled analysts to interpret and act on the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062517</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-53786: CISA Issues Emergency Directive for Critical Microsoft Exchange Hybrid Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-53786-cisa-microsoft-exchange-hybrid-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53786; Summary: The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-53786, is an Elevation of Privilege flaw in hybrid Microsoft Exchange Server configurations. It allows attackers to escalate privileges from on-premises environments into connected cloud services, potentially compromising the organization's entire Exchange Online environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062510</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Deep Web Threat Intelligence?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/what-is-deep-web-threat-intelligence/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of threat intelligence from the deep web, which is often misunderstood as being equivalent to the dark web. It highlights that the deep web is a hidden layer of the internet that contains valuable information for threat detection and response efforts. The article explains the differences between the surface web, deep web, and dark web, and how incorporating deep web intelligence into security operations can enhance visibility and speed up incident response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062491</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Credentials Up 160%: What Attackers Are Doing With Them</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/leaked-credentials-up-160-what.html</link>
      <description>Leaked credentials accounted for 22% of breaches in 2024, with a 160% increase in leaked credentials in 2025 compared to the previous year. The report highlights the growing trend of credential theft, automation making it easier, and the downstream effects of these leaks, including account takeover, credential stuffing, spam distribution, blackmail, and extortion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/leaked-credentials-up-160-what.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyGems, PyPI Hit by Malicious Packages Stealing Credentials, Crypto, Forcing Security Changes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/rubygems-pypi-hit-by-malicious-packages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RubyGems; CVE(s): None; Summary: A threat actor has published 60 malicious gems posing as automation tools for social media and messaging services, stealing credentials from unsuspecting users. The gems have been downloaded over 275,000 times since at least March 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/rubygems-pypi-hit-by-malicious-packages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GreedyBear Steals $1M in Crypto Using 150+ Malicious Firefox Wallet Extensions</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/greedybear-steals-1m-in-crypto-using.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Firefox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Over 150 malicious extensions were discovered in the Firefox marketplace, designed to impersonate popular cryptocurrency wallets and steal digital assets. The extensions used a technique called Extension Hollowing to bypass safeguards and exploit user trust.

FYSA: A campaign dubbed GreedyBear has leveraged these malicious extensions to steal over $1 million in digital assets. The threat actor also uses a C2 server to collect and manage stolen data, and may be targeting other browser marketplaces. Additionally, an AI-powered tool was used to create the malware distribution pipeline, indicating the group's ability to adapt tactics as needed.

FYSA: A separate cryptocurrency scam campaign has been flagged by SentinelOne, where a malicious smart contract is distributed disguised as a trading bot to drain user wallets. The scam uses AI-generated YouTube videos and aged accounts to build legitimacy, with over $900,000 in stolen profits reported so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/greedybear-steals-1m-in-crypto-using.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google discovered a new scam—and also fell victim to it</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/08/google-sales-data-breached-in-the-same-scam-it-discovered/</link>
      <description>Google disclosed that its Salesforce instance was compromised by UNC6040, resulting in the retrieval of limited business information such as names and contact details. A second group, ShinyHunters, has engaged in extortion activities, potentially preparing to escalate tactics by launching a data leak site (DLS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/08/google-sales-data-breached-in-the-same-scam-it-discovered/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocGholish Malware Spread via Ad Tools; Delivers Access to LockBit, Evil Corp, and Others</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/socgholish-malware-spread-via-ad-tools.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the SocGholish malware, a JavaScript loader malware distributed via compromised websites and masquerading as deceptive updates for web browsers and software. It is attributed to TA569 (Gold Prelude, Mustard Tempest, Purple Vallhund, and UNC1543) and has been observed leveraging Traffic Distribution Systems (TDSs) like Parrot TDS and Keitaro TDS to filter and redirect users to sketchy content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/socgholish-malware-spread-via-ad-tools.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI wrote my code and all I got was this broken prototype</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/ai-wrote-my-code-and-all-i-got-was-this-broken-prototype/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the use of AI in software development, specifically in identifying and resolving vulnerabilities. The author shares their personal experience with using an AI agent to write code for a project, highlighting both its benefits (e.g., generating boilerplate code) and limitations (e.g., failing to interface with required libraries).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6893f06f5999ea0001bfbe9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: How to Stop Python Supply Chain Attacks—and the Expert Tools You Need</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-how-to-stop-python-supply-chain.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the rising threat of malicious packages in the Python Package Index (PyPI), including attacks such as typo-squatting, repojacking, and slop-squatting. It highlights the importance of securing the Python supply chain to prevent attacks that can compromise code and cause real harm.

FYSA: The article describes a growing trend of malicious package uploads on PyPI, with attackers exploiting weak links in the open-source supply chain. It also mentions the need for visibility and control over what packages are installed, as well as the importance of using modern signing and provenance frameworks to trust code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/webinar-how-to-stop-python-supply-chain.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Go, npm Packages Deliver Cross-Platform Malware, Trigger Remote Data Wipes</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/malicious-go-npm-packages-deliver-cross.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Go Packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A set of 11 malicious Go packages has been discovered, which can download and execute additional payloads on Windows and Linux systems. The packages conceal an obfuscated loader that fetches second-stage ELF and PE binaries, allowing attackers to gather host information, access web browser data, and beacon out to their C2 server.

FYSA: A threat actor has been identified as the author of 11 malicious Go packages designed to download additional payloads from remote servers and execute them on both Windows and Linux systems. The packages were published on GitHub repositories and are part of a larger malware distribution channel in software supply chains, which can be used to steal sensitive information and target cryptocurrency wallets.

FYSA: Two npm packages masquerading as WhatsApp socket libraries have been discovered, which incorporate a phone number-based kill switch that can remotely wipe developers' systems. The packages were published by a user named "nayflore" in early July 2025 and have collectively been downloaded over 1,110 times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/malicious-go-npm-packages-deliver-cross.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-54948 &amp; CVE-2025-54987: Trend Micro Apex One Exploited for RCE</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-54948-cve-2025-54987-trend-micro-apex-one-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro Apex One (on-premise); CVE(s): CVE-2025-54948, CVE-2025-54987; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities allow unauthenticated attackers to execute remote code on unpatched systems, with one already observed in the wild. The flaws are command injection vulnerabilities found in the Trend Micro Apex One Management Console (on-premise) and target different CPU architectures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062482</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burk Technology ARC Solo</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Burk Technology ARC Solo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5095; Summary: The ARC Solo monitoring and control device lacks authentication for its password change mechanism, allowing an attacker to take over the device without proper credentials. Successful exploitation could result in unauthorized access, locking out authorized users, or disrupting operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23730</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues ED 25-02: Mitigate Microsoft Exchange Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/07/cisa-issues-ed-25-02-mitigate-microsoft-exchange-vulnerability</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Exchange Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53786; Summary: A vulnerability exists in Microsoft Exchange server hybrid deployments, presenting significant risk to organizations operating such configurations. The vulnerability must be mitigated by August 11, 2025, and CISA strongly encourages all organizations to address this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23738</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Ten Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/07/cisa-releases-ten-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA released 10 Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 7, 2025, providing timely information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories include multiple vendors and products, such as Delta Electronics, Johnson Controls, Rockwell Automation, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23736</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreame Technology iOS and Android Mobile Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-06</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dreame Technology Dreamehome and MOVAhome mobile applications; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8393; Summary: The Dreamehome and MOVAhome mobile apps have a TLS vulnerability that allows man-in-the-middle attacks on untrusted networks, which could result in unauthorized information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23733</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Electronics DIAView</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Delta Electronics DIAView; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53417; Summary: The DIAView industrial automation management system is vulnerable to a path traversal vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to read or write files on the affected device. Successful exploitation may allow attackers to access sensitive information or disrupt operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23728</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson Controls FX80 and FX90</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Johnson Controls Inc. FX80 and FX90; CVE(s): CVE-2025-43867; Summary: The vulnerability is a dependency on a vulnerable third-party component, which could allow an attacker to compromise device configuration files. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could trigger other CVEs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23729</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EG4 Electronics EG4 Inverters</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-07</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: EG4 Electronics Equipment; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52586, CVE-2025-53520, CVE-2025-47872, CVE-2025-46414; Summary: The affected products have multiple vulnerabilities that allow an attacker to intercept and manipulate critical data, install malicious firmware, hijack device access, and gain unauthorized control over the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23734</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yealink IP Phones and RPS (Redirect and Provisioning Service)</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-08</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Yealink IP Phones; CVE(s): CVE-2025-52916, CVE-2025-52917, CVE-2025-52918, CVE-2025-52919; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could result in information disclosure. The affected products lack serial number verification attempt limits, enabling brute-force enumeration (last five digits). Additionally, the products lack rate limiting, potentially enabling information disclosure via excessive requests, and fail to enforce access restrictions on OpenAPIs for frozen enterprise accounts, allowing unauthorized access to deactivated interfaces. The certificate upload function in the affected products does not properly validate certificate content, potentially allowing invalid certificates to be uploaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23735</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockwell Automation Arena</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation Arena; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7025, CVE-2025-7032, CVE-2025-7033; Summary: The vulnerabilities in Rockwell Automation's Arena product are out-of-bounds read, stack-based buffer overflow, and heap-based buffer overflow. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to disclose information and execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23731</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packet Power EMX and EG</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-219-05</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Packet Power EMX and EGV; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8284; Summary: The missing authentication for the critical function in Packet Power's EMX and EGV products allows attackers to gain full access to the device without authentication, potentially leading to manipulation of monitoring and control functions. Successful exploitation could be done remotely with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23732</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s how deepfake vishing attacks work, and why they can be hard to detect</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/heres-how-deepfake-vishing-attacks-work-and-why-they-can-be-hard-to-detect/</link>
      <description>A simulated phishing exercise conducted by Mandiant's security team demonstrated the ease with which AI voice spoofing can facilitate a breach of an organization. The exercise used publicly available voice samples and real-world scenarios, such as a VPN service outage, to convincingly simulate a scenario that elicited immediate action from employees. This highlights the importance of remaining calm and vigilant when receiving unexpected requests or calls, even if they seem urgent or legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/heres-how-deepfake-vishing-attacks-work-and-why-they-can-be-hard-to-detect/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI-Powered Security Shift: What 2025 Is Teaching Us About Cloud Defense</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/the-ai-powered-security-shift-what-2025.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of artificial intelligence (AI) in cybersecurity, particularly in cloud-native environments. It highlights the need for real-time, context-aware defense and the role AI plays in empowering defenders while creating new attack surfaces. The article also emphasizes the importance of securing AI systems and implementing data guardrails to filter prompts and outputs for sensitive information.

FYSA: The article highlights the evolving threat landscape and the increasing reliance on AI-powered attacks. It notes that attackers are automating faster, using open-source tools to perform reconnaissance, lateral movement, and credential harvesting. The article also emphasizes the importance of runtime visibility and detection in cloud-native environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/the-ai-powered-security-shift-what-2025.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Discloses Exchange Server Flaw Enabling Silent Cloud Access in Hybrid Setups</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-discloses-exchange-server.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Exchange Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53786; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker with administrative access to gain elevated privileges in a connected cloud environment without leaving detectable traces. Successful exploitation could enable the attacker to escalate privileges within the organization's connected cloud environment, compromising the identity integrity of the Exchange Online service if left unpatched.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-discloses-exchange-server.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6,500 Axis Servers Expose Remoting Protocol; 4,000 in U.S. Vulnerable to Exploits</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/6500-axis-servers-expose-remoting.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Axis Communications; CVE(s): CVE-2025-30023, CVE-2025-30024, CVE-2025-30025, CVE-2025-30026; Summary: Multiple security flaws in video surveillance products from Axis Communications allow for takeover attacks, including pre-authentication remote code execution and authentication bypass. Successful exploitation could grant system-level access and control over cameras within a specific deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/6500-axis-servers-expose-remoting.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall Confirms Patched Vulnerability Behind Recent VPN Attacks, Not a Zero-Day</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/sonicwall-confirms-patched.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall; CVE(s): CVE-2024-40766; Summary: The vulnerability, an improper access control issue (CVSS score 9.3), allows malicious actors to gain unauthorized access to SonicWall firewalls with SSL VPN enabled. The spike in activity targeting Gen 7 and newer firewalls is attributed to password reuse and the failure to reset local user passwords after firmware upgrades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/sonicwall-confirms-patched.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Infection Chain and ConfuserEx-Based Obfuscation for DarkCloud Stealer</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/new-darkcloud-stealer-infection-chain/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the evolution of DarkCloud Stealer, a malware family that employs obfuscation techniques and intricate payload structures to evade traditional detection mechanisms. The latest attacks involve an additional infection chain, obfuscation by ConfuserEx, and a final payload written in Visual Basic 6 (VB6).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=150463</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddled Libra: Why Are We So Obsessed With You?</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/why-the-focus-on-muddled-libra/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) of a threat group called Muddled Libra, which uses social engineering tactics to target organizations in various industries. The article highlights why Muddled Libra receives more media attention than other similar groups, including their unique vishing playbook and ability to attack companies in waves by industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=150445</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Uncover ECScape Flaw in Amazon ECS Enabling Cross-Task Credential Theft</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-uncover-ecscape-flaw-in.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS); CVE(s): None; Summary: Sweet Security researchers have discovered an "end-to-end privilege escalation chain" in Amazon ECS that allows a malicious container to hijack the IAM privileges of a higher-privileged container on the same EC2 instance, enabling lateral movement, access to sensitive data, and control of the cloud environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/researchers-uncover-ecscape-flaw-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake VPN and Spam Blocker Apps Tied to VexTrio Used in Ad Fraud, Subscription Scams</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fake-vpn-and-spam-blocker-apps-tied-to.html</link>
      <description>VexTrio Viper is a malicious ad tech purveyor that has been developing fake apps, including VPNs, device "monitoring" apps, RAM cleaners, dating services, and spam blockers. These apps deceive users into signing up for subscriptions, flooding them with ads, and parting with personal information like email addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/fake-vpn-and-spam-blocker-apps-tied-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Got Arrested in the Raid on the XSS Crime Forum?</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/08/who-got-arrested-in-the-raid-on-the-xss-crime-forum/</link>
      <description>A Russian-language cybercrime forum administrator known as Toha has been arrested by Ukrainian authorities, allegedly operating XSS since its inception. The arrest has triggered widespread speculation among forum members about Toha's real identity, with some suggesting it may be a Russian man named Anton Avdeev. However, evidence points to the true identity of the arrested individual being Anton Medvedovskiy, a 38-year-old Ukrainian citizen who owns multiple domains linked to Toha's email address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71819</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWBN, MedDream, Eclipse vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/wwbn-meddream-eclipse-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: WWBN AVideo; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2205, TALOS-2025-2206, TALOS-2025-2207, TALOS-2025-2208, TALOS-2025-2209, TALOS-2025-2212, TALOS-2025-2213; Summary: Five cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities and two vulnerabilities that can lead to arbitrary code execution when chained together. An attacker must get a user to visit a webpage or send a series of specially crafted HTTP requests to trigger these vulnerabilities.

Vulnerable Product: MedDream PACS Premium; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2154, TALOS-2025-2156, TALOS-2025-2176, TALOS-2025-2177; Summary: Four unique vulnerabilities, including an incorrect default permissions vulnerability, a privilege escalation vulnerability, a reflected XSS vulnerability, and a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. An attacker can exploit these vulnerabilities by uploading a malicious file, sending a specially crafted HTTP request, or providing a crafted URL.

Vulnerable Product: Eclipse ThreadX; CVE(s): TALOS-2024-2088; Summary: A buffer overflow vulnerability that can lead to code execution when an attacker sends a sequence of requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688a5d584ffb850001bf6b13</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Malware Analysis Report Associated with Microsoft SharePoint Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/06/cisa-releases-malware-analysis-report-associated-microsoft-sharepoint-vulnerabilities</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49704, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Cyber threat actors chain CVE-2025-49704 and CVE-2025-49706 to gain unauthorized access to on-premises SharePoint servers. The malware steals cryptographic keys and executes a Base64-encoded PowerShell command to fingerprint the host system and exfiltrate data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23720</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAR-251132.c1.v1 Exploitation of SharePoint Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/analysis-reports/ar25-218a</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided articles appear to be analyzing malware and vulnerabilities related to Microsoft SharePoint. The first rule detects .NET DLL payload samples that extract machine key configuration settings within an ASP.NET application's configuration. The second rule detects ToolShell CVE-2025-53770 exploitation of SharePoint servers, including updated IOCs and activity. The third rule is not provided.

The articles are discussing malware and vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint, which could potentially lead to unauthorized access, data breaches, or other security incidents if left unchecked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23719</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Releases Guidance on High-Severity Vulnerability (CVE-2025-53786) in Hybrid Exchange Deployments</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/06/microsoft-releases-guidance-high-severity-vulnerability-cve-2025-53786-hybrid-exchange-deployments</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Exchange Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53786; Summary: A high-severity vulnerability in Microsoft Exchange Server allows an attacker with administrative access to escalate privileges and potentially compromise the organization's Exchange Online service. The vulnerability can be exploited by leveraging vulnerable hybrid-joined configurations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23726</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Akira Exploits SonicWall SSLVPN in Suspected Zero-Day Attacks</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/akira-exploits-sonicwall-sslvpn-zero-day-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall; CVE(s): CVE-2024-40766; Summary: The article discusses a high-severity cyberattack targeting SonicWall's Gen 7 firewall appliances, exploiting what appears to be a zero-day vulnerability in SSLVPN functionality. The attack chain involves initial access, privilege escalation, persistence, lateral movement, credential theft, defense evasion, and payload deployment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100062445</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Slashes Workloads for vCISOs by 68% as SMBs Demand More – New Report Reveals</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-slashes-workloads-for-vcisos-by-68.html</link>
      <description>According to the report, the demand for vCISO (Virtual Chief Information Security Officer) services among SMBs is growing rapidly, with 79% of MSPs and MSSPs reporting high demand. Service providers are scaling up to meet this demand, with adoption increasing by 319% in just one year. The report highlights the benefits of vCISO services, including increased upsell opportunities, improved operating margins, and measurable expansion of the customer base. AI is playing a key role in delivering these services efficiently and profitably.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-slashes-workloads-for-vcisos-by-68.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Launches Project Ire to Autonomously Classify Malware Using AI Tools</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-launches-project-ire-to.html</link>
      <description>This article is about Microsoft's Project Ire, an autonomous artificial intelligence (AI) agent that can analyze and classify software without assistance to advance malware detection efforts. The system uses specialized tools to reverse engineer software, conducting analysis at various levels, and claims a high accuracy rate in classifying files as malicious or benign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/microsoft-launches-project-ire-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Good Accounts Go Bad: Exploiting Delegated Managed Service Accounts in Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/badsuccessor-attack-vector/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the BadSuccessor technique, which is an exploit that can be used to escalate privileges in Active Directory on Windows Server 2025. The technique takes advantage of the newly introduced Delegated Managed Service Accounts (dMSAs) and allows an attacker to create a dMSA object and then access specific attributes without requiring legitimate administrative credentials. The article provides an in-depth analysis of the BadSuccessor technique, including its operational footprints, and proposes novel detection strategies to identify such attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=149694</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro Confirms Active Exploitation of Critical Apex One Flaws in On-Premise Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/trend-micro-confirms-active.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Trend Micro; CVEs: CVE-2025-54948, CVE-2025-54987; Summary: Trend Micro Apex One Management Console has critical security flaws (command injection and remote code execution) exploited in the wild. The vulnerabilities can be exploited by a pre-authenticated remote attacker to upload malicious code and execute commands on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/trend-micro-confirms-active.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERT-UA Warns of HTA-Delivered C# Malware Attacks Using Court Summons Lures</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cert-ua-warns-of-hta-delivered-c.html</link>
      <description>The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned about cyber attacks carried out by the UAC-0099 threat actor targeting government agencies, defense forces, and enterprises in Ukraine. The attacks use phishing emails to deliver malware families like MATCHBOIL, MATCHWOK, and DRAGSTARE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cert-ua-warns-of-hta-delivered-c.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Is Transforming Cybersecurity Adversarial Testing - Pentera Founder’s Vision</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-is-transforming-cybersecurity.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the future of cybersecurity testing with AI and its potential to revolutionize the field. It presents a vision for Pentera, a company that offers automated penetration testing software, where AI will transform every layer of adversarial testing, making it more conversational, intelligent, and instantly actionable. The article highlights how AI can enhance web attack techniques, make sensitive data discovery and use more precise, and enable language-independent testing. It also describes the role Pentera plays in validating the security of Large Language Models (LLMs) and AI infrastructure, ensuring that organizations can close the gap in their security posture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/ai-is-transforming-cybersecurity.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds 3 D-Link Vulnerabilities to KEV Catalog Amid Active Exploitation Evidence</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cisa-adds-3-d-link-router-flaws-to-kev.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: D-Link; CVEs: CVE-2020-25078, CVE-2020-25079, CVE-2020-40799; Summary: Three high-severity vulnerabilities in D-Link Wi-Fi cameras and video recorders were added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog by CISA due to active exploitation. The flaws, from 2020 and 2022, could allow for remote administrator password disclosure, authenticated command injection, and unauthenticated code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cisa-adds-3-d-link-router-flaws-to-kev.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project AK47: Uncovering a Link to the SharePoint Vulnerability Attacks</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/ak47-activity-linked-to-sharepoint-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The provided article appears to be an analysis of malicious activities and toolsets used by threat actors, specifically CL-CRI-1040. It discusses the overlap between recent ToolShell exploit activity and the activity of this cluster, which is tracked as CL-CRI-1040.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=149927</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice phishers strike again, this time hitting Cisco</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/attackers-who-phished-cisco-downloaded-user-data-from-third-party-crm/</link>
      <description>FIDO multi-factor authentication (MFA) is a defense mechanism against phishing attacks, as it requires the MFA credential to be physically proximal to the device logging in and binds cryptographic keys to the domain name of the service being logged into. This prevents spoofed or lookalike phishing sites from working.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/08/attackers-who-phished-cisco-downloaded-user-data-from-third-party-crm/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickFix Malware Campaign Exploits CAPTCHAs to Spread Cross-Platform Infections</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/clickfix-malware-campaign-exploits.html</link>
      <description>A new social engineering tactic called ClickFix has emerged, which uses propagation methods, narrative sophistication, and evasion techniques to deceive users into infecting their own machines. The tactic involves fake CAPTCHA verification messages guiding victims to execute malicious commands that deploy various types of malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/clickfix-malware-campaign-exploits.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s August Patch Fixes Two Qualcomm Vulnerabilities Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/google-fixes-3-android-vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Android; CVE(s): CVE-2025-21479, CVE-2025-27038, CVE-2025-22441, CVE-2025-48530, CVE-2025-48533; Summary: The article discusses multiple security flaws in Android, including two Qualcomm bugs that were actively exploited. The vulnerabilities include an incorrect authorization vulnerability and a use-after-free vulnerability, which could lead to memory corruption and remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/google-fixes-3-android-vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursor AI Code Editor Vulnerability Enables RCE via Malicious MCP File Swaps Post Approval</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cursor-ai-code-editor-vulnerability.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cursor; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54136; Summary: A high-severity security flaw in Cursor's AI-powered code editor allows remote code execution by modifying Model Context Protocol (MCP) server configurations. The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2025-54136, can be exploited to achieve persistent code execution and expose organizations to supply chain risks and data theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/cursor-ai-code-editor-vulnerability.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReVault! When your SoC turns against you…</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/revault-when-your-soc-turns-against-you/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Broadcom, Dell; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24311, CVE-2025-25050, CVE-2025-25215, CVE-2025-24922, CVE-2025-24919; Summary: The ReVault attack can be used as a post-compromise persistence technique that remains even across Windows reinstalls, and can also bypass Windows Login and/or grant local user Admin/System privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688ccd58d514580001c0fb25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds Three Known Exploited Vulnerabilities to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/05/cisa-adds-three-known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: D-Link DCS-2530L, D-Link DCS-2670L Devices, and D-Link DNR-322L; CVE(s): CVE-2020-25078, CVE-2020-25079, CVE-2022-40799; Summary: The vulnerabilities in these D-Link devices allow for unspecified, command injection, and code download without integrity check, which can be exploited by malicious cyber actors. These types of vulnerabilities pose significant risks to the federal enterprise and should be prioritized for remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23716</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-217-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Tigo Energy Cloud Connect Advanced; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7768, CVE-2025-7769, CVE-2025-7770; Summary: The Cloud Connect Advanced device contains hard-coded credentials allowing unauthorized access, command injection vulnerability in the /cgi-bin/mobile_api endpoint, and insecure session ID generation. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized administrative access, privilege escalation, data exposure, and service disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23715</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/08/05/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on August 5, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits affecting ICS products. The advisories encourage users and administrators to review the technical details and mitigations for the affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23717</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions Multiple Products</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-217-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric ICONICS Product Suite and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7376; Summary: An information tampering vulnerability exists in multiple processes of GENESIS64, MC Works64, and GENESIS due to Windows Shortcut Following (.LNK), allowing an attacker to cause unauthorized writes to arbitrary files on the file system. Successful exploitation could result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the PC if the modified file is necessary for the operation of the PC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23714</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misconfigurations Are Not Vulnerabilities: The Costly Confusion Behind Security Risks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/misconfigurations-are-not.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the distinction between vulnerabilities and misconfigurations in SaaS environments. It emphasizes that understanding this difference is crucial for securing SaaS platforms, as most incidents are caused by user-controlled settings rather than vendor-provided infrastructure. The article also stresses the importance of posture management and visibility into configurations, permissions, and third-party access to prevent conditions that cause breaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/misconfigurations-are-not.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Top CISOs Save Their SOCs from Alert Chaos to Never Miss Real Incidents</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/how-top-cisos-save-their-socs-from.html</link>
      <description>None. This article is not about a vulnerability but contains cybersecurity-relevant content discussing strategies for improving the efficiency of Security Operations Centers (SOCs), including interactive sandboxes, automation, collaboration, and privacy-first workflows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/how-top-cisos-save-their-socs-from.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15,000 Fake TikTok Shop Domains Deliver Malware, Steal Crypto via AI-Driven Scam Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/15000-fake-tiktok-shop-domains-deliver.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TikTok Shop; CVE(s): None; Summary: A widespread malicious campaign targeting TikTok Shop users globally aims to steal credentials and distribute trojanized apps. The scam uses phishing, malware, and AI-generated content to trick users into installing a variant of cross-platform malware called SparkKitty that can harvest data from Android and iOS devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/15000-fake-tiktok-shop-domains-deliver.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall Investigating Potential SSL VPN Zero-Day After 20+ Targeted Attacks Reported</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/sonicwall-investigating-potential-ssl.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall; CVE(s): None; Summary: A spike in Akira ransomware attacks is reported, targeting Gen 7 SonicWall firewalls with SSL VPN enabled. The incidents involve the exploitation of a suspected zero-day vulnerability, which allows attackers to pivot directly to domain controllers and conduct enumeration, detection evasion, lateral movement, and credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/sonicwall-investigating-potential-ssl.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 05:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI site Perplexity uses “stealth tactics” to flout no-crawl edicts, Cloudflare says</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/08/ai-site-perplexity-uses-stealth-tactics-to-flout-no-crawl-edicts-cloudflare-says/</link>
      <description>Perplexity, an AI engine, has been accused of violating website content usage guidelines by allegedly plagiarizing content from multiple publishers. The company was found to have manipulated its crawling bots' ID strings to bypass website blocks and ignored robots.txt exclusions. Cloudflare has taken actions to prevent Perplexity's crawlers from accessing sites that use its content-delivery service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/08/ai-site-perplexity-uses-stealth-tactics-to-flout-no-crawl-edicts-cloudflare-says/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Triton Bugs Let Unauthenticated Attackers Execute Code and Hijack AI Servers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/nvidia-triton-bugs-let-unauthenticated.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Triton Inference Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23319, CVE-2025-23320, CVE-2025-23334; Summary: The vulnerabilities in NVIDIA's Triton Inference Server can be exploited to take over susceptible servers, potentially allowing remote code execution, information disclosure, denial of service, and data tampering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/nvidia-triton-bugs-let-unauthenticated.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoors &amp; Breaches: How Talos is helping humanitarian aid NGOs prepare for cyber attacks</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/backdoors-breaches-how-talos-is-helping-humanitarian-aid-ngos-prepare-for-cyber-attacks/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the creation of customized tabletop exercises (TTXs) for international humanitarian organizations and domestic NGOs to improve their cybersecurity preparedness. The TTXs, based on the popular "Backdoors &amp; Breaches" game, are designed to help NGOs respond to cyber attacks and other security incidents in a cost-effective and engaging way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d462a8d2eb38000171d1f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnamese Hackers Use PXA Stealer, Hit 4,000 IPs and Steal 200,000 Passwords Globally</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/vietnamese-hackers-use-pxa-stealer-hit.html</link>
      <description>A Python-based information stealer called PXA Stealer is being distributed in campaigns targeting over 4,000 unique IP addresses across 62 countries. The malware can harvest passwords, browser autofill data, cryptocurrency wallet and financial institution data, and exfiltrate stolen data through Telegram APIs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/vietnamese-hackers-use-pxa-stealer-hit.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: VPN 0-Day, Encryption Backdoor, AI Malware, macOS Flaw, ATM Hack &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-vpn-0-day-encryption.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article appears to be a comprehensive threat intelligence report that covers various cybersecurity-related topics, including malware attacks, vulnerability exploitation, and APT group activities.

Some notable takeaways from the article include:

* The increasing use of zero-day and 1-day flaws in attacks (32.1% of exploited vulnerabilities were discovered within 24 hours or less)
* The resurgence of BreachForums after it went offline earlier this year
* The exploits of Microsoft SharePoint flaws by the Mimo threat group to deliver ransomware
* The use of fake Flash plugins by the Silver Fox APT group to deliver malware
* The arrest of a Spanish hacker who allegedly stole sensitive data from major financial institutions and educational organizations

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the ever-evolving cyber threat landscape and highlights the importance of staying vigilant and proactive in defending against these threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/weekly-recap-vpn-0-day-encryption.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man-in-the-Middle Attack Prevention Guide</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/man-in-middle-attack-prevention-guide.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses man-in-the-middle (MITM) attacks, where criminals exploit weaknesses in communication protocols to silently position themselves between two unsuspecting parties. It highlights the effectiveness of MITM attacks and provides best practices for preventing them, including enforcing HTTPS and TLS, using trusted VPNs, implementing certificate pinning, and deploying DNSSEC and DoH/DoT.

FYSA: The article warns about the insidious nature of MITM attacks, which can go unnoticed until long after the attacker has disappeared. It emphasizes the importance of implementing a layered defense strategy to mitigate these attacks, including intrusion detection and prevention systems, external attack surface management tools, and advanced endpoint detection and response solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/08/man-in-middle-attack-prevention-guide.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actor Groups Tracked by Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 (Updated Aug. 1, 2025)</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/threat-actor-groups-tracked-by-palo-alto-networks-unit-42/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

As a cybersecurity analyst, I've analyzed the article and identified several key points that are relevant to the field of cybersecurity.

1. **Ransomware groups:** The article highlights three ransomware groups: Ambitious Scorpius, Bashful Scorpius, and Bitter Scorpius. These groups are known for their adaptability and ability to quickly exploit newly disclosed vulnerabilities.
2. **Cybercrime motivation:** The article notes that some threat groups have a primary motivation of financial gain rather than political or ideological goals. This is seen in the cases of Bling Libra and Muddled Libra, which target organizations across various industries for financial gain.
3. **Geopolitical motivations:** On the other hand, several threat groups are motivated by geopolitical interests. For example, Cloaked Ursa is attributed to Russia's Foreign Intelligence Service (SVR), while Fighting Ursais is linked to Russia's General Staff Main Intelligence Directorate (GRU).
4. **Cybercrime forums:** The article mentions the use of cybercrime forums as a means for threat groups to solicit affiliates and share information.
5. **Law enforcement efforts:** The article notes that joint law enforcement efforts have had an impact on some threat groups, such as Ambitious Scorpius.

In conclusion, this article provides valuable insights into the motivations and tactics employed by various threat groups in the cybercrime landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42-preview.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=135181</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft catches Russian hackers targeting foreign embassies</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/07/microsoft-catches-russian-hackers-targeting-foreign-embassies/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malware campaign called ApolloShadow. It uses social engineering tactics and exploits Windows features to gain elevated privileges on infected devices. The malware checks the privilege level of the ProcessToken, displays a User Access Control (UAC) pop-up window, and masquerades as a Kaspersky installer to install root certificates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2025/07/microsoft-catches-russian-hackers-targeting-foreign-embassies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 21:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blame the governor! Oklahoma’s “board meeting porn” scandal goes gonzo.</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/blame-the-governor-oklahomas-board-meeting-porn-scandal-goes-gonzo/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be discussing an incident where inappropriate content aired during a school board meeting, with board members describing their reactions and the situation unfolding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/blame-the-governor-oklahomas-board-meeting-porn-scandal-goes-gonzo/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Booker Prize Longlist and Hacker Summer Camp</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/the-booker-prize-longlist-and-hacker-summer-camp/</link>
      <description>The article does not discuss a specific vulnerability, but it mentions the Cisco Talos Incident Response Trends Q2 2025 report, which provides insights into recent attacker behavior. It highlights phishing as the top initial access vector and notes that credential harvesting is the primary objective of most observed phishing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688a6edf4ffb850001bf6b4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Two Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/31/cisa-releases-two-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA (Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency) released two Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 31, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories recommend reviewing technical details and mitigations for the affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23707</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockwell Automation Lifecycle Services with VMware</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-212-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Rockwell Automation, VMware ESXi, Workstation, and Fusion; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41236, CVE-2025-41237, CVE-2025-41238, CVE-2025-41239; Summary: Four vulnerabilities exist in the VMXNET3 virtual network adapter, Virtual Machine Communication Interface (VMCI), Paravirtualized SCSI (PVSCSI) controller, and vSockets. Exploitation of these vulnerabilities can lead to code execution on the host or leakage of memory from processes communicating with vSockets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23706</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thorium Platform Public Availability</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/31/thorium-platform-public-availability</link>
      <description>Thorium, a scalable and distributed platform for automated file analysis and result aggregation, has been announced by CISA in partnership with Sandia National Laboratories. It enables cybersecurity teams to automate analysis workflows through seamless integration of commercial, open-source, and custom tools, supporting various mission functions such as software analysis, digital forensics, and incident response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23702</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and USCG Issue Joint Advisory to Strengthen Cyber Hygiene in Critical Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/31/cisa-and-uscg-issue-joint-advisory-strengthen-cyber-hygiene-critical-infrastructure</link>
      <description>The article announces a joint cybersecurity advisory between CISA and the USCG, highlighting cybersecurity risks identified during a proactive threat hunt engagement at a critical infrastructure facility. The advisory shares best practices to improve cyber hygiene, including not storing passwords in plaintext, avoiding shared administrator credentials, and implementing comprehensive logging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23701</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Güralp Systems Güralp FMUS series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-212-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Güralp Systems Güralp FMUS Series Seismic Monitoring Devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8286; Summary: Missing authentication for a critical function allows an attacker to modify hardware configurations, manipulate data, or factory reset the device. Successful exploitation could have significant impacts on seismic monitoring devices and potentially affect critical infrastructure sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23705</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA and USCG Identify Areas for Cyber Hygiene Improvement After Conducting Proactive Threat Hunt at US Critical Infrastructure Organization</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/cybersecurity-advisories/aa25-212a</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a cybersecurity analysis of a control system infrastructure, specifically focusing on the security controls and best practices for securing Industrial Control Systems (ICS) networks. The article highlights several vulnerabilities and areas for improvement in the existing network architecture, including:

1. Lack of segmentation between IT and OT networks
2. Inadequate access controls and monitoring
3. Use of plaintext credentials
4. Insufficient encryption and authentication mechanisms

The analysis provides recommendations for improving the security posture of the ICS infrastructure, including:

1. Implementing VLAN segmentation with inter-VLAN access controls
2. Deploying firewalls and intrusion prevention systems (IPS) to monitor traffic between IT and OT networks
3. Enforcing strict access controls and monitoring for SCADA devices and servers
4. Disabling FTP services and replacing them with secure alternatives
5. Enhancing authentication and encryption mechanisms

Overall, the article provides a comprehensive analysis of the security controls and best practices for securing ICS networks, highlighting the importance of implementing robust segmentation, access controls, and monitoring to prevent breaches and ensure the integrity of industrial control systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23692</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs as a reverse engineering sidekick</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/using-llm-as-a-reverse-engineering-sidekick/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article analyzes the effectiveness of both cloud-based and local language models (LLMs) in assisting cybersecurity analysts with reverse engineering unknown code and improving malware analysis. The results show that while both models can provide valuable insights, the cloud-based model is more thorough in its analysis due to its access to a larger input context.

However, the article also highlights several limitations of using LLMs for malware analysis, including high usage costs, time overhead, potential malicious tools, and vulnerabilities. These factors must be carefully considered by researchers and analysts looking to incorporate LLMs into their workflow.

The article does not discuss any specific vulnerability or security issue related to a product, making it an FYSA response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68880b342e0cc100010c3642</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR Trends Q2 2025: Phishing attacks persist as actors leverage compromised valid accounts to enhance legitimacy</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/ir-trends-q2-2025/</link>
      <description>Phishing remained the top method of initial access this quarter, with threat actors leveraging compromised internal or trusted business partner email accounts to deploy malicious emails. Credential harvesting was the end goal in most phishing attacks, suggesting cybercriminals consider brokering compromised credentials as simpler and more reliably profitable than other post-exploitation activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688292572e0cc100010c35d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Unit 42’s Attribution Framework</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/unit-42-attribution-framework/</link>
      <description>The provided article discusses a cybersecurity analyst's analysis of an activity cluster, which they have named "Stately Taurus". The analysis is based on the Unit 42 Attribution Framework, which uses a structured approach to analyzing threat data and attributing observed activity to named threat actors or groups. The article provides an overview of the framework and how it was used to track the evolution of an activity cluster into a named threat group.

The article does not discuss a vulnerability (software, hardware, or firmware) and therefore does not meet the criteria for starting the response with "Vulnerable Product:".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=148610</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In search of riches, hackers plant 4G-enabled Raspberry Pi in bank network</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/in-search-of-riches-hackers-plant-4g-enabled-raspberry-pi-in-bank-network/</link>
      <description>A threat actor, known as UNC2891, compromised a bank's internal network by installing a Raspberry Pi device and compromising a mail server. The attacker used process masquerading to disguise their custom backdoor as the legitimate LightDM display manager, attempting to evade detection and mislead forensic analysts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/in-search-of-riches-hackers-plant-4g-enabled-raspberry-pi-in-bank-network/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Paul, MN, was hacked so badly that the National Guard has been deployed</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/st-paul-mn-was-hacked-so-badly-that-the-national-guard-has-been-deployed/</link>
      <description>The city of St. Paul experienced a cyber attack over the weekend, which required a full shutdown of its information systems as a defensive measure. The attack has affected various city functions, including library services and online payments, but emergency services remain operational.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/st-paul-mn-was-hacked-so-badly-that-the-national-guard-has-been-deployed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scammers Unleash Flood of Slick Online Gaming Sites</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/scammers-unleash-flood-of-slick-online-gaming-sites/</link>
      <description>The article describes a widespread social engineering scheme involving over 1,200 fake online gaming and wagering websites that lure victims with free credits and eventually abscond with cryptocurrency funds. Scammers use deceptive ads on social media platforms like Discord, claiming partnership with popular personalities, to get users to create accounts and deposit cryptocurrency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71791</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flaw in Gemini CLI coding tool could allow hackers to run nasty commands</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/flaw-in-gemini-cli-coding-tool-allowed-hackers-to-run-nasty-commands-on-user-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Gemini CLI; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a vulnerability in Gemini CLI, where an attacker can inject malicious commands using prompt injection and exploiting the tool's lack of whitelisting. The vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands without being detected, making it possible for them to steal sensitive information or cause harm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/flaw-in-gemini-cli-coding-tool-allowed-hackers-to-run-nasty-commands-on-user-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Talos at Black Hat 2025: Briefings, booth talks and what to expect</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/cisco-talos-at-black-hat-2025-briefings-booth-talks-and-what-to-expect/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather a collection of talks and sessions by Cisco Talos at Black Hat. The topics include threat intelligence, incident response, machine learning-based firewalls, and more.

FYSA: None</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68878cd32e0cc100010c3605</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Unit 42 Global Incident Response Report: Social Engineering Edition</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/2025-unit-42-global-incident-response-report-social-engineering-edition/</link>
      <description>The article discusses social engineering attacks and their impact on organizations. It provides insights into the tactics used by attackers, including phishing, impersonation, and pretexting. The report also highlights the importance of strengthening the human layer in cybersecurity and recommends strategies for detecting and responding to social engineering attacks.

Key findings from the report include:

* Social engineering attacks are a significant threat to organizations, with 60% of cases resulting in data exposure.
* Phishing is one of the most common tactics used by attackers, with 75% of social engineering attacks involving phishing emails or messages.
* Attackers often use built-in utilities like PowerShell or WMI to move undetected within an organization's network.
* The report emphasizes the importance of visibility beyond traditional indicators and recommends correlating signals across identity, endpoint, network, and SaaS activity to expose escalation attempts early.

Overall, the article provides a comprehensive overview of social engineering attacks and their impact on organizations. It highlights the need for defenders to think beyond malware and infrastructure controls and focus on strengthening the human layer in cybersecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147913</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Covert Operator's Playbook: Infiltration of Global Telecom Networks</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/infiltration-of-global-telecom-networks/</link>
      <description>This article appears to be a report on a cybersecurity threat actor known as CL-STA-0969, which targets telecommunications companies. The report provides an analysis of the threat actor's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs), including their use of backdoors, anti-analysis techniques, and obfuscation.

The report highlights the threat actor's ability to adapt to different environments and evade detection by using novel methods such as creating custom C2 communication channels. It also provides information on the malware samples associated with this threat actor, including hashes for various files.

Palo Alto Networks customers are advised to take measures to protect themselves from these threats, including using Advanced WildFire cloud-delivered malware analysis service, Cortex XDR and XSIAM, Cortex Xpanse, and Next-Generation Firewall (NGFW) with Cloud-Delivered Security Services (CDSS).

It is unclear whether this article discusses a vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=148315</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights from Talos IR: Navigating NIS2 technical implementation</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/insights-from-talos-ir-navigating-nis2-technical-implementation/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the European Union's NIS2 Directive and its technical implementation guidance, which requires organizations to implement enhanced cybersecurity measures. The guidance emphasizes the importance of balancing incident response, forensic analysis, and operational continuity during incidents. It highlights the challenges of meeting the 24-hour deadline for reporting incidents, maintaining comprehensive logs, and developing playbooks that prioritize evidence preservation, threat containment, and operational continuity.

FYSA:</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6887ca5f2e0cc100010c3622</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Ukrainian hackers take credit for attack that snarls Russian flight travel</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/pro-ukrainian-hackers-take-credit-for-attack-that-snarls-russian-flight-travel/</link>
      <description>The Belarusian Cyberpartisans have claimed responsibility for a cyberattack on Russia's largest airline, Aeroflot, which has resulted in the airline's systems being paralyzed. The attack has also allegedly compromised personal data of Aeroflot customers and intercepted conversations and emails of staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/pro-ukrainian-hackers-take-credit-for-attack-that-snarls-russian-flight-travel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft to stop using China-based teams to support Department of Defense</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/microsoft-to-stop-using-china-based-teams-to-support-department-of-defense/</link>
      <description>Microsoft's use of foreign workers to maintain Defense Department computer systems has been criticized for lack of oversight, with foreign-based tech support personnel potentially having advanced skills and limited policing by US-based digital escorts. The practice has raised concerns about the handling of sensitive information, with some experts calling for greater transparency in cloud computing products and services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/microsoft-to-stop-using-china-based-teams-to-support-department-of-defense/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After BlackSuit is taken down, new ransomware group Chaos emerges</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/after-blacksuit-is-taken-down-new-ransomware-group-chaos-emerges/</link>
      <description>Chaos ransomware likely rebranded from BlackSuit or operated by former BlackSuit members, gaining initial access through social engineering and voice phishing techniques, eventually persuading victims to connect to the attacker's endpoint using Microsoft Quick Assist. The ransomware operation shares similarities with its predecessor, Royal, which is a splinter group of the Conti ransomware group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/after-blacksuit-is-taken-down-new-ransomware-group-chaos-emerges/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 00:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korean hackers ran US-based “laptop farm” from Arizona woman’s home</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-ran-us-based-laptop-farm-from-arizona-womans-home/</link>
      <description>A cybercrime story about a woman who was involved with North Korean actors in an identity theft scheme. The article highlights the psychological and financial damage caused by identity theft, including feelings of vulnerability and lack of control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/north-korean-hackers-ran-us-based-laptop-farm-from-arizona-womans-home/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ηоmоgraph Illusion: Not Everything Is As It Seems</title>
      <link>https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/homograph-attacks/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a type of email attack known as homograph attacks, where attackers use non-Latin characters that visually resemble Latin characters to create words. The article provides case studies demonstrating how threat actors use homographs in different fields within an email to evade detection and analysis, and ultimately exploit targets.

FYSA: Homograph attacks are a type of email compromise technique used by threat actors to trick users into engaging with malicious content. These attacks can be highly targeted and convincing, making it difficult for recipients to distinguish between legitimate and fraudulent emails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://unit42.paloaltonetworks.com/?p=147711</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply-chain attacks on open source software are getting out of hand</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/open-source-repositories-are-seeing-a-rash-of-supply-chain-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply-chain attack affected several npm packages, including 'is' and others from the @toptal/picasso-* namespace. The packages received a combined 2.8 million downloads weekly. Developers working with these packages should ensure they have not been installed or incorporated into their projects and follow best practices for securing open-source dependencies.

FYSA: The attacks demonstrate the potential for widespread damage through supply-chain attacks, highlighting the importance of monitoring repository visibility changes, reviewing package.json lifecycle scripts, using automated security scanning, and rotating authentication tokens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/open-source-repositories-are-seeing-a-rash-of-supply-chain-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-649: Veeam Agent for Microsoft Windows Incorrect Default Permissions Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-649/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Veeam; Veeam Agent for Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): CVE-2025-24287; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Veeam Agent for Microsoft Windows. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the product installer due to incorrect permissions on a file used by the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25685</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-650: ATEN eco DC Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-650/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: ATEN eco DC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6685; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of ATEN eco DC, requiring authentication to exploit. The specific flaw exists within the web-based interface due to a lack of validating the assigned user role when handling requests, enabling privilege escalation to resources normally protected from the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26647</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-651: (Pwn2Own) Red Hat Enterprise Linux CBS Packet Scheduling Use-After-Free Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-651/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Red Hat Enterprise Linux; CVE(s): CVE-2025-38350, ZDI-CAN-27159, ZDI-25-651; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Red Hat Enterprise Linux by exploiting a use-after-free flaw in the handling of hfsc_class objects. An attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution on the target system to exploit this vulnerability and execute arbitrary code in kernel context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27159</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackSuit ransomware leak sites seized in Operation Checkmate</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/law-enforcement-seizes-blacksuit-ransomware-leak-sites/</link>
      <description>Law enforcement has seized the dark web leak sites of the BlackSuit ransomware operation, which has targeted hundreds of organizations worldwide. The operation involved multiple international agencies, including Europol and Romanian cybersecurity company Bitdefender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/law-enforcement-seizes-blacksuit-ransomware-leak-sites/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI confirms ChatGPT Agent is now rolling out for $20 Plus users</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-chatgpt-agent-is-now-rolling-out-for-20-plus-users/</link>
      <description>OpenAI's ChatGPT Agent mode is now rolling out to users with $20 Plus or $200 Pro subscriptions. This feature allows ChatGPT to perform complex tasks independently, such as handling calendar requests and creating PowerPoint decks, by using its own computer and browser. It will likely improve in the coming months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-confirms-chatgpt-agent-is-now-rolling-out-for-20-plus-users/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Koske Linux malware hides in cute panda images</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-koske-linux-malware-hides-in-cute-panda-images/</link>
      <description>Koske is a sophisticated Linux malware that uses artificial intelligence and seemingly benign JPEG images of panda bears to deploy CPU and GPU-optimized cryptocurrency miners directly into system memory. The malware achieves initial access by leveraging misconfigurations of JupyterLab instances, downloads malicious payloads from legitimate services, and establishes persistence via cron jobs and custom systemd services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-koske-linux-malware-hides-in-cute-panda-images/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers—hope to defect to Russia? Don’t Google “defecting to Russia.”</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-hope-to-defect-to-russia-dont-google-defecting-to-russia/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the case of a military individual, Wagenius, who attempted to sell stolen information to Country-1's military intelligence service. He was caught due to his poor operational security (opsec) and lack of forethought, with incriminating evidence found on his devices and in online searches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-hope-to-defect-to-russia-dont-google-defecting-to-russia/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Cyber Attacks Utilize ML Algorithms to Deploy Malware and Circumvent Traditional Security</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ai-powered-cyber-attacks-utilize-ml-algorithms/</link>
      <description>AI-powered attacks are becoming increasingly complex and adaptive, leveraging unsupervised ML algorithms to process vast datasets, detect patterns, and adapt dynamically to security protocols. These attacks often initiate with automated data aggregation from sources like social media and dark web repositories, followed by algorithmic pattern recognition to pinpoint vulnerabilities, strategic attack planning, and real-time evolution to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151220</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-647: Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-647/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Anritsu ShockLine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7975; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CHX files due to a lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26913</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-648: Anritsu ShockLine CHX File Parsing Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-648/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Anritsu ShockLine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7976; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Anritsu ShockLine. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability, which occurs when parsing CHX files due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26882</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hive0156 Hackers Targeting Government and Military Organizations to Deploy REMCOS RAT</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hive0156-hackers-targeting-government-and-military-organizations/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the activities of a Russian-aligned threat actor group called Hive0156, which has been targeting Ukrainian government and military personnel with sophisticated malware attacks. The group uses Remcos Remote Access Trojan (RAT) to maintain persistent access to critical infrastructure and sensitive military communications, and has recently expanded its targeting strategy to include broader civilian targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151210</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in Phishing Attacks Exploiting Spoofed SharePoint Domains and Sneaky 2FA Tactics</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surge-in-phishing-attacks-exploiting-spoofed-sharepoint-domains/</link>
      <description>The article describes a surge in phishing campaigns that impersonate Microsoft SharePoint domains using structured naming conventions and a .org top-level domain. These malicious domains mimic legitimate U.S.-based organizations and are hosted on platforms like Alboompro.com, which allows user-defined subdomains for hosting phishing content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151201</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT28 Hackers Unveil First LLM-Powered Malware, Enhancing Attack Techniques with AI</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt28-hackers-unveil-first-llm-powered-malware/</link>
      <description>LAMEHUG is a malware campaign attributed to APT28 (Fancy Bear) that leverages large language model (LLM) capabilities in its attack chain. The malware targets Ukrainian government officials through phishing emails and executes commands via Hugging Face's API, enabling dynamic reconnaissance and data harvesting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151191</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRB, pausing for a "Sanctuary Moon" marathon</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/brb-pausing-for-a-sanctuary-moon-marathon/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

No cybersecurity-relevant content in this article. It appears to be a newsletter-style update from Cisco Talos, featuring news and insights on various topics, including the "Humans of Talos" series, which highlights the people behind the research at Talos. There is no discussion of vulnerabilities, threats, or security incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687fcd682e0cc100010c3464</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishers Target Aviation Execs to Scam Customers</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/phishers-target-aviation-execs-to-scam-customers/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a long-running Nigerian cybercrime ring that is actively targeting established companies in the transportation and aviation industries. The group, known as "SilverTerrier," excels at business email compromise (BEC) scams, which target legitimate business email accounts through social engineering or computer intrusion activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71635</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Mitel Flaw Lets Hackers Bypass Login, Gain Full Access to MiVoice MX-ONE Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-mitel-flaw-lets-hackers-bypass.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in the Provisioning Manager component of Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an authentication bypass attack and gain unauthorized access to user or admin accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-mitel-flaw-lets-hackers-bypass.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Ant Exploits VMware Flaws to Compromise ESXi Hosts and vCenter Environments</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fire-ant-exploits-vmware-flaw-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware; CVE(s): CVE-2023-34048, CVE-2023-20867; Summary: A threat actor known as Fire Ant exploited a vulnerability in VMware vCenter Server (CVE-2023-34048) to gain access to virtualization management layers and then leveraged another flaw in VMware Tools (CVE-2023-20867) to interact with guest virtual machines. The attacker deployed persistent backdoors, used V2Ray framework for network tunneling, and maintained covert access by suppressing audit trails.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/fire-ant-exploits-vmware-flaw-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker sneaks infostealer malware into early access Steam game</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-sneaks-infostealer-malware-into-early-access-steam-game/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Aether Forge Studios, Chemia; CVE(s): None; Summary: EncryptHub compromised the Chemia game files on Steam to distribute info-stealing malware, specifically HijackLoader and Fickle Stealer. The malware was distributed through a DLL file and PowerShell script, which harvested data stored in web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-sneaks-infostealer-malware-into-early-access-steam-game/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitel warns of critical MiVoice MX-ONE authentication bypass flaw</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitel-warns-of-critical-mivoice-mx-one-authentication-bypass-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitel Networks MiVoice MX-ONE; CVE(s): None; Summary: The MiVoice MX-ONE Provisioning Manager component contains an improper access control weakness that allows unauthenticated attackers to gain unauthorized access to administrator accounts on unpatched systems, which can be exploited in low-complexity attacks without user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mitel-warns-of-critical-mivoice-mx-one-authentication-bypass-flaw/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CastleLoader Malware Infects 469 Devices Using Fake GitHub Repos and ClickFix Phishing</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/castleloader-malware-infects-469.html</link>
      <description>CastleLoader is a versatile malware loader used to distribute various information stealers and remote access trojans (RATs). It employs dead code injection, packing techniques, and anti-analysis measures to hinder analysis. The loader connects to a C2 server, downloads target modules, and executes them, making it a primary distribution mechanism in the current threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/castleloader-malware-infects-469.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant APT Group Exploits VLC Player and Encrypted Shellcode in Attacks on Defense Sector</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/elephant-apt-group-exploits-vlc-player/</link>
      <description>The article reports a sophisticated cyber-espionage operation attributed to the Dropping Elephant APT group, targeting Turkish defense contractors specializing in precision-guided missile systems. The campaign involves spear-phishing emails with malicious LNK files, DLL side-loading techniques, and shellcode injection using QueueUserAPC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151150</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Using .hwp Files to Distribute RokRAT Malware and Evade Detection Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-using-hwp-files/</link>
      <description>The AhnLab Security Intelligence Center (ASEC) discovered a sophisticated campaign using Hangul Word Processor (.hwp) documents to spread the RokRAT remote access trojan (RAT). The malware uses Object Linking and Embedding (OLE) objects, DLL side-loading, and steganographic analysis to evade security detections and execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151140</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophos and SonicWall Patch Critical RCE Flaws Affecting Firewalls and SMA 100 Devices</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/sophos-and-sonicwall-patch-critical-rce.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos Firewall; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6704 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-7624 (CVSS score: 9.8), CVE-2025-7382 (CVSS score: 8.8); Summary: Two vulnerabilities in Sophos Firewall, including arbitrary file writing and SQL injection flaws, can lead to remote code execution. Additionally, a high-severity command injection vulnerability in the WebAdmin component can result in pre-auth code execution on High Availability auxiliary devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/sophos-and-sonicwall-patch-critical-rce.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Comdb2 null pointer dereference and denial-of-service vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/bloomberg-comdb2-null-pointer-dereference-and-denial-of-service-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Bloomberg Comdb2; CVE(s): TALOS-2025-2197 (CVE-2025-36520), TALOS-2025-2201 (CVE-2025-35966), TALOS-2025-2199 (CVE-2025-48498), TALOS-2025-2198 (CVE-2025-46354), TALOS-2025-2200 (CVE-2025-36512); Summary: Three null pointer dereference vulnerabilities exist in Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1, which can lead to denial of service by sending crafted messages over TCP. Additionally, there are two denial-of-service vulnerabilities in the Distributed Transaction Commit/Abort Operation and database handling a distributed transaction heartbeat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687ff9ac2e0cc100010c346e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-646: Amazon AWS Client VPN Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-646/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Amazon AWS Client VPN; CVE(s): CVE-2025-8069; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Amazon AWS Client VPN by exploiting an uncontrolled search path element in the OpenSSL configuration. The attacker must first obtain low-privileged code execution to exploit this vulnerability, which can be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26780</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoName057(16) Hackers Target 3,700 Unique Devices Over the Last 13 Months</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/noname05716-hackers-target-3700-unique-devices/</link>
      <description>This article is about the NoName057(16) hacktivist collective, which has been executing distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks against government and public-sector entities in European nations. The group uses a volunteer-driven platform called DDoSia to orchestrate large-scale application-layer DDoS campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151131</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers breach Toptal GitHub account, publish malicious npm packages</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-breach-toptal-github-account-publish-malicious-npm-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Toptal's GitHub organization account; CVE(s): None; Summary: Hackers compromised Toptal's GitHub organization account and used their access to publish ten malicious packages on the Node Package Manager (NPM) index. The packages included data-stealing code that collected GitHub authentication tokens and then wiped the victims' systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-breach-toptal-github-account-publish-malicious-npm-packages/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC3944 Exploits VMware vSphere to Deploy Ransomware and Steal Data from Organizations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/unc3944-exploits-vmware-vsphere-to-deploy-ransomware/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a highly advanced cyber operation orchestrated by the threat actor UNC3944, which uses social engineering tactics to infiltrate organizations and conduct reconnaissance on internal resources. The group exploits VMware vSphere environments, using a "living-off-the-land" methodology to minimize detectable indicators of compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151122</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splunk Guide to Detect, Mitigate, and Respond to the CitrixBleed 2 Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/splunk-guide-to-detect-mitigate-and-respond/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: An out-of-bounds memory read vulnerability (CVE-2025-5777) affects Citrix NetScaler ADC and Gateway devices, enabling unauthenticated attackers to leak sensitive memory contents via malformed HTTP POST requests. The vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.3 and is exploited through simple payloads like an incomplete "login" parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151095</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-205-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor 24950 and 24952; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4393, CVE-2025-4394, CVE-2025-4395; Summary: Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could lead to system compromise, unauthorized access to sensitive data, and manipulation of the monitor's functionality. The vulnerabilities are due to cleartext storage of sensitive information, an empty password in a configuration file, and deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23675</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Six Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/24/cisa-releases-six-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released six Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 24, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. These advisories are intended for users and administrators to review technical details and mitigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series; CVE(s): CVE-2016-2542; Summary: The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious code by getting setup-launcher to load a malicious DLL due to Uncontrolled Search Path Element (CWE-427). Successful exploitation could lead to the execution of malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23674</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Thermostat X-Series WiFi Thermostats</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-02</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Network Thermostat X-Series WiFi thermostats; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6260; Summary: The vulnerable embedded web server allows unauthenticated attackers to gain direct access, reset user credentials, and potentially gain full administrative access. This vulnerability can be exploited remotely with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23676</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG Innotek Camera Model LNV5110R</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-04</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: LG Innotek Camera Model LNV5110R; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7742; Summary: An authentication vulnerability exists in the camera model's firmware, allowing a malicious actor to upload an HTTP POST request to the device's non-volatile storage and potentially gain administrative access. Successful exploitation could lead to remote code execution at the administrator privilege level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23678</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeywell Experion PKS</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-205-03</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Honeywell Experion PKS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-2520, CVE-2025-2521, CVE-2025-2522, CVE-2025-3946, CVE-2025-3947; Summary: The Honeywell Experion PKS contains multiple vulnerabilities including uninitialized variables, memory buffer issues, sensitive information reuse, integer underflows, and wrong handler deployments. Successful exploitation could lead to information exposure, denial of service, or remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23677</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch This Webinar to Uncover Hidden Flaws in Login, AI, and Digital Trust — and Fix Them</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/watch-this-webinar-to-uncover-hidden.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of managing customer logins and data privacy in the era of AI. It highlights the need for organizations to adapt their identity strategies to keep pace with changing user expectations and emerging threats. The webinar "Navigating Customer Identity in the AI Era" offers insights from Auth0's 2025 CIAM Trends Report, providing attendees with practical advice on navigating these challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/watch-this-webinar-to-uncover-hidden.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall urges admins to patch critical RCE flaw in SMA 100 devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-critical-rce-flaw-in-sma-100-VPN-appliances/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40599; Summary: The SMA 100 series appliances contain a critical authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability that can allow remote threat actors to gain code execution. Attackers need admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability, but SonicWall has not found evidence of active exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-warns-of-critical-rce-flaw-in-sma-100-VPN-appliances/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentests once a year? Nope. It’s time to build an offensive SOC</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/pentests-once-year-nope-its-time-to.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of having an ongoing and dynamic approach to offensive security, rather than relying on periodic pentests or audits. It argues that traditional approaches are insufficient in today's rapidly changing threat landscape and introduces the concept of an "Offensive Security Operations Center" (OSOC) as a solution. The OSOC would continuously validate exposures across prevention, detection, and response layers, using tools such as Breach and Attack Simulation (BAS) and Automated Penetration Testing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/pentests-once-year-nope-its-time-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China-Based APTs Deploy Fake Dalai Lama Apps to Spy on Tibetan Community</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-based-apts-deploy-fake-dalai-lama.html</link>
      <description>A China-nexus cyber espionage group has been targeting the Tibetan community with two campaigns (Operation GhostChat and Operation PhantomPrayers) ahead of the Dalai Lama's 90th birthday. The attacks use watering hole techniques, compromising legitimate websites and installing backdoors on victim systems to gather sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/china-based-apts-deploy-fake-dalai-lama.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Exploit Cursor Background Agents to Take Over Amazon EC2 Instance</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-exploit-cursor-background-agents/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cursor's Background Agents; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability in Cursor's Background Agents that allows unauthorized access to an Amazon EC2 instance. The vulnerability is exploited through the "Show Terminal" button, which provides direct command-line access to the remote infrastructure. The researchers gain root access and can execute commands on the compromised machine, highlighting potential risks for privilege escalation and malicious activities such as cryptocurrency mining or data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=151112</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm-2603 Exploits SharePoint Flaws to Deploy Warlock Ransomware on Unpatched Systems</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/storm-2603-exploits-sharepoint-flaws-to.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: The article discusses a vulnerability in on-premises Microsoft SharePoint Server that allows attackers to deploy Warlock ransomware. The attack chain involves exploiting two vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-49706 and CVE-2025-49704) to gain initial access, conduct lateral movement, and ultimately deploy the ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/storm-2603-exploits-sharepoint-flaws-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the new Chaos RaaS group attacks</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/new-chaos-ransomware/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be an analysis of the Chaos ransomware group's tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs). The article highlights the similarities between the Chaos ransomware and other notable groups such as BlackSuit (Royal) ransomware. It also provides details on how the malware works, including its encryption methods and cleanup procedures.

Some key points from the article include:

1. The Chaos ransomware uses hybrid cryptographic techniques, combining Elliptic Curve Diffie-Hellman (ECDH) with Curve25519 for asymmetric operations and AES-256 for symmetric file encryption.
2. The ransomware performs selective encryption based on command-line configuration parameters, allowing operators to customize the attack.
3. The malware targets local and network resources, using SMB connections to encrypt shared drives and distributed file systems.
4. The article provides details on how the Chaos ransomware can be detected and blocked by various Cisco products, including Secure Endpoint, Secure Email, Secure Firewall, and others.

Overall, this article appears to be a comprehensive analysis of the Chaos ransomware group's TTPs, highlighting their similarities with other notable groups and providing insights into how they operate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68812cd32e0cc100010c34d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
