<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:04:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0-PHP Vulnerability Enables Unauthorized Access for Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/auth0-php-vulnerability-enables-unauthorized-access/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Auth0-PHP SDK; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Auth0-PHP SDK versions 8.0.0-BETA1 and newer have a critical security vulnerability that allows unauthorized access to applications through brute force attacks on session cookie authentication tags, potentially leading to session hijacking and exploitation of sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136783</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Exploitation of Ivanti EPMM Zero-Day Vulnerability in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-epmm-zero-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Enterprise Mobility Management (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: The zero-day vulnerability in Ivanti's EPMM platform can be chained with another vulnerability to achieve remote code execution, posing a significant threat to unpatched systems. Attackers have already attempted to exploit these security flaws, and many vulnerable instances remain exposed despite public disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136770</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft unveils Windows AI Foundry for AI-powered PC apps</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-unveils-windows-ai-foundry-for-ai-powered-pc-apps/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article discusses Microsoft's new Windows AI Foundry, a tool that helps developers build, experiment, and reach users with AI experiences in their apps. The feature allows for the integration of various AI models, including open-source ones from Nvidia, and provides ready-to-use APIs for tasks such as text intelligence and image description. Additionally, it includes features like Foundry Local, which automatically matches models to a device's hardware, and developer tools like a command-line tool and SDK.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-unveils-windows-ai-foundry-for-ai-powered-pc-apps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Arrested for Taking Over SEC Social Media to Spread False Bitcoin News</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hacker-arrested-for-taking-over-sec-social-media/</link>
      <description>A 26-year-old man, Eric Council Jr., has been sentenced to 14 months in prison for orchestrating a sophisticated SIM swap attack that allowed him to hijack the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) social media account on X, formerly known as Twitter. The unauthorized access was used to post false information about Bitcoin ETF approvals, causing significant market volatility in cryptocurrency prices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136763</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Cobalt Strike Beacons Using Shodan: A Researcher’s Guide</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/investigating-cobalt-strike-beacons-using-shodan/</link>
      <description>A security researcher has published a method for gathering threat intelligence on Cobalt Strike beacons using Shodan and PowerShell. The technique allows security professionals to collect configuration data from active Cobalt Strike servers, including beacon SpawnTo values and watermarks, which are critical for detection and attribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136752</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Car Hack Exposes Owner’s Personal Data and Service Records</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/volkswagen-car-hack-exposes-owners-personal-data/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Volkswagen My Volkswagen app; CVE(s): None; Summary: The My Volkswagen app contains critical security flaws that allowed unauthorized access to vehicle information and personal data. A security researcher discovered the vulnerabilities by exploiting a fundamental authentication weakness and identified multiple API vulnerabilities, including the exposure of sensitive user information and internal system credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136714</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms new "Advanced" Settings for Windows 11</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-new-advanced-settings-for-windows-11/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability, but rather discusses the new "Advanced Settings" feature in Windows 11. The feature allows users and developers to personalize their OS experience by customizing File Explorer and Virtual Machines settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-new-advanced-settings-for-windows-11/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft open-sources Windows Subsystem for Linux at Build 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-open-sources-windows-subsystem-for-linux-at-build-2025/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has open-sourced the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), making its source code available on GitHub, except for a few components that are part of Windows. This move is expected to increase community involvement and contributions to the project, allowing developers to inspect the code, build it themselves, submit improvements, and understand how WSL works under the hood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-open-sources-windows-subsystem-for-linux-at-build-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RVTools Official Site Hacked to Deliver Bumblebee Malware via Trojanized Installer</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/rvtools-official-site-hacked-to-deliver.html</link>
      <description>The official site for RVTools has been hacked to serve a compromised installer for the popular VMware environment reporting utility. Additionally, Procolored printers have been found to include malicious software with features such as collecting system information, logging keystrokes, and propagating via connected USB drives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/rvtools-official-site-hacked-to-deliver.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Legal Aid Agency confirms applicant data stolen in data breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-legal-aid-agency-confirms-applicant-data-stolen-in-data-breach/</link>
      <description>A data breach has occurred at the United Kingdom's Legal Aid Agency (LAA), where hackers stole a large amount of sensitive applicant data, including contact details, dates of birth, national ID numbers, criminal history, employment status, and financial information. The agency is advising all applicants to be vigilant for potential scam attempts targeting them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-legal-aid-agency-confirms-applicant-data-stolen-in-data-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Reveals Hackers Targeting US Following UK Retailer Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-reveals-hackers-targeting-us/</link>
      <description>UNC3944, a well-known hacker collective, has been identified by the Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) as a persistent and dynamic cyberthreat. The group has evolved from initial SIM swap operations to ransomware and data theft extortion tactics, with a focus on large enterprises in English-speaking countries. Their modus operandi relies heavily on sophisticated social engineering, and they have orchestrated sector-specific waves of attacks, including financial services, food services, and retail sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136669</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skitnet Malware Employs Stealth Techniques to Execute Payload and Maintain Persistence Techniques</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/skitnet-malware-employs-stealth-techniques/</link>
      <description>Skitnet (Bossnet) is a highly sophisticated multi-stage malware developed by the threat group LARVA-306. It features advanced stealth techniques and evasion methods to execute its malicious payload, maintain persistent access on infected systems, and evade detection by security defenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136656</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Gangs Use Skitnet Malware for Stealthy Data Theft and Remote Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ransomware-gangs-use-skitnet-malware.html</link>
      <description>Skitnet is a multi-stage malware used by ransomware actors for post-exploitation efforts, stealing sensitive data and establishing remote control over compromised hosts. It uses programming languages like Rust and Nim to evade detection, and incorporates persistence mechanisms, remote access tools, commands for data exfiltration, and download of additional payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/ransomware-gangs-use-skitnet-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla fixes Firefox zero-days exploited at hacking contest</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-zero-days-exploited-at-hacking-contest/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4918, CVE-2025-4919; Summary: Two Firefox zero-day vulnerabilities were demonstrated at the Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 hacking competition. The flaws, tracked under CVE-2025-4918 and CVE-2025-4919, are an out-of-bounds read/write issue in the JavaScript engine and a flaw allowing attackers to perform out-of-bounds reads/writes on a JavaScript object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/mozilla-fixes-firefox-zero-days-exploited-at-hacking-contest/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers earn $1,078,750 for 28 zero-days at Pwn2Own Berlin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-earn-1-078-750-for-28-zero-days-at-pwn2own-berlin/</link>
      <description>The article reports on the Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 hacking competition, where security researchers exploited 29 zero-day vulnerabilities and earned $1,078,750 in cash awards. No specific vulnerability details are provided.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-earn-1-078-750-for-28-zero-days-at-pwn2own-berlin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CTEM is the Winning Bet for CISOs in 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/why-ctem-is-winning-bet-for-cisos-in.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the concept of Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM), which solidifies its role as a strategic enabler for Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs). CTEM integrates Adversarial Exposure Validation (AEV) and Exposure Assessment Platforms (EAP) to empower CISOs to adopt a continuous, adaptive model that keeps pace with attacker techniques and the evolving threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/why-ctem-is-winning-bet-for-cisos-in.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Patches 2 Zero-Days Exploited at Pwn2Own Berlin with $100K in Rewards</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/firefox-patches-2-zero-days-exploited.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4918, CVE-2025-4919; Summary: Two critical security flaws in Firefox browser could allow an attacker to perform out-of-bounds read or write, potentially accessing sensitive data or executing code. The vulnerabilities affect all versions of Firefox before 138.0.4 and certain ESR versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/firefox-patches-2-zero-days-exploited.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: Zero-Day Exploits, Insider Threats, APT Targeting, Botnets and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/weekly-recap-zero-day-exploits-insider.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses various cybersecurity-related topics, including:

1. A Nomad Bridge crypto hack and its alleged perpetrator, Alexander Gurevich.
2. Rogue communication devices found in some Chinese-made solar power inverters that could potentially allow remote control of energy infrastructure.
3. Using V8 browser exploits to bypass Windows Defender Application Control (WDAC).
4. Hidden threats in files users trust too much, such as .desktop files running hidden shell commands or .lnk files launching PowerShell or remote scripts.
5. Cybersecurity tools and webinars for improving security practices.

No specific software or hardware vulnerabilities are discussed in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/weekly-recap-zero-day-exploits-insider.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit RVTools to Deploy Bumblebee Malware on Windows Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-rvtools-to-deploy-bumblebee-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: RVTools; CVE(s): None; Summary: The RVTools installer was compromised with a custom variant of the Bumblebee loader malware, which served as an initial access vector for cyber campaigns. The vulnerability allowed attackers to exploit trust in the software supply chain and deploy malicious payloads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136620</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confluence Servers Under Attack: Hackers Leverage Vulnerability for RDP Access and Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-leverage-vulnerability-for-rdp-access-and-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Atlassian Confluence; CVE(s): CVE-2023-22527; Summary: A template injection flaw in unpatched Atlassian Confluence servers exposed to the internet allowed threat actors to exploit remote code execution (RCE), gaining initial access and establishing a foothold within targeted networks. The vulnerability was exploited through a meticulously planned intrusion, leading to data encryption and lateral movement using various tools and tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136580</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ModiLoader Malware Campaign Targets Windows PCs, Harvesting User Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-modiloader-malware-campaign-targets-windows-pcs/</link>
      <description>The article describes a malicious campaign distributing ModiLoader (DBatLoader) malware through phishing emails. The malware uses a multi-stage infection process to deploy SnakeKeylogger, an infostealer malware that steals sensitive data and transmits it to a Telegram bot. The infection process involves various evasion tactics, including DLL side-loading and manipulation of Windows Defender exclusion paths, making detection challenging for standard antivirus solutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136549</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Care Data Breach Costs BreachForums Admin $700,000 Fine</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/health-care-data-breach-costs-breachforums/</link>
      <description>Conor Brian Fitzpatrick, a former administrator of the cybercrime forum Breachforums, will forfeit approximately $700,000 to settle a civil lawsuit related to a healthcare data breach. This marks a rare instance where a cybercriminal's assets directly compensate victims of a data breach. The case highlights connections between cybercriminal communities and more serious offenses, such as possession of child sexual abuse material (CSAM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136685</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Firefox 0-Day Flaws Allow Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-firefox-0-day-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Mozilla Firefox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4918, CVE-2025-4919; Summary: Two critical 0-day vulnerabilities in Firefox allow remote attackers to execute malicious code. The flaws, tracked as CVE-2025-4918 and CVE-2025-4919, arise from out-of-bounds access conditions when resolving Promise objects or handling linear sums in array operations, allowing data leakage, browser crashes, or arbitrary code execution under the context of the browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136587</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA to Stop Publishing Cybersecurity Alerts and Advisories on Webpages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-to-stop-publishing-cybersecurity-alerts/</link>
      <description>CISA has announced changes to its communication strategy for cybersecurity updates and guidance, shifting away from listing advisories on its webpage to focus on direct communication channels. The change was temporarily paused after community feedback, with the agency reassessing its approach to information sharing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136652</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pwn2Own Day 3: Zero-Day Exploits Windows 11, VMware ESXi, and Firefox</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pwn2own-day-3-zero-day-exploits/</link>
      <description>The Pwn2Own Berlin 2025 competition showcased impressive technological achievements, demonstrating critical zero-day vulnerabilities in high-profile targets like Windows 11, VMware ESXi, and Mozilla Firefox. The event's prize pool reached $1,078,750, highlighting the growing importance of security research in an increasingly connected world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136611</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNU C(glibc) Vulnerability Let Attackers Execute Arbitrary Code on Millions of Linux Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-glibc-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: GNU C Library (glibc); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4802; Summary: A vulnerability in the glibc library allows attackers to execute malicious code with elevated privileges by placing a malicious shared library in a location specified by the LD_LIBRARY_PATH environment variable. The flaw affects statically linked setuid binaries that incorrectly search library paths, potentially allowing local attackers to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136576</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting dMSA for Advanced Active Directory Persistence</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/exploiting-dmsa-for-advanced-ad-persistence/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): None; Summary: Delegated Managed Service Accounts (dMSAs) in Windows Server 2025 can be manipulated by attackers with specific permissions to establish persistent access. Attackers can exploit Access Control List (ACL) inheritance to gain full visibility and control over dMSA objects, achieving persistence through creating additional dMSAs or adding unauthorized entities to the PrincipalAllowedToRetrieveManagedPassword attribute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136553</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'Defendnot' tool tricks Windows into disabling Microsoft Defender</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/new-defendnot-tool-tricks-windows-into-disabling-microsoft-defender/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: No specific product mentioned; Defendnot is the tool being discussed; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Defendnot tool can disable Microsoft Defender on Windows devices by registering a fake antivirus product, using an undocumented Windows Security Center API. This allows the tool to bypass Windows' safeguards and register the dummy antivirus, effectively disabling real-time protection for the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/new-defendnot-tool-tricks-windows-into-disabling-microsoft-defender/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware ESXi, Firefox, Red Hat Linux &amp; SharePoint Hacked – Pwn2Own Day 2</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-esxi-firefox-red-hat-linux-sharepoint-hacked/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): None; Summary: Viettel Cyber Security used an OOB Write for a Guest-to-Host escape on Oracle VirtualBox, earning $40,000 and 4 Master of Pwn points.

FYSA: The competition has awarded a cumulative total of $695,000 with participants revealing 20 unique zero-day vulnerabilities thus far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136532</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft confirms May Windows 10 updates trigger BitLocker recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-may-windows-10-updates-trigger-bitlocker-recovery/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: Some Windows 10 and Windows 10 Enterprise LTSC 2021 systems will boot into BitLocker recovery after installing the May 2025 security updates. This issue may trigger an Automatic Repair, which requires input of a BitLocker recovery key to initiate the repair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-confirms-may-windows-10-updates-trigger-bitlocker-recovery/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 18:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical WordPress Plugin Flaw Puts Over 10,000 Sites of Cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-wordpress-plugin-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Eventin plugin for WordPress; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Eventin plugin allows unauthenticated users to gain administrative access to affected sites due to a lack of proper permission checks in the /wp-json/eventin/v2/speakers/import REST API endpoint. This vulnerability can be exploited by uploading a CSV file containing user details, including the desired role set to administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136486</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophisticated NPM Attack Leverages Google Calendar2 for Advanced Communication</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophisticated-npm-attack-leverages-google-calendar2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: os-info-checker-es6; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated malware campaign was embedded within the npm package os-info-checker-es6, which evolved from gathering basic OS information to a complex threat using platform-specific compiled Node.js modules and obfuscation techniques. The malware employed steganography, Unicode-based hiding of malicious payloads, and a command-and-control mechanism utilizing Google Calendar short links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136460</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ransomware Attack Targets Elon Musk Supporters Using PowerShell to Deploy Payloads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-ransomware-attack-targets-elon-musk-supporters/</link>
      <description>A newly identified ransomware campaign targets supporters of Elon Musk through a sophisticated phishing-based attack. The attack begins with a deceptive PDF document, which leads to the download of malicious ZIP files hosted on Netlify. The infection chain involves multi-stage PowerShell scripts and executables designed to compromise the target system, ultimately deploying a variant of the Fog ransomware for financial gain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136498</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printer Company Distributes Malicious Drivers Infected with XRed Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/printer-company-distributes-malicious-drivers-infected/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Procolored; CVE(s): None; Summary: Procolored's software drivers contained malicious code, including the XRed backdoor malware and SnipVex virus. The XRed backdoor facilitated keylogging, file downloads, screenshots, and remote command execution, while SnipVex posed a persistent threat by targeting .exe files and replacing Bitcoin addresses in the clipboard to divert transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Agent Impersonate as Stanford Student For Intelligence Gathering</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-agent-impersonate-as-stanford-student/</link>
      <description>A Chinese intelligence operative posing as a Stanford University student has been uncovered, targeting students conducting China-related research. The agent used the alias "Charles Chen" and employed a "crowdsourced approach" to gather sensitive information, including using civilians unaffiliated with intelligence agencies to collect data. This case highlights concerns about Chinese intelligence activities at American universities and the need for increased awareness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136455</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel arrests new suspect behind Nomad Bridge $190M crypto hack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/israel-arrests-new-suspect-behind-nomad-bridge-190m-crypto-hack/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Nomad bridge smart-contract; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Nomad bridge smart-contract introduced a critical vulnerability in its Replica smart contract, allowing hackers to siphon over $190 million worth of assets. The flaw allowed any message with a correct root hash to be accepted, even if the underlying proof was invalid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/legal/israel-arrests-new-suspect-behind-nomad-bridge-190m-crypto-hack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT rolls out Codex, an AI tool for software programming</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-rolls-out-codex-an-ai-tool-for-software-programming/</link>
      <description>The article discusses OpenAI's new AI agent, Codex, which automates and delegates programming tasks for software engineers. Codex can write new code, propose pull requests, and run each task in its own sandbox, making developers more productive with AI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-rolls-out-codex-an-ai-tool-for-software-programming/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers exploit VMware ESXi, Microsoft SharePoint zero-days at Pwn2Own</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-vmware-esxi-microsoft-sharepoint-zero-days-at-pwn2own/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Multiple; CVE(s): None; Summary: Competitors successfully exploited zero-day bugs in multiple products, including Microsoft SharePoint, VMware ESXi, Oracle VirtualBox, Red Hat Enterprise Linux, and Mozilla Firefox, earning a total of $695,000 over the first two days of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-exploit-vmware-esxi-microsoft-sharepoint-zero-days-at-pwn2own/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printer maker Procolored offered malware-laced drivers for months</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/printer-maker-procolored-offered-malware-laced-drivers-for-months/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Procolored printers; CVE(s): None; Summary: The official software supplied with Procolored printers included a remote access trojan (XRedRAT) and a cryptocurrency stealer (SnipVex) for at least six months. These malware were delivered through the companion software and drivers for Procolored UV printer models F8, F13, F13 Pro, V6, V11 Pro, and VF13 Pro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/printer-maker-procolored-offered-malware-laced-drivers-for-months/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gangs increasingly use Skitnet post-exploitation malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-increasingly-use-skitnet-post-exploitation-malware/</link>
      <description>Skitnet ("Bossnet") is a new malware used by ransomware gangs for post-exploitation activities. It uses a Rust-based loader to decrypt a Nim binary and establish a DNS-based reverse shell for communication with the command and control server. The malware supports various commands, including persistence, screenshot capture, remote access tool installation, and antivirus enumeration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/ransomware-gangs-increasingly-use-skitnet-post-exploitation-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 KB5058379 Update Causes PCs to Enter Recovery Mode and Prompt for BitLocker Key</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-10-kb5058379-update-causes-pcs/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Windows 10; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Windows 10 KB5058379 security update causes technical issues for numerous systems, booting them into Windows Recovery mode and requiring BitLocker recovery keys. This issue affects enterprise environments, particularly those using SCCM or WSUS deployment mechanisms, and is caused by the update triggering BitLocker's hardware validation mechanisms inappropriately during installation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136448</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal Andrei Tarasov Escapes US Extradition, Returns to Russia</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cybercriminal-andrei-tarasov-escapes-us-extradition/</link>
      <description>Andrei Vladimirovich Tarasov, a Russian cybercrime figure known as "Aels," has returned to Russia after evading US extradition. He was released from German custody and used ride-sharing services and transportation routes without showing identification documents to make his escape. Tarasov remains active in cybercrime circles, participating in spamming channels on Telegram and sharing plans for hacking Zimbra servers at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136434</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HTTPBot Botnet Launches 200+ Precision DDoS Attacks on Gaming and Tech Sectors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-httpbot-botnet-launches-200.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a botnet malware called HTTPBot that targets Windows systems in China's gaming industry, technology companies, and educational institutions. It uses various attack modules to launch distributed denial-of-service attacks with "scalpel-like" precision, bypassing traditional rule-based detection mechanisms by simulating HTTP protocols and mimicking legitimate browser behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/new-httpbot-botnet-launches-200.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Alerts Public to Malicious Campaign Impersonating US Government Officials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fbi-alerts-public-to-malicious-campaign/</link>
      <description>The Federal Bureau of Investigation has issued a warning about an ongoing malicious messaging campaign targeting current and former senior US government officials and their contacts. Threat actors are impersonating high-ranking US officials through text messages and AI-generated voice calls to gain access to personal accounts and potentially sensitive information, using "smishing" (SMS phishing) and "vishing" (voice phishing) tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136383</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frigidstealer Malware Targets macOS Users to Harvest Login Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/frigidstealer-malware-targets-macos-users/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: macOS; CVE(s): None; Summary: FrigidStealer is an information-stealing malware that targets macOS users by masquerading as routine browser updates. It bypasses Gatekeeper protections and steals sensitive data such as browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and system information. The malware operates with sophistication, establishing persistence through launchservicesd and employing Apple Events for unauthorized inter-process communication to harvest data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136377</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT Group 123 Targets Windows Systems in Ongoing Malicious Payload Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/apt-group-123-targets-windows-systems/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: This article is about Group123, a North Korean state-sponsored APT group that targets Windows-based systems across multiple regions. The group's primary motivation is information theft and espionage, often aligning with North Korea's strategic interests. They use various tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) to carry out their attacks, including spear phishing, exploiting software vulnerabilities, and using custom malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136321</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH Auth Key Reuse Uncovers Advanced Targeted Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ssh-auth-key-reuse-targeted-phishing-campaign/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated phishing campaign targeting Kuwait's fisheries, telecommunications, and insurance sectors has been exposed by Hunt.io researchers. The campaign uses 230 malicious domains, a network of servers, and advanced tradecraft to harvest credentials from unsuspecting users. It leverages reused SSH authentication keys, consistent Autonomous System Number (ASN) usage, and multi-tenant server usage for efficiency, underscoring the threat actors' focus on scalability and persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136349</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Endpoint Manager Vulnerabilities Allow Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ivanti-endpoint-manager-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM); CVE(s): CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428; Summary: A critical vulnerability chain in Ivanti EPMM allows pre-authenticated remote code execution attacks without credentials. The chain consists of an authentication bypass (CVE-2025-4427) and a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability (CVE-2025-4428), enabling attackers to compromise systems without credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136342</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Best Practices for Effective Data Protection</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-10-best-practices-for-effective.html</link>
      <description>This article discusses data protection best practices to safeguard sensitive data from cyber threats. It covers topics such as understanding the outcome you want, identifying crown jewel data, defining a data protection program, using AI-powered classification, adopting a zero-trust architecture, and ensuring compliance with regulations. The article also touches on unmanaged devices, browser isolation, cloud posture management, and data security training.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/05/top-10-best-practices-for-effective.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenkins Released Security Updates – Multiple Vulnerabilities Fixed That Allow Attackers to Exploit CI/CD Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/jenkins-released-security-updates-multiple-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various Jenkins plugins; CVEs: CVE-2025-47884, CVE-2025-47889, CVE-2025-47885, CVE-2025-47886, CVE-2025-47887, CVE-2025-47888; Summary: Multiple vulnerabilities were identified in various Jenkins plugins, including authentication bypasses, cross-site scripting, and missing permission checks. These flaws could allow attackers to compromise Jenkins environments, bypass authentication, or gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=136288</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
