<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://janebytes.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>JaneBytes Cybersecurity Feed</title>
    <link>https://janebytes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Summarized articles from top cybersecurity sources.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>1800</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Cybercriminal Listings Target Fujitsu, Baxter Kelly, AGX Financeira, and a Belgian IT Platform</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cybercriminal-listings-target-fujitsu-baxter-kelly-agx-financeira-and-a-belgian-it-platform/</link>
      <description>This article reports on several new listings for unauthorized access sales and data breaches affecting companies across Japan, the U.K., Brazil, and Belgium. The listings include sensitive internal files, Citrix access, customer data, and administrative control over a monitoring system, with prices ranging from $1,500 to $20,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061978</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolShell Campaign: New SharePoint Zero-Day (CVE-2025-53770) Triggers Widespread Exploitation</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/toolshell-sharepoint-zero-day-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint, identified as CVE-2025-53770, is actively being exploited in targeted attacks. The vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication, gain remote code execution capabilities, and establish persistent access using stolen cryptographic keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061964</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHP PDO Flaw Allows Attackers to Inject Malicious SQL Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/php-pdo-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: PHP PDO; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious SQL commands by exploiting weaknesses in PDO's SQL parser. This affects millions of web applications worldwide, even when developers implement prepared statements correctly. Attackers can manipulate PDO's parsing logic through carefully constructed payloads, leading to SQL injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150385</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚡ Weekly Recap: SharePoint 0-Day, Chrome Exploit, macOS Spyware, NVIDIA Toolkit RCE and More</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The provided article appears to be a summary of various cyber-related incidents, attacks, and trends from around the world. The article discusses malware families like Rainbow Hyena, DiskStation Security, and Katz Stealer; phishing campaigns targeting specific industries or organizations; and large-scale cyber thefts affecting financial institutions and other entities.

There are no explicit discussions about vulnerabilities in software, hardware, or firmware within this article. However, the article does touch upon various cybersecurity concerns and threats that could potentially impact different systems and organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/weekly-recap-sharepoint-0-day-chrome.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 CrushFTP servers exposed to ongoing hijack attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: All CrushFTP versions below 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23 are vulnerable to hijack attacks that exploit a critical security bug due to mishandled AS2 validation, allowing admin access to the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/over-1-000-crushftp-servers-exposed-to-ongoing-hijack-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Role of AI in Zero Trust</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in Zero Trust architecture, highlighting its capabilities in adaptive trust, continuous risk evaluation, and automation. It also emphasizes the importance of human-machine teaming, where AI amplifies human decision-making rather than replacing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/assessing-role-of-ai-in-zero-trust.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance Firm Exploits SS7 Flaw to Track User Locations</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/surveillance-firm-exploits-ss7-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SS7 (Signaling System No. 7) protocol; CVE(s): None; Summary: A sophisticated surveillance operation has been discovered exploiting critical vulnerabilities in the global telecommunications infrastructure to track mobile phone users' locations without authorization. The attack leverages weaknesses in the decades-old SS7 protocol that underpins international cellular networks, manipulating the TCAP layer and using an obscure encoding technique called "extended tag encoding" to disguise malicious location tracking requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn 14 Languages from Babbel with this exclusive StackSocial deal</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</link>
      <description>The article is promoting language learning platforms Babbel, uTalk, and Rosetta Stone, offering lifetime subscriptions and discounts. It highlights the features of each platform, such as AI conversation partners and personalized review sessions. The article also includes a free board report deck for CISOs to present cloud security risks and priorities in business terms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/learn-14-languages-from-babbel-with-this-exclusive-stacksocial-deal/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dell confirms breach of test lab platform by World Leaks extortion group</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</link>
      <description>World Leaks, a rebranded extortion gang, has breached Dell's product demonstration platform and is trying to extort the company into paying a ransom. The stolen data is believed to be synthetic test data used in product demonstrations and trials, with only a very outdated contact list being legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/dell-confirms-breach-of-test-lab-platform-by-world-leaks-extortion-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinDCX Hack Leads to $44.2 Million Loss</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/coindcx-hack-leads-to-44-2-million-loss/</link>
      <description>CoinDCX, an Indian cryptocurrency exchange, suffered a significant security breach that resulted in approximately $44 million in losses. Despite the incident, customer funds remain secure and unaffected, thanks to the company's segregated account architecture. The investigation is ongoing to identify vulnerabilities, implement additional safety measures, and trace the movement of compromised funds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150352</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE‑2025‑37103: Remote Access Risk in Aruba Instant On Access Points Due to Hardcoded Passwords</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve202537103-aruba-instant-on-hardcoded-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, CVE-2025-37102; Summary: The Aruba Instant On access points contain a critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-37103) that allows remote access to the device's web interface without authentication due to a hardcoded admin password. This flaw can be exploited to gain administrative access and launch lateral attacks across the internal network, and when combined with CVE-2025-37102, it enables command injection and remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061953</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-54309: New CrushFTP Zero-Day Exploited in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-54309-new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in CrushFTP allows attackers to gain administrator-level access through the HTTPS interface on unpatched servers, enabling file theft, privilege escalation, and deeper network compromise. The flaw affects versions prior to 10.8.5 and 11.3.4_23, and building released after July 1, 2025, contain the fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061943</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AppLocker Flaw Lets Malicious Apps Bypass Security Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-applocker-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft AppLocker; CVE(s): None; Summary: The vulnerability in Microsoft's AppLocker security feature allows malicious applications to bypass established security restrictions by exploiting a seemingly minor error in the MaximumFileVersion field. Attackers could potentially modify a blocked executable's version number to exceed the configured maximum version, but this would simultaneously break the file's digital signature, making it detectable by systems configured with "signed executables only" policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150306</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Livewire Flaw Puts Millions of Laravel Apps at Risk of RCE Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/livewire-flaw-of-rce-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Livewire; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54068; Summary: A critical remote command execution vulnerability exists in Livewire versions from 3.0.0-beta.1 to 3.6.3, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the server by injecting malicious code through property updates. Exploitation requires only a vulnerable component with default configuration, and no user authentication or interaction is necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Issues Alert on Microsoft SharePoint 0-Day RCE Exploited in Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-issues-alert-on-microsoft-sharepoint-0-day-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint Server allows unauthorized attackers to execute arbitrary code remotely over a network, potentially giving cybercriminals complete control over affected systems. The flaw stems from deserialization of untrusted data and is actively being exploited in cyberattacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150250</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-Zip Vulnerability Lets Malicious RAR5 Files Crash Systems</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/7-zip-vulnerability-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: 7-Zip; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53816; Summary: A critical denial-of-service vulnerability in 7-Zip's RAR5 decoder allows attackers to crash systems by processing specially crafted RAR5 archive files, leading to memory corruption and system crashes. The vulnerability occurs due to a heap buffer overflow when the decoder attempts to repair corrupted archive items, resulting in writing data beyond allocated buffer boundaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150238</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoisonSeed Hackers Bypass FIDO Keys Using QR Phishing and Cross-Device Sign-In Abuse</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/poisonseed-hackers-bypass-fido-keys.html</link>
      <description>A novel attack technique has been disclosed, allowing threat actors to downgrade Fast IDentity Online (FIDO) key protections by deceiving users into approving authentication requests from spoofed company login portals. The attack exploits a legitimate FIDO feature called cross-device sign-in and does not exploit any flaw in the FIDO implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/poisonseed-hackers-bypass-fido-keys.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoisonSeed Attack Tricks Users into Scanning Malicious MFA QR Codes</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/poisonseed-attack-scanning-malicious-mfa-qr-codes/</link>
      <description>The PoisonSeed threat group has developed an attack technique that exploits FIDO key cross-device sign-in features, bypassing multifactor authentication (MFA) and allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to protected accounts through social engineering tactics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150201</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 05:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharePoint 0-Day RCE Flaw Actively Exploited for Full Server Takeover</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sharepoint-0-day-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A new SharePoint vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770) is being actively exploited in large-scale attacks worldwide, enabling attackers to gain complete control of on-premise servers without authentication. The exploit chain, dubbed "ToolShell," leverages previously demonstrated Pwn2Own vulnerabilities to achieve remote code execution and steals cryptographic secrets from SharePoint servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150197</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrushFTP 0-Day Vulnerability Actively Exploited to Breach Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/crushftp-0-day-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability in CrushFTP servers is being actively exploited by threat actors to compromise systems worldwide. The vulnerability allows attackers to exploit a previously patched issue that remained present in outdated installations, making it critical for organizations to maintain current software versions and implement recommended security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150193</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft releases emergency patches for SharePoint RCE flaws exploited in attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-patches-for-sharepoint-rce-flaws-exploited-in-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: Two zero-day vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-53770 and CVE-2025-53771) were exploited in "ToolShell" attacks to achieve remote code execution on Microsoft SharePoint servers worldwide. The flaws bypassed previous patches and impacted over 54 organizations. Emergency updates have been released for Microsoft SharePoint Subscription Edition, SharePoint 2019, and are still being worked on for SharePoint 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-releases-emergency-patches-for-sharepoint-rce-flaws-exploited-in-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Releases Urgent Patch for SharePoint RCE Flaw Exploited in Ongoing Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-releases-urgent-patch-for.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-53771; Summary: The exploited vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770) is a remote code execution flaw that arises from the deserialization of untrusted data in on-premise versions of Microsoft SharePoint Server. The newly disclosed spoofing flaw (CVE-2025-53771) allows an authorized attacker to perform spoofing over a network. These flaws are related to two other SharePoint vulnerabilities, and the exploit chain has been patched as part of Microsoft's July 2025 Patch Tuesday update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/microsoft-releases-urgent-patch-for.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-Coded Credentials Found in HPE Instant On Devices Allow Admin Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hard-coded-credentials-found-in-hpe.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett-Packard Enterprise (HPE) Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, CVE-2025-37102; Summary: The HPE Instant On Access Points have a critical security flaw that allows an attacker to bypass authentication and gain administrative access. Additionally, there is an authenticated command injection flaw in the command-line interface that could be exploited with elevated permissions to run arbitrary commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hard-coded-credentials-found-in-hpe.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,500 Websites Hijacked to Secretly Mine Crypto Using Stealth JavaScript and WebSocket Tactics</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/3500-websites-hijacked-to-secretly-mine.html</link>
      <description>A new attack campaign has compromised over 3,500 websites worldwide with JavaScript cryptocurrency miners, using obfuscated JavaScript, WebSockets, and infrastructure reuse to stay hidden. The malware assesses device capabilities, spawns background Web Workers for mining tasks, and dynamically adjusts mining intensity based on device power without raising alarms.

FYSA: Threat actors are leveraging browser-based cryptojacking attacks, exploiting JavaScript embeds, Google OAuth endpoints, WordPress databases, and plugins to compromise websites and inject malicious code. They use stealthy miners, obfuscation, and infrastructure reuse to stay hidden, prioritizing persistence over resource theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/3500-websites-hijacked-to-secretly-mine.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EncryptHub Targets Web3 Developers Using Fake AI Platforms to Deploy Fickle Stealer Malware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/encrypthub-targets-web3-developers.html</link>
      <description>EncryptHub (aka LARVA-208 and Water Gamayun), a financially motivated threat actor, has been attributed to a new campaign targeting Web3 developers with information stealer malware. The attackers use fake AI platforms and trick victims into clicking on meeting links, which ultimately lead to the download of malicious software disguised as a genuine Realtek HD Audio Driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/encrypthub-targets-web3-developers.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SharePoint zero-day exploited in RCE attacks, no patch available</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-sharepoint-zero-day-exploited-in-rce-attacks-no-patch-available/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706, CVE-2025-49704; Summary: A critical zero-day vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint (CVE-2025-53770) is being actively exploited since July 18th, allowing attackers to steal the MachineKey configuration and inject malicious code. The vulnerability has been chained with two other flaws (CVE-2025-49706 and CVE-2025-49704) to achieve remote code execution. A security update will be released as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-sharepoint-zero-day-exploited-in-rce-attacks-no-patch-available/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPE warns of hardcoded passwords in Aruba access points</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hpe-warns-of-hardcoded-passwords-in-aruba-access-points/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: HPE Aruba Instant On Access Points; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37103, None; Summary: Hardcoded login credentials in Aruba Instant On Access Points allow attackers to bypass normal device authentication and access the web interface, enabling administrative access. This vulnerability can be exploited by remote attackers to change settings, install backdoors, capture traffic, or perform lateral movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hpe-warns-of-hardcoded-passwords-in-aruba-access-points/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability, CVE-2025-53770 “ToolShell,” to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/20/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-cve-2025-53770-toolshell-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770; Summary: The vulnerability, a remote code execution issue, has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalog due to active exploitation. It poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and should be remediated by affected organizations as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23642</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Releases Guidance on Exploitation of SharePoint Vulnerability (CVE-2025-53770)</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/20/microsoft-releases-guidance-exploitation-sharepoint-vulnerability-cve-2025-53770</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, CVE-2025-49706; Summary: A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in on-premise SharePoint servers enables unauthorized access and allows malicious actors to execute code over the network. The vulnerability is actively being exploited and poses a risk to organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23640</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Unpatched SharePoint Zero-Day Actively Exploited, Breaches 75+ Global Organizations</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-microsoft-sharepoint-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53770, None; Summary: A zero-day flaw in Microsoft SharePoint Server tracked as CVE-2025-53770 (CVSS score: 9.8) allows an unauthorized attacker to execute code over a network through deserialization of untrusted data. The vulnerability is being exploited in a large-scale campaign and has been linked to the previously disclosed CVE-2025-49706.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-microsoft-sharepoint-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malware Injected into 6 npm Packages After Maintainer Tokens Stolen in Phishing Attack</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malware-injected-into-6-npm-packages.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm packages; CVE(s): None; Summary: A supply chain attack targeted popular npm packages via a phishing campaign designed to steal project maintainers' npm tokens. The captured tokens were used to publish malicious versions of the packages, attempting to execute a DLL on Windows machines and potentially allowing remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/malware-injected-into-6-npm-packages.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Critical CrushFTP Flaw to Gain Admin Access on Unpatched Servers</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-critical-crushftp-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to obtain admin access via HTTPS due to mishandled AS2 validation in CrushFTP 10 before 10.8.5 and 11 before 11.3.4_23, when the DMZ proxy feature is not used. This critical flaw has been actively exploited in the wild since July 18, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-critical-crushftp-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat actors downgrade FIDO2 MFA auth in PoisonSeed phishing attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-downgrade-fido2-mfa-auth-in-poisonseed-phishing-attack/</link>
      <description>The PoisonSeed threat actors are bypassing FIDO2 security key protections by abusing the cross-device sign-in feature in WebAuthn to trick users into approving login authentication requests from fake company portals. This attack does not exploit a flaw in FIDO2's implementation but rather uses a legitimate feature that downgrades the FIDO key authentication process. The threat actors can initiate a login flow that relies on cross-device authentication instead of the user's physical FIDO2 key, effectively bypassing security key protections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/threat-actors-downgrade-fido2-mfa-auth-in-poisonseed-phishing-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular npm linter packages hijacked via phishing to drop malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/popular-npm-linter-packages-hijacked-via-phishing-to-drop-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: npm package eslint-config-prettier; CVE(s): None; Summary: The npm package eslint-config-prettier was compromised after its maintainer fell victim to a phishing attack, allowing the attacker to publish malicious versions of the package that can infect Windows machines. The affected versions are 8.10.1, 9.1.1, 10.1.6, and 10.1.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/popular-npm-linter-packages-hijacked-via-phishing-to-drop-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT"s GPT-5-reasoning-alpha model spotted ahead of launch</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-gpt-5-reasoning-alpha-model-spotted-ahead-of-launch/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the upcoming release of OpenAI's GPT-5 model, which may unify breakthroughs from previous models. Additionally, leaks suggest that a new "o3-alpha" model may be released, featuring improved coding and frontend design capabilities. There is no mention of vulnerabilities or cybersecurity threats in this article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/chatgpts-gpt-5-reasoning-alpha-model-spotted-ahead-of-launch/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 12:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI, Anthropic, Google may disrupt education market with new AI tools</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-anthropic-google-may-disrupt-education-market-with-new-ai-tools/</link>
      <description>AI companies like OpenAI and Anthropic are developing new AI-based learning tools for students, such as Study Together features that guide the learning process. Google is also testing a similar feature called Guided Learning for Gemini. These tools aim to aid in student learning and potentially disrupt the online education market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-anthropic-google-may-disrupt-education-market-with-new-ai-tools/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New CrushFTP zero-day exploited in attacks to hijack servers</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks-to-hijack-servers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: CrushFTP; CVE(s): CVE-2025-54309; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-54309 allows attackers to gain administrative access via the web interface on vulnerable servers. The vulnerability affects versions prior to CrushFTP v10.8.5 and v11.3.4_23, which were released around July 1st.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-crushftp-zero-day-exploited-in-attacks-to-hijack-servers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux pulls AUR packages that installed Chaos RAT malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arch-linux-pulls-aur-packages-that-installed-chaos-rat-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Arch User Repository (AUR); CVE(s): None; Summary: The AUR was compromised when a malicious user uploaded three packages containing the CHAOS remote access trojan (RAT). The packages were designed to install the malware on Linux devices, which can be used for cryptocurrency mining, credential harvesting, or cyber espionage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/arch-linux-pulls-aur-packages-that-installed-chaos-rat-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 21:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Threat Actors Operate 2,800 Malicious Domains to Distribute Windows Malware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-threat-actors-operate-2800-malicious-domains/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated threat actor, known as "SilverFox," has been conducting a large-scale malware distribution campaign since at least June 2023, targeting Chinese-speaking individuals and entities. The campaign employs various tactics such as fake application download sites, spurious update prompts, and phishing emails to deliver Windows-specific malware designed for credential theft, financial exploitation, and potential access brokering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150153</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Veeam-Themed Phishing Attack Uses Weaponized WAV File to Target Users</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-veeam-themed-phishing-attack/</link>
      <description>Cybercriminals are using voicemail notifications to distribute malware by impersonating Veeam Software. The attack begins with an email containing a WAV file that, upon playback, reveals a scripted call attempting to create urgency around license expiration. The real danger lies in the weaponized nature of the WAV file itself, which can be embedded with malicious code exploiting vulnerabilities in media players or audio processing libraries.

(Note: Since there is no specific vulnerability mentioned, I've summarized the article as a non-vulnerability related cybersecurity content)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150136</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK ties GRU to stealthy Microsoft 365 credential-stealing malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-ties-russian-gru-to-authentic-antics-credential-stealing-malware/</link>
      <description>The Authentic Antics espionage malware attacks are attributed to APT28 (Fancy Bear), a threat actor linked to Russia's military intelligence service (GRU). The malware steals credentials and OAuth 2.0 tokens, allowing access to victim email accounts, and sends stolen data to an attacker-controlled email address using the victim's own Outlook account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/uk-ties-russian-gru-to-authentic-antics-credential-stealing-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft mistakenly tags Windows Firewall error log bug as fixed</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-mistakenly-tags-windows-firewall-error-log-bug-as-fixed/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows; CVE(s): None; Summary: A bug in the Windows Firewall With Advanced Security logs an error message as event ID 2042 every time the device is restarted, but Microsoft states it's not an issue with the Windows Firewall and can be disregarded. The bug was mistakenly marked as fixed in recent updates, and a fix will be released in an upcoming update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/microsoft-mistakenly-tags-windows-firewall-error-log-bug-as-fixed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumma Infostealer Steals Browser Data and Sells It as Logs on Underground Markets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lumma-infostealer-steals-browser-data/</link>
      <description>This article discusses infostealers, specifically the Lumma malware variant, which steals sensitive data from compromised systems. It spreads through phishing operations, social engineering tactics, and malvertising, and is attributed to the Russian-based threat actor Shamel. The malware's ecosystem has been disrupted by a coordinated international effort, but new C2 servers have reemerged, indicating ongoing threat persistence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150143</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishers have found a way to downgrade—not bypass—FIDO MFA</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-phishers-are-not-bypassing-fido-mfa-at-least-not-yet-heres-why/</link>
      <description>An attacker downgraded FIDO MFA to a weaker form of authentication. The attack is classified as a FIDO downgrade attack, not a bypass, and requires intentional configuration by an admin to fall back to the weaker method.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/no-phishers-are-not-bypassing-fido-mfa-at-least-not-yet-heres-why/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ChatGPT o3-alpha model hints at coding upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/new-chatgpt-o3-alpha-model-hints-at-coding-upgrade/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; FYSA: The article mentions OpenAI's o3-alpha model, which features significant coding-related improvements and is capable of designing web pages and creating simple web games. It also hints at the upcoming GPT-5 model, which is expected to unify breakthroughs from different models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/new-chatgpt-o3-alpha-model-hints-at-coding-upgrade/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Surge of Crypto-Jacking Hits Over 3,500 Websites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-surge-of-crypto-jacking/</link>
      <description>The article describes a campaign that infected over 3,500 websites with JavaScript miners, using advanced obfuscation and low-profile execution to evade detection. The miners employ Web Workers to execute mining logic off the main thread, minimizing performance impacts and avoiding traditional red flags like excessive CPU usage or overt network activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150120</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Massistant Tool Secretly Extracts SMS, GPS Data, and Images From Confiscated Phones</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinas-massistant-tool-secretly.html</link>
      <description>Massistant is a mobile forensics tool used by law enforcement authorities in China to gather information from seized mobile devices. It requires physical access to the device and can collect data such as GPS location, SMS messages, images, audio, contacts, and phone services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinas-massistant-tool-secretly.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fancy Bear Hackers Target Governments and Military Entities with Advanced Tools</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/fancy-bear-hackers-target-governments-and-military-entities/</link>
      <description>The article discusses Fancy Bear, a sophisticated Russian cyberespionage collective that has been operational since 2007. They exploit vulnerabilities in office suites, operating systems, and web applications to gain access to targeted organizations. Their tactics include phishing, spearphishing, exploitation of public-facing applications, and command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150128</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Group Hits China, Hong Kong, Pakistan Using LNK Files and RATs in Twin Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ung0002-group-hits-china-hong-kong.html</link>
      <description>The article describes a threat activity cluster tracked as UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002), which has been targeting multiple sectors in China, Hong Kong, and Pakistan. The group uses shortcut files, VBScript, and post-exploitation tools like Cobalt Strike and Metasploit to launch cyber espionage campaigns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ung0002-group-hits-china-hong-kong.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian alcohol retailer WineLab closes stores after ransomware attack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-alcohol-retailer-winelab-closes-stores-after-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>WineLab, a retail store of the largest alcohol company in Russia, has closed its stores following a cyberattack that is impacting its operations and causing purchase problems to its customers. The attackers requested a ransom payment, but the company declined to engage and won't comply with their demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/russian-alcohol-retailer-winelab-closes-stores-after-ransomware-attack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Zero-Days Exploited to Drop MDifyLoader and Launch In-Memory Cobalt Strike Attacks</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ivanti-zero-days-exploited-to-drop.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Connect Secure (ICS) appliances; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0282, CVE-2025-22457; Summary: The vulnerabilities in ICS appliances have been weaponized to drop MDifyLoader, which is used to launch Cobalt Strike in memory. The attacks exploit a critical security flaw (CVE-2025-0282) and a stack-based buffer overflow (CVE-2025-22457) that were previously patched by Ivanti in January 2025 and April 2025, respectively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ivanti-zero-days-exploited-to-drop.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snake Keylogger Bypasses Windows Defender and Uses Scheduled Tasks to Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/snake-keylogger-bypasses-windows-defender/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated phishing operation impersonates Turkish Aerospace Industries (TUSAŞ) to attack Turkish businesses in the defense and aerospace sectors. The campaign distributes malicious emails containing a PE32 executable that delivers a variant of the Snake Keylogger, an information-stealing malware designed to harvest sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150163</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Phobos ransomware decryptor lets victims recover files for free</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phobos-ransomware-decryptor-lets-victims-recover-files-for-free/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Phobos and 8Base Ransomware; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article discusses the release of a free decryptor by the Japanese police for victims of the Phobos and 8Base ransomware operations. The decryptor can recover files encrypted by these operations, including those with extensions such as ".phobos", ".8base", ".elbie", ".faust", and ".LIZARD".</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-phobos-ransomware-decryptor-lets-victims-recover-files-for-free/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers scanning for TeleMessage Signal clone flaw exposing passwords</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-scanning-for-telemessage-signal-clone-flaw-exposing-passwords/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessage SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48927, CVE-2025-48928; Summary: The TeleMessage SGNL app allows retrieving usernames, passwords, and other sensitive data due to the exposure of the '/heapdump' endpoint from Spring Boot Actuator without authentication. This vulnerability (CVE-2025-48927) lets an attacker download a full Java heap memory dump, which may contain plaintext usernames, passwords, tokens, and other sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hackers-scanning-for-telemessage-signal-clone-flaw-exposing-passwords/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web vs Dark Web: What’s the Real Difference?</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/deep-web-vs-dark-web-difference/</link>
      <description>The article explains the difference between the deep web and the dark web. While both are non-indexed by search engines, the deep web is a larger part of the internet that includes private content accessible through standard browsers, whereas the dark web is a smaller subset that uses encryption to maintain anonymity and often hosts illegal or malicious activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New QR Code Attacks Through PDFs Bypass Detection and Steal Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/new-qr-code-attacks-through-pdfs/</link>
      <description>The article discusses an ongoing phishing campaign called "Scanception" that uses QR code-based delivery mechanisms to distribute credential-harvesting URLs. The campaign involves targeted emails with PDF lures, social engineering tactics, and abuse of trusted services to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150095</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophos Intercept X for Windows Flaws Enable Arbitrary Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/sophos-intercept-x-for-windows-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Sophos; CVE(s): CVE-2024-13972, CVE-2025-7433, CVE-2025-7472; Summary: Three critical security vulnerabilities were discovered in Sophos Intercept X for Windows, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain system-level privileges. The vulnerabilities affect different components of the software, including the updater, Device Encryption module, and installer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150111</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Sues BadBox 2.0 Botnet Operators Behind 10 Million+ Infected Devices</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/google-sues-badbox-2-0-botnet-operators/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the BadBox 2.0 botnet, a network of over 10 million insecure devices running Android Open Source Project (AOSP) that were compromised by malware during manufacturing and used for ad fraud schemes and other illicit activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150080</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grafana Flaws Allow User Redirection and Code Execution in Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/grafana-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Grafana; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6023, CVE-2025-6197; Summary: Two critical vulnerabilities were discovered in Grafana's scripted dashboards and organization switching functionality. The first vulnerability is a high-severity cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw that can redirect users to malicious websites and execute arbitrary code, while the second is a medium-severity open redirect flaw that requires specific conditions for exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150097</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquiti UniFi Vulnerability Lets Hackers Inject Malicious Commands</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ubiquiti-unifi-vulnerability-2/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ubiquiti UniFi Access devices; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27212; Summary: The vulnerability allows malicious actors to inject and execute arbitrary commands on affected systems due to improper input validation within certain UniFi Access devices, carrying a maximum CVSS score of 9.8. It can be exploited by attackers with access to the UniFi Access management network, enabling them to bypass normal security controls and potentially gain unauthorized access to sensitive areas or systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150090</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for Office 365 Gets Enhanced Threat Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-defender-threat-dashboard/</link>
      <description>Microsoft has introduced a new customer-facing dashboard for its email security platform, providing detailed visibility into threat protection effectiveness across organizations. The enhanced dashboard and two comparative benchmarking reports aim to empower organizations with actionable data about their security posture and foster trust through transparency in threat protection capabilities. The initiative recognizes the importance of continuous evaluation of security solutions in today's sophisticated threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150085</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Adds One Known Exploited Vulnerability to Catalog</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/18/cisa-adds-one-known-exploited-vulnerability-catalog</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: The vulnerability, an SQL injection flaw, has been added to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) Catalog due to active exploitation. It poses significant risks to the federal enterprise and requires timely remediation to protect against cyber threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23639</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web Profile: CrazyHunter Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/dark-web-profile-crazyhunter-ransomware/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the "CrazyHunter" ransomware group, which has been targeting Taiwanese organizations, particularly in the healthcare and technology sectors. The group uses advanced tactics, techniques, and tools (TTPs) such as BYOVD, SharpGPOAbuse, and Prince Ransomware builder to carry out sophisticated attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061922</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERT-UA Discovers LAMEHUG Malware Linked to APT28, Using LLM for Phishing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cert-ua-discovers-lamehug-malware.html</link>
      <description>This article reports on a phishing campaign that delivered a malware codenamed LAMEHUG, attributed with medium confidence to the Russian state-sponsored hacking group tracked asAPT28. The malware uses a large language model (LLM) to generate commands based on textual representation, and supports commands to harvest basic information about the compromised host and search for specific files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cert-ua-discovers-lamehug-malware.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Sues 25 Chinese Entities Over BADBOX 2.0 Botnet Affecting 10M Android Devices</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-sues-25-chinese-entities-over.html</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it reports on Google's legal action against 25 unnamed individuals or entities in China for allegedly operating the BADBOX 2.0 botnet and residential proxy infrastructure, which compromises over 10 million Android devices running open-source software. The botnet is used to conduct large-scale ad fraud and other digital crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-sues-25-chinese-entities-over.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit Ivanti Connect Secure Flaws to Deploy Cobalt Strike Beacon</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-ivanti-connect-secure-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Ivanti Connect Secure; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0282, CVE-2025-22457; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting vulnerabilities in Ivanti Connect Secure to deploy advanced malware, including MDifyLoader and Cobalt Strike Beacon. The attacks use DLL hijacking and side-loading to inject malware into memory, and employ obfuscation and encryption to evade detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150041</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical NVIDIA Container Toolkit Flaw Allows Privilege Escalation on AI Cloud Services</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266; Summary: The NVIDIA Container Toolkit contains a critical container escape vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-23266, which carries a CVSS score of 9.0 out of 10.0. An attacker could execute arbitrary code with elevated permissions, potentially leading to escalation of privileges, data tampering, information disclosure, and denial-of-service. The vulnerability affects all versions up to and including 1.17.7 and has been addressed in versions 1.17.8 and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Backup to Cyber Resilience: Why IT Leaders Must Rethink Backup in the Age of Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-cyber-resilience-helps-it-defend-against-ransomwa.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of maintaining operations during an incident, especially in light of escalating IT outages and ransomware attacks. It highlights the limitations of traditional backup strategies, which often rely on manual testing and may not account for targeted cyberattacks that aim to destroy recovery infrastructure. The article emphasizes the need for a "resilience-first" approach, which integrates immutable backups, automated testing, and orchestrated recovery playbooks to ensure business continuity even during an attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/how-cyber-resilience-helps-it-defend-against-ransomwa.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit ClickFix Tactics to Spread NetSupport RAT, Latrodectus, and Lumma Stealer</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-clickfix-tactics/</link>
      <description>Attackers are using the ClickFix social engineering technique to distribute malware families like NetSupport RAT, Latrodectus, and Lumma Stealer. This technique tricks users into executing malicious commands by hijacking their clipboard and injecting obfuscated PowerShell scripts or commands that victims unwittingly paste into system interfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149986</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Protection Driver Flaw Enables Privilege Escalation and Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lenovo-protection-driver-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo; CVE(s): CVE-2025-4657; Summary: Lenovo's protection driver software contains a buffer overflow vulnerability that allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges, posing significant security risks. The flaw affects Lenovo PC Manager, Lenovo Browser, and Lenovo App Store versions prior to 5.1.110.4231, impacting millions of users worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=150016</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI: GPT-5 is coming, "we'll see" if it creates a shockwave</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-gpt-5-is-coming-well-see-if-it-creates-a-shockwave/</link>
      <description>OpenAI's next AI model, GPT-5, is still in development and no release date has been announced. Additionally, the company is planning to upgrade its Operator tool and adding new features to its Image Gen model, including a built-in style feature on ChatGPT. There are also hints about an Operator-like tool being tested on ChatGPT ahead of GPT-5's launch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openai-gpt-5-is-coming-well-see-if-it-creates-a-shockwave/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Uncovers Scattered Spider Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures in Recent Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-uncovers-scattered-spider-tactics/</link>
      <description>This article discusses the tactics and techniques used by a financially motivated cybercriminal group called Octo Tempest (Scattered Spider, Muddled Libra, UNC3944, or 0ktapus). The group uses advanced social engineering campaigns, phishing attacks, and exploitation of Azure Active Directory environments to gain initial access and pivot to cloud resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149967</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAFFLED: New Technique Targets Web Application Firewall Weaknesses</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/waffled-new-technique-targets-web-application/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various WAF platforms (AWS WAF, Azure WAF, Google Cloud Armor, Cloudflare, and ModSecurity); CVE(s): None; Summary: The WAFFLED attack technique exploits parsing discrepancies in Web Application Firewalls (WAFs) to bypass security measures and compromise the security of millions of websites worldwide. The technique targets three content types (multipart/form-data, application/json, and application/xml) and affects five major WAF platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149970</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Exploit GitHub Accounts to Host Payloads, Tools, and Amadey Malware Plugins</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-exploit-github-accounts/</link>
      <description>This article discusses a Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation that employed the Amadey botnet to distribute various payloads. The operation exploited fake GitHub accounts as open directories, bypassing web filtering mechanisms and simplifying distribution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149921</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Vodka Maker Beluga Struck by Ransomware Attack</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/beluga-ransomware-attack/</link>
      <description>Novabev Group, the parent company of Beluga vodka, was hit by a sophisticated ransomware attack on July 14, 2025, causing temporary disruptions to its IT infrastructure and services. The company refused to pay any ransom demands and is working to restore normal operations with the help of external cybersecurity experts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149962</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 08:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Daemon Ex Plist’ Vulnerability Grants Root Access on macOS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/daemon-ex-plist-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apple macOS; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27981; Summary: A newly discovered vulnerability in macOS allows attackers to escalate privileges from standard user to root access by exploiting a timing flaw in how the operating system handles daemon configuration files. The vulnerability requires no initial elevated permissions and can be exploited through simple XML modifications, giving attackers complete system control, including disabling System Integrity Protection (SIP), manipulating privacy databases, and installing persistent backdoors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149950</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Publishes 13 ICS Security Advisories on Critical Flaws</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisa-publishes-13-ics-security-advisories/</link>
      <description>The Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) released thirteen Industrial Control Systems (ICS) security advisories highlighting critical vulnerabilities in operational technology networks across multiple sectors. The advisories warn of potential disruptions to essential infrastructure services, emphasizing the importance of immediate action to prevent exploitation by threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149942</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Best XDR (Extended Detection And Response) Solutions 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/best-xdr-solutions/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article presents an analysis of top 10 Extended Detection and Response (XDR) solutions in the market. The review highlights the strengths and approaches of each solution, including their ability to integrate with existing security stacks, detect advanced threats, and streamline incident response.

The XDR solutions reviewed are:

1. Google Chronicle Security Operations
2. Exabeam Fusion XDR
3. Fortinet FortiXDR
4. Sophos XDR
5. Mandiant Security Operations (part of Google Chronicle)
6. Microsoft Azure Sentinel
7. Palo Alto Networks XDR
8. FireEye Helix XDR
9. RSA NetWitness XDR
10. CrowdStrike Falcon XDR

The analysis notes that each solution has its unique strengths and weaknesses, making it essential for organizations to carefully evaluate their specific needs and requirements before selecting an XDR solution.

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the current state of XDR solutions in the market and highlights the importance of choosing a suitable solution to effectively detect and respond to advanced threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=126278</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal App Clone Telemessage App Vulnerability Actively Exploited for Password Theft</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/signal-app-clone-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: TeleMessageTM SGNL; CVE(s): CVE-2025-48927; Summary: A critical vulnerability in TeleMessageTM SGNL's legacy configuration of Spring Boot Actuator allows threat actors to steal passwords and sensitive data by exploiting a publicly accessible diagnostic endpoint. The vulnerability affects certain deployments of the secure communications archiving system and has been actively exploited since at least May 5, 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149907</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 06:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIND 9 Vulnerabilities Enable Cache Poisoning and Service Disruption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/bind-9-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Internet Systems Consortium (ISC) BIND 9; CVE(s): CVE-2025-40776, CVE-2025-40777; Summary: Two critical security vulnerabilities in BIND 9, one allowing cache poisoning attacks and the other causing assertion failures leading to service disruption. These flaws primarily impact DNS resolvers rather than authoritative servers, with potential for redirecting users to malicious websites or intercepting communications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149900</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 05:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor Passwords Tattle on AI Hiring Bot Maker Paradox.ai</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/07/poor-passwords-tattle-on-ai-hiring-bot-maker-paradox-ai/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Paradox.ai; CVE(s): None; Summary: The personal information of millions of people who applied for jobs at McDonald's was exposed after researchers guessed the password ("123456") for Paradox.ai's account. The weak password allowed access to 64 million records, including applicants' names, email addresses, and phone numbers.

FYSA: Threat actors exploited a Paradox.ai administrator in Vietnam's malware-infected device, stealing usernames and passwords for various internal and third-party services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=71668</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 01:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Bleed 2 exploited weeks before PoCs as Citrix denied attacks</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-exploited-weeks-before-pocs-as-citrix-denied-attacks/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix NetScaler; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: A critical memory overread vulnerability, dubbed "CitrixBleed 2," allows attackers to send malformed POST requests and leak 127 bytes of memory. The flaw can be exploited to expose sensitive data, hijack sessions, and gain unauthorized access to internal resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/citrix-bleed-2-exploited-weeks-before-pocs-as-citrix-denied-attacks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 23:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub abused to distribute payloads on behalf of malware-as-a-service</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/malware-as-a-service-caught-using-github-to-distribute-its-payloads/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a malicious activity campaign called Amadey, which is likely part of a larger Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation. Threat actors behind Amadey are distributing various malware families from fake GitHub repositories onto infected hosts, suggesting they may be serving payloads for other individuals or groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/malware-as-a-service-caught-using-github-to-distribute-its-payloads/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 22:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware fixes four ESXi zero-day bugs exploited at Pwn2Own Berlin</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-fixes-four-esxi-zero-day-bugs-exploited-at-pwn2own-berlin/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware ESXi, Workstation, Fusion, and Tools; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41236, CVE-2025-41237, CVE-2025-41238, CVE-2025-41239; Summary: Three of the patched flaws allow programs running in a guest virtual machine to execute commands on the host, while the fourth is an information disclosure. The first three have a severity rating of 9.3 and were exploited as zero-days during Pwn2Own Berlin 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/vmware-fixes-four-esxi-zero-day-bugs-exploited-at-pwn2own-berlin/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams voice calls abused to push Matanbuchus malware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-voice-calls-abused-to-push-matanbuchus-malware/</link>
      <description>The Matanbuchus malware loader is being distributed through social engineering over Microsoft Teams calls impersonating IT helpdesk, allowing attackers to gain initial access and deliver malicious payloads. The latest version, Matanbuchus 3.0, includes enhanced evasion, obfuscation, and post-compromise capabilities, making it a sophisticated threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/microsoft-teams-voice-calls-abused-to-push-matanbuchus-malware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-616: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer CATPRODUCT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-616/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6971; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer. User interaction is required, and the specific flaw exists within the parsing of CATPRODUCT files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26975</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-617: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer CATPRODUCT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-617/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6972; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer by parsing CATPRODUCT files without validating the existence of an object. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26971</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-618: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer JT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-618/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6974; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations, requiring user interaction. It exists within the parsing of JT files due to uninitialized memory access. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26895</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-619: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer JT File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-619/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-0831; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations by parsing out-of-bounds read. User interaction is required, and the issue results from lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26813</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-620: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer JT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-620/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6973; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer by parsing JT files without validating the existence of an object. User interaction is required, as the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26901</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-611: VMware ESXi VMCI Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-611/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware ESXi; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41239; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of VMware ESXi. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which exists within the implementation of VMCI due to uninitialized memory prior to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27123</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-612: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server Hard-coded Credentials Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-612/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37105; Summary: This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server without authentication. The specific flaw exists within the hsqldb service, which listens on TCP port 9001 by default, due to hard-coded credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25789</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-613: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-613/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37106; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information or edit configuration on affected installations of Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server without requiring authentication. The specific flaw exists within the web service, which listens on TCP port 5814 by default, due to hard-coded credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25790</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-614: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-614/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server; CVE(s): CVE-2025-37107; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of the Hewlett Packard Enterprise AutoPass License Server, making an authorization decision based on a non-canonical URL. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability, and it exists within the web service that listens on TCP port 5814 by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-25791</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-615: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer IPT File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-615/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Dassault Systèmes eDrawings Viewer; CVE(s): CVE-2025-7042; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations by parsing IPT files without validating the existence of an object. User interaction is required, and an attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27117</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google sues to disrupt BadBox 2.0 botnet infecting 10 million devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-sues-to-disrupt-badbox-20-botnet-infecting-10-million-devices/</link>
      <description>The article discusses a lawsuit filed by Google against the operators of the Android BadBox 2.0 malware botnet, which has infected over 10 million devices and is conducting global ad fraud schemes against Google's advertising platforms. The botnet uses infected Android Open Source Project (AOSP) devices, including smart TVs, streaming boxes, and other connected devices that lack security protections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-sues-to-disrupt-badbox-20-botnet-infecting-10-million-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-604: Cisco Identity Services Engine disableStrongSwanTunnel Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-604/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20283; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Cisco Identity Services Engine, requiring authentication. The issue is due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the iseadminportal user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26479</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-605: Cisco Identity Services Engine IpAccessFilter Direct Request Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-605/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20285; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass IP restrictions on affected installations of Cisco Identity Services Engine. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the issue results from an incomplete Spring Boot filter mapping in the web.xml file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26480</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-606: Cisco Identity Services Engine handleStrongSwanTunnelStatus Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-606/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20284; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Cisco Identity Services Engine. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, and the flaw exists within the implementation of the handleStrongSwanTunnelStatus method due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, resulting in deserialization of untrusted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26482</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-607: Cisco Identity Services Engine enableStrongSwanTunnel Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-607/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20337; Summary: The vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations without authentication, due to the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data in the enableStrongSwanTunnel method. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the iseadminportal user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26481</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-608: Cisco Identity Services Engine handleFilesUpload Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-608/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20282; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Cisco Identity Services Engine without authentication. The issue occurs due to a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, allowing the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the iseadminportal user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26483</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-609: Cisco Identity Services Engine invokeStrongSwanShellScript Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-609/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Cisco Identity Services Engine without authentication. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call, allowing an attacker to execute code in the context of root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27121</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-610: Linux Kernel ksmbd destroy_previous_session Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-610/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Linux Kernel; CVE(s): CVE-2025-38191; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of the Linux Kernel without authentication. The issue is due to a lack of proper validation of a pointer prior to accessing it in the destroy_previous_session function, which can be exploited to cause a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27391</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LameHug malware uses AI LLM to craft Windows data-theft commands in real-time</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lamehug-malware-uses-ai-llm-to-craft-windows-data-theft-commands-in-real-time/</link>
      <description>LameHug is a novel malware family that uses a large language model (LLM) to generate commands for execution on compromised Windows systems. It relies on the Hugging Face API and an open-source LLM designed specifically for generating code, reasoning, and follow coding-focused instructions. The malware is written in Python and has been attributed to Russian state-backed threat group APT28.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/lamehug-malware-uses-ai-llm-to-craft-windows-data-theft-commands-in-real-time/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is your sign to step away from the keyboard</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/this-is-your-sign-to-step-away-from-the-keyboard/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; Summary: The article discusses the importance of self-care and stress management for cybersecurity professionals, highlighting the risks of burnout and the need to prioritize mental health.

FYSA: A Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation was identified by Cisco Talos that used Emmenhtal loader and Amadey malware to deliver malicious payloads targeting Ukrainian entities via public GitHub repositories. The operation shows how easily adversaries can use trusted platforms like GitHub to deliver malware, making it more difficult for organizations to detect and block threats.

Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): 2025-25257; Summary: A proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit allows unauthenticated attackers to execute remote code by writing malicious files to the server's filesystem, potentially leading to full remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6877bdb118fde0000159044e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use GitHub Repositories to Host Amadey Malware and Data Stealers, Bypassing Filters</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-use-github-repositories-to-host.html</link>
      <description>Threat actors are using public GitHub repositories to host malicious payloads and distribute them via Amadey as part of a campaign observed in April 2025. The malware loader Emmenhtal delivers Amadey, which downloads various custom payloads from public GitHub repositories operated by the threat actors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-use-github-repositories-to-host.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker steals $27 million in BigONE exchange crypto breach</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-27-million-in-bigone-exchange-crypto-breach/</link>
      <description>This article does not discuss a vulnerability. Instead, it reports on a cryptocurrency exchange hack that resulted in the theft of digital assets valued at $27 million. The article also discusses broader trends and statistics related to cryptocurrency crime.

FYSA: The article highlights a significant cryptocurrency heist, with hackers stealing $223 million worth of Cetus Protocol cryptocurrency. Additionally, it notes that there has been an increase in attacks on personal wallets, accounting for 23.35% of all stolen funds this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/hacker-steals-27-million-in-bigone-exchange-crypto-breach/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers breached National Guard to steal network configurations</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-breached-national-guard-to-steal-network-configurations/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various; CVE(s): CVE-2018-0171, CVE-2023-20198, CVE-2023-20273, CVE-2024-3400; Summary: Salt Typhoon, a Chinese state-sponsored hacking group, exploited vulnerabilities in Cisco routers and other devices to breach a US Army National Guard network for nine months, stealing configuration files and administrator credentials. The vulnerabilities included a critical flaw in Cisco IOS and IOS XE Smart Install (CVE-2018-0171), a zero-day affecting Cisco IOS XE web UI (CVE-2023-20198), a privilege escalation flaw targeting IOS XE (CVE-2023-20273), and a command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks' PAN-OS GlobalProtect (CVE-2024-3400).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/chinese-hackers-breached-national-guard-to-steal-network-configurations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max severity Cisco ISE bug allows pre-auth command execution, patch now</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/max-severity-cisco-ise-bug-allows-pre-auth-command-execution-patch-now/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco's Identity Services Engine (ISE); CVE(s): CVE-2025-20337; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Cisco's ISE allows an unauthenticated attacker to store malicious files, execute arbitrary code, or gain root privileges on vulnerable devices. The issue is caused by insufficient user-supplied input validation checks and received the maximum severity rating of 10 out of 10.

FYSA: Although no exploitation of the three maximum severity vulnerabilities has been observed in the wild as of yet, it is recommended that system administrators take immediate action to mitigate the risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/max-severity-cisco-ise-bug-allows-pre-auth-command-execution-patch-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams Exploited to Deliver Matanbuchus Ransomware Payload</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/microsoft-teams-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Teams; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article describes a sophisticated cyberattack campaign targeting organizations through Microsoft Teams impersonation. Attackers compromise systems by pretending to be IT helpdesk personnel during external Teams calls, leading to the execution of malicious scripts that deploy the Matanbuchus 3.0 malware loader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149861</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Hackers Claim Cyberattack on Major Russian Drone Supplier</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ukrainian-hackers-claim-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The article describes the story of a Ukrainian woman, Nelya Leonidova, who survived a cluster munition attack in 2014 and has been dealing with the long-term consequences of her severe combat-related injuries. The story highlights the humanitarian impact of explosive ordnance use in populated areas and emphasizes individual resilience in the face of catastrophic trauma.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149843</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H2Miner Targets Linux, Windows, and Containers to Illicitly Mine Monero</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/h2miner-targets-linux-windows-and-containers/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a sophisticated cryptomining campaign called H2Miner, which targets Linux, Windows, and containerized environments simultaneously. The campaign uses updated scripts and infrastructure to deploy Kinsing malware, disable security defenses, and download additional payloads, including miners and information stealers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149797</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massistant: Chinese Mobile Forensic Tool Accesses SMS, Images, Audio, and GPS Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massistant-chinese-mobile-forensic-tool/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Meiya Pico's Massistant; CVE(s): None; Summary: Massistant is a sophisticated mobile forensics application deployed by Chinese law enforcement to extract comprehensive data from confiscated mobile devices. It can bypass device security measures and collect sensitive information, raising critical security concerns for international business travelers and enterprise organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149825</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-25257: Attackers Exploit FortiWeb SQL Injection Bug for Remote Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cve-2025-25257-fortiweb-sql-injection-bug-rce/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A critical SQL injection vulnerability (CVSS 9.6) in Fortinet's FortiWeb Fabric Connector allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands and Remote Code Execution (RCE). The flaw impacts several FortiWeb versions, including 7.0.0 through 7.6.3, and has been actively exploited since July 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Apache HTTP Server Flaw to Deploy Linuxsys Cryptocurrency Miner</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-apache-http-server-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Apache HTTP Server; CVE(s): CVE-2021-41773; Summary: The vulnerability in Apache HTTP Server version 2.4.49 is a high-severity path traversal vulnerability that could result in remote code execution, exploited by threat actors to deliver a cryptocurrency miner called Linuxsys.

FYSA: Threat actors have been conducting a long-term campaign, exploiting known security flaws and employing consistent techniques such as n-day exploitation, staging content on compromised hosts, and coin mining on victim machines. The campaign has resulted in the delivery of malware, including the Linuxsys cryptocurrency miner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-exploit-apache-http-server-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SquareX Collaborates With Top Fortune 500 CISOs To Launch The Browser Security Field Manual At Black Hat</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/squarex-collaborates-with-top-fortune-500-cisos-to-launch-the-browser-security-field-manual-at-black-hat/</link>
      <description>The article announces the official launch of "The Browser Security Field Manual" by SquareX, a comprehensive guide to browser security threats and tactics. The manual features industry perspectives from leading CISOs and covers five major threat vectors, including phishing, malicious extensions, data loss, identity attacks, and browser-native ransomware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149807</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese State-Sponsored Hackers Target Semiconductor Industry with Weaponized Cobalt Strike</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-state-sponsored-hackers-target-semiconductor-industry/</link>
      <description>This article reports on a sophisticated cyberespionage campaign targeting Taiwan's semiconductor industry. Three Chinese state-sponsored threat actors (UNK_FistBump, UNK_DropPitch, and UNK_SparkyCarp) conducted coordinated phishing operations against organizations in the semiconductor sector, using various tactics, techniques, and procedures to deliver malware payloads and collect intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149808</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 4 Million Exposed Devices Used in Two New DoS Attack Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/over-4-million-exposed-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Various tunneling protocols (IPIP, GRE, 4in6, 6in4); CVE(s): CVE-2024-7595, CVE-2024-7596, CVE-2025-23018, and CVE-2025-23019; Summary: The vulnerability affects millions of Internet hosts that accept unauthenticated tunneling traffic, allowing for devastating denial-of-service attacks, including TuTL and Ping-Pong amplification attacks. Additionally, the EDoS attack targets cloud-hosted services by forcing vulnerable hosts to generate massive amounts of outbound traffic, leading to increased costs or service disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149794</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Hit by CVSS 10 RCE Vulnerabilities Allowing Full System Takeover – Patch Now</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/cisco-ise-cvss-10-rce-full-system-takeover/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE), Cisco Unified Intelligence Center, and Cisco Prime Infrastructure; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20281, CVE-2025-20282, CVE-2025-20337; Summary: Three critical vulnerabilities with a maximum CVSS score of 10.0 allow unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected systems with root privileges by sending specially crafted API requests. The flaws exist in specific APIs within Cisco ISE and its Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061891</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Reveal How Hacktivist Groups Gain Attention and Choose Their Targets</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/researchers-reveal-how-hacktivist-groups/</link>
      <description>Cybersecurity researchers have released findings on the operational dynamics of hacktivist organizations, revealing sophisticated attention-seeking behaviors and strategic target selection methodologies. The study highlights hacktivists' calculated targeting strategies, self-promotion mechanisms, and use of psychological warfare approaches to amplify their perceived influence. It also notes the commercialization trend within the hacktivist community and the increasing focus on capability development, leading to a more complex threat landscape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149772</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISA Releases Three Industrial Control Systems Advisories</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/alerts/2025/07/17/cisa-releases-three-industrial-control-systems-advisories</link>
      <description>CISA issued three Industrial Control Systems (ICS) advisories on July 17, 2025, providing information about current security issues, vulnerabilities, and exploits surrounding ICS. The advisories aim to inform users and administrators of technical details and mitigations for the affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23635</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoramic Corporation Digital Imaging Software</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-medical-advisories/icsma-25-198-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Panoramic Corporation Digital Imaging Software (Version 9.1.2.7600); CVE(s): CVE-2024-22774; Summary: The Digital Imaging Software is vulnerable to DLL hijacking, allowing an attacker with standard user privileges to obtain NT Authority/SYSTEM privileges. Successful exploitation could allow a standard user to gain elevated access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23634</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leviton AcquiSuite and Energy Monitoring Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.cisa.gov/news-events/ics-advisories/icsa-25-198-01</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Leviton AcquiSuite and Leviton Energy Monitoring Hub; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6185; Summary: The vulnerability is a cross-site scripting (XSS) weakness that allows an attacker to craft malicious payloads in URL parameters, execute them in a client browser, steal session tokens, and control the service. Exploitation can occur remotely with low attack complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/23633</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNG0002 Actors Weaponize LNK Files via ClickFix Fake CAPTCHA Pages</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/ung0002-actors-weaponize-lnk-files/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a sophisticated espionage group known as UNG0002 (Unknown Group 0002) that has been conducting persistent campaigns across multiple Asian jurisdictions since May 2024. The group uses social engineering techniques, advanced malware deployment methods, and custom-developed implants to target organizations in China, Hong Kong, and Pakistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149751</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK’s Co-op Retailer Hit by Cyberattack, 6.5 Million Members’ Data Exposed</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/uks-co-op-retailer-hit-by-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The UK's Co-op retailer suffered a significant cyberattack in April 2024, resulting in the theft of personal data from all 6.5 million members. While no financial information was compromised, hackers accessed names, addresses, and contact information. The breach highlights the ongoing cybersecurity challenges facing major retailers and the importance of robust preventive measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149774</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Disrupts NoName057(16) Hacktivist Group Linked to DDoS Attacks Against Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-disrupts-noname05716-hacktivist.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses an international operation led by Europol to disrupt the infrastructure of a pro-Russian hacktivist group called NoName057(16) that has been linked to DDoS attacks against Ukraine and its allies. The joint effort resulted in the dismantling of the group's central server infrastructure, arrests, searches, and issuance of arrest warrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/europol-disrupts-noname05716-hacktivist.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Container Toolkit Vulnerability Allows Privileged Code Execution by Attackers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nvidia-container-toolkit-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: NVIDIA Container Toolkit and GPU Operator; CVE(s): CVE-2025-23266, CVE-2025-23267; Summary: The NVIDIA Container Toolkit and GPU Operator contain two critical vulnerabilities that allow attackers to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges. The first vulnerability (CVE-2025-23266) has a CVSS score of 9.0, while the second (CVE-2025-23267) has a score of 8.5. These flaws enable privilege escalation, data tampering, information disclosure, and denial-of-service attacks in containerized environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149760</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-Click Oracle Cloud Code Editor RCE Flaw Allows Malicious File Upload to Shell</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/1-click-oracle-cloud-code-editor-rce-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Code Editor; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure's Code Editor enabled attackers to silently hijack victim Cloud Shell environments through a single malicious link, allowing for potential lateral movement across OCI services and compromise of integrated developer tools. The vulnerability stemmed from a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) weakness in the file upload mechanism, which was remediated by implementing additional CSRF protections requiring a custom HTTP header.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149729</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM vs ASM vs Vulnerability Management: What Security Leaders Need to Know in 2025</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ctem-vs-asm-vs-vulnerability-management.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses the importance of implementing Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) programs, which complement Vulnerability Management (VM) and Attack Surface Management (ASM). CTEM provides a systematic approach to discover, prioritize, validate, and respond to security exposures. The article also highlights the benefits of integrating VM, ASM, and penetration testing solutions into a unified interface to support a holistic CTEM program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ctem-vs-asm-vs-vulnerability-management.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Threat Actors Use AI-Generated Emails to Target Cybersecurity Researchers and Academics</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/iranian-threat-actors-use-ai-generated-emails/</link>
      <description>This article discusses Iranian state-backed Advanced Persistent Threat (APT) groups and their hacktivist allies' increased cyber operations following Israeli and American strikes on Iranian nuclear and military facilities. The article highlights the groups' tactics, including espionage, disruption, and psychological warfare, as well as their use of AI-enhanced phishing operations and industrial control system scanning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149704</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaaS operation using Emmenhtal and Amadey linked to threats against Ukrainian entities</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/maas-operation-using-emmenhtal-and-amadey-linked-to-threats-against-ukrainian-entities/</link>
      <description>A Malware-as-a-Service (MaaS) operation, dubbed "Amadey," has been identified by Cisco Talos. The operation uses fake GitHub accounts to host payloads and tools, allowing operators to deliver various malware families to infected hosts. This MaaS operation overlaps with a previous SmokeLoader phishing campaign targeting Ukrainian entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6876776cec6298000147ad76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Use DNS Queries to Evade Defenses and Exfiltrate Data</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-use-dns-queries-to-evade-defenses-and-exfiltrate-data/</link>
      <description>DNS tunneling is a technique used by cybercriminals to bypass corporate security measures and steal sensitive data by encoding data within DNS queries and responses. The attack process begins when threat actors gain control of a domain name's authoritative name server, allowing them to conduct command-and-control (C2) operations and data exfiltration while remaining largely undetected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149688</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Deploy 28+ Malicious Packages to Spread Protestware Scripts</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-deploy-28-malicious-packages/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Socket's Threat Research Team; CVE(s): None; Summary: A network of at least 28 malicious packages, including protestware scripts, was discovered in the npm supply chain. The protestware disrupts user interface interactions by disabling mouse events and initiating playback of the Ukrainian national anthem, affecting Russian-language users on specific domains. The vulnerability highlights the risks of code reuse in open-source repositories, where undisclosed payloads can cascade through dependencies, amplifying potential impacts on downstream applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149690</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Stealer Logs</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/top-10-stealer-logs/</link>
      <description>The provided article is an analysis of infostealer malware and their associated logs in 2025. It does not discuss a specific vulnerability in software, hardware, or firmware.

The article provides an overview of various infostealer malware families, including Lumma, Vidar, RedLine, StealC, Raccoon Stealer, MetaStealer, Mystic Stealer, and Hawklog. Each section highlights the features, target range, and evasion techniques used by each malware family to steal sensitive data such as credentials, credit card numbers, and cryptocurrency wallet details.

The article also discusses the role of stealer logs in enabling ransomware attacks, account takeovers, and financial fraud. It emphasizes the importance of threat hunting and stealer log analysis for detecting early signs of compromise and reducing the time gap between initial breach detection.

No specific vulnerabilities are mentioned or analyzed in the article.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100047829</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPI Blocks Inbox.ru Domains After 1,500+ Fake Package Uploads</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/pypi-blocks-inbox-ru-domains/</link>
      <description>PyPI blocked the inbox.ru email domain after a campaign created over 250 fraudulent accounts and uploaded more than 1,500 empty projects, causing confusion among end-users and straining resources. The incident highlights the delegated security model of PyPI's registration process and emphasizes the importance of user vigilance and advanced detection mechanisms to prevent future incursions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149680</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical SharePoint RCE Vulnerability Exploited via Malicious XML in Web Part</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/critical-sharepoint-rce-vulnerability-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft SharePoint; CVE(s): None; Summary: A severe remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in Microsoft SharePoint allows attackers to execute arbitrary code through malicious XML content embedded within web parts. The vulnerability originates from the deserialization process of web part properties and can be exploited through multiple endpoints, including the _/vti_bin/webpartpages.asmx service using the ConvertWebPartFormat SOAP action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149676</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Actively Exploited CitrixBleed 2 Flaw Ahead of PoC Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-actively-exploited-citrixbleed-2-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Citrix; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5777; Summary: The CitrixBleed 2 vulnerability was exploited by threat actors nearly two weeks before a public proof-of-concept was released, highlighting the sophistication of modern attack campaigns. Initial exploitation began on June 23, followed by the public release of a proof-of-concept on July 4, and GreyNoise's subsequent creation of a tracking tag on July 7. The vulnerability represents a significant security risk for organizations running Citrix NetScaler appliances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149671</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Unified Intelligence Center Flaw Lets Remote Attackers Upload Arbitrary Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cisco-unified-intelligence-center-flaw/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco Unified Intelligence Center; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20274; Summary: A critical vulnerability in Cisco's Unified Intelligence Center allows authenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files, potentially enabling complete system compromise through privilege escalation to root access. The flaw stems from improper file validation and can be exploited by users with Report Designer role privileges, allowing for the execution of arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149656</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 08:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponizing SVG: How Threat Actors Embed Malicious JavaScript in Vector Files</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/how-threat-actors-embed-malicious-javascript-in-vector-files/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: Researchers have identified an emerging attack campaign using Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) files to deliver JavaScript-based redirect attacks. The technique exploits the inherent trust in image formats, allowing malicious actors to embed obfuscated JavaScript within SVG files that execute automatically when opened in web browsers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149610</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hackers Target Taiwan's Semiconductor Sector with Cobalt Strike, Custom Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwans.html</link>
      <description>The article reports on spear-phishing campaigns conducted by three Chinese state-sponsored threat actors targeting the Taiwanese semiconductor industry. The campaigns involve phishing emails with malicious payloads, including Cobalt Strike or a custom backdoor, and DLL side-loading to spawn reverse shells and establish command-and-control connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwans.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0-Day RCE Flaw in SonicWall SMA Devices Exploited to Launch OVERSTEP Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/0-day-rce-flaw-in-sonicwall-sma-devices-exploited/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall; CVE(s): CVE-2024-38475, None; Summary: Threat actors are exploiting previously stolen credentials and a new rootkit called OVERSTEP to target end-of-life SonicWall Secure Mobile Access (SMA) 100 series appliances. The campaign represents a significant escalation in attacks against network infrastructure devices, as the threat actors are successfully compromising appliances even after organizations have applied the latest security updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149604</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Confirms BGP Hijack Behind 1.1.1.1 DNS Disruption</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cloudflare-confirms-bgp-hijack-behind-1-1-1-1-dns-disruption/</link>
      <description>A global outage of Cloudflare's 1.1.1.1 DNS resolver service was caused by an internal configuration error rather than an external attack. The incident affected millions of users worldwide and coincided with an unrelated BGP hijack, which complicated the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149591</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol Takes Down NoName057(16)’s Global Network of Over 100 Servers</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/europol-takes-down-noname05716s-global-network/</link>
      <description>Europol and Eurojust conducted Operation Eastwood to dismantle the NoName057(16) hacktivist collective's global infrastructure of over 100 servers worldwide. The operation resulted in two arrests, seven international arrest warrants, 24 house searches, and disruption of over 100 servers globally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149587</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Warns of Critical ISE Flaw Allowing Unauthenticated Attackers to Execute Root Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-ise-flaw.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Cisco ISE and Cisco ISE-PIC; CVE(s): CVE-2025-20337; Summary: The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system with elevated privileges. It affects ISE and ISE-PIC releases 3.3 and 3.4, regardless of device configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-ise-flaw.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 05:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submarine Cables Face Increasing Threats Amid Geopolitical Tensions and Limited Repair Capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/submarine-cables-face-increasing-threats</link>
      <description>FYSA:

This analysis highlights various vulnerabilities in the submarine cable ecosystem, including:

1. **Concentration of cables at landing stations**: The clustering of multiple submarine cables at single landing sites increases the likelihood that damage to or near a landing site will impact multiple cables.
2. **Limited repair capacity**: Repair vessels are focused on laying new cable systems, constraining their ability to respond immediately to cable faults, leading to extended repair times.
3. **Regulatory hurdles**: Complex and lengthy permitting processes for repair ships vary by national territory, prolonging repair timelines and exacerbating the impact of limited repair capacity.

These vulnerabilities can have significant consequences for global internet connectivity, highlighting the need for investments in streamlining repair processes and expanding cable ship repair capacity to mitigate potential disruptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.recordedfuture.com/research/submarine-cables-face-increasing-threats</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-op confirms data of 6.5 million members stolen in cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/co-op-confirms-data-of-65-million-members-stolen-in-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>A massive cyberattack on UK retailer Co-op resulted in the theft of personal data for 6.5 million members. The attackers accessed and stole Windows domain's Windows NTDS.dit file, which contains password hashes for Windows accounts.

FYSA: Threat actors associated with Scattered Spider were behind the Co-op cyberattack, as well as other attacks on M&amp;S, Harrods, and MGM Resorts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/co-op-confirms-data-of-65-million-members-stolen-in-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 22:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Army soldier pleads guilty to extorting 10 tech, telecom firms</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-army-soldier-pleads-guilty-to-extorting-10-tech-telecom-firms/</link>
      <description>A 21-year-old former U.S. Army soldier pleaded guilty to charges of hacking and extorting at least ten telecommunications and technology companies in the country. The man, Cameron John Wagenius, used online accounts associated with the nickname “kiberphant0m” and conspired with others to defraud victim organizations by obtaining login credentials for their protected computer networks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/us-army-soldier-pleads-guilty-to-extorting-10-tech-telecom-firms/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google finds custom backdoor being installed on SonicWall network devices</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/google-finds-custom-backdoor-being-installed-on-sonicwall-network-devices/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): 2024-38475; Summary: UNC6148 exploited vulnerabilities in SMA appliances, gaining local administrator credentials and valid session tokens. They may have used infostealer logs or credential marketplaces to obtain credentials. A reverse shell was installed, providing a web interface for running commands and installing Overstep. The motivations of the group and what they do after Overstep is installed are unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/google-finds-custom-backdoor-being-installed-on-sonicwall-network-devices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracked Apps Delivering Infostealers Identified as Leading Attack Vector in June 2025</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/cracked-apps-delivering-infostealers-identified/</link>
      <description>The article discusses infostealer malware masquerading as keygens and cracked software, which uses advanced SEO poisoning to elevate malicious distribution sites in search results. It highlights the diversity of infostealers, including variants like LummaC2, Rhadamanthys, ACRStealer, Vidar, and StealC, and notes their evolving sophistication through techniques like evasion, deception, and anti-analysis mechanisms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149538</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leverage 607 Malicious Domains to Spread APK Malware with Remote Command Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-leverage-607-malicious-domains/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: None; CVE(s): Janus vulnerability on Android versions 5.0 through 8.0 (None); Summary: Rogue domains were used in a large-scale phishing campaign to spread fake Telegram Messenger application files (APKs) over the course of a month, leveraging QR codes and centralized redirection for efficient malware delivery. The malicious APKs employ cleartext traffic protocols, grant broad permissions, and integrate MediaPlayer invocations and socket-based callbacks for remote command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149532</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Vuitton says regional data breaches tied to same cyberattack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/louis-vuitton-says-regional-data-breaches-tied-to-same-cyberattack/</link>
      <description>The article reports a data breach at luxury fashion giant Louis Vuitton, which affected customers in the UK, South Korea, and Turkey. The breach is believed to be linked to the ShinyHunters extortion group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/louis-vuitton-says-regional-data-breaches-tied-to-same-cyberattack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threat Actors Weaponize WordPress Sites to Redirect Visitors to Malicious Domains</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/threat-actors-weaponize-wordpress-sites/</link>
      <description>The article describes a sophisticated malware campaign targeting WordPress websites, where threat actors embedded malicious code within core files to facilitate unauthorized redirects and SEO poisoning. The malware uses obfuscation techniques and bot-evasion tactics to evade detection, and can manipulate search engine rankings by injecting fake sitemaps and verifying with Google Search Console.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149525</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation Eastwood Targets NoName057(16) in Global Crackdown</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/operation-eastwood-targets-noname05716/</link>
      <description>This article is not about a vulnerability but rather discusses an international law enforcement operation called Operation Eastwood, which targeted a pro-Russian hacktivist group known as NoName057(16). The group was responsible for carrying out widespread DDoS attacks against Ukraine and other perceived enemies of Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061854</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SquidLoader Deploys Stealthy Malware with Near-Zero Detection to Evade Security Measures</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/squidloader-deploys-stealthy-malware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SquidLoader; CVE(s): None; Summary: A new variant of SquidLoader malware has been discovered, which achieves near-zero detection rates on platforms like VirusTotal by leveraging advanced anti-analysis, anti-sandbox, and anti-debugging mechanisms. The malware deploys Cobalt Strike Beacons for remote access and contains a multi-stage infection process with various evasion techniques, including anti-emulation tricks and API resolution via PEB walking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149514</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Leverage Microsoft Teams to Spread Matanbuchus 3.0 Malware to Targeted Firms</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-leverage-microsoft-teams-to.html</link>
      <description>Matanbuchus 3.0 is a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) that packs significant features to enhance its stealth and evade detection. It can be used as a conduit for next-stage payloads, including Cobalt Strike beacons and ransomware. The loader is often deployed using hands-on social engineering tactics, making it more targeted and coordinated than typical commodity loaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/hackers-leverage-microsoft-teams-to.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare says 1.1.1.1 outage not caused by attack or BGP hijack</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-says-1111-outage-not-caused-by-attack-or-bgp-hijack/</link>
      <description>The article explains that the recent 1.1.1.1 Resolver service outage was caused by an internal misconfiguration at Cloudflare, not a cyberattack or BGP hijack incident. The misconfiguration occurred due to a configuration change for a future Data Localization Suite (DLS) performed on June 6, which mistakenly linked 1.1.1.1 Resolver IP prefixes to a non-production DLS service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/cloudflare-says-1111-outage-not-caused-by-attack-or-bgp-hijack/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicWall SMA devices hacked with OVERSTEP rootkit tied to ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-sma-devices-hacked-with-overstep-rootkit-tied-to-ransomware/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall Secure Mobile Access appliances (SMA 100 Series); CVE(s): CVE-2021-20038, CVE-2024-38475, CVE-2021-20035, CVE-2021-20039, CVE-2025-32819; Summary: The article describes a previously unseen malware called OVERSTEP that modifies the boot process of fully-patched but no longer supported SonicWall SMA appliances. The backdoor allows hackers to hide malicious components, maintain persistent access on the device, and steal sensitive credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/sonicwall-sma-devices-hacked-with-overstep-rootkit-tied-to-ransomware/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-603: Autodesk Revit RTE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-603/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Autodesk Revit; CVE(s): CVE-2025-5037; Summary: This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Autodesk Revit, requiring user interaction. The flaw exists in the parsing of RTE files due to lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, leading to a read past the end of an allocated object.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27152</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Fortinet FortiWeb hacks likely linked to public RCE exploits</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-fortinet-fortiweb-hacks-likely-linked-to-public-rce-exploits/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Fortinet FortiWeb; CVE(s): CVE-2025-25257; Summary: A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-25257 affects FortiWeb 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10. The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized SQL code or commands via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests, which can lead to web shell infections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/new-fortinet-fortiweb-hacks-likely-linked-to-public-rce-exploits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europol disrupts pro-Russian NoName057(16) DDoS hacktivist group</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-disrupts-pro-russian-noname05716-ddos-hacktivist-group/</link>
      <description>Operation Eastwood, an international law enforcement operation led by Europol and Eurojust, targeted the pro-Russian hacktivist group NoName057(16) responsible for DDoS attacks across Europe, Israel, and Ukraine. The operation disrupted over 100 servers hosting the group's infrastructure, resulted in two arrests, and issued seven European arrest warrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/europol-disrupts-pro-russian-noname05716-ddos-hacktivist-group/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC6148 Backdoors Fully-Patched SonicWall SMA 100 Series Devices with OVERSTEP Rootkit</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/unc6148-backdoors-fully-patched.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SonicWall Secure Mobile Access (SMA) 100 series; CVE(s): CVE-2021-20035, CVE-2021-20038, CVE-2021-20039, CVE-2024-38475, CVE-2025-32819; Summary: A threat activity cluster has been observed targeting fully-patched end-of-life SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances to drop a backdoor called OVERSTEP. The attackers are believed to have initially gained access through the exploitation of known security flaws or obtained administrator credentials through information-stealing logs or credential marketplaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/unc6148-backdoors-fully-patched.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITRE Launches AADAPT Framework to Secure Digital Assets</title>
      <link>https://socradar.io/mitre-launches-aadapt-framework-secure-digital-assets/</link>
      <description>The MITRE organization has launched a new cybersecurity initiative called AADAPT (Adversarial Actions in Digital Asset Payment Technologies), which aims to help organizations detect and mitigate cyber threats in digital finance. The framework provides a structured approach to tackling risks in cryptocurrencies, smart contracts, decentralized applications, and blockchain systems, drawing on lessons from over 150 real-world incidents and expert sources across government, academia, and industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://socradar.io/?p=100061842</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenovo Vantage Flaws Enable Attackers to Gain SYSTEM-Level Privileges</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/lenovo-vantage-flaws-enable-attackers/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Lenovo Vantage; CVE(s): 2025-6230, 2025-6231, 2025-6232; Summary: Multiple privilege escalation vulnerabilities in Lenovo Vantage allow unprivileged users to bypass authentication mechanisms and execute code with SYSTEM-level privileges, potentially leading to full system compromise. The flaws stem from Lenovo Vantage's modular architecture and expose JSON-based requests routed to add-ins defined in XML files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149490</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung WLAN AP Flaws Let Remote Attackers Run Commands as Root</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/samsung-wlan-ap-flaws/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Samsung WEA453e Wireless Access Point; CVE(s): None; Summary: The WEA453e wireless access point has a critical chain of vulnerabilities that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute commands with full administrative privileges. The vulnerability chain begins with a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw and ends with local file inclusion (LFI) and command injection, allowing attackers to read sensitive files and gain root-level access without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149460</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese ‘Salt Typhoon’ Hackers Infiltrated US National Guard Network for Almost a Year</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/chinese-salt-typhoon-hackers-infiltrated/</link>
      <description>A sophisticated advanced persistent threat (APT) group, known as Salt Typhoon, has successfully penetrated a U.S. state's Army National Guard network, enabling potential exfiltration of sensitive military and law enforcement data. The intrusion leveraged lateral movement techniques across interconnected systems, highlighting vulnerabilities in hybrid federal-state infrastructures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149463</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Secure Boot Certificate Expired in June, Microsoft Issues Warning</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/windows-secure-boot-certificate-expired-in-june/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft; CVE(s): None; Summary: The Secure Boot certificates used by most Windows devices are scheduled to expire starting in June 2026, potentially affecting device functionality and security. If not properly updated, affected devices may encounter boot failures or security vulnerabilities, leaving systems exposed to malware attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149449</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s AI ‘Big Sleep’ Detects Critical SQLite 0-Day, Halts Ongoing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/googles-ai-big-sleep-detects-critical-sqlite-0-day/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SQLite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6965; Summary: A zero-day vulnerability was found in SQLite by Google's AI agent "Big Sleep", which allowed it to stop exploitation attempts before widespread attacks could occur. The vulnerability was detected using threat intelligence and advanced code analysis, demonstrating a proactive approach to predictive threat prevention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149441</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Golden dMSA Attack in Windows Server 2025 Enables Cross-Domain Attacks and Persistent Access</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-golden-dmsa-attack-in-windows.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Windows Server 2025; CVE(s): None; Summary: A critical design flaw in Delegated Managed Service Accounts (dMSAs) allows for high-impact attacks, enabling cross-domain lateral movement and persistent access to all managed service accounts and their resources across Active Directory. Exploitation requires possession of a Key Distribution Service (KDS) root key, which is typically only available to privileged accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/critical-golden-dmsa-attack-in-windows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Partners Hacker Group Drains Crypto Wallets Using Fake AI Tools and VPN Services</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/dark-partners-hacker-group-drains-crypto-wallets/</link>
      <description>Dark Partners, a financially driven cybercrime organization, has been planning massive cryptocurrency theft since May 2025 using over 250 malicious domains posing as AI tools, VPN services, and software brands. The group's infrastructure facilitates data harvesting from victims across multiple countries, with a focus on cryptocurrency, blockchain, technology, financial services, and VPN sectors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149392</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Message Exploit Triggers Code Execution in Claude, Bypassing Protections</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/gmail-message-exploit-triggers-code-execution-in-claude/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Claude Desktop; CVE(s): None; Summary: A cybersecurity researcher demonstrated a code execution attack on Claude Desktop, an AI assistant application, by leveraging the Model Context Protocol (MCP) and exploiting compositional risk. The attack did not rely on any vulnerabilities in individual MCP servers but rather the combination of untrusted input sources, excessive execution permissions, and lack of contextual guardrails between different tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149423</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Act Like Employees With Root Access—Here's How to Regain Control</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ai-agents-act-like-employees-with-root.html</link>
      <description>The article highlights the importance of identity-first security in securing generative AI systems. It warns that most organizations are not securing their AI deployments properly and that every LLM access point or website is a new identity edge that can be exploited. The article emphasizes the need for phishing-resistant MFA, granular RBAC, and continuous device trust enforcement to eliminate AI access risk without hindering innovation.

FYSA: The threat surface of AI systems expands internal attack surfaces, especially if access control and identity segmentation aren't enforced at runtime. Third-party tools can be misused or accessed by unauthorized users, or corporate users on personal accounts, where governance gaps exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/ai-agents-act-like-employees-with-root.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Issues Critical Update Fixing 309 Vulnerabilities Across Products</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/oracle-issues-critical-update/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle; CVE(s): 309 (None); Summary: The Oracle July 2025 Critical Patch Update addresses 309 security vulnerabilities across its product portfolio, including Oracle Database Server, MySQL Server, WebLogic Server, Java SE, and other products. The update affects multiple version ranges, with some affecting software dating back several years. The vulnerabilities can be exploited remotely without authentication, leading to unauthorized access, data breaches, and system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149332</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers exploit a blind spot by hiding malware inside DNS records</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-exploit-a-blind-spot-by-hiding-malware-inside-dns-records/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the use of Domain Name System (DNS) records to host malicious PowerShell scripts. Researchers have found that threat actors are using TXT records to embed attacker-devised text into documents or files being analyzed by AI chatbots, which can be exploited through prompt injections. This technique allows attackers to manipulate the chatbot's behavior and achieve malicious objectives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/07/hackers-exploit-a-blind-spot-by-hiding-malware-inside-dns-records/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NimDoor MacOS Malware Abuses Zoom SDK Updates to Steal Keychain Credentials</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/nimdoor-macos-malware-abuses-zoom-sdk-updates/</link>
      <description>SentinelOne researchers discovered NimDoor, a sophisticated MacOS malware campaign attributed to North Korean-affiliated attackers (Stardust Chollima gang) targeting the bitcoin industry, exploiting social engineering tactics to steal sensitive data. The malware uses Nim-compiled binaries and process injection techniques for stealthy operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149355</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok 4 benchmark results: Tops math, ranks second in coding</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-benchmark-results-tops-math-ranks-second-in-coding/</link>
      <description>The article discusses various AI-related topics, including the performance of Grok 4, a reasoning model, in different domains such as coding and math. It also mentions the threat actors' techniques used for cloud-fluent attacks, which are surprisingly simple despite growing sophistication. Additionally, it touches on upcoming developments in the AI space, including the potential launch of Grok 3.5 and GPT-5 models.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/grok-4-benchmark-results-tops-math-ranks-second-in-coding/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Konfety Android Malware Exploits ZIP Tricks to Masquerade as Legit Apps on Google Play</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/konfety-android-malware-exploits-zip-tricks/</link>
      <description>The Konfety Android malware uses complex ZIP-level changes to avoid detection and mimic genuine apps on the Google Play Store, employing an "evil-twin" strategy, runtime decryption, and deceptive manifest declarations. It can redirect users to fraudulent websites, initiate unwanted app sideloads, and severely impact user privacy and device integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149334</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-598: Oracle VirtualBox BusLogic Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-598/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53025; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability, which results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26654</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-599: Oracle VirtualBox LSILogic Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-599/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53026; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability, and it can be leveraged with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-26653</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-600: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox VMSVGA Out-Of-Bounds Write Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-600/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53028; Summary: The vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting an out-of-bounds write local privilege escalation flaw in the VMSVGA virtual device, which can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27163</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-601: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox VMSVGA Integer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-601/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53024; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting an integer overflow in the VMSVGA virtual device. An attacker must first obtain high-privileged code execution on the target guest system to exploit this flaw, which results from a lack of proper validation of user-supplied data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27122</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZDI-25-602: (Pwn2Own) Oracle VirtualBox OHCI USB Controller Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://www.zerodayinitiative.com/advisories/ZDI-25-602/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Oracle VirtualBox; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53027; Summary: This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Oracle VirtualBox by exploiting a lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object in the virtual OHCI USB controller. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system to exploit this vulnerability, which can then be used to execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ZDI-CAN-27154</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talos IR ransomware engagements and the significance of timeliness in incident response</title>
      <link>https://blog.talosintelligence.com/talos-ir-ransomware-engagements-and-the-significance-of-timeliness-in-incident-response/</link>
      <description>FYSA:

The article appears to be a case study on a cybersecurity incident involving a series of malicious activities by an attacker. The analyst's analysis reveals that the attack involved multiple tools and techniques, including social engineering, malware deployment, data exfiltration, and command and control (C2) communication.

From a security perspective, several concerns are raised:

1. **Lack of robust security controls**: The article highlights the importance of implementing strong security controls to prevent unauthorized access and data breaches.
2. **Inadequate logging and monitoring**: The analyst notes that the attack was only detected due to the victim's logging and monitoring efforts. This emphasizes the need for organizations to maintain comprehensive logging and monitoring capabilities.
3. **Malware deployment**: The article highlights the importance of maintaining up-to-date antivirus software and implementing sandboxing or virtualization technologies to contain malware outbreaks.
4. **Command and control (C2) communication**: The analyst notes that the attacker used C2 servers to communicate with compromised hosts. This underscores the need for organizations to implement robust C2 detection and mitigation strategies.

In terms of specific vulnerabilities, the article does not discuss any particular software, hardware, or firmware vulnerabilities. However, it highlights the importance of keeping systems and applications up-to-date with the latest security patches and updates.

Overall, the article provides valuable insights into the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) used by attackers and emphasizes the need for organizations to prioritize robust security controls, logging, monitoring, and incident response capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">687548cf405515000149657a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Filters Defeated by Polyglot File Trick Used in Malware Campaigns</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/email-filters-defeated-by-polyglot-file/</link>
      <description>This article discusses advanced techniques used by attackers to evade email filters and successfully send phishing payloads. The techniques include the use of polyglot files, which can be interpreted as multiple file formats simultaneously, allowing malicious content to appear benign to security scanners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149288</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google fixes actively exploited sandbox escape zero day in Chrome</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-sandbox-escape-zero-day-in-chrome/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6558; Summary: The vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-6558, is a high-severity issue in ANGLE and GPU that affects Google Chrome versions before 138.0.7204.157. It allows an attacker to perform a sandbox escape by using a specially crafted HTML page, potentially executing arbitrary code within the browser's GPU process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/google-fixes-actively-exploited-sandbox-escape-zero-day-in-chrome/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive DDoS Attack Slams Internet with 7.3 Tbps and 4.8 Billion Packets Per Second</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/massive-ddos-attack-slams-internet/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: N/A; CVE(s): None; Summary: The article reports on a massive DDoS attack mitigated by Cloudflare, peaking at 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps) and 4.8 billion packets per second (Bpps). The report highlights the increasing frequency and intensity of DDoS attacks, with a focus on HTTP and L3/4 attacks, as well as emerging threats like Teeworlds and RIPv1 floods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149276</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Konfety Malware Variant Evades Detection by Manipulating APKs and Dynamic Code</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-konfety-malware-variant-evades.html</link>
      <description>The article discusses a sophisticated variant of an Android malware called Konfety that uses the evil twin technique for ad fraud. The malware employs dynamic code loading, obfuscation, and deception to evade detection. It can redirect users to malicious websites, prompt unwanted app installs, and trigger spam-like notifications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/new-konfety-malware-variant-evades.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urgent: Google Releases Critical Chrome Update for CVE-2025-6558 Exploit Active in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/urgent-google-releases-critical-chrome.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Google Chrome; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6558; Summary: The high-severity vulnerability (CVSS score: 8.8) allows a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page, exploiting an incorrect validation of untrusted input in the browser's ANGLE and GPU components, allowing attackers to break out of the browser's security bubble and interact with the underlying system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/urgent-google-releases-critical-chrome.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfakes. Fake Recruiters. Cloned CFOs — Learn How to Stop AI-Driven Attacks in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/deepfakes-fake-recruiters-cloned-cfos.html</link>
      <description>Social engineering attacks are evolving with the use of generative AI, stolen branding assets, and deepfake tools, allowing attackers to mimic executives, hijack social channels, and create convincing fakes. Modern attacks involve long-term, multi-channel campaigns across email, LinkedIn, SMS, and support portals, targeting employees, customers, and partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/deepfakes-fake-recruiters-cloned-cfos.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command-Line Editor Vim Hit by Vulnerability Allowing File Overwrites</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/command-line-editor-vim-hit-by-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Vim; CVE(s): CVE-2025-53906; Summary: The vulnerability allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files on users' systems by exploiting a path traversal issue in Vim's zip.vim plugin when opening specially crafted zip archives. Successful exploitation could lead to arbitrary code execution, compromising entire systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149326</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers Exploit Ivanti and Fortinet VPN Vulnerabilities in Attacks on Japanese Companies</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/hackers-exploit-ivanti-and-fortinet-vpn-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>The article reports on a surge in cyber espionage campaigns against Japanese companies, primarily targeting North Korean threat actors. These campaigns aim to exfiltrate sensitive data, including manufacturing blueprints and personal information, using various tactics such as spear phishing, malware, and social engineering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149267</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curl 8.15.0 Officially Released: 233 Bugs Fixed in Major Update</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/curl-8-15-0-officially-released/</link>
      <description>The article discusses the release of Curl 8.15.0, which addresses over 230 bugs and streamlines its internal architecture. The update removes support for Apple's Secure Transport API and BearSSL library to reduce maintenance overhead and promote adoption of widely tested TLS providers like OpenSSL. The article highlights the community-driven nature of the project, with many newcomers contributing to the codebase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149308</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities Take Down ‘Diskstation’ Ransomware Gang Targeting Synology NAS Globally</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/authorities-take-down-diskstation-ransomware-gang/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Synology NAS systems; CVE(s): None; Summary: The "Diskstation" ransomware operation targeted Synology Network Attached Storage (NAS) systems worldwide, exploiting vulnerabilities to encrypt entire organizational datasets. The attackers specifically targeted these systems for data storage and backup solutions, allowing them to maximize their leverage over victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149301</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abacus Dark Web Market Suspected of Exit Scam with Held Bitcoin Funds</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/abacus-dark-web-market-suspected-of-exit-scam/</link>
      <description>The largest Bitcoin-enabled Western darknet marketplace, Abacus Market, has gone offline amid suspicions of an exit scam that may have cost users millions of dollars in held cryptocurrency funds. The market's administrators likely shut down operations and disappeared with users' deposits, leaving behind a trail of frozen funds and delayed transactions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google AI "Big Sleep" Stops Exploitation of Critical SQLite Vulnerability Before Hackers Act</title>
      <link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ai-big-sleep-stops-exploitation.html</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: SQLite; CVE(s): CVE-2025-6965; Summary: The vulnerability is a memory corruption flaw affecting all versions prior to 3.50.2, which could allow an attacker to cause an integer overflow resulting in read off the end of an array.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://thehackernews.com/2025/07/google-ai-big-sleep-stops-exploitation.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former U.S. Army Member Pleads Guilty in Telecom Hacking Case</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/former-u-s-army-member-pleads-guilty/</link>
      <description>A 21-year-old former U.S. Army soldier has pleaded guilty to participating in a sophisticated cybercrime operation that targeted telecommunications companies through hacking, data theft, and extortion schemes. The conspiracy involved at least 10 victim organizations, using specialized hacking tools and Telegram group chats to coordinate activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149262</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 06:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vulnerabilities Leave Windows Apps Vulnerable to Path Traversal and HashDoS</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/node-js-vulnerabilities-leave-windows-apps-vulnerable/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Node.js; CVE(s): CVE-2025-27210, CVE-2025-27209; Summary: Two high-severity vulnerabilities affecting Windows applications, including denial-of-service attacks. The first vulnerability allows attackers to bypass path traversal protection mechanisms, while the second introduces a HashDoS vulnerability through changes in the V8 JavaScript engine's string hashing implementation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149257</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware ESXi and Workstation Vulnerabilities Allow Host-Level Code Execution</title>
      <link>https://gbhackers.com/vmware-esxi-and-workstation-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: VMware; CVE(s): CVE-2025-41236, CVE-2025-41237, CVE-2025-41238, CVE-2025-41239; Summary: Four critical vulnerabilities in VMware's virtualization suite allow attackers to escape virtual machines and execute code directly on host systems. The flaws affect ESXi, Workstation, Fusion, and VMware Tools across enterprise and desktop environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gbhackers.com/?p=149253</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 05:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI's image model gets built-in style feature on ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-image-model-gets-built-in-style-feature-on-chatgpt/</link>
      <description>The article does not discuss a vulnerability. It appears to be focused on updates and features of OpenAI's image generation model, ChatGPT, including the introduction of a "Style" feature that allows users to create images in different styles.

FYSA: The article mentions threat actors using simple techniques for cloud attacks and notes that attackers are leveraging ChatGPT to write malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/artificial-intelligence/openais-image-model-gets-built-in-style-feature-on-chatgpt/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abacus dark web drug market goes offline in suspected exit scam</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/abacus-dark-web-drug-market-goes-offline-in-suspected-exit-scam/</link>
      <description>Abacus Market, the largest Western darknet marketplace supporting Bitcoin payments, has shut down its public infrastructure, suspected to be an exit scam or covert law enforcement operation. The market reportedly enabled transactions of nearly $100 million worth of Bitcoin and possibly up to $300 million when including Monero transactions. User deposits dropped significantly after withdrawal delays, leading many to believe it was an exit scam rather than a law enforcement takedown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/abacus-dark-web-drug-market-goes-offline-in-suspected-exit-scam/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows KB5064489 emergency update fixes Azure VM launch issues</title>
      <link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-kb5064489-emergency-update-fixes-azure-vm-launch-issues/</link>
      <description>Vulnerable Product: Microsoft Azure; CVE(s): None; Summary: The bug prevented Azure virtual machines from launching when Trusted Launch setting was disabled and Virtualization-Based Security (VBS) was enabled, affecting Windows Server 2025 and Windows 11 24H2. The issue was caused by a secure kernel initialization problem and has been fixed with the KB5064489 out-of-band update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/microsoft/windows-kb5064489-emergency-update-fixes-azure-vm-launch-issues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
